<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/industry/wholesale-distribution/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Wholesale Distributors Can Stand Out in a Direct-to-Consumer World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/wholesale-distributors-stand-out-direct-to-consumer-world</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/wholesale-distributors-stand-out-direct-to-consumer-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the help of SAP ECM solutions by OpenText, wholesale distributors can close the gap in their e-commerce strategies. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/opentext</category>
            <category>industry/wholesale-distribution</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Wholesale Distribution Trends to Watch in 2022]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/three-wholesale-distribution-trends-to-watch-in-2022</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/three-wholesale-distribution-trends-to-watch-in-2022</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Industry experts from SAP have identified and written about trends affecting wholesale distribution in today’s changing world. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15d1908211af5344246c80feb3870b66599057506.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15d1908211af5344246c80feb3870b66599057506.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15d1908211af5344246c80feb3870b66599057506.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Three Wholesale Distribution Trends to Watch in 2022" src="./media_15d1908211af5344246c80feb3870b66599057506.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="three-wholesale-distribution-trends-to-watch-in-2022">Three Wholesale Distribution Trends to Watch in 2022</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>A well-known proverb says, “To know the road ahead, ask those coming back.” Throughout the past year, industry experts from SAP have identified and written about trends affecting wholesale distributors in today’s changing world.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>These trends are shaping the future of the industry and prompting companies to take a serious look at the way they will do business in years to come. Here are a few to watch in 2022.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-whitepaper-the-intelligent-enterprise-for-the-wholesale-distribution-industry">Read the whitepaper: The Intelligent Enterprise for the Wholesale Distribution Industry</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2016/03/8e7998d0-627c-0010-82c7-eda71af511fa.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="e-commerce--an-online-lifeline">E-Commerce – an Online Lifeline</h2>
  <p>The events of the past two years have revealed a critical trend: distributors must have a modern, online customer experience to compete and survive against global marketplaces like Amazon. Many companies have an online presence, but customers want more products and more personalized services – and they want them now. We’re at a tipping point for the industry, and distributors need to evolve, as described in <a href="https://www.inddist.com/e-commerce/article/21283028/the-future-of-wholesale-distribution-b2b-marketplaces">“The Future of Wholesale Distribution: B2B Marketplaces.”</a></p>
  <p>How do companies get started? While a goal may be to stay relevant against competitors, distributors should capitalize on the unique value they add, especially for longtime customers. One idea getting some traction is establishing a marketplace to offer a more extensive list of products. The article <a href="https://www.digitalcommerce360.com/2021/08/13/finding-your-place-in-the-new-b2b-marketplace-battle-zone/">“Finding Your Place in the New B2B Marketplace Battle Zone”</a> discusses six vantage points to help analyze readiness for a B2B marketplace.</p>
  <p>But there are other initiatives that can help distributors stay in the e-commerce game. Customers are looking for personalized buying experiences, similar to their consumer purchasing. If companies can leverage data around inventory, incentives, and processes, they can support these types of engagements. Read more in “<a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/08/25/how-successful-distributors-are-beating-amazon-at-their-own-game/?sh=197faff53a09">How Successful Distributors Are Beating Amazon at Their Own Game.”</a></p>
  <h2 id="everyones-talking-supply-chain">Everyone’s Talking Supply Chain</h2>
  <p>Recently, an older, retired relative was telling me about the supply chain crisis. She never worked in the industry, and I’m pretty certain that until this year she never used the term “supply chain.” Global challenges in this area are making news everywhere, but are most painfully clear to the wholesale distribution industry that has always been the conduit for goods and services.</p>
  <p>And while disruptions in the supply chain are nothing new, a new approach is needed – like using intelligent data to plan for disruptions. Learn how companies can be more prepared in this article, <a href="https://www.inddist.com/operations/article/21330998/planning-for-disruption-in-wholesale-distribution">“Planning for Disruption in Wholesale Distribution.”</a></p>
  <p>The <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> has also shown that distributors need more supply chain flexibility as well as more visibility. <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/08/20/supply-chain-collaboration-in-wholesale-distribution/">“Supply Chain Collaboration in Wholesale Distribution”</a> is a way to help mitigate risk and respond to unforeseen challenges. Giving suppliers greater transparency can help transform the supply chain from disconnected to collaborative.</p>
  <p>Collaboration is just one part of the overall transformation of a distributor’s logistics processes. To compete in the global market, companies need to innovate to meet demands, but also do a better job of planning, procuring, storing, and delivering goods. <a href="https://www.inddist.com/supply-chain/article/21415453/transforming-the-distribution-supply-chain-with-a-connected-network">“Transforming the Digital Supply Chain”</a> discusses the challenges and offers some solutions for improvement.</p>
  <h2 id="sustainability-for-the-future">Sustainability for the Future</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="differentiate-your-wholesale-distribution-business-with-sap">Differentiate your wholesale distribution business with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/wholesale-distribution.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the past, we didn’t hear too much about sustainability from wholesale distributors. For these companies with traditionally small margins, the cost of “going green” seemed out of reach. But recently, the topic is gaining some traction as the definition of sustainability is being rewritten in this industry.</p>
  <p>For example, a healthcare distributor might have sustainability goals around the reduction of hazardous waste or product integrity. A food distributor might focus on green logistics, zero emissions, and lowering their carbon footprint. Some companies are already moving in this direction. Read their stories in this article, <a href="https://www.the-future-of-commerce.com/2021/10/12/sustainable-distribution/">“Sustainable Distribution: Profitability with Purpose.”</a></p>
  <p>One company that is serious about sustainability is wholesale distributor BayWa, which has been recognized as one of 50 sustainability and climate leaders worldwide. BayWa is helping farmers grow profits while pioneering new, more sustainable farming models with renewable energy projects and technologies. Learn more about its innovative efforts in <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/06/03/on-world-environment-dayhow-baywa-is-working-with-farmers-to-increase-yield-and-protect-biodiversity/?sh=564a2f48108c">“How BayWa Is Working with Farmers to Increase Yield and Protect Biodiversity.”</a></p>
  <h2 id="the-future-is-now">The Future Is Now</h2>
  <p>There are certainly threads that run through all these trends – planning, innovation, flexibility, visibility. While these ideas have always been around, they have never been more important for distributors than now. The industry – and the world – will continue to change, and wholesale distributors must plan for the road ahead.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Lynn Lupo is solution manager for Wholesale Distribution at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-supply-chain</category>
            <category>industry/wholesale-distribution</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The New Rules of Competition for Today’s Distributor]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/new-rules-of-competition-for-todays-distributors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/new-rules-of-competition-for-todays-distributors</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To stay relevant and competitive in any market condition, wholesale distributors need to rethink their business and operations strategies.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f9da2820936b7055a711bcac1c73b9837db4504d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f9da2820936b7055a711bcac1c73b9837db4504d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f9da2820936b7055a711bcac1c73b9837db4504d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The New Rules of Competition for Today’s Distributor" src="./media_1f9da2820936b7055a711bcac1c73b9837db4504d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-new-rules-of-competition-for-todays-distributor">The New Rules of Competition for Today’s Distributor</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>It is common knowledge that every business experienced some form of unpredictable disruption over the last two years. Acting as the first responders in the logistics supply chain, this disruption threatened many wholesale distributors’ ability to provide essential goods to vital businesses, such as healthcare providers and grocery stores. To stay relevant and competitive amidst all market conditions, distribution leaders need to rethink their business and operations strategies.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>During a recent online event, Distribution Strategy Group’s Founder and Senior Partner Ian Heller exposed five major sources of disruption for this vital industry:</p>
  <ol>
    <li><strong>Workforce</strong>: The youngest generations (Generation Y and Generation Z) now make up approximately 70% of the total workforce. These generations are the most technically affluent, which means they expect to be connected on any device, anytime, anywhere, with easy-to-use applications.</li>
    <li><strong>E-Commerce</strong>: E-commerce is no longer just about having a slick website. Today, distributors must have a strong technology foundation to deliver an easy-to-use, personalized, B2C-like purchasing experience for customers.</li>
    <li><strong>Cybersecurity</strong>: The <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19 pandemic</a> has underlined cybersecurity as a prevalent concern as new vulnerabilities arose due to employees working from home. Phishing and ransomware attacks have virtually exploded across every industry in the past few years.</li>
    <li><strong>Cloud</strong>: To stay competitive, many distributors are moving their technology stack to the cloud to lower capital expenditures and enjoy a better margin advantage.</li>
    <li><strong>Marketplaces</strong>: B2B buyers are turning to marketplaces for a one-stop shopping experience. Distributors that can successfully adopt a marketplace model will stand to deepen customer relationships and drive growth.</li>
  </ol>
  <p>Heller shared that as an industry, distributors are still working out solutions to these challenges as they continue to adjust to the ever-evolving market challenges. Digital transformation continues to be an enabler of business models, allowing distributors to go from reactive, reporting on things that are happening, to proactive, anticipating the future and mitigating risks.</p>
  <p>Magnus Meier, vice president and global head of the Wholesale Distribution Business Unit at SAP, went on to share that high-tech distributors have started to market themselves as solution aggregators to underline how committed they are to long-term customer relationships, taking care of the product and customer life cycle. In addition, digital transformation continues to play a significant role during the pandemic, specifically in operations. “Distributors that have a modern ERP system have data on hand, which gives them a significant advantage over their competitors,” says Meier.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="expand-beyond-traditional-industry-boundaries-with-sap-solutions">Expand beyond traditional industry boundaries with SAP solutions</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/wholesale-distribution.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="using-services-as-a-differentiator">Using Services as a Differentiator</h2>
  <p>For distributors to successfully implement everything from business strategy to operations to customer experience, they first need to determine what is most important to their business. Competitive differentiators come in all shapes and sizes for wholesale distributors, be it a great service like replenishment of bins near the production line, dedicated jobs like delivery of materials, on-site safety training, or even simply having the most responsive, proactive salespeople. Aligning business priorities with competitive differentiators allows distributors to position their business model as not just indispensable to customers, but profitable.</p>
  <p>The big players, by and large, are not great at services. Services almost always represent the introduction of variable costs into a business model. Traditionally, distributors have rolled the costs of services into the gross margin of products, but they have not monetized them or charged the cost back to customers. “If distributors put a general manager in charge of services, one must treat it the way that a manufacturer treats new product development. Figure out how to monetize it with a P&#x26;L to build a business that’s much different and adds value for their customers,” says Heller.</p>
  <p>The technology that enables distributors to have the right level of visibility into their business starts with an enterprise resource planning (ERP) system, which is critical to transformation. Having the right processing system enables order-to-cash (O2C) and procure-to-pay (P2P) business processes, which are critical to operations. For many distributors, more than 50% of orders come through as e-mailed PDF or Excel files, creating a manual process for customer sales representatives to then enter the orders into proprietary systems.</p>
  <p>Counterintuitive to what distributors assume, the number of manual orders received is increasing, not decreasing. To enable efficiency and resiliency, distributors must find a way to automate manual and redundant tasks and redirect that energy towards value-added efforts. “Conexiom can help process those orders with the same customer service expectations that a buyer experiences when placing an e-commerce order, a marketplace order, or any other type of digital order,” says Erik Severinghaus, executive vice president of Business Development at Conexiom.</p>
  <h2 id="preempting-issues-within-the-supply-chain">Preempting Issues within the Supply Chain</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-conexiom-on-sap-store">Explore Conexiom on SAP Store</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-0000059854_live_v1/Conexiom%20Digital%20Order%20Capture%20for%20SAP%20Solutions">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Whether it’s due to trade agreements, politics, or biological threats like pandemics, these is less predictability in the supply chain. A good example is what happened at the Suez Canal. The only way distributors can anticipate these issues is to have complete transparency and visibility across the supply chain, all the way through to the demand side. They need to leverage technology to gain the transparency to track which boxes are in which containers and on which ships. And if one of those ships goes astray, they need to be able to understand the implications and trigger follow-up processes to minimize disruption.</p>
  <p>“Distributors are operating at greater scale than ever before and it is essential that distributors overcome silos, talk to sellers to overcome those challenges, understand how their customers will be affected, and take mitigating action,” says Meier.</p>
  <h2 id="navigating-the-talent-shortage">Navigating the Talent Shortage</h2>
  <p>Every business is grappling with the talent shortage today. To attract the right talent, distributors need to invest in modern technology to bolster employee experience in the workplace. Distributors need to leverage intelligent technologies to automate routine tasks so employees can focus on more complex customer requirements. They need to provide collaboration tools between different teams to drive ongoing business alignment, openness for change, business agility, and improved collaboration between sales, marketing, and demand-planning teams. The distribution industry as a whole must challenge the way it has traditionally handled work-from-home policies, salaries, long-term incentives, and other benefits to make employees want to stay in this lesser-known B2B industry. “Distributors need to offer a competitive workplace environment, not just against other distributors, but against other industries,” says Severinghaus.</p>
  <p>Meier, Severinghaus, and Heller have a lot of commendable and proven advice on these topics. In this <a href="https://conexiom.com/resources/the-new-rules-of-competition-for-todays-distributor/">on-demand video</a>, these speakers discuss the challenges facing distributors today and provide tangible guidance on how to prepare and respond to market disruptions.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Sam Nohava is global industry marketing lead at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/e-commerce</category>
            <category>industry/wholesale-distribution</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Celebrating Wholesale Distribution Transformation Excellence]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/wholesale-distribution-transformation-excellence</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/wholesale-distribution-transformation-excellence</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For 2022, celebrate wholesale distribution transformation excellence by applying for an SAP Innovation Award. Learn more here.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18b2c05ec82f0820e380276c21fc99f7a9ff60fca.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18b2c05ec82f0820e380276c21fc99f7a9ff60fca.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18b2c05ec82f0820e380276c21fc99f7a9ff60fca.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Celebrating Wholesale Distribution Transformation Excellence" src="./media_18b2c05ec82f0820e380276c21fc99f7a9ff60fca.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="celebrating-wholesale-distribution-transformation-excellence">Celebrating Wholesale Distribution Transformation Excellence</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The <a href="/2021/09/sap-innovation-awards-2022-submissions-open">2022 SAP Innovation Awards are now open</a>. We are excited to celebrate wholesale distributors that are leading the way in their industry by their use of SAP intelligent solutions to transform the way they do business.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As we enter a new chapter of the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, the use of technology within the wholesale distribution industry continues to accelerate. Distributors are in the perfect position to showcase their successes and innovation leadership as an essential member of the supply chain.</p>
  <p>Last year, we were excited to receive a significant number of SAP Innovation Award submissions, with six finalists and two notable distributors winning the honor. In 2021, trailblazing customers and partners truly stood out by combining their ingenuity and the power of SAP solutions to achieve operational excellence and business innovation.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-sap-innovation-awards">Learn more about the SAP Innovation Awards</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="wholesale-distribution-innovation-award-highlights">Wholesale Distribution Innovation Award Highlights</h2>
  <p><strong>AmerisourceBergen</strong></p>
  <p>The leading global healthcare company makes a positive impact on the health of people and communities around the world by advancing the development and delivery of pharmaceuticals and healthcare products.</p>
  <p>In 2013, the Drug Supply Chain Security Act (DSCSA) was passed to protect the safety and security of the supply chain due to the counterfeit drug market in developing countries causing thousands of deaths. To protect the U.S. market, the DSCSA required that drugs be traced for millions of daily shipments across thousands of companies.</p>
  <p>AmerisourceBergen and SAP stepped up to the plate, along with 12 other pharmaceuticalpartners, to pursue the development of SAP Advanced Track and Trace for Pharmaceuticals. This allowed them to manage the drug supply chain at the batch and unit level. SAP and AmerisourceBergen also collaborated on the SAP Information Collaboration Hub for Life Sciences to meet the messaging regulations for AmerisourceBergen and its thousands of trading partners.</p>
  <p>This solution now tracks the supply chain at the batch level for more than 100 customers, protecting business continuity for the $185 billion pharmaceutical supply chain, 250,000 messages exchanged daily among hundreds of trading partners, and 14,000 employees protected from the burdens of these new regulations. Eighteen of the top 20 pharmaceutical companies and two U.S. distributors, responsible for 65% of the distribution volume in the U.S. market, are all on SAP Advanced Track and Trace for Pharmaceuticals.</p>
  <p><strong>TRUSCO</strong></p>
  <p>The industrial distributor supports Japan’s manufacturing industry with its PRO TOOLs consumables, tools, furniture, fixtures, and other goods that are needed in factories and construction sites. To meet its growth goals, the company needed an agile, next-generation solution to support a digital transformation initiative.</p>
  <p>To streamline business operations and eliminate manual processes, TRUSCO implemented SAP S/4HANA, SAP Integration Suite. This enabled the company to automate business processes and inventory management. Customers enjoyed increased convenience with improved business productivity, speed, and accuracy through automating quotations and inventory management based on historical information and sales insights of over 2 million products and 380,000 stocked items.</p>
  <p>The benefit of improvements allowed Trusco to automate 2,949 hours per month worth of previously manual quotation tasks, shorten response time to customers’ orders by 29%, and reduce replenishment time from several hours to zero, offering customer-specific and seasonal inventory directly to the customer’s location.</p>
  <p><strong>PROMESA</strong></p>
  <p>The leading distributor of tools, hardware, and automotive products based in Guayaquil, Ecuador, supplies spare parts for vehicles and construction machinery, plus a long list of smaller hardware items that includes everything from nails to industrial drills.</p>
  <p>In order to automate aging manual processes to better meet customer expectations for the right product at the right time, PROMESA implemented SAP S/4HANA as its digital core and integrated SAP SuccessFactors, SAP Concur, SAP Sales Cloud, and SAP Service Cloud solutions to shape itself into a true intelligent enterprise.</p>
  <p>PROMESA immediately saw immense results, with a 30% increase in sales due to product design improvements, only two hours to process a typical report that normally took 12 days, and only five seconds to run an average core process that used to take five minutes. With this implementation, PROMESA was able to meet customer expectations, improving the overall customer and employee operations experience.</p>
  <p><strong>Bechtle AG</strong></p>
  <p>One of Germany’s largest IT systems houses, the European leader in IT e-commerce combines services for the operation and maintenance of industrial and public sector infrastructure. With 75 systems houses, offices in 14 EU countries, and partnerships on every continent, its business knows few boundaries.</p>
  <p>Bechtle AG and SAP collaborated on a warehouse robotics solution, which integrates robotics into SAP Extended Warehouse Management (SAP EWM). On a Kubernetes backbone, the company created a smart, flexible automation system, allowing multi-vendor robots to move crates from point-to-point.</p>
  <p>The advantage of this solution is that it can support many use cases. It hooks together robotics fleets, even heterogeneous ones, into an existing system using SAP EWM. IT governance procedures integrate plug-and-play collaborative robots that perform “3D” — dull, dangerous, or dirty — tasks in logistics and help bring operations beyond Industry 4.0, resulting in a yearly 30% ROI from this robotic project.</p>
  <p><strong>Border States Electric</strong></p>
  <p>Border States Electric (BSE), the seventh largest electrical distributor in the U.S., provides innovative supply chain products and services to the construction, industrial, and utility markets. As COVID-19 impacted supply chains, BSE needed to optimize and streamline its purchase and sales order management to specifically manage delayed and escalated orders. It was critical to consolidate disjointed systems and tools, increase cross-team visibility, and reduce the duplication of work.</p>
  <p>By implementing an integrated order management cockpit on SAP Business Technology Platform, the company was able to experience end-to-end, real-time visibility into sales and purchase orders. This enabled colleagues from procurement, customer service, and application engineering to collaborate and efficiently manage material delays, escalations, reduce duplicate work thereby increasing CSP and buyer productivity by 2% and save 16,000 CSR hours so that they could deliver value-added services to their customers.</p>
  <h2 id="emerging-from-the-pandemic-stronger">Emerging from the Pandemic Stronger</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="expand-beyond-traditional-industry-boundaries-and-become-a-proactive-insight-driven-distributor">Expand beyond traditional industry boundaries and become a proactive, insight-driven distributor</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/wholesale-distribution.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Groundbreaking wholesale distributors transformed their business models while adjusting to the change in buyer behavior and supply chain constraints, not to mention workforce limitations. They seized on these opportunities to digitally transform business to accommodate these monumental shifts in business dynamics.</p>
  <p>In 2021, distributors have continued to ensure operations run smoothly, delivering essential goods around the world and keeping the supply chain on track, all while balancing volatility in demand. The time is now to have your innovation story heard and recognized.</p>
  <h2 id="share-your-wholesale-distribution-innovation-story-and-win">Share Your Wholesale Distribution Innovation Story and Win</h2>
  <p>The objective of this year’s <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards.html">SAP Innovation Awards</a> is to celebrate the achievements of cutting-edge companies that have harnessed the power of SAP technology to become an intelligent enterprise, thrive in new business realities, differentiate themselves, achieve tremendous business outcomes, and adapt to evolving customer needs.</p>
  <p>SAP is delighted to showcase these inspirational customer and partner stories. More information on the <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/faq.html">award timeline and list of prizes is available here</a>. For details on the judging criteria and category definitions, visit the <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/criteria.html">SAP Innovation Awards website</a>. The submission period is open now and all entries are due by February 1, 2022. <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/how-to-enter.html">Get started today</a> and be sure to join the conversation online using the hashtag #SAPInnovation. For more innovation stories, follow <a href="https://twitter.com/SAPIndustries">@SAPIndustries</a> on Twitter and join us on <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-industries/">LinkedIn</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Magnus Meier is global vice president of Wholesale Distribution at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>industry/wholesale-distribution</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wholesale Distribution: Operating with a Purpose Along the Value Chain]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/wholesale-distribution-value-chain-purpose</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/wholesale-distribution-value-chain-purpose</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In a session on operating with a purpose in the value chain, SAP and AmerisourceBergen discussed the vital role of healthcare distributors.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_180c94b9d4110b32aa61155d3fa696189e925f94f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_180c94b9d4110b32aa61155d3fa696189e925f94f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_180c94b9d4110b32aa61155d3fa696189e925f94f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Wholesale Distribution: Operating with a Purpose Along the Value Chain" src="./media_180c94b9d4110b32aa61155d3fa696189e925f94f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="wholesale-distribution-operating-with-a-purpose-along-the-value-chain">Wholesale Distribution: Operating with a Purpose Along the Value Chain</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>While every industry has been affected in some form in recent months, wholesale distribution has been at the center of the global supply chain revolution. Extraordinary measures have been implemented across a variety of industries to handle the unique challenges presented by the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Those in supply chain and logistics have made significant adjustments to help ensure that every segment — including healthcare — has continued to move forward as efficiently and effectively as possible.</p>
  <p>AmerisourceBergen, a wholesale distributor of pharmaceutical products to nearly 100% of hospitals in the U.S., recently joined Cloud Wars Host and Creator Bob Evans and Magnus Meier, global head and vice president of Wholesale Distribution at SAP, for a <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/video/live/urn:li:ugcPost:6798252598970327040/">LinkedIn Live interview</a> to discuss these fundamental changes.</p>
  <p>During the session, Jeff Denton, vice president of Global Secure Supply Chain at AmerisourceBergen, discussed the vital role healthcare distributors play to get life-saving drugs to those who need them most and how the company has managed to ethically balance supplier and customer needs.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="meet-international-and-regional-directives-for-drug-serialization-with-sap-advanced-track-and-trace-for-pharmaceuticals">Meet international and regional directives for drug serialization with SAP Advanced Track and Trace for Pharmaceuticals</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/track-trace-pharmaceuticals.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="new-normal-customer-centric-patient-focused-business">New Normal: Customer-Centric, Patient-Focused Business</h2>
  <p>Wholesale distributors across all sub-segments have managed to keep the supply chain moving forward despite numerous hurdles on a global scale. However, distributors of today can no longer simply focus on moving products through the supply chain. The entire industry has shifted to take on new responsibilities that address the latest regulatory requirements and heightened customer expectations.</p>
  <p>To address these growing concerns, wholesale distributors — especially those in the healthcare distribution segment — are now focused on “doing business with a purpose,” as Meier perfectly described it. By operating with a purpose, this helps ensure the supply chain is safe and secure. It also protects the integrity of the products and provides peace of mind to hospitals, pharmacies, and patients.</p>
  <p>In the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/video/live/urn:li:ugcPost:6798252598970327040/">interview</a>, Denton describes how creating healthier futures starts with protecting the health of people and our planet. As a purpose-driven industry leader with a global footprint, AmerisourceBergen has an obligation to champion global sustainability and corporate responsibility. This includes processing more than $2.5 billion in saleable product returns annually, allowing products that would otherwise have been removed and destroyed to be reintroduced into the supply chain. This is good for AmerisourceBergen along with its customers, patients, and manufacturers across the entire supply chain.</p>
  <h2 id="to-thrive-distributors-require-collaboration-and-innovation">To Thrive, Distributors Require Collaboration and Innovation</h2>
  <p>To address the new concerns and increased responsibility of the distribution industry, AmerisourceBergen approached SAP to co-innovate and create a cross-industry solution centered around meeting the latest regulatory requirements. The result was a new and innovative solution that allows products to be tracked and traced across the entire supply chain: <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/track-trace-pharmaceuticals.html">SAP Advanced Track and Trace for Pharmaceuticals.</a></p>
  <p>The collaboration also allowed AmerisourceBergen and other industry leaders to streamline communication across the entire supply chain, from suppliers through to the pharmacies and hospitals. This supports business continuity through not only an individual enterprise but the entire business network. With this technology, the AmerisourceBergen team can “<a href="/2021/04/amerisourcebergen-best-in-class-industry-innovation">seamlessly match digital data to physical data</a>,” which aids in counterfeit prevention and sustainability efforts.</p>
  <h2 id="data-and-purpose-will-drive-the-industry-forward">Data and Purpose Will Drive the Industry Forward</h2>
  <p>AmerisourceBergen is focused on what the future holds, shifting focus beyond simply reacting to regulatory requirements to understanding the use cases for all of the new data obtained through track and trace technology.</p>
  <p>Without the consortium brought about by AmerisourceBergen and SAP, these industry-specific outcomes and supply chain alignment may not have been possible. Moving forward, collaboration and innovation will be key aspects of the industry and areas in which distributors can add immense value to the supply chain.</p>
  <p>New advancements, technology, and cross-industry collaborations must continue to drive solutions that keep up with the latest regulatory requirements and consumer needs.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>If you missed the LinkedIn Live interview, “Wholesale Distribution: Operating with a Purpose Along the Value Chain” <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/video/live/urn:li:ugcPost:6798252598970327040/">watch the replay here</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-supply-chain</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advanced-track-and-trace-for-pharmaceuticals</category>
            <category>industry/wholesale-distribution</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Help Shape the Future of E-Commerce for Wholesale Distribution]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/future-e-commerce-wholesale-distribution</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/future-e-commerce-wholesale-distribution</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Mirakl are conducting a survey to learn how e-commerce and market trends are evolving for the wholesale distribution industry online]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1db3e3f9e6abd1aa7965fd5be6ef9b158c059b013.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1db3e3f9e6abd1aa7965fd5be6ef9b158c059b013.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1db3e3f9e6abd1aa7965fd5be6ef9b158c059b013.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Help Shape the Future of E-Commerce for Wholesale Distribution" src="./media_1db3e3f9e6abd1aa7965fd5be6ef9b158c059b013.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="help-shape-the-future-of-e-commerce-for-wholesale-distribution">Help Shape the Future of E-Commerce for Wholesale Distribution</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Over the last year, five major trends have impacted wholesale distributors and morphed customer expectations into a demand for consumer-grade experiences.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP is sponsoring a <a href="https://www.mdm.com/">Modern Distribution Management (MDM)</a> research project regarding the state of e-commerce and marketplaces to understand how these market trends are evolving for the distribution industry online.</p>
  <p>This research will provide SAP and partner Mirakl the opportunity to gain further insights into wholesale distribution trends and expose opportunities for improvement from an industry perspective.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="take-the-modern-distribution-management-survey">Take the Modern Distribution Management survey</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/2G95ZZ2">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="market-trends-impacting-commerce-for-distributors">Market Trends Impacting Commerce for Distributors</h2>
  <p>To understand the current state of commerce, we must analyze the market conditions that are having a ripple effect in the industry and creating challenges for wholesale distributors.</p>
  <p>First, competition is driving distributors to find new revenue sources, such as value-added services. Some examples provided to customers include light manufacturing, kitting, product training, and product management.</p>
  <p>Customers are looking to distributors to collaborate and provide complete solutions for specific business needs, such as providing materials for every phase of a stadium renovation. Meanwhile, customers are also looking for distributors to carry a wider range of products with more flexible delivery options.</p>
  <p>To add value to the business and meet growing customer expectations, new talent is looking for roles where they can make a positive impact and leverage new technologies.</p>
  <p>Lastly, the requirement for business resilience in the face of health, environmental, and trade challenges has moved from addressing tactical issues of continuity towards strategic decisions driving overall longevity.</p>
  <h2 id="why-participate-in-the-state-of-e-commerce-research">Why Participate in the State of E-Commerce Research?</h2>
  <p>The <a href="https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/2G95ZZ2">2021 State of E-Commerce</a> research initiative provides wholesale distributors the ability to share insights related to their company’s e-commerce and marketplace ambitions in a confidential way.</p>
  <p>Within the survey, MDM asks distributors to report on each organization’s current commerce landscape, including key capabilities or customer needs that they are looking to support in the coming years.</p>
  <p>Example questions include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>What is your greatest concern or reservation about the value, effectiveness, or risks of e-commerce within your organization?</li>
    <li>What initiatives are you undertaking to broaden and deepen your catalog?</li>
    <li>Have you considered launching or operating an online marketplace, where third-party sellers provide the stock and fulfill orders?</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Any wholesale distributor employee who is located within the United States or Canada can participate in this survey. As a thank you for your participation, you will be entered to win a $250 gift card. This brief survey should take no longer than 10 minutes to complete.</p>
  <p>To impact the future of wholesale distribution commerce, please take the <a href="https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/2G95ZZ2">State of E-Commerce survey</a> today!</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>John McDonnell is industry advisor for Wholesale Distribution at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-how-to-deliver-a-rich-personalized-omnichannel-e-commerce-experience">Explore how to deliver a rich, personalized omnichannel e-commerce experience</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/e-commerce-platforms.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/e-commerce</category>
            <category>industry/wholesale-distribution</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wholesale Distributors Kick-Start Digital Transformation at SAPPHIRE NOW]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/wholesale-distribution-at-sapphire-now</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/wholesale-distribution-at-sapphire-now</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[This year, wholesale distribution at SAPPHIRE NOW offers up industry leaders that have leveraged their digital investment for future success.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f4a36399eb20e3b3aeb72516bd11ae5d22e688cc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f4a36399eb20e3b3aeb72516bd11ae5d22e688cc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f4a36399eb20e3b3aeb72516bd11ae5d22e688cc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Wholesale Distributors Kick-Start Digital Transformation at SAPPHIRE NOW" src="./media_1f4a36399eb20e3b3aeb72516bd11ae5d22e688cc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="wholesale-distributors-kick-start-digital-transformation-at-sapphire-now">Wholesale Distributors Kick-Start Digital Transformation at SAPPHIRE NOW</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For <a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/wholesale-distribution.html?pdf-asset=8e7998d0-627c-0010-82c7-eda71af511fa&#x26;page=1">wholesale distributors</a>, the past year has shown that, more than ever, the right time to digitally transform the business is now. The <a href="/covid-19">disruption</a> we experienced in 2020 has shown how interdependent the supply chain can be.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Companies have known for some time that new business models and new processes are needed to stay competitive. They have been extending their business growing revenue with value-added services, a wider range of products, and automation of manual tasks. But distributors also need new ways to ensure their supply chain is resilient, reduce cost and risk, and manage their business with intelligence, agility, and speed.</p>
  <h2 id="join-us-for-sapphire-now">Join Us for SAPPHIRE NOW</h2>
  <p>This year’s SAPPHIRE NOW offers the opportunity to learn from industry leaders that have leveraged their digital investment to protect the business and set the stage for future success. Hear how forward-thinking distributors have integrated processes to optimize performance, applied industry best practices, and built interconnected networks for speed and resilience.</p>
  <p>The event will host eight content tracks dedicated to industry and line-of-business topics. In addition, there will be regional tracks that will include live broadcasts, breakouts, and customer round tables.</p>
  <h2 id="wholesale-distribution-at-sapphire-now-cant-miss-sessions">Wholesale Distribution at SAPPHIRE NOW: Can’t-Miss Sessions</h2>
  <p>In the <a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapphirenow2021/portal/page/sessions?search.industry=1620179531203028WhpM">session catalog</a>, look for these industry sessions:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Gordon Food Service</strong>: Realize the Imperative for a Modern Business Platform</li>
    <li>Streamline the Lead-to-Cash Process with Insight from <strong>Gordon Food Service</strong></li>
    <li>Discover How <strong>Novolex</strong> Transformed Its Business to Support Growth</li>
    <li><strong>PROMESA</strong>: Learn About Tailored IT Solutions That Help Your Midsize Company Grow</li>
    <li><strong>Zuellig Pharma</strong>: Transforming Healthcare with Best in Class Technology</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="global-keynote-hear-from-amerisourcebergen">Global Keynote: Hear from AmerisourceBergen</h2>
  <p>Tune in on June 2 for the SAPPHIRE NOW global keynote, where SAP CEO Christian Klein will deliver exciting strategy updates and discuss their impact with other special guests. One story you’ll hear is from wholesale distributor <strong>AmerisourceBergen</strong>, a leader in the pharmaceutical distribution sector.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="think-beyond-tomorrow-at-sapphire-now">Think beyond tomorrow at SAPPHIRE NOW</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapphirenow2021/portal/page/home">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="register-today">Register Today</h3>
  <p>SAPPHIRE NOW is a free event in 2021. Secure your spot, then watch your inbox for detailed information on this industry-leading event.</p>
  <p><a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapphirenow2021/portal/page/home">Register now</a></p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Lynn Lupo is solution manager for Wholesale Distribution at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="join-wholesale-distribution-sessions-at-sapphire-now">Join wholesale distribution sessions at SAPPHIRE NOW</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapphirenow2021/portal/page/sessions?search.industry=1620179531203028WhpM">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>industry/wholesale-distribution</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Building a Resilient E-Commerce Business with Arrow Electronics]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/arrow-electronics-resilient-e-commerce</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/arrow-electronics-resilient-e-commerce</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For Arrow Electronics, industry trends impact commerce strategy. Learn what it's doing to support evolving business and customer needs.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>industry/wholesale-distribution</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Distributor Powell Electronics Digitally Transformed with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/powell-electronics-digital-transformation-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/powell-electronics-digital-transformation-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For Powell Electronics, SAP S/4HANA helped the company stop "driving in reverse"; they can now look forward, plan, and execute on the plan.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>industry/wholesale-distribution</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>