<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-advisory-services/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Retailers Need to Know About the Rise of Recommerce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/retailers-rise-of-recommerce</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/retailers-rise-of-recommerce</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Retailers that invest in recommerce can better weather economic downturns and reap the benefits of becoming a more sustainable brand.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/commerce</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advisory-services</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Upward Momentum Builds with Digitalization in the Chemicals Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/upward-momentum-digitalization-chemicals-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/upward-momentum-digitalization-chemicals-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the right approach to digitalization and the help of SAP Advisory Services, the chemicals industry can innovate across the value chain.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Upward Momentum Builds with Digitalization in the Chemicals Industry" src="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="upward-momentum-builds-with-digitalization-in-the-chemicals-industry">Upward Momentum Builds with Digitalization in the Chemicals Industry</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Chemical companies are on a nonstop roller coaster of market shocks and digital transformation. Sandwiched between feedstock and energy companies and downstream processing industries, they’re predestined to play a vital role in fulfilling business-to-business (B2B) and consumer expectations for sustainable, reliable, innovative, and trusted products and services.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But rising to the challenge of today’s marketplace – especially increasing raw material and energy prices, margin pressure, supply chain complexity, and regulatory requirements – requires much more than Industry 4.0 initiatives focused on efficiency and price reduction. From operational performance to customer experience, companies must integrate data from across the enterprise into a single source to form sound decisions that make sustainability profitable and profitability sustainable.</p>
  <p>Such a transformation is undoubtedly technology intensive, but the key enablers are also unassailably human. Understanding this reality, many chemical companies rely on the <a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/business-transformation.html">SAP Advisory Services</a> portfolio, provided by the Business Transformation Services group at SAP, to help transform their operations and gain a competitive edge amid fast global changes.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="transform-your-business-and-unlock-digital-innovation-with-help-from-sap-advisory-services">Transform your business and unlock digital innovation with help from SAP Advisory Services</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/business-transformation.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="turning-challenges-into-great-opportunities">Turning Challenges into Great Opportunities</h2>
  <p>Competitively addressing turbulence depends on the ability to view transformation through the lens of six fundamental challenges:</p>
  <p><strong>R&#x26;D Pressure across the Product Portfolio</strong> The imperative to resist margin shrinkage, mitigate risks, increase ROI, and boost growth calls for innovative products and services that offer business value and foster close partnerships with customers. By pushing forward the adoption of advanced technologies to drive global R&#x26;D, supplier, and customer collaborations and joint ventures, businesses can prevent commoditization.</p>
  <p><strong>The Need for Vertical Integration</strong> Evolving production facilities with a balance of high efficiency, global scale, flexibility, and intelligent responsiveness allows supply chains to weigh the synergistic benefits of integrated manufacturing plants or industrial parks against the flexibility of smaller plants. As a result, businesses can leverage new opportunities with disruptive business models, such as making raw materials instead of buying them and producing semi-finished or even finished goods.</p>
  <p><strong>Global Supply Chain Complexity</strong> Global supply chains must be secure enough to mitigate volatile market conditions, such as global health emergencies, rising prices for raw materials and energy, and other factors that impact economic conditions. Companies can gain this advantage by establishing commercial and logistical transparency to support optimization and global planning of demand, sales, and operations.</p>
  <p><strong>Hidden Advantages of Business Networks</strong> Business cannot stay competitive in a complex ecosystem alone. They must also scale and optimize their supply chain globally with business networks, such as the <a href="/2021/03/catena-x-automotive-alliance-picks-up-speed">Catena-X Automotive Network</a>. Doing so empowers suppliers, contract and toll manufacturers, joint ventures, and customers to collaborate openly and create new prospects for co-innovating better products and services, improving value chain efficiency, and fueling long-term growth.</p>
  <p><strong>Compliance and Sustainability Urgency</strong> A primary objective for any chemical business is ensuring compliance with industry regulations. Yet, B2B customers also favor suppliers that help meet their own environmental, social, and governance (ESG) mandates. Sustainable businesses and innovations provide balance between these two expectations, creating a highly sought-after competitive edge by gearing products and services towards a circular economy.</p>
  <p><strong>Business Agility</strong> The industry’s dynamic and fast-changing environment of mergers, acquisitions, and divestitures is creating tremendous complexity and pressure for permanent change and adaptation. Chemical companies need to balance industry-wide globalization and centralization while increasing business agility.</p>
  <p>Chemical companies with a digital strategy encompassing all these topics can address industry challenges and seize on market trends in a disruptive manner. Through <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2016/03/d2238cd0-627c-0010-82c7-eda71af511fa.html">digital innovation</a>, businesses can gain new opportunities and capabilities never previously considered possible – including increased speed and efficiency, process automation, and data transparency.</p>
  <h2 id="seizing-the-moment-with-advisory-expertise">Seizing the Moment with Advisory Expertise</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="at-sap-your-success-is-our-goal">At SAP, your success is our goal</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/support.html#services-support-offerings">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>From the perspective of SAP Advisory Services, digitalization is not just another IT term but also a critical business priority. The more intelligent and sustainable a company becomes, the more agile, flexible, and integrated its value chain becomes.</p>
  <p>Advisory experts from SAP can enable chemical companies to turn their fundamental challenges into opportunities with a well-structured, business-driven design. This approach elaborates on the steps of the digital transformation journey – leading to a road map for future architecture design. Each phase of the road map follows an ideal sequence of digital innovation, technology adoption, and industry best practices and leverages the highest value for the company in the short term.</p>
  <p>SAP Advisory Services help organizations evaluate and act on the sentiments of their customers, partners, and employees and improve their environmental impact. Chemical companies can then be well positioned to keep their workforce engaged, increase organizational agility, and deliver the products and services customers need and trust. Furthermore, they can control their varied sources and categories of spending with outstanding finance and operational efficiency and real-time enterprise insight.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13184d5b5d29ebbc4d371c407a9c86acc71402ad2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13184d5b5d29ebbc4d371c407a9c86acc71402ad2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_13184d5b5d29ebbc4d371c407a9c86acc71402ad2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_13184d5b5d29ebbc4d371c407a9c86acc71402ad2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="300" height="283">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Intelligent enterprise framework</em></p>
  <p>Essentially, chemical companies that work with SAP advisory experts can realize their potential as <a href="https://www.sap.com/intelligent-enterprise.html">intelligent enterprises</a>. They can make confident decisions and drive continuous innovation to adapt, innovate, and overcome challenges while making responsible choices that help reduce waste and emissions and drive long-term growth.</p>
  <p>This business model is accomplished with intelligent technologies, including business networks, a business technology platform, cloud-based infrastructures, and solutions for business process management, experience management, industry cloud, and sustainability management. Additionally, artificial intelligence (AI), blockchain, data platforms, the Internet of Things (IoT), machine learning, predictive analytics, and virtual as well as augmented realities (VR/AR) are embedded in the intelligent technologies to drive end-to-end business processes and decision-making across enterprise domains.</p>
  <h2 id="bringing-to-life-an-intelligent-and-sustainable-network">Bringing to Life an Intelligent and Sustainable Network</h2>
  <p>The pressures on the chemicals industry may be relentless, with shocks coming in from all directions. However, this doesn’t mean businesses cannot find great opportunities in this volatile environment. With the right approach to digitalization, they can transform, innovate, and collaborate across the value chain to build upward momentum and better serve customers as an intelligent and sustainable network.</p>
  <p>Learn more about the <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2022/09/29/business-and-digital-trends-in-the-chemical-industry/">market trends and business priorities shaping various lines of businesses in the chemical industry</a> and how SAP can help guide the innovation needed to overcome them. Read the series <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/tag/business-digital-trends-in-the-chemical-industry/">“Business and Digital Trends in the Chemical Industry</a>” on SAP Community.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Ornulf Rexin is chief business consultant of Chemicals and Life Sciences for Business Transformation Services at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advisory-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How the Cloud Changes the Business Transformation Mindset]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/how-cloud-changes-business-transformation-mindset</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/how-cloud-changes-business-transformation-mindset</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A cloud-based business model transformation changes much more than the value of companies’ software assets and revenue streams. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/cloud-success-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advisory-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Unique Relationship Between Businesses and Their Cloud Solution Providers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/unique-relationship-between-businesses-and-cloud-solution-providers</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/unique-relationship-between-businesses-and-cloud-solution-providers</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read to learn how SAP Advisory Services can create a trust environment across operational and strategic areas for future-oriented business.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advisory-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital Transformation: The Importance of New Technology and the Human Factor]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/digital-transformation-importance-of-technology-and-the-human-factor</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/digital-transformation-importance-of-technology-and-the-human-factor</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Services and Support can give the necessary digital transformation guidance to gain the full potential of SAP BTP. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f9c6f0bfcccf6e95cda70514e753925ce62dba7d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f9c6f0bfcccf6e95cda70514e753925ce62dba7d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f9c6f0bfcccf6e95cda70514e753925ce62dba7d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Digital Transformation: The Importance of New Technology and the Human Factor" src="./media_1f9c6f0bfcccf6e95cda70514e753925ce62dba7d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="digital-transformation-the-importance-of-new-technology-and-the-human-factor">Digital Transformation: The Importance of New Technology and the Human Factor</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>From the simplest to the most complex projects, SAP Business Technology Platform is a critical piece of the larger digital transformation puzzle – empowering organizations to deliver human experiences that are integrated, data-driven, and extensible.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The more sophisticated technology becomes, the greater the struggle to adopt new business models and establish internal policies and processes to support them. Yet, the barrier is not the technology – it’s how people experience those models.</p>
  <p>One of the ways you can focus on the human factor of digital transformation is by implementing <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP). The platform features a comprehensive selection of solutions and functionalities that are cloud native or can be used for on-premise or hybrid environments and architectures. It includes database and data management solutions, analytics advancements, application development and integration capabilities, and intelligent technologies.</p>
  <p>By integrating your choice of functionalities across SAP solutions and processes on a single platform, you can obtain the critical insights and tools you need to amplify the value of those investments. But many organizations are gaining even more value when leveraging SAP Services and Support offerings that emphasize enablement, integration, optimization, and operational change.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="gain-the-full-potential-of-sap-btp-with-sap-services-and-support">Gain the full potential of SAP BTP with SAP Services and Support</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://youtu.be/6wFzZpf7pwY">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="connecting-digital-change-to-the-human-experience">Connecting Digital Change to the Human Experience</h2>
  <p>It seems that SAP customers know a secret to meaningful change that most businesses do not. According to a newly released <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/btp-technology-services-study/index.html">IDC Vendor Spotlight</a>, “The Benefits of Services and Support for Complex Technology Adoption,” surveyed CIOs and business managers indicated that they are too focused on their processes and organizational structure to take full advantage of new technology solutions and platforms. As a result, they cannot quantify business value adequately, nor scale and innovate with the IT architecture effectively.</p>
  <p>Many organizations worldwide are using SAP BTP to help address operational- and talent-related challenges in digital transformation initiatives. You can innovate a wide variety of new business scenarios and strengthen existing ones with technology providers and partners that provide ongoing services and support with a portfolio of integrated applications and services.</p>
  <p>But with the help of SAP Services and Support, you can safeguard a key part of your future success – how your customers and employees experience change. Every day, our service experts and I see how an outside perspective from vendor-driven services can help an organization gain the full value of increasingly complex technology. Such support brings much more than deep, industry-specific expertise and proprietary solutions and methodologies. It’s a much-needed answer to addressing unique people-related challenges quickly and effectively when they occur.</p>
  <p>For example, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/premium-engagement.html">premium engagements services</a> from SAP, with tailored business scenarios enabled by SAP BTP, offer detailed road maps for specific business objectives. The <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/preferred-success-cloud.html">SAP Preferred Success</a> offering provides recommendations for optimizing cloud solutions from SAP. Our step-by-step, quick-start <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/advisory-development/business-transformation.html">SAP Advisory Services</a> help ensure technical and functional cloud readiness to adopt new industry and business scenarios and accelerate deployment and delivery. Meanwhile, our <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/advisory-development/education-consulting.html">training and adoption options</a> provide the continuous learning, hands-on practice, and skill validation you need to use the platform confidently.</p>
  <p>Combining SAP BTP and SAP Services and Support helps unlock human-centered solution design that empathizes with real-world challenges of customers and employees. This collaboration allows you to identify significant use cases, create relevant and engaging user experiences, and develop value-added services. In fact, one of our customers – <a href="/2021/09/kakao-work-b2b-domain-sap-btp">Kakao Enterprise</a> – verified 68 cross-industry use cases to expand its consumer-grade mobile app’s functionality to improve user flow and overall performance quality for a business-to-business market.</p>
  <h2 id="building-up-transformations-that-last">Building Up Transformations That Last</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="download-the-idc-infographic">Download the IDC infographic</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/11/b4e04e3b-037e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Without question, your organization has profound opportunities to advance your digital transformation, especially when leveraging our technologies and the expertise of our global ecosystem of partners. But that does not mean that the internal challenges encountered along the way are becoming any less critical to resolve.</p>
  <p>SAP BTP and SAP Services and Support provide the tools and expertise that help you and your partners overcome technical and nontechnical barriers that get in the way of realizing a future as an intelligent enterprise. And as you continue to refine, innovate, and expand business scenarios and digital capabilities, we help you, as our customer, become well-positioned to deliver ongoing value to your business and the people that support you.</p>
  <p>Find out how vendor-provided services and support can help your business manage a complicated digital transformation more effectively, with minimal disruption and long-term success. Read the IDC Vendor Spotlight, sponsored by SAP, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/btp-technology-services-study/index.html">The Benefits of Services and Support for Complex Technology Adoption</a>.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Augusta Spinelli is interim services president and head of Services Intelligent Delivery Group at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advisory-services</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Build a Data-Driven Business]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/how-to-build-a-data-driven-business</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/how-to-build-a-data-driven-business</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Businesses can acquire the insight and capabilities they need to stay competitive by becoming a data-driven business. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_117beddf39984ac6cf818de5960d925f140691325.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_117beddf39984ac6cf818de5960d925f140691325.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_117beddf39984ac6cf818de5960d925f140691325.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How to Build a Data-Driven Business" src="./media_117beddf39984ac6cf818de5960d925f140691325.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-to-build-a-data-driven-business">How to Build a Data-Driven Business</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Data cannot fulfill its true purpose within the structure of a traditional enterprise. But when organizational strategies are defined down to the data-strategy level and supported by a data-centric structure, businesses can acquire the insight and capabilities they need to stay competitive.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Unfortunately, consequences can run deep when executives place insufficient importance on the value of data at strategic and operational levels. Organizations often become too stagnant to evolve with market dynamics and changing business needs to effectively challenge competitors and gain considerable market share.</p>
  <p>I have experienced how the long-term success of a company begins with an executive-level commitment to become a data-driven business. By unifying every area of the enterprise with this foundational goal, organizations can collaboratively develop an outcome-driven data strategy that breaks down the enterprise strategy into measurable data key performance indicators (KPIs).</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="keep-your-systems-running-at-peak-performance-with-sap-services-and-support">Keep your systems running at peak performance with SAP Services and Support</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/support.html#services-support-offerings">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="setting-the-foundation-for-a-data-culture">Setting the Foundation for a Data Culture</h2>
  <p>For many SAP customers, <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/advisory-development/business-transformation.html">SAP Advisory Services</a> is a critical part of their transformation into a truly data-driven business. The opportunity to foster innovation, nurture ideas, and build a resilient infrastructure with supporting processes enables organizations to understand the value of data and apply it to resolve business challenges with less risk and cost.</p>
  <p>One of the first steps that our advisory experts undertake is to help our customers establish the essential cornerstone of a data-driven business. They outline a framework of critical positions – which we call a “house of roles” – needed to support the data transformation of each organization.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ae1b28af3c62c4b212f0bca246b431a7c896bfc4.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ae1b28af3c62c4b212f0bca246b431a7c896bfc4.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1ae1b28af3c62c4b212f0bca246b431a7c896bfc4.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Figure showing house of roles framework" src="./media_1ae1b28af3c62c4b212f0bca246b431a7c896bfc4.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="607" height="284">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>The ‘house of roles’ of a data-driven business</em></p>
  <p>Each role in the framework has a unique set of responsibilities to help ensure control over the data landscape in terms of quality, consistency, relevance, processing performance, regulatory compliance, security, and authorized access:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>The <strong>data owner</strong> (usually a level-one manager) is accountable for a specific subset of data and defines management goals.</li>
    <li>The <strong>head of master data management (MDM) or chief data officer</strong> oversees data objects within scope, defines objectives for data quality and specifications, and monitors respective service-level agreements and KPIs.</li>
    <li>The <strong>data steward</strong> defines governance rules and validates maintenance requests for specific data objects to help ensure business intelligence remains high in quality and integrity.</li>
    <li>The <strong>data architect</strong> designs master data processes and logistics for dependent systems and provides technical support, such as data-quality rules and analysis.</li>
    <li>The <strong>data requester</strong> (any employee) requests new data or changes in existing data.</li>
    <li>The <strong>data agent</strong> creates and maintains master data in consultation with a data requester.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>When setting up the framework, conflicts may occur within it. For example, the head of MDM may want data agents to be responsible for maintaining a specific set of data, while business organizations may disagree.</p>
  <p>SAP Advisory Services helps defuse such controversies by leading workshops that allow our customers to transparently define roles with the involvement of all relevant stakeholders. This exercise includes the appointment of employees to each position and a data domain for which they will manage communications and governance requirements.</p>
  <h2 id="cultivating-pivotal-change">Cultivating Pivotal Change</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-importance-of-being-earnest-with-your-data-models">The Importance of Being Earnest with Your Data Models</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://insights.sap.com/data-models-importance-of-being-earnest/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Data-driven businesses begin with a clear decision-making process that transforms the company into a culture that values data accountability and governance. Through the “house of rules” framework, SAP Advisory Services can bring customers one giant leap closer to realizing this vision.</p>
  <p>What does this mean for SAP customers? A world of opportunity. In addition to having a complete foundation for correct, fact-based decision-making, they can open up new revenue streams through data monetization and uncover insights already existing in their business applications.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Jan Hoffmann is a business processes principal consultant at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advisory-services</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Quick Start into Industry Services]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/quick-start-into-industry-services</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/quick-start-into-industry-services</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Specific industry services, like those offered by SAP Services and Support and SAP's industry cloud, can help business run more successfully.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advisory-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Is Your Business Ready for the Cloud?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/is-your-business-ready-for-the-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/is-your-business-ready-for-the-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how SAP Advisory Services offer a comprehensive investigation to help ensure valuable outcomes through a migration or upgrade to cloud.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advisory-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[More Than Data: Why Master Data Management Is a Critical Part of Digital Readiness]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/more-than-data-why-master-data-management-is-a-critical-part-of-digital-readiness</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/more-than-data-why-master-data-management-is-a-critical-part-of-digital-readiness</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Businesses gain a more profound and innovative edge by using MDM to open the door to more accurate, consistent, and predictive analytics.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e404247fbc4fba1e35a30b19b3cdae22b36d3149.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e404247fbc4fba1e35a30b19b3cdae22b36d3149.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e404247fbc4fba1e35a30b19b3cdae22b36d3149.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="More Than Data: Why Master Data Management Is a Critical Part of Digital Readiness" src="./media_1e404247fbc4fba1e35a30b19b3cdae22b36d3149.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="more-than-data-why-master-data-management-is-a-critical-part-of-digital-readiness">More Than Data: Why Master Data Management Is a Critical Part of Digital Readiness</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Collecting, unifying, managing, integrating, and using data that is clean, consistent, and accessible have been the ultimate goals of master data management (MDM) for most organizations. However, these activities only mark the beginning of a much more revolutionary digital transformation story.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As B2B and B2C customers continue to shift more of their commerce transactions toward digital channels and engage in product-based digital services, the volume of master data is set to explode. <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=prUS47560321">IDC</a> predicts that the “amount of digital data created over the next five years will be greater than twice the amount of data created since the advent of digital storage.”</p>
  <p>This growing trend is not only an opportunity, but also a challenge to how master data is managed. While considered a preparatory step for transitioning to the latest technologies, such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a>, MDM can also lay the foundation for future application development and business innovation.</p>
  <h2 id="harmonizing-data-to-drive-meaningful-transformation">Harmonizing Data to Drive Meaningful Transformation</h2>
  <p>While the pressure to innovate groundbreaking, sustainable value for customers and the business increases, many SAP customers are solving unique challenges quickly with less cost and risk. The key to their success is <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/advisory-development/business-transformation.html">SAP Advisory Services</a>, enabling a methodical, forward-thinking MDM approach to fostering innovation, nurturing new ideas, and building strong solutions.</p>
  <p>By enhancing the quality of master data with the assistance of SAP Advisory Services, our customers are overcoming significant challenges that many companies face in their MDM practices, including the following.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="transform-your-company-into-an-intelligent-enterprise-with-sap-advisory-services">Transform your company into an intelligent enterprise with SAP Advisory Services</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services/advisory-development/business-transformation.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="turning-a-lack-of-commitment-into-a-shared-vision">1. Turning a Lack of Commitment into a Shared Vision</h3>
  <p>Executive sponsors do not always connect how the benefits of an IT strategy can advance the overall business strategy, especially quick wins in MDM projects. Unfortunately, this level of detachment among decision-makers undermines the efforts of any solution implementation.</p>
  <p>Consider an organization that purchased a solution license without setting aside the budget to support activities such as creating a master data team, staffing new roles, and setting up governance procedures. By not addressing errors made along the way and reconsidering the need for better MDM support, stakeholders likely feel frustrated once the project goes live because business needs were not met as expected. Worse yet, gaining the executive confidence and commitment needed for future projects become increasingly tricky as stakeholders feel their input will not make a difference in the outcome.</p>
  <p>SAP Advisory Services help alleviate the situation by framing and solving various business and IT challenges and relaying how improved MDM processes can help. The organization can start its journey toward solution implementation by cultivating the business’s collective genius in an unconventional and creative atmosphere. This is accomplished with pragmatic design thinking workshops, pilots, prototypes, road maps, digital working models, and organizational expertise and enablement.</p>
  <h3 id="strengthening-communication-between-it-and-the-business">2. Strengthening Communication Between IT and the Business</h3>
  <p>IT departments typically lead MDM projects. However, users may still refuse to participate in the early discussions because they cannot see how the effort can benefit their business function. Over time, this lack of awareness turns into a lack of desire to fulfill MDM responsibilities, leaving behind any chance of leveraging data as a way to expand the company’s capabilities and help fuel revenue growth.</p>
  <p>To overcome this bidirectional misunderstanding, SAP Advisory Services help ensure that IT pays attention to the immediate needs of the business users and establishes MDM processes that are efficient and simple to maintain. Furthermore, the convenient delivery of training and timely knowledge allows closer collaboration between IT and the business and a better understanding of how the MDM project impacts the specific organization and overall business.</p>
  <h3 id="establishing-governance-and-common-data-definitions">3. Establishing Governance and Common Data Definitions</h3>
  <p>When MDM tools and best practices are not implemented globally, individual organizations often feel compelled to act locally on their terms – limiting the visibility and consistency to make decisions at the corporate level. Meanwhile, users working with the same data sets have little idea of how they are being processed in other departments or whether decisions are based on the same understanding of what the data means.</p>
  <p>Companies that rely on SAP Advisory Services can employ universal governance of their master data processes at any point of their MDM project. Setting up a change management team and conducting an initial assessment early on improves organizational understanding of the level and magnitude of change needed to ensure MDM capabilities support the digital investment or transformation initiative. Plus, every user can access the proven knowledge, tools, and templates required to adapt and comply with data standards.</p>
  <h3 id="speeding-business-optimization-and-innovation">4. Speeding Business Optimization and Innovation</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="gain-more-insight-into-data-mangement">Gain more insight into data mangement</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-data-management/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Although complex in theory, MDM is emerging as a critical part of digital readiness as companies recognize its long-term value and involve the right people to establish the right best practices. Even a standard approach to MDM can drive innovation when the right data strategy is in place and IT objectives are aligned with business strategies.</p>
  <p>However, with SAP Advisory Services, businesses can gain a more profound edge by using MDM to open the door to more accurate and consistent analytics tools. Data sets become more predictive and multidimensional by combining master data with <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-machine-learning/">machine learning</a>, <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-artificial-intelligence/">artificial intelligence (AI)</a>, graphical visualization, and other intelligent technologies. Different views on similar domains support the demands of various business groups on context-dependent insights.</p>
  <h2 id="realizing-the-full-potential-of-mdm-advancements">Realizing the Full Potential of MDM Advancements</h2>
  <p>From the viewpoint of the business, MDM is valuable when cost reduction and closer cross-departmental collaboration are achieved. IT organizations can deliver on those expectations by implementing solutions successfully on the first attempt, harmonizing the way technologies and people work, and avoiding any misunderstandings along the way.</p>
  <p>SAP Advisory Services enable IT and non-IT organizations to maximize the potential of their digital transformation by creating a master data foundation that drives greater visibility, agility, and focus. The service portfolio establishes emerging technologies and draws on the latest innovations, industry experts, and ecosystem of innovators from SAP. And for the business, this means an opportunity to further optimize operations and initiate change – faster and with less risk.</p>
  <p><em>Stay in the conversation by following the SAP Services and Support offerings on</em> <em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/sapsupportinfo">YouTube</a></em>, <em><a href="https://twitter.com/SAPDigitalSvcs">Twitter</a>,</em> <em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/138840">LinkedIn</a>, and</em> <em><a href="https://www.facebook.com/SAPDigitalBusinessServices">Facebook</a></em>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Gelena Artemenko is a business enterprise consultant for CPG &#x26; Retail Industries at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/master-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advisory-services</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Four Ways to Turn Innovation into the Best Part of Working in an IT Organization]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/sap-advisory-services-use-cases-innovation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/sap-advisory-services-use-cases-innovation</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Four SAP Advisory Services use cases can help organizations respond effectively to ever-evolving priorities and market dynamics.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fde0c1eac23d1dfd27fa55a3aad3254958053b54.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fde0c1eac23d1dfd27fa55a3aad3254958053b54.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1fde0c1eac23d1dfd27fa55a3aad3254958053b54.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Four Ways to Turn Innovation into the Best Part of Working in an IT Organization" src="./media_1fde0c1eac23d1dfd27fa55a3aad3254958053b54.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="four-ways-to-turn-innovation-into-the-best-part-of-working-in-an-it-organization">Four Ways to Turn Innovation into the Best Part of Working in an IT Organization</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>People may love what innovation delivers while others may loathe the process and risk involved when turning ideas into real-world solutions. But for IT organizations, a choice of four use cases enabled by SAP Advisory Services can respond effectively to ever-evolving priorities and market dynamics.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Without question, demand for “keeping the lights on” remains strong. But at the same time, many IT leaders are concerned that they are neglecting investments in innovation that could help their business seize opportunities and mitigate risk quickly and effectively.</p>
  <p>One prime example is the debate over legacy enterprise resource planning (ERP). Organizational executives may regard modernizing this trusted software as an unnecessary budget line item when business systems work well for the user. But from the CIO’s perspective, it is a critical must-have to unify the processes and data every employee needs to make the best decisions and act in real time, enterprise wide. Most importantly, the effort can reduce the cost of long-term system maintenance and enhance operational efficiency, the customer experience, and compliance.</p>
  <p>The value of such IT innovation ultimately depends on how every person in the enterprise – across all roles and levels – embrace it. Based on the experience of our advisory services experts working with SAP customers worldwide, our research has identified four use cases to illustrate IT organizational best practices. These use cases may look different from each other, but they all have the same goal: to deliver on rising expectations for intelligent innovation and strengthen IT performance continuity.</p>
  <h2 id="use-case-1-structuring-toward-technology">Use Case 1: Structuring Toward Technology</h2>
  <p>Some SAP customers choose to take a technology-oriented approach to their innovation processes. Consider the structure adopted by a global software company shown in figure 1 below. At first glance, the structure seems very traditional. However, if you look further down in the chart, you’ll see that must-have characteristics of a modern IT landscape are supported, such as a digital core, rock-solid and intelligent operations, smart connected cloud, and innovative business models.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e0b70f9ca380ee2333e23fb05ee60d9dad3f3d32.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e0b70f9ca380ee2333e23fb05ee60d9dad3f3d32.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e0b70f9ca380ee2333e23fb05ee60d9dad3f3d32.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Figure 1: Graphic on Technology-Oriented Structure" src="./media_1e0b70f9ca380ee2333e23fb05ee60d9dad3f3d32.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="858" height="397">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Figure 1: Technology-Oriented Structure</em></p>
  <p>A dedicated team is set up to support a continuous process for enterprise architecture and innovation creation. The agile and DevOps center of expertise (COE) provides the capabilities, methodologies, and training needed to help any regional, central, and line-of-business team participate in innovation programs.</p>
  <p>The formal organization chart shown in figure 1 was first created eight years ago and continues to guide our customer’s agile transformation today. More than 80 product teams are in place with nearly 100 defined products, and each group contains six to 10 experts who are developed and reskilled on demand. More importantly, the innovation delivered enables the company’s 1,500 employees – from the front office to the back office –to adopt more agile ways of working and making decisions.</p>
  <h2 id="use-case-2-focusing-on-a-specific-business-domain">Use Case 2: Focusing on a Specific Business Domain</h2>
  <p>Other SAP customers prefer a business domain-oriented IT organization. In this model, the IT organization mirrors the business structure, and DevOps teams emerge and retire it on demand and as expected to deliver a well defined outcome.</p>
  <p>For instance, a customer in the automotive industry has created stable core DevOps teams staffed by function and IT experts (see figure 2). While function experts are permanently appointed, IT experts are temporarily assigned from their home-base organization. Plus, an agile COE can be used by any team or line of business.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1efe5f847de17315de46ab959abc19851a0286997.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1efe5f847de17315de46ab959abc19851a0286997.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1efe5f847de17315de46ab959abc19851a0286997.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Figure 2: Graphic on Business Domain-Oriented IT Organization" src="./media_1efe5f847de17315de46ab959abc19851a0286997.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="850" height="400">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Figure 2: Business Domain-Oriented IT Organization</em></p>
  <h2 id="use-case-3-expanding-coe-capabilities">Use Case 3: Expanding COE Capabilities</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-about-services-and-support-from-sap">Read more about services and support from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/support.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>When our customers primarily use SAP solutions for various functions, they often structure IT by business domains and expand them with the support of COE capabilities. SAP application and solution experts are assigned to the business area, whereas cross functions are organized in the COE structure. For one of our customers from the research and development industry, this setup enabled it to facilitate business and IT integration, as illustrated in figure 3.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ab168d22d13d2b8ea4a465d8802d1b125f16abbe.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ab168d22d13d2b8ea4a465d8802d1b125f16abbe.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ab168d22d13d2b8ea4a465d8802d1b125f16abbe.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Figure 3: Graphic on Expansion of COE Capabilities Across the Business" src="./media_1ab168d22d13d2b8ea4a465d8802d1b125f16abbe.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="850" height="524">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Figure 3: Expansion of COE Capabilities Across the Business</em></p>
  <p>SAP solutions experts with process knowledge are assigned to each business team and embedded into the support chain as second-level support. Additionally, the solution experts are responsible for customizing, making standard changes, and evaluating requirements in close cooperation with cross-functional experts in the COE.</p>
  <p>The customer’s COE must protect the productive SAP landscape by performing design authority for new IT demands, centralized release management, and an operation control center.</p>
  <h2 id="use-case-4-directing-product-and-service-innovation">Use Case 4: Directing Product and Service Innovation</h2>
  <p>Last is the product-oriented structure. With this use case, one of our customers from the financial services industry adopted this approach to distinguish between market products, enabling products, and corporate products (see figure 4).</p>
  <p>A significant portion of our customer’s enabling and corporate products are supported by SAP software and technology, and IT experts from SAP were well integrated into its business activities. Meanwhile, the company’s product areas, such as market products and specific corporate products, relied on third-party software and technologies maintained by the second larger COE within company’s IT organization. Since every product area drives agility, and innovation was a critical responsibility.</p>
  <p>In this case, our customer’s COE is the home base for SAP innovation and DevOps capabilities. Plus, a scaled, agile framework (SAFE) is the chose innovation methodology.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e5e26a33a8d6a19f4ba4bb9ee8ddab0733af8d45.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e5e26a33a8d6a19f4ba4bb9ee8ddab0733af8d45.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e5e26a33a8d6a19f4ba4bb9ee8ddab0733af8d45.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Figure 4: Graphic on Consequential Product Orientation, Including SAP Solutions" src="./media_1e5e26a33a8d6a19f4ba4bb9ee8ddab0733af8d45.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="865" height="322">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Figure 4: Consequential Product Orientation, Including SAP Solutions</em></p>
  <h2 id="building-its-future-as-an-innovation-best-practice-organization">Building IT’s Future as an Innovation Best Practice Organization</h2>
  <p>Across all four of these use cases, SAP S/4HANA is the chosen intelligent ERP that serves as the core of all data, applications, and processes. However, no one-size-fits-all strategy for implementing, using, and benefiting from the solution exists. Each company must identify an approach that best fits their structure, meets their needs, and brings the desired success.</p>
  <p>Today’s competitive landscape is pushing companies to become more agile and renew themselves. In response, the three dimensions of innovation – technologies, capabilities, and structures – need to be rethought and reconciled. Only then will businesses emerge stronger through meaningful transformation and take advantage of the opportunities that arise in the future with confidence and ambition.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-sap-advisory-services">Explore SAP Advisory Services</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services/advisory-development/business-transformation.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="for-more-information-explore-sap-advisory-services">For more information, explore <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/advisory-development/business-transformation.html">SAP Advisory Services</a>.</h3>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Stay in the conversation by following SAP Services and Support on<br><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/sapsupportinfo">YouTube</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/SAPDigitalSvcs">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/138840">LinkedIn</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SAPDigitalBusinessServices">Facebook</a>.</p>
        <p><em>Torsten Scheffler is a business transformation consultant at SAP.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="subscribe-to-the-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter">Subscribe to the Innovation and Transformation Newsletter</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advisory-services</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Advisory Services: Elevating IT Organizations to the Innovation Level for the Best Business Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/elevating-it-organizations-innovation-level</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/elevating-it-organizations-innovation-level</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP Advisory Services, experts guide customers in elevating their innovation level by attending to three major requirements. Learn them.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10414de0a8884506e30afb363d8e21057ad6b6551.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10414de0a8884506e30afb363d8e21057ad6b6551.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10414de0a8884506e30afb363d8e21057ad6b6551.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Advisory Services: Elevating IT Organizations to the Innovation Level for the Best Business Outcomes" src="./media_10414de0a8884506e30afb363d8e21057ad6b6551.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-advisory-services-elevating-it-organizations-to-the-innovation-level-for-the-best-business-outcomes">SAP Advisory Services: Elevating IT Organizations to the Innovation Level for the Best Business Outcomes</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For years, CIOs have dedicated the bulk of their resources to maintaining a connected, efficient, and always-on technology landscape. But this “keeping the lights on” mindset is quickly shifting as technology innovation, market dynamics, and new business priorities fundamentally alter every aspect of the IT function.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Getting ahead of the competition has become increasingly challenging as market dynamics continue to shock businesses to their core. But change itself is not the issue for IT; the real concern is providing a connected, collaborative, and agile ecosystem that the entire company needs to renew the customer experience, employee engagement, and business productivity.</p>
  <p>From the CIO’s perspective, this new reality is only intensifying the pressure to rethink the IT function. Demand for fast, agile innovation continues to grow, but the existing technology landscape is being stretched beyond its capacity to effectively respond to ever-evolving priorities and market dynamics.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-about-services-and-support-from-sap">Read more about services and support from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/support.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="accelerating-it-transformation-to-address-pressing-trends">Accelerating IT Transformation to Address Pressing Trends</h2>
  <p>Regardless of industry and business model, CIOs have been working diligently to implement a wide variety of changes within their organization to produce technology innovations that support the ever-expanding interconnection of people, devices, content, and relationships. But this overall transformation journey is an ongoing, fluid process.</p>
  <p>Based on many years of working with SAP customers from various industries and using a multitude of business models, our advisory services experts have identified key trends of well-running IT organizations that deliver on rising expectations for enterprise-wide intelligence.</p>
  <p><strong>Trend 1: Widespread availability of new technologies</strong></p>
  <p>An explosion of intelligent technology options is now universally accessible to businesses of any size, from any industry, and within any market. The Internet of Things (IoT), Industry 4.0, the cloud, automation, predictive analytics, Big Data, machine learning, artificial intelligence (AI), and blockchain — all these digital advancements and more are empowering peers and competitors alike to produce better outcomes.</p>
  <p>However, companies that are adopting these data-driven technologies quickly are achieving game-changing benefits. They are experiencing accelerated growth in available information and harnessing it with advancements in real-time analytics enabled by AI and machine learning. More importantly, engagement among customers and employees is higher with immersive experiences enabled by voice recognition and virtual and augmented reality.</p>
  <p><strong>Trend 2: Changing expectations for the work experience</strong></p>
  <p>By connecting business and industry knowledge with expertise in technology, data management, and human behavior, IT organizations play a critical role in optimizing the value of every digital investment. This unique capability allows every business function to take advantage of existing and new applications in ways that meet employee expectations.</p>
  <p>For example, migrating to the cloud can provide a much-needed platform for increased agility and adoption of next-generation solutions that drive innovation. While the project offers data-hungry organizations with massive volumes of data, employees of all generations and roles can also expand their skills, use intelligence more meaningfully, and satisfy their desire for purposeful work.</p>
  <p><strong>Trend 3: Rising competition to satisfy evolving customer behavior</strong></p>
  <p>As switching costs continue to decline, customers are empowered to evolve their behaviors and expectations in ways that benefit them. This constant evolution also opens the door to new competitors that provide more straightforward and satisfying business models as barriers to entry lower.</p>
  <p>Even the most well-managed business can benefit from scaling its value proposition to shifts across its customer base. By considering changes in society, culture, and the world around it, IT organizations can connect the dots between digital investments and the larger purpose they serve beyond immediate business goals. Such opportunities may include attracting and retaining the best talent, building a brand name around unparalleled customer service, and setting a foundation for strategic market leadership.</p>
  <h2 id="balancing-risk-and-opportunity">Balancing Risk and Opportunity</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-sap-advisory-services">Explore SAP Advisory Services</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services/advisory-development/business-transformation.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/advisory-development/business-transformation.html">SAP Advisory Services</a>, many SAP customers are taking advantage of these three trends to create and run new business models, processes, and products and services uniquely designed for a hyperconnected world. Our Intelligent Enterprise concept allows them to address their challenges head-on when transforming their operations.</p>
  <p>Our team of technology and business experts guides customers through their innovation journey by attending to three major requirements.</p>
  <p><strong>Requirement 1: Modernize the technology stack</strong></p>
  <p>This requisite is much more than meeting business demands and lowering IT costs. For us, it’s about undergoing a thorough search for the right technology that enables each customer’s workforce to focus on higher-value tasks by replacing repetitive tasks with automation.</p>
  <p>The Intelligent Enterprise concept allows SAP to offer a broad portfolio of available technologies, covering a range of business functions and capabilities supported by three critical components:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Intelligent suite:</strong> Automate day-to-day business processes and improve interactions with customers, partners, suppliers, and employees through applications with embedded intelligence.</li>
    <li><strong>Digital platform:</strong> Facilitate the collection, connection, and orchestration of data and the integration and extension of processes within the intelligent suite by leveraging SAP Business Technology Platform and the SAP Database and Data Management portfolio.</li>
    <li><strong>Intelligent technologies:</strong> Leverage embedded intelligence to detect patterns, predict outcomes, and suggest actions.</li>
  </ul>
  <p><strong>Requirement 2: Realign capabilities with the business strategy</strong></p>
  <p>By thinking beyond organizational boxes and lines, IT organizations can help business functions redefine their structure in terms of skill advancement and culture change. Every organization can work together as a dynamic network in which end-to-end accountability is fostered, flexible resources allow for quick changes, and the leadership team shows direction. More importantly, every employee is focused on delivering business outcomes that contribute to one shared objective: providing rock-solid operations to help ensure business continuity.</p>
  <p>In our research of SAP customers that successfully transformed their operating model with an adaptive and outcome-oriented approach, a thread of six key attributes is often present. These qualities help safeguard innovation efforts with the support of leadership and organizational structures across all levels.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1662c5e52e097a1e7205f7179a7c058f4bd0b5c0b.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1662c5e52e097a1e7205f7179a7c058f4bd0b5c0b.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1662c5e52e097a1e7205f7179a7c058f4bd0b5c0b.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Graphic: 6 best practices" src="./media_1662c5e52e097a1e7205f7179a7c058f4bd0b5c0b.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1133" height="266">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Figure 1: Six key features of best-practice IT organizations</em></p>
  <ol>
    <li><strong>Business IT integration:</strong> IT capabilities are embedded in all business-led product areas. Roles are usually characterized by fluid boundaries that allow people to work with smaller teams across organizational entities with common goals. Additionally, IT support is redefined by giving employees a choice of interaction channels, such as online chat, phone call, ticket submission, and service desk.</li>
    <li><strong>Product orientation:</strong> Priorities and budgets are set for specific business capabilities and products, not projects. Plus, product owners are accountable for objectives, end to end, which align with well-defined priorities.</li>
    <li><strong>Agility and DevOps:</strong> By creating a competence center for IT agility and DevOps, customers can scale new ways for employees to work productively. This approach combines continuous integration, delivery, and deployment to deliver uninterrupted operations automation, for example site reliability engineering.</li>
    <li><strong>Cloudification:</strong> In this case, customers are relying on a cloud environment. They can either increase their consumption of software as a service (SaaS), move to infrastructure as a service (IaaS) such as a hyperscalers, or access self-services in a landscape that scales automatically to changing needs and skills.</li>
    <li><strong>Innovation and emerging technologies:</strong> Innovation creation is considered an unceasing process. Customer and user experiences are the central focus when designing new technologies and leveraging emerging capabilities, including AI and machine learning.</li>
    <li><strong>Rock-solid IT operations:</strong> When protecting production and automation, our customers engage central release management to actively support continuous delivery and rely on an operations control center to enable nearly 100% availability.</li>
  </ol>
  <p><strong>Requirement 3: Redefine the organizational structure</strong></p>
  <p>Customers that fulfill requirements one and two often transform their organizational structures to address many external factors. They tend to implement an <a href="/2021/03/sap-advisory-services-use-cases-innovation">agile, outcome-focused IT operating model</a> that anchors and applies the six key features of best-practice IT organizations, as listed in the figure above, within various organizational setups.</p>
  <h2 id="embracing-the-potential-of-modern-it-innovation-practices">Embracing the Potential of Modern IT Innovation Practices</h2>
  <p>One organization’s risk can be another business’s opportunity. It all depends on how people embrace it. The same perspective can be applied when continuously modernizing the IT infrastructure.</p>
  <p>The goal may be any number of possibilities, such as skill development, process realignment, organizational structure change, or reimagined operational models. But the real value of every newly adopted technology is the opportunity to revive the fundamental purpose of IT innovation – to deliver the right business outcomes every time.</p>
  <p>For more information, explore <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/advisory-development/business-transformation.html">SAP Advisory Services on sap.com</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Stay in the conversation by following the SAP Services and Support on<br><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/sapsupportinfo">YouTube</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/SAPDigitalSvcs">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/138840">LinkedIn</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SAPDigitalBusinessServices">Facebook</a>.</p>
        <p><em>Torsten Scheffler is a business transformation Consultant at SAP.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="subscribe-to-the-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter">Subscribe to the Innovation and Transformation Newsletter</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advisory-services</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Data Quality: The True Measurement of Digital Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/data-quality-measurement-digital-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/data-quality-measurement-digital-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Data quality is the heart of every digital transformation, a must-have for every company pursuing an increasingly digital marketplace.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d207f50e7f71802134a75441a0013716f1007a38.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d207f50e7f71802134a75441a0013716f1007a38.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d207f50e7f71802134a75441a0013716f1007a38.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Data Quality: The True Measurement of Digital Transformation" src="./media_1d207f50e7f71802134a75441a0013716f1007a38.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="data-quality-the-true-measurement-of-digital-transformation">Data Quality: The True Measurement of Digital Transformation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Despite the immense attention and investment paid to digital transformation, most businesses still miss the most critical part of their evolution: data. It doesn’t matter if artificial intelligence (AI), process automation, bots, or predictive analytics is adopted. Without high-quality data, these core technologies can never truly benefit any company.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>If your company has yet to catch on to the importance of data quality, it’s not too late. Though Big Data has been around since the early nineties, the value and strong focus on data has increased drastically in the last decade. Since then, some organizations have undergone a <a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0963868717302615">continuous cycle</a> of work realignment, process refinement, and business model innovation to reap the benefits of this information gold mine.</p>
  <p>Companies that leverage their data want to create more value for their customers and themselves. But the <a href="https://www.hbs.edu/faculty/Publication%20Files/SMR-How-Big-Data-Is-Different_782ad61f-8e5f-4b1e-b79f-83f33c903455.pdf">concept of “value”</a> is broad and depends on a defined set of strategic goals, technology adoption, and data operationalization. In most cases, businesses that cite “value” as the <a href="https://aisel.aisnet.org/icis2014/proceedings/ISStrategy/30/">ultimate outcome of their transformation</a> efforts really mean boosting efficiency, optimizing supply chain flows, or using economies of scale to improve customer relationships.</p>
  <p>So, how can organizations use data effectively? According to <a href="https://wiki.uib.no/info310/images/4/4c/McAfeeBrynjolfsson2012-BigData-TheManagementRevolution-HBR.pdf">Edwards Deming and Peter Drucker</a>, “You can’t manage what you don’t measure.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-sap-advisory-services">Explore SAP Advisory Services</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services/advisory-development/business-transformation.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="clearing-the-path-to-pivotal-change">Clearing the Path to Pivotal Change</h2>
  <p>To measure data use and find areas for improvements, many companies have created a new role within their C-level ranks – <a href="https://books.google.de/books?hl=de&#x26;lr=&#x26;id=h7vOSdWVV5UC&#x26;oi=fnd&#x26;pg=PP1&#x26;dq=chief+data+officer&#x26;ots=RNfYYw-q-s&#x26;sig=mWIgy-HnH5RiNGqXovMoBZ7bZHU&#x26;redir_esc=y#v=onepage&#x26;q=chief%20data%20officer&#x26;f=false">the chief data officer (CDO)</a> – over the last eight years. This executive is tasked with defining the company-wide data strategy, including controlling, governing, and managing data-driven engagements to shape the business into an intelligent enterprise. One operational example is the cleanup of inaccurate, incomplete, and duplicated information – also known as “dirty data” – residing within the digital infrastructure.</p>
  <p>Gartner describes “<a href="https://search.proquest.com/openview/2e55d82a02441d0c7599830046ad30c9/1?pq-origsite=gscholar&#x26;cbl=47365">dirty data</a>” as information that is inaccurate, incomplete, and pervaded of duplicates, impacting customer turnover, expense management, sales opportunities, and back-office functions. Therefore, companies should address this issue with the following practices based on a part of Gartner’s basic principles of data quality management:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Consistency</strong>: Data is stored in one or multiple locations with equal values.</li>
    <li><strong>Accuracy</strong>: Data value is consistent across the target model.</li>
    <li><strong>Validity</strong>: Data values are within a certain predefined range or domain.</li>
    <li><strong>Integrity</strong>: Relationships between data values are complete.</li>
    <li><strong>Relevance</strong>: Data holds the right information to support the business.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Improving data quality to the point where any digital transformation gains a beneficial edge is like losing weight – it takes special effort to attain it and consistency to maintain it. With a focused mindset and healthy habits, companies can leverage their data to stay relevant and financially stable with room for future growth and new business models.</p>
  <h2 id="managing-data-with-a-principled-approach">Managing Data with a Principled Approach</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-about-services-and-support-from-sap">Read more about services and support from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/support.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While approaches to assessing data quality are numerous, some methods work better than others. For example, many companies use the Friday afternoon measurement method, known as <a href="https://hbr.org/2016/07/assess-whether-you-have-a-data-quality-problem">FAM</a>. Using FAM, one assesses the most common errors within the last 100 data records, such as sales orders or business partner information, on a paper-sheet table to derive an improvement strategy for corrupted data sets.</p>
  <p>FAM may not be the best solution for most organizations. We recommend an online tool, namely a data quality dashboard. This online tool provides real-time insights into a company’s overall data health, uncovering all inefficiencies across different domains to be addressed by the CDO organization in one location, millions at a time. A rules framework combined with innovation technologies, such as machine learning and intelligent robotic process automation (iRPA), provides real-time insight to action across all systems in which master data is stored to restore inconsistencies.</p>
  <p><strong>1. Data consistency is evaluated in terms of quantity, not quality.</strong></p>
  <p>To enhance key performance indicators for data quality, organizations should consider a specific master data domain, such as material master data, against its availability in cloud-based or on-premise systems. This could be helpful if master data is scattered across different landscapes.</p>
  <p>Master data records must also be checked for duplicate values based on the variety of their attributes. Duplicates, followed by missing entries, are the most common occurrence within corrupted data. To support the duplicate search, further aspects, like data accuracy, need to be taken into consideration.</p>
  <p><strong>2. Data accuracy is measured by the format and content of defined data sets.</strong></p>
  <p>The use of country-specific data formats – such as the structural difference between European and American dates – can significantly impact a company’s ability to deliver tangible outcomes. Decision-makers can never assume that data means the same to everyone.</p>
  <p>A popular use case for verifying content for accuracy is the handling of workflows and abbreviations. Following logic like “shipment date must not come before the order date” can help ensure the dates on specific activities communicate the same insight to everyone involved in the delivery process.</p>
  <p>Further content-related accuracy checks are necessary for homogenous data sets. Abbreviations should be set to a company-wide standard. For instance, in the “City” field, “New York” must be appear as “NYC,” not “NY.” Such checks will be useful also in the duplicate search, once applied.</p>
  <p><strong>3. Data validity checks are a recurring task.</strong></p>
  <p>As a byproduct of manual processes or reorganizations, companies often have addresses that are only up to date for a specific time frame. A dedicated business rule can frequently check time frames against a specified date, mark affected records, and alert the data quality responsible to derive actions. Such checks need to be done on a frequent basis.</p>
  <p><strong>4. Data integrity is assessed to identify data sets with a recurring pattern.</strong></p>
  <p>Key performance indicators for meaningful data quality should consider data integrity patterns from all master data domains. For example, detecting a recurring data pattern could be as simple as programming a required field as mandatory to capture necessary insights. However, a more complex scenario may also be applied to classify a material code to a specific characteristic category or plant location. Patterns within the integrity key performance indicator (KPI) must be of major weighting within the overall data quality KPI.</p>
  <p><strong>5. Data relevance is achieved through continuous maintenance.</strong></p>
  <p>After setting up rules for deriving meaningful data quality, the dashboard setup still requires attention to help ensure users can drill down to the line item level for dynamic, real-time, and actionable insight. Directing analytics results generated by the dashboard to the maintenance layer allows CDOs to easily improve data quality by opening service requests. Furthermore, user feedback from service requests can serve as input to improve rule composition. This feedback should be the starting point of a cycle to resolve and refine the rules and data issues.</p>
  <h2 id="focusing-on-data-improvement-and-consistency-at-scale">Focusing on Data Improvement and Consistency at Scale</h2>
  <p>Every company needs a single source of truth to pinpoint their weaknesses and inefficiencies. Fortunately, innovations in mobility, artificial intelligence, process automation, bots, and predictive analytics are making data creation and editing more efficient and convenient than ever before.</p>
  <p>But to be truly successful, businesses must take a quantum leap in data quality with the assistance of tools such as a CDO dashboard. Why? Because data quality is the heart of every digital transformation and a must-have for every company pursuing an increasingly digital marketplace.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Explore how <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/advisory-development/business-transformation.html">SAP Advisory Services</a> can help energize your business’s digital transformation with a flexible and scalable rule framework for data quality management.</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Quote</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>Stay in the conversation by following SAP Services and Support on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/sapsupportinfo">YouTube</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/SAPDigitalSvcs">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/138840">LinkedIn</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SAPDigitalBusinessServices">Facebook</a>.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td>Pascal Angerhausen is business transformation lead for CIO Advisory at SAP.</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p><em>Tobias Fischer is data architect for CIO Advisory at SAP.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="subscribe-to-the-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter">Subscribe to the Innovation and Transformation Newsletter</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advisory-services</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[One Data Platform: The Bridge to the Full Promise of Data-Centric Businesses]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/one-data-platform-bridge-sap-advisory-services</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/one-data-platform-bridge-sap-advisory-services</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[One data platform is needed to achieve business objectives and deliver innovations ahead of the competition. Learn why.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1660dcc9776ecad88e64d1bd0b7f0663d963b0e9f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1660dcc9776ecad88e64d1bd0b7f0663d963b0e9f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1660dcc9776ecad88e64d1bd0b7f0663d963b0e9f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="One Data Platform: The Bridge to the Full Promise of Data-Centric Businesses" src="./media_1660dcc9776ecad88e64d1bd0b7f0663d963b0e9f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="one-data-platform-the-bridge-to-the-full-promise-of-data-centric-businesses">One Data Platform: The Bridge to the Full Promise of Data-Centric Businesses</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Businesses are defined not just by the objectives achieved and innovations delivered ahead of the competition, but how well they harness data to make them happen. But first, this intelligence must be organized and managed with a strong digital backbone. What’s needed is one data platform.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Most organizations have spent the last several years deploying new technologies in a legacy infrastructure to deliver high-demand capabilities such as personalized experiences, process automation, and predictive maintenance.</p>
  <p>While these digital investments fulfill well-defined business needs, they rarely lead to a data architecture that is simplified enough to accelerate future innovation and help ensure the integrity of every artificial intelligence (AI) model. Unfortunately, current market dynamics are not compatible with companies that cannot pivot, adapt, and respond to change quickly.</p>
  <p>Businesses must align their processes with customer experiences and analyze those connections for deep insights that lead to confident, trusted decisions and actions. Only then can organizations drive continuous innovation.</p>
  <p>Achieving such an interconnected landscape of systems, processes, and data requires an agile digital backbone infused with intelligence to redefine and create new business models and processes in a more dynamic fashion. And a majority of executives seem to be getting the message: 65 percent of organizations surveyed by <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2020/03/da5ecbc7-887d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html#page=1">IDC</a> indicated plans for aggressive modernization of legacy systems with extensive new technology platform investments through 2023.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-sap-advisory-services">Explore SAP Advisory Services</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services/advisory-development/business-transformation.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="setting-the-foundation-for-real-time-data-organization-and-access">Setting the Foundation for Real-Time Data Organization and Access</h2>
  <p>Searching for a platform that can quickly organize data and enable access is easier said than done. It’s true that a wide variety of platform technologies promise to consolidate and harmonize data into one architecture. However, those that are comprehensive and scalable enough to support requirements that range from basic analytics to sophisticated data intelligence and algorithms provide the foundation businesses need to become genuinely data centric. This approach is what we call “one data platform.”</p>
  <p>The one data platform approach integrates heterogeneous solution components into a cohesive fit-for-purpose data management environment. This design delivers business-centric platform services that converge with common systems and leverage cloud concepts – all while lowering IT costs.</p>
  <p>The platform’s architecture groups technologies into four decipherable layers: data analytics, data integration, data ingestion pipelines, and source systems. This tactic is not meant to provide a one-size-fits-all structure. Instead, it should encourage IT architects to consider the distinct functions of each layer to create an environment that scales with the business as market dynamics and customer expectations evolve.</p>
  <p><strong>Layer #1: Data Analytics</strong></p>
  <p>Users can choose to leverage standardized dashboards with guided navigation and storytelling or customize their view for ad hoc analysis.</p>
  <p>The data science behind this layer turns information mining into new information models that can be extended with enterprise-scale data. Furthermore, organizations can blend and manage Big Data from multiple sources and apply statistical methods, algorithms, and analytic engines to tease out relevant, in-the-moment insights that help improve the bottom line.</p>
  <p><strong>Layer #2: Data Integration</strong></p>
  <p>As a data integration hub, this layer moves the needle on data-driven business transformation by getting data assets out from siloed sources, exposing them for different applications and systems to consume, and accelerating opportunities for self-service analytics.</p>
  <p>Within this layer, a multi-node production system enables mission-critical data warehousing functions for several business domains and across divisions. A near-line storage solution is also available for archiving and accessing massive data volumes cost effectively.</p>
  <p>Meanwhile, containerized data systems increase the computing power by providing self-contained modular technical areas that cater to specific business domains and requirements, such as country-specific reporting. Ingested data sets are then confined within a container, allowing analytical data models to be flexibly and independently deployed.</p>
  <p><strong>Layer #3: Data Ingestion Pipelines</strong></p>
  <p>This layer provides transformation, filtering, and integrated data type mapping capabilities. It enables agile data delivery and feeds insights into business processes through continuous data provisioning across a wide range of sources. More importantly, streaming data can be handled to support use cases that require real-time data management – from capture and processing to analysis, reporting, and decision-making.</p>
  <p><strong>Layer #4: Source Systems</strong></p>
  <p>This area houses the entire ecosystem of existing technology. Internal and external packaged applications, homegrown solutions, systems of record, and enterprise data repositories are brought together to create a centralized intelligence core that accurately reflects every stakeholder’s needs.</p>
  <h2 id="smoothing-the-road-to-a-hybrid-multi-cloud-landscape">Smoothing the Road to a Hybrid, Multi-Cloud Landscape</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-about-services-and-support-from-sap">Read more about services and support from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/support.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In addition to reassessing the harmonization of their IT architecture, organizations are upgrading their global data center strategy as the pace of change continues to accelerate. With the assistance of <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/advisory-development/business-transformation.html">SAP Advisory Services</a>, many SAP customers have even taken steps toward fully transitioning their data platform to public and private cloud infrastructures to rapidly deploy the latest data-driven innovations at scale.</p>
  <p>For example, some of our customers consider cloud-based infrastructure as a service (IaaS). An IaaS strategy enables organizations to replace on-premise infrastructure with elastic pay-per-use infrastructure that can scale up or down rapidly on demand. Efforts related to this transformation help businesses adapt to broader analytical requirements and manage rising data volumes while avoiding significant capital expenditure investments and lowering operating costs.</p>
  <p>The target infrastructure design includes integration enablement and connectivity within and across clouds to support cross-application analytical requirements. In broad terms, migration planning considers factors such as:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Migration approaches for various SAP and third-party solutions</li>
    <li>Scalability, stability, performance, reliability, and cost reduction</li>
    <li>Compliance and security</li>
    <li>Testing and validation strategies</li>
    <li>Monitoring and operations</li>
    <li>Application lifecycle management</li>
    <li>Alignment of the IT organizational structure to the new IaaS engagement model</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Another option that other SAP customers pick is a software-as-a-service (SaaS) strategy focused on pushing their transformation into a data-driven enterprise even further. In this case, executives are interested in expanding their data warehousing capabilities to realize more business benefits from the cloud with relative ease and without creating large-scale disruptions often associated with uprooting the mission-critical enterprise data backbone.</p>
  <p>Co-deployment of a <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/data-warehouse-cloud.html">cloud-based data warehousing solution</a> and existing digital assets such as a <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/bw4hana-data-warehousing.html">business warehousing solution</a> may appear plausible because the solutions address very different, yet mission-critical, problems. The cloud-based data warehouse solution consumes data from the business warehouse solution and other source systems with an abstraction or semantic layer, reducing IT complexity and applying much-needed governance and security.</p>
  <p>When coupled with cloud data management and virtualization technology, the cloud-based data warehousing solution is well-positioned to provide opportunities for self-service analytics. From this perspective, it is sensible to hedge that the solution can evolve to provision user-facing and domain-based analytical services at an enterprise scale, even with a well-established business warehousing system.</p>
  <h2 id="amplifying-business-value-with-flexibility-and-scalability">Amplifying Business Value with Flexibility and Scalability</h2>
  <p>The urgency around innovating data-driven business models, processes, and products and services is not going away anytime soon. So why not strategically respond to that demand with a flexible, scalable, and structured data platform that can distill value from massive volumes of data?</p>
  <p>For many SAP customers, taking this step is the key to hedging against uncertainty and driving business outcomes that better secure their foothold, profitability, and longer-term viability.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Quote</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>Explore how <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/advisory-development/business-transformation.html">SAP Advisory Services</a> can help your company reveal its true potential as a data-centric business with the one data platform approach.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td>Stay in the conversation by following SAP Services and Support on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/sapsupportinfo">YouTube</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/SAPDigitalSvcs">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/138840">LinkedIn</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SAPDigitalBusinessServices">Facebook</a>.</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p><em>Christine Lucea is a business enterprise principal consultant in Customer Success at SAP.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="subscribe-to-the-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter">Subscribe to the Innovation and Transformation Newsletter</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advisory-services</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ERP Strategies for High-Impact, Behind-the-Scenes Business Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/erp-business-transformation-strategies</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/erp-business-transformation-strategies</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn why when it comes to ERP business transformation, the most significant changes are still relevant to legacy business functions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1999d0b7355fc77701365e4b4079ba1b0c6ac1c32.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1999d0b7355fc77701365e4b4079ba1b0c6ac1c32.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1999d0b7355fc77701365e4b4079ba1b0c6ac1c32.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="ERP Strategies for High-Impact, Behind-the-Scenes Business Transformation" src="./media_1999d0b7355fc77701365e4b4079ba1b0c6ac1c32.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="erp-strategies-for-high-impact-behind-the-scenes-business-transformation">ERP Strategies for High-Impact, Behind-the-Scenes Business Transformation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>New go-to-market models, digitalized products and services, and process automation – all these changes bring tremendous value. But don’t forget long-simmering evolutions in legacy business functions, as they also require the attention of a well-supported transformation plan to keep IT costs low and help ensure business continuity.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Many executives guide their transformation efforts by following the signs of emerging market trends and ticking off the boxes of their corporate strategy. This mindset unquestionably generates exciting new business models, products, services, and experiences. But it still misses the ultimate goal: to reimagine everything from the innermost depth of their infrastructure to the furthest reach of their operational edge, including soon-to-be decommissioned legacy business functions.</p>
  <p>This reality is also true when modernizing enterprise resource planning (ERP) systems. When moving from SAP ERP to SAP S/4HANA, IT teams must also support the change process for legacy business areas with a three-fold approach:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Reduce overall IT complexity and total cost of ownership</li>
    <li>Maintain a stable IT environment for current operations</li>
    <li>Prepare for and provide a future-ready IT landscape and operation</li>
  </ul>
  <p>By paying attention to these less strategic functions, ERP modernization can further minimize IT cost and effort. More importantly, unplanned shutdowns and intelligence displacement can be avoided while operations and data security remain stable.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-sap-advisory-services">Explore SAP Advisory Services</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services/advisory-development/business-transformation.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="strategy-1-keep-legacy-erp-as-is">Strategy #1: Keep Legacy ERP As Is</h2>
  <p>When considering the future of legacy ERP, some organizations choose to preserve their existing system as long as possible and carry out housekeeping activities to simplify the system operations, especially when supporting less strategic business areas. This approach helps ensure stable, continuous operation of the SAP production environment while avoiding new investments.</p>
  <p>Sounds good, right? Unfortunately, extending an ERP system beyond its useful life can require incremental expenses that do not fully deliver any real impact – for example, cost savings – for the business. On the IT side, the historically grown complexity of the ERP system keeps IT operational costs high.</p>
  <h2 id="strategy-2-convert-legacy-erp-to-sap-s4hana">Strategy #2: Convert Legacy ERP to SAP S/4HANA</h2>
  <p>Converting the legacy ERP to SAP S/4HANA is the best choice when organizations must retain proven business processes and value chains, use in-house applications, support numerous subsidiaries, or rely on historical data. In addition, the overall business benefits from a long-term maintenance and support relationship with SAP.</p>
  <p>Our team of advisory experts supports the conversion model in two phases: first, housekeeping and preparation and second, execution. During the initial stage, organizations simplify their existing ERP system by reducing its data footprint and removing unused custom developments, data, and software inconsistencies and redundancies. The latter phase delivers the measures necessary for the transition to SAP S/4HANA, including delta solution design and a multi-cycle execution plan covering every aspect up to full production.</p>
  <p>This tactic gives our customers the ability to adopt SAP S/4HANA with few training and change management needs and no additional data migration. The conversion also allows organizations to maintain operations for their familiar legacy processes in a new technical environment, helping to ensure that SAP S/4HANA and the data it leverages is maintenance proof.</p>
  <h2 id="strategy-3-implement-sap-s4hana-with-a-steady-move-to-the-cloud">Strategy #3: Implement SAP S/4HANA with a Steady Move to the Cloud</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-about-services-and-support-from-sap">Read more about services and support from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/support.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP S/4HANA can be built alongside an active legacy ERP system, which can be retired later. While it encourages organizations to redefine processes and consider new ways to balance traditional operations with new capabilities, this approach may not make sense for legacy business, considering the cost and effort involved.</p>
  <p>This is where deploying SAP S/4HANA in a public cloud environment can help. By following the SAP Activate methodology and standardizing business processes, our customers can quickly start moving to a modern ERP, build it up intelligently, operate it with simplicity, and innovate continuously.</p>
  <p>While implementation costs can be reasonably controlled by adopting the SAP software standard, the public cloud allows customers to significantly reduce operating costs by scaling their digital capabilities and processes to meet today’s business needs. Plus, they can simplify system operations to prepare for tomorrow’s changes with a future-proof, maintainable, and scalable ERP.</p>
  <p>However, this doesn’t mean that these customers must start with a new implementation and move to the cloud immediately. With a mixed mindset of “keep legacy as is,” and “implement the modern ERP as new,” organizations can first maintain the status quo and improve the legacy system operations. This perspective gives executives additional time to react to market trends, business changes, and innovations. Then, they can define a comprehensive transition strategy to SAP S/4HANA. Meanwhile, SAP S/4HANA continues to evolve with broader functional innovations.</p>
  <p>When ready, our customers can transition SAP S/4HANA fully to the cloud to help ensure a future-proof, lean ERP that further optimizes operating costs and reduces IT complexity – even across legacy business functions.</p>
  <h2 id="bringing-the-true-spirit-of-transformation">Bringing the True Spirit of Transformation</h2>
  <p>C.S. Lewis once wrote, “Mere change is not growth. Growth is the synthesis of change and continuity, and where there is no continuity there is no growth.”</p>
  <p>The same is true for ERP transformation: Projects that bring the most significant changes are still relevant to legacy business functions that may no longer appear as strategic as newer approaches to go-to-market models, products and services, and organizational processes.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Explore how <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/advisory-development/business-transformation.html">SAP Advisory Services</a> can help energize your business’s digital transformation with flexible and scalable options for deploying a modern ERP software, such as SAP S/4HANA.</p>
        <p>Stay in the conversation by following SAP Services and Support<br>on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/sapsupportinfo">YouTube</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/SAPDigitalSvcs">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/138840">LinkedIn</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SAPDigitalBusinessServices">Facebook</a>.</p>
        <p><em>Di Li is a principal business consultant and enterprise architect at SAP.</em><br><em>Georg Heberle is a senior business consultant and enterprise architect at SAP.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="subscribe-to-the-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter">Subscribe to the Innovation and Transformation Newsletter</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advisory-services</category>
            <category>product/sap-erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>