<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-business-network-for-industry/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Multi-Enterprise Supply Chain Commerce Network Report]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-leader-idc-worldwide-multi-enterprise-supply-chain-commerce-network</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-leader-idc-worldwide-multi-enterprise-supply-chain-commerce-network</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been recognized as a Leader in the IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Multi-Enterprise Supply Chain Commerce Network 2023 Vendor Assessment.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_135f4226168fd5f6686d7e1a231112cde982b97a7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_135f4226168fd5f6686d7e1a231112cde982b97a7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_135f4226168fd5f6686d7e1a231112cde982b97a7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named a Leader in IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Multi-Enterprise Supply Chain Commerce Network Report" src="./media_135f4226168fd5f6686d7e1a231112cde982b97a7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-a-leader-in-idc-marketscape-worldwide-multi-enterprise-supply-chain-commerce-network-report">SAP Named a Leader in IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Multi-Enterprise Supply Chain Commerce Network Report</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP continues to act on our vision of enabling companies to create transparent, resilient, and sustainable supply chains across a massive amount of trading partners. We’re being recognized as a Leader in the <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/12/02200664-9f7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Multi-Enterprise Supply Chain Commerce Network 2023 Vendor Assessment</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="why-sap-is-a-leader">Why SAP Is a Leader</h2>
  <p>In an increasingly digitalized world, it is imperative that companies stay connected via a business network. I believe SAP was selected as a Leader because <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-SAPLeaderinIDCMarketScape">SAP Business Network</a> – our entry into the Multi-Enterprise Supply Chain Commerce Network space – can successfully drive buyer-supplier collaboration across procurement, supply chain, logistics, and asset management by providing a digital platform for trading partners to collaborate externally and exchange data just as, if not more, efficiently as their own internal processes.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_187994eca96ea26313df6a84f0d5d56cfe3bbffac.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_187994eca96ea26313df6a84f0d5d56cfe3bbffac.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_187994eca96ea26313df6a84f0d5d56cfe3bbffac.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_187994eca96ea26313df6a84f0d5d56cfe3bbffac.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="620" height="615">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Source: “IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Multi-Enterprise Supply Chain Commerce Network 2023 Vendor Assessment,” by Simon Ellis, December 2023, IDC #US49948423.* Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The IDC MarketScape report notes these competitive strengths of SAP Business Network:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Depth and breadth</strong> of product features and functionalities, as well as a future road map covering all major B2B collaboration categories (indirect, direct material, MRO logistics, financial, services, and sustainability) and scenarios in an end user, persona-based manner.</li>
    <li><strong>Integration and extensibility capabilities</strong> include integration between SAP ERP, SAP procurement modules, other applications like ERP, SCAM, and customer applications, and technologies such as machine learning, AI, and blockchain through SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP).</li>
    <li><strong>Global adoption and breadth of collaboration</strong> makes SAP among the industry’s largest, highly adopted B2B collaboration platforms enabling trading partners to collaborate in real time. Ongoing efforts to harmonize commerce, asset intelligence, and logistics continue to enhance the power of the connected economy.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The IDC MarketScape report notes, “Manufacturers and retailers looking for a vendor of both a multi-enterprise network and supply chain procurement application should consider SAP,” citing the “breadth and depth of [its] business network capabilities, strategic road map vision, and unmatched integration with core SAP and non-SAP supply chain and procurement applications,” making SAP a strong choice.</p>
  <h2 id="charting-the-evolution-of-sap-business-network">Charting the Evolution of SAP Business Network</h2>
  <p>I’m so pleased that as a pioneer in business networks, we continue to be recognized for our commitment to executing our vision. As we’ve continued to evolve our road map, I’m reflecting on how far we’ve come and paved the way for the future of intelligent business networks. From the founding of Ariba Supplier Network in 1996 to what we’ve become today, SAP Business Network touches US$4.9 trillion in commerce annually across many business processes and industries and has over 2 million active users on the network.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-network-powers-transparency-resiliency-and-sustainability">SAP Business Network powers transparency, resiliency, and sustainability</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Recent years have shown us that intelligent, digital business networks are essential to supporting an agile supply chain. SAP Business Network is a comprehensive platform that helps connect people, processes, and systems across multiple enterprises, ultimately creating transparent, resilient, and sustainable supply chains that can span the globe and be tailored to each line of business, helping to drive partner collaboration beyond a company’s own four walls and spanning the entire value chain.</p>
  <p>I’m proud to say that SAP Business Network can provide best-in-class supply chain collaboration, helping companies adhere to legal mandates, scale with confidence, and automate repetitive tasks, leaving more time for strategic decision-making informed by patterns gleaned from vast amounts of data. Our vision – what so many talented people at SAP are working towards every day – is to create the world’s best and largest B2B marketplace to help our customers meet their business goals.</p>
  <h2 id="recent-advancements-continue-to-revolutionize-b2b-collaboration">Recent Advancements Continue to Revolutionize B2B Collaboration</h2>
  <p>If you know SAP, you know about our commitment to continuous innovation. In 2023, we announced many exciting innovations around SAP Business Network, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Build on artificial intelligence in SAP Business Network.</strong> My colleague Muhammad Alam <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/11/40a14527-977e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-SAPLeaderinIDCMarketScape">announced our plans</a> to further integrate generative AI in spend management at SAP Spend Connect Live. Customers can look forward to enriched supplier responses to SAP Business Network Discovery postings, helping to facilitate more transparent communication between buyers and suppliers. Generative AI improvements can give suppliers the ability to generate clear, concise catalog descriptions, as well as summarize common errors for users so buyers can find exactly what they’re looking for.</li>
    <li><strong>Tackle industry-specific challenges with SAP Business Network for Industry.</strong> We’ve combined our more than 50 years of industry knowledge with the power of business networks to help customers address industry-specific supply chain challenges. Take a look at <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/industries.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-SAPLeaderinIDCMarketScape">how companies across industries use SAP Business Network</a> to help predict and respond to disruptions, comply with industry regulations, and meet sustainability goals.</li>
    <li><strong>Learn more with trading partner insights.</strong> Account managers struggle with obtaining comparative measures to assess the performance of trading partners. New KPIs and benchmarks, presented in a streamlined dashboard, can allow suppliers to evaluate customer transaction performance of orders, invoices, and payments with automatically generated KPIs and SAP Business Network community benchmarks. These insights can support collaborative dialogues with customers to help reduce transaction costs and mitigate business risk. <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/05/44712fba-737e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-SAPLeaderinIDCMarketScape">Watch the demo to learn more</a>.</li>
    <li><strong>Draw insights from data with component planning collaboration.</strong> With component planning collaboration, buyers and suppliers can view the forecast planning data for a finished good together with its components. Armed with this visibility, buyers and suppliers can respond to material shortages and adjust production accordingly, making supply more predictable. <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/05/585c0fc7-737e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-SAPLeaderinIDCMarketScape">Learn more in this demo</a>.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Stay tuned for more exciting innovations this year. Stay up-to-date about recent and upcoming innovations and explore road maps <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/innovations.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-SAPLeaderinIDCMarketScape">here</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="transforming-the-future-of-business-networks">Transforming the Future of Business Networks</h2>
  <p>I am proud that SAP is being recognized as a leader in delivering solutions that connect people, processes, and systems, enabling trading partners to collaborate effectively. I can’t wait to see our road map continue to come to life as we collaborate with our customers to develop innovations that help them achieve their business objectives by automating tasks, scaling efficiently, and operating sustainably.</p>
  <p>To learn more, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-SAPLeaderinIDCMarketScape">the SAP Business Network product page</a> and read the full IDC MarketScape report <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/12/02200664-9f7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">here</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Tony Harris is senior vice president and chief marketing and solutions officer for SAP Business Network.</p>
        <p>*IDC MarketScape vendor analysis model is designed to provide an overview of the competitive fitness of ICT suppliers in a given market. The research methodology utilizes a rigorous scoring methodology based on both qualitative and quantitative criteria that results in a single graphical illustration of each vendor’s position within a given market. The Capabilities score measures vendor product, go-to-market and business execution in the short-term. The Strategy score measures alignment of vendor strategies with customer requirements in a 3-5-year timeframe. Vendor market share is represented by the size of the circles. Vendor year-over-year growth rate relative to the given market is indicated by a plus, neutral or minus next to the vendor name.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc-marketscape</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network-for-industry</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Business Network Innovations Give Suppliers More Ways to Grow Their Businesses]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-business-network-innovations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-business-network-innovations</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP Sapphire, we announced five SAP Business Network innovations to help trading partners onboard quickly and grow their businesses.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network-for-industry</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Business Network for Industry Helps Meet Unique Business Needs]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-business-network-for-industry-meet-unique-business-needs</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-business-network-for-industry-meet-unique-business-needs</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Every industry faces challenges that a one-size-fits-all approach can't address. That's where SAP Business Network for Industry can help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1859392f911d9814db661b8bac76fdce9ce2568e6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1859392f911d9814db661b8bac76fdce9ce2568e6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1859392f911d9814db661b8bac76fdce9ce2568e6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Business Network for Industry Helps Meet Unique Business Needs" src="./media_1859392f911d9814db661b8bac76fdce9ce2568e6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-business-network-for-industry-helps-meet-unique-business-needs">SAP Business Network for Industry Helps Meet Unique Business Needs</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Companies have been forced to reevaluate the fundamentals of their supply chains over the past several years, often completely overhauling their processes to meet shifting demands. Some of the most significant challenges businesses are facing include skilled labor shortages, shipping and logistics issues, and evolving environmental, social, and governance (ESG) regulations.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The reactive, ad-hoc approach that companies have taken to tackle disruption has resulted in mismatched supply chain processes that offer little visibility and don’t keep up with the speed of change. Companies rely on convoluted, manual communication methods between suppliers and buyers. E-mails and calls get lost in the shuffle of vacations and holidays, making critical collaboration untraceable and delayed.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-sap-sapphire-news-guide-tackle-the-future-with-confidence">Read the SAP Sapphire News Guide: Tackle the Future with Confidence</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="sap-business-network-is-an-industry-ready-digital-network-of-suppliers-and-buyers">SAP Business Network Is an Industry-Ready Digital Network of Suppliers and Buyers</h2>
  <p>Businesses need a collaborative, many-to-many platform to drive transparent, resilient, and sustainable supply chains. That’s where <a href="/topics/business-network">SAP Business Network</a> comes in: a multi-enterprise collaboration network, built for industry, that helps companies execute their vision and meet growth targets by connecting with trading partners seamlessly.</p>
  <p>Only SAP Business Network provides collaboration across a broad range of processes, including indirect and direct procurement, supply chain, logistics, asset collaboration, finance, and talent.</p>
  <p>But each industry faces unique challenges that can’t always be addressed with a one-size-fits-all approach. For this reason, we are introducing SAP Business Network for Industry with an initial focus on the <strong>consumer products</strong>, <strong>life sciences</strong>, <strong>high tech</strong>, and <strong>industrial manufacturing</strong> industries. This includes:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>A portfolio of SAP Business Network capabilities that address industry needs</li>
    <li>A new SAP Business Network Industry Advisory Board to guide our product and road map strategy</li>
    <li>New SAP Business Network for Supply Chain industry services accelerators for select industries to help customers fast-track their implementation and post go-live success</li>
  </ul>
  <p>With SAP’s more than 50 years of industry expertise and industry process excellence embedded in our technology, we know better than anyone how to help customers tackle their specific challenges.</p>
  <h2 id="capabilities-designed-to-meet-industry-needs">Capabilities Designed to Meet Industry Needs</h2>
  <p>As we work to help companies tackle challenges with supply chain transparency, resiliency, and sustainability, we’ve engaged directly with customers to improve existing functionalities and develop new capabilities for SAP Business Network.</p>
  <p>We developed capabilities including contract manufacturing, planning and forecasting, quality collaboration, stock transfers, support for supplier-managed inventory, material traceability, and track and trace. Several of these capabilities were developed alongside customers to answer unique industry challenges in a variety of industries, including consumer products, high tech, industrial manufacturing, and life sciences. While these and other innovations were originally created to address a specific industry need, many of them can be applied cross-industry to help businesses increase visibility, mitigate risks, and operate more efficiently.</p>
  <p>Working with our customers has helped evolve SAP Business Network into the well-rounded, comprehensive solution it is today. It has been amazing to see the innovations that have come out of these relationships with customers, and their stories and successes have truly inspired me. To build on what we’ve accomplished so far, we’re strengthening the way we collaborate with customers and helping accelerate implementation with new industry-specific use cases.</p>
  <h2 id="continuing-the-tradition-of-customer-collaboration">Continuing the Tradition of Customer Collaboration</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="press-release-saps-vision-for-future-proofed-business-in-the-age-of-ai-comes-to-life">Press Release: SAP’s Vision for Future-Proofed Business in the Age of AI Comes to Life</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2023/05/sap-sapphire-future-proofed-business-age-of-ai">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To continue the tradition of working with our customers to enhance and extend our product capabilities, we’re introducing the SAP Business Network Industry Advisory Board. This select group of industry leaders will provide strategic direction for our product and road map, making sure we’re meeting the needs of our customers and helping their businesses grow. I’m eager to see the exciting new ideas and developments that will come out of this collaborative forum of industry experts.</p>
  <h2 id="expedite-time-to-value-with-industry-services-accelerators-for-sap-business-network-for-supply-chain">Expedite Time to Value with Industry Services Accelerators for SAP Business Network for Supply Chain</h2>
  <p>For customers beginning their journey with SAP Business Network for Supply Chain in particular, we’re introducing new industry services accelerators from our SAP Business Network Services team to help expedite time to value and achieve success.</p>
  <p>These industry services accelerators support critical supply chain business processes in the consumer products, high tech, industrial manufacturing, and life sciences industries. With prepackaged industry use cases and capabilities, implementation best practices, and dedicated post go-live support, industry services accelerators are based on SAP’s knowledge and expertise with SAP Business Network for Supply Chain. Industry services accelerators can be delivered in collaboration with partners.</p>
  <h2 id="stay-tuned-for-more">Stay Tuned for More</h2>
  <p>Other additions to SAP Business Network include new supplier innovations that will help support supplier adoption, focusing on creating an easier integration process to reduce friction and help grow your business to achieve maximum value.</p>
  <p>To learn more, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-ISM-1982254&#x26;source=blog-glo-blog">SAP Business Network for Industry on sap.com</a>. Here, we’ll keep you up-to-date on all of the exciting innovations happening and share resources to help you tailor your SAP Business Network experience.</p>
  <p>And, don’t miss learning more about SAP Business Network and how SAP can help solve the unique business challenges of your industry at <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/spend-connect-live.html">SAP Spend Connect Live in Vienna</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Val Blatt is global head for SAP Business Network Customer Success &#x26; Go-to-Market at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire">Read more news and coverage from SAP Sapphire</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>industry/high-tech</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network-for-industry</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>