<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/future-of-work/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meeting Workout: A Game to Improve the Meeting Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/meeting-workout-game-to-improve-meeting-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/meeting-workout-game-to-improve-meeting-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To address the challenge of unproductive meetings, SAP's Future of Work team and SAP AppHaus created the Meeting Workout board game.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Future of Work Beyond Flex Work]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/future-of-work-beyond-flex-work</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/future-of-work-beyond-flex-work</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The future of work will go beyond flex work; we are just scratching the surface when it comes to the many opportunities. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fe50fe3db75fc6d5437a22dc37e75d23a81dacf4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fe50fe3db75fc6d5437a22dc37e75d23a81dacf4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1fe50fe3db75fc6d5437a22dc37e75d23a81dacf4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Future of Work Beyond Flex Work" src="./media_1fe50fe3db75fc6d5437a22dc37e75d23a81dacf4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-future-of-work-beyond-flex-work">The Future of Work Beyond Flex Work</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For many, the introduction into a new world of work was driven by a focus on employee safety and business continuity in response to the pandemic. As we move forward into a post-pandemic era, organizations can finally shift their focus from crisis management to strategically thinking about the future of work. Now is the time to switch gears.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It’s the heyday of flex-work models, but the future of work is so much more, with opportunities ready to be tackled along the spectrum of workforce transformation, new people practices, and next-generation HR models.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-mission-and-vision-of-saps-chief-future-of-work-officer">The Mission and Vision of SAP's Chief Future of Work Officer</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2022/07/christian-schmeichel-sap-chief-future-of-work-officer">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="saps-holistic-future-of-work-agenda-shaping-the-next-world-of-work">SAP’s Holistic Future of Work Agenda: Shaping the Next World of Work</h2>
  <p>Managing the future of work holistically is a strategic imperative to build a resilient, agile, and innovative organization that is future-fit for the digital age. As global provider of leading-edge human experience management (<a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/what-is-hxm-suite.html">HXM</a>) software, SAP has been putting its focus on designing a holistic future of work agenda that empowers its more than 100,000 people across the globe to thrive while creating value for its customers.</p>
  <p>The agenda is SAP’s north star to reimagine work at its core. It considers business elements and strategic HR components along three dimensions to create a sustainable work experience for its global and diverse workforce:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Future of Workforce</strong>, aiming to define a target picture for a future-proof workforce at SAP</li>
    <li><strong>Future of People Practices</strong>, making new, flexible, and healthy work “work” for everyone</li>
    <li><strong>Future of HR</strong>, reimagining the way how HR functions need to operate in future along a strategic HR master plan</li>
  </ul>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e04b008630c7dc9c8f6a1874d5435820627aa597.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e04b008630c7dc9c8f6a1874d5435820627aa597.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e04b008630c7dc9c8f6a1874d5435820627aa597.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Infographic: SAP&#x27;s Future of Work agenda" src="./media_1e04b008630c7dc9c8f6a1874d5435820627aa597.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1986" height="1129">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Click to enlarge</em></p>
  <h2 id="future-proof-the-workforce">Future-Proof the Workforce</h2>
  <p>Accelerated digitalization and technology advances fuel the need for skill transformations across large portions of today’s workforce. The shift of skills as well as demographic changes result in a shortage of available talent, emphasizing the necessity of a clear understanding of future workforce demands. At the same time, this increases the competition for available talent in the market.</p>
  <p>SAP’s workforce transformation is based on scenario modeling to provide a clear understanding of what our workforce will need to look like five to 10 years down the road and how it will be composed. From these projections, we can derive a strategy to define the target picture with the right mix of permanent employees, gig workers, as well as the use of technology and <a href="/topics/artificial-intelligence">artificial intelligence</a> (AI). HR leaders play a crucial role by engaging in systematic resource planning in line with business strategy requirements.</p>
  <p>To future-proof their workforce, organizations need to prioritize continuous employee development through up- and reskilling. One example of this commitment is SAP’s internal talent marketplace, which offers project work, fellowships, or mentoring opportunities. Employees can take on respective assignments and apply their expertise where it is most needed while also acquiring new skills on the job: a win-win for everybody.</p>
  <h2 id="leading-edge-people-practices">Leading-Edge People Practices</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="what-is-human-experience-management">What is human experience management?</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/what-is-hxm-suite.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>People are the heartbeat of every organization. To meet ever-changing employee needs, organizations need to create innovative and effective strategies to attract, develop, engage, and retain top talent, as well as constantly challenge and evolve their people and workplace practices.</p>
  <p><strong>Empowerment Through Flexibility</strong> Flexibility is in more demand than ever, making it a strong lever for outstanding employee experience. With <a href="/topics/pledge-to-flex">Pledge to Flex</a>, SAP offers a hybrid work model that empowers employees to decide with their managers when, where, and how they work best in alignment with customer and business requirements.</p>
  <p>There is measurable success to the advantages of flexibility: SAP’s recent global future of work pulse survey revealed that over 80% of the workforce feel at least as or even more productive, satisfied, and engaged through hybrid work. The grand majority also believes that flexibility increases SAP’s attractiveness as employer.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c1940cbbe88ce3898664f0813f29bbe2f1039fc3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c1940cbbe88ce3898664f0813f29bbe2f1039fc3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c1940cbbe88ce3898664f0813f29bbe2f1039fc3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Infographic: Pledge to Flex continuum" src="./media_1c1940cbbe88ce3898664f0813f29bbe2f1039fc3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1994" height="1127">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Click to enlarge</em></p>
  <p>Providing the best setup for every team with the right balance between office and remote work is one of the key elements in making hybrid work “work” for everyone. At the same time, the office remains the number one place to meet and support cultural affiliation, networking, and onboarding of new joiners.</p>
  <p>To promote SAP’s hybrid work approach with Pledge to Flex, we launched the internal “I’m In” campaign, encouraging employees to find the right ratio of in-office and remote work. At SAP, we see that a combination of splitting time between remote work and two to three days of in-person office work per week seems to be a good practice, given that it fosters team spirit, engagement, and excitement about the organization.</p>
  <p><strong>Enablement for a Successful Transition</strong> To navigate the added level of complexity in a hybrid landscape and build a routine, enablement and trainings are key. SAP supports employees, managers, and teams with hands-on tools and resources to balance team and individual needs while keeping customer requirements front and center.</p>
  <p>One example is the Flex Team Workshop, allowing leaders and team members to jointly determine the hybrid work setup that best fits their needs in terms of productivity, collaboration, work-life balance, and, of course, business and customer requirements. Additionally, the Meeting Workout toolkit is a gamified approach to review and declutter meetings, making each interaction more valuable to everyone. And with “Lighten the Load” and “Are you OK?,” SAP runs powerful personalized programs to enhance employee health and people sustainability, while providing stress relief.</p>
  <p>Leadership becomes more demanding in the new world of work. Leaders need to become even stronger facilitators when communicating direction and strategy in a hybrid environment. Critical skills to adjust to the evolving role of management include communicating and listening with empathy and being agile when connecting with people. Modern leadership today also includes to keep teams engaged and tackle Zoom fatigue in times of unprecedented change.</p>
  <h2 id="next-generation-hr">Next-Generation HR</h2>
  <p>A data-driven and agile HR approach is the foundation to bringing the future of workforce and people practices to life. With the help of leading-edge technology, the HR function can evolve while addressing the demand for scalable and flexible services to meet changing needs of employee and the business quickly and efficiently.</p>
  <p>Besides technological advancements, the required skills for the future HR function will evolve as well. SAP focuses on a set of key themes:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Experience management in HR, emphasizing the needs of employees, managers, or applicants from a HR consumer point of view</li>
    <li>Data-driven HR, leveraging advanced analytics to solve talent and organization related business problems and support decision-making</li>
    <li>Digital HR to reap the fruits of technological advances across the entire employee life cycle</li>
    <li>Agile HR, applying an agile mindset, values, principles, practices, and tools when serving the business</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Capabilities like digital savviness, analytical skills, data interpretation, and an agile mindset will become must-have skills for successful HR work in the new era.</p>
  <h2 id="stay-curious-and-keep-learning">Stay Curious and Keep Learning</h2>
  <p>Looking ahead, it is fair to say that we are just scratching the surface when it comes to the many opportunities to shape the future of work. With an industry-leading hybrid work model in place, SAP built a strong foundation to tackle the workplace evolution as part of a holistic future of work agenda.</p>
  <p>Getting the triad of future workforce planning, people practices, and next generation HR teams right sets the path to make organizations more future-ready while the world around us is changing at breakneck speed. In the end it all comes down to continuously learning and discovering what works best for the creation of outstanding employee experiences while driving sustainable business success — truly exciting times for HR!</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Dr. Christian Schmeichel is chief future of work officer at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/pledge-to-flex</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[San Pablo Farmacia: Realizing the Power of Customer-Facing Employees as Brand Ambassadors]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/san-pablo-farmacia-employees-brand-ambassadors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/san-pablo-farmacia-employees-brand-ambassadors</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To become an employer of choice in Mexico, San Pablo Farmacia set out to improve its employee experience with SAP SuccessFactors solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors First Half 2023 Release: Skill-Centric Innovation to Build Your Future-Ready Workforce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-successfactors-first-half-2023-release</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-successfactors-first-half-2023-release</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the SAP SuccessFactors first half 2023 release, we continue to deliver on our promise to help build future-ready workforces. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Working with Cancer: Creating a Recovery-Forward Culture]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/working-with-cancer-pledge-recovery-forward-culture</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/working-with-cancer-pledge-recovery-forward-culture</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP CEO Christian Klein recently signed the Working with Cancer Pledge to support people working with cancer in the best possible way.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Study Reveals Nearly 99% Fair Pay Across Race and Gender at SAP North America]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/equal-pay-at-sap-north-america</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/equal-pay-at-sap-north-america</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A recent study on equal pay at SAP North America supported the global analysis that 99% of employees are paid equally for equal work.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How SAP Is Embracing Pay Equity on the Road to Equality]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/embracing-pay-equity-at-sap-road-to-equality</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/embracing-pay-equity-at-sap-road-to-equality</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For 2023 and beyond, SAP is doubling down on its commitment to pay equity and transparency for its more than 109,000 people.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d9824118b7d7fe95b32de7fddbf82ac62b3982ae.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d9824118b7d7fe95b32de7fddbf82ac62b3982ae.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d9824118b7d7fe95b32de7fddbf82ac62b3982ae.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How SAP Is Embracing Pay Equity on the Road to Equality" src="./media_1d9824118b7d7fe95b32de7fddbf82ac62b3982ae.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-sap-is-embracing-pay-equity-on-the-road-to-equality">How SAP Is Embracing Pay Equity on the Road to Equality</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="new-study-reveals-nearly-99-equal-pay-across-race-and-gender-at-sap-north-america">New Study Reveals Nearly 99% Equal Pay Across Race and Gender at SAP North America</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2023/03/equal-pay-at-sap-north-america">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>With every new year, personal financial goals tend to be at the top of the resolution list. As the global employer to more than 109,000 people, we’re committed to doing our part by ensuring fair pay. For 2023 and beyond, we’re doubling down on that commitment.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It is important to us because our business is built on trust with our colleagues. That trust leads to high performance and gives us a competitive edge for both talent retention and attraction.</p>
  <p>In January 2022, we published a fair pay statement, explaining our philosophy and principles around fair pay. It outlined our efforts to create a culture of equity and inclusion, and a promise to ensure our compensation practices are transparent. Our fair pay motto is “aggregate, don’t segregate.”</p>
  <p>In April, we reported that 99.8% of our employees around the world had transparency on their pay range. We also launched a new annual global statistical analysis and made pay equity adjustments.</p>
  <p>Even with such positive results, however, it’s still not a time for chest thumping. Among professionals who have a career focusing on diversity, equity, and inclusion (DE&#x26;I), we know how easy it is to regress. And we have no interest in going backwards. We must continue to raise the bar and push ourselves.</p>
  <p>Our current compensation results are not a coincidence and did not happen overnight. We have prioritized fair pay through implementing a global job architecture and global grades framework. We have pushed pay range transparency for employees. We’ve targeted salary adjustments to pay range minimums for those employees whose compensation was below the range. And since last year, we committed to annually reviewing internal pay leveraging statistics to ensure employees are paid appropriately.</p>
  <p>At SAP, “fair pay” is more than reducing the gender and ethnicity pay gap. For us, it means focusing on the processes, programs, and guidelines across the organization. We are pushing ourselves to examine the tools leaders use to ensure talent is treated fairly, and that employees with an exceptional work performance are rewarded accordingly.</p>
  <p>Fair pay also is about rewarding individuals based on their unique contribution and impact in their teams and the overall company.</p>
  <p>We are so committed to promoting pay equity that we’re sharing our insights with others.</p>
  <p>Business Beyond Bias features in our SAP SuccessFactors solutions work to help eliminate the inherent biases around age, race, ethnicity, differently abled, and LGBTQ+ communities in HR processes. Our software helps companies uncover unconscious bias in calibration and compensation decisions. It shows where an employee’s pay stands relative to the rest of their job family or group within the company. In addition, it allows you to pull in external market pay information into the compensation worksheet to provide additional data points for ensuring fair and equitable pay decisions.</p>
  <p>We’re moving toward a day when equitable pay for all people will no longer be an issue but a basic right for every individual. Until then, we’ll keep working on it.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Supriya Jha is chief diversity and inclusion officer at SAP.</em><br><em>Chetna Singh is senior vice president and global head of Total Rewards at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unlocking Value from HCM Transformations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/josh-bersin-company-unlock-value-hcm-transformations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/josh-bersin-company-unlock-value-hcm-transformations</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Josh Bersin Company presents research on best practices for HCM projects and key lessons from SAP SuccessFactors transformations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pledge to Flex: Empowerment in the Future of Work]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/pledge-to-flex-empowerment-new-world-of-work</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/pledge-to-flex-empowerment-new-world-of-work</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Success in the new world of work requires a flexible and trust-based working environment. Learn what SAP is doing.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/pledge-to-flex</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Future Workforce: Talent When You Need It, from Wherever People Want to Be]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/future-workforce-planning-talent-when-you-need-it</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/future-workforce-planning-talent-when-you-need-it</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The supply of people and the demand for skill sets have become more dynamic than ever. Read to find out how this affects workforce planning.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/dynamic-teams</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Take: This Holiday Season, Workers Need a Culture that Supports Healthy Habits]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/the-take-healthy-habits-at-work</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/the-take-healthy-habits-at-work</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get SAP's take on how employees benefit from a culture that supports healthy habits at work, like rest and micro-breaks.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/perspective</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
            <category>news-tag/the-take</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Positioned as a Leader in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises for Seventh Consecutive Year]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-a-leader-magic-quadrant-for-cloud-hcm-suites-employee-enterprises</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-a-leader-magic-quadrant-for-cloud-hcm-suites-employee-enterprises</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is a a Leader in the Magic Quadrant for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises for the seventh consecutive year.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12e84929eba593a9c963c2135bbd9c29c6a2d4176.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12e84929eba593a9c963c2135bbd9c29c6a2d4176.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12e84929eba593a9c963c2135bbd9c29c6a2d4176.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Positioned as a Leader in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises for Seventh Consecutive Year" src="./media_12e84929eba593a9c963c2135bbd9c29c6a2d4176.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-positioned-as-a-leader-in-2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-cloud-hcm-suites-for-1000-employee-enterprises-for-seventh-consecutive-year">SAP Positioned as a Leader in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises for Seventh Consecutive Year</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For the seventh consecutive year, <a href="http://sap.com/hr">SAP</a> has been named a Leader in the “Gartner Magic Quadrant for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises.”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The world of work has changed dramatically since the report’s inception, elevating the role of people and culture leaders. The need for rich data and actionable insights, employee expectations for greater self-service and mobile functionality, a growing skills gap, and the ability to manage an increasingly dispersed workforce are just a few of the major shifts we have experienced. With all of these changes, one constant has remained clear: the need for people to be at the center of business is more critical than ever.</p>
  <p>This is why more than 9,400 customers worldwide — from mid-market organizations to global enterprises with 100,000+ employees — count on SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite to elevate their people function and drive transformational change throughout their business. Together with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a>, <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/">SAP Fieldglass</a> solutions, and the broader SAP portfolio, they can connect their people processes across the business to truly put people at the center.</p>
  <p>“For MOD Pizza, providing exceptional employee experiences is key to driving workforce engagement and business success,” said Tara Gambill, senior director of Enterprise Systems for <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2022/8/ed4692e7-32d5-49e9-9240-a0a2dc2f8909.html">MOD Pizza LLC</a>. “People data is the lifeblood of the system. With intelligent technologies from SAP, we can create integration end to end, and leverage that data to get people connected and productive faster.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="put-people-at-the-heart-of-your-hr-strategy">Put people at the heart of your HR strategy</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="building-a-future-ready-workforce">Building a Future-Ready Workforce</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-new-and-coverage-from-successconnect">Read more new and coverage from SuccessConnect</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/successconnect">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As we look at the changing dynamics of what people and organizations need to succeed, it requires a change in thinking. People thrive when they are engaged in their careers and have a sense of belonging; organizations thrive when their people are properly skilled and aligned to the right opportunities.</p>
  <p>Global HR industry influencer Josh Bersin recently <a href="https://joshbersin.com/2022/09/sap-successfactors-launches-its-biggest-release-in-a-decade/">said</a>: “[<a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/opportunity-marketplace.html">SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace]</a> is integrated into the [SAP] SuccessFactors stack, making talent marketplace an integrated part of HCM. SAP is going further. While the talent marketplace is often seen as a ‘product’ or set of features, it really is much more. It’s a new, modern way of thinking about pay, jobs, roles, and growth.”</p>
  <p>At <a href="https://events.sap.com/successconnect/en/global-home">SuccessConnect</a>, we introduced new innovations to transform talent development for the future of work, and bring the whole self model to life. Informed by our team of behavioral scientists, these innovations use data and machine learning to continuously understand the capabilities within the workforce as well as each person’s whole self — their skills, aspirations, interests, strengths. This intelligence enables organizations to match people with dynamic teams and ongoing growth opportunities. The result is people-centric organizations that provide individuals with opportunities to grow and learn in alignment with the needs of the business.</p>
  <p>Vicki Furnish, vice president of Global People Solutions Operations and Analytics at <a href="/2022/09/ntt-data-it-takes-entire-team-to-win">NTT DATA Services,</a> said it perfectly when discussing NTT DATA Services’ move to SAP SuccessFactors: “If we put the right foundation in for our team and people, our team members will be successful. If they are successful, we will then be successful in our business.”</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>Read the full report here: <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-2BGRQGI7&#x26;ct=221021&#x26;st=sb">Gartner Magic Quadrant for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises</a>.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Amy Wilson is senior vice president of Products and Design for SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Second Half 2022 Release: Building a Future-Ready Workforce Today]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-successfactors-second-half-2022-release</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-successfactors-second-half-2022-release</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The SAP SuccessFactors second half 2022 release introduces new innovations around creating an agile and future-ready workforce. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1074c8b37f11498501b456579a1cc6d70dabc96f4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1074c8b37f11498501b456579a1cc6d70dabc96f4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1074c8b37f11498501b456579a1cc6d70dabc96f4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP SuccessFactors Second Half 2022 Release: Building a Future-Ready Workforce Today" src="./media_1074c8b37f11498501b456579a1cc6d70dabc96f4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-successfactors-second-half-2022-release-building-a-future-ready-workforce-today">SAP SuccessFactors Second Half 2022 Release: Building a Future-Ready Workforce Today</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In today’s business landscape, organizations must equip themselves to respond to workforce opportunities or challenges <em>before</em> they arise. If recent trends have taught us anything, it’s that by the time a business reacts to a market shift, a new one is already occurring. Staying a step ahead of workforce demands is no longer a step ahead – it’s step one.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The SAP SuccessFactors second half 2022 release, which is available for preview today, introduces new innovations focused on empowering organizations to create an agile and future-ready workforce in a rapidly changing workplace as well as further investments for individualized experiences and agile and compliant HR.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="realizing-a-people-centered-future-of-work-through-the-intelligent-enterprise">Realizing a People-Centered Future of Work Through the Intelligent Enterprise</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/06/people-centered-future-of-work-intelligent-enterprise-hxm">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="creating-a-future-ready-workforce">Creating a Future-Ready Workforce</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="change-the-world-of-work-for-good-with-the-next-generation-of-hcm-software-from-sap">Change the world of work for good with the next generation of HCM software from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the face of increasingly complex and more urgent transformations, organizations must accelerate their talent development at scale. At the core of such adaptability is an understanding of the skills organizations need to build and grow. As part of our early adopter care program, select customers will have access to skills ontology, growth portfolio, and dynamic teams, which work together to deliver greater intelligence on the skills and capabilities that currently exist and are needed within an organization.</p>
  <p><strong>The skills ontology</strong> is a major advancement for SAP SuccessFactors that’s connected to global skills databases to help ensure that organizations have a comprehensive and up-to-date view of the most important skills for their workforce. It delivers machine learning and artificial intelligence (AI) powered recommendations to employees about relevant and trending skills to prioritize for development.</p>
  <p><strong>The growth portfolio</strong>, also part of the early adopter care program, is how employees can reveal their skills, capabilities, education, language proficiencies, and certifications. In the second half release, this data will connect employees to the most relevant assignments in <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/opportunity-marketplace.html">SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace</a>. While the skills ontology gives organizations the ability to align talent development to the ambitions of the organization, the growth portfolio enables employees to align their own talent development to their ambitions.</p>
  <p><strong>Dynamic teams</strong> is also part of the SAP SuccessFactors foundation and available to all customers. Within organizations today, there are countless teams that exist outside of traditional organizational structures – groups of people that work cross-functionally on a project for a certain amount of time. The dynamic teams functionality can provide organizations with visibility into these teams as well as tools to help manage and assemble teams. Team progress can be measured using objectives and key results (OKRs) and employees can find a dynamic team within SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace to help learn new skills and continue to grow their career. This transparency within the organization levels the playing field and creates equal opportunity for employees.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11660a4ded960363037d3e57f808136c91669c786.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11660a4ded960363037d3e57f808136c91669c786.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11660a4ded960363037d3e57f808136c91669c786.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_11660a4ded960363037d3e57f808136c91669c786.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="534">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Click to enlarge</em></p>
  <p>With richer data and greater talent intelligence, organizations can help ensure that employees are connected to the most relevant talent development opportunities that are aligned to the ambitions of employees and the needs of the organization. Skills ontology, growth portfolio, and dynamic teams provide significant updates to the foundation of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/hxm-suite.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a> – built into what customers already have instead of requiring an entirely new solution.</p>
  <p>Some more exciting features for our second half 2022 release are around individualized experiences and agile and compliant HR, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Chosen name and personal pronouns:</strong> As part of our commitment to diversity, equity, and inclusion, we are taking important steps to help every individual be seen and valued. People can now indicate their chosen name, personal pronouns, and gender directly within the people profile. This information is displayed consistently across SAP SuccessFactors solutions – from recruiting to learning, helping to foster a greater sense of belonging.</li>
    <li><strong>End-to-end visual redesign:</strong> We are enhancing the overall look and feel of SAP SuccessFactors by implementing the Horizon visual theme for SAP Fiori. This new theme enhances consistency while delivering a more informed and streamlined product experience. Employees will find nearly every element of the solution updated with new colors, typography, iconography, layouts, and visual hierarchy focused on intent and success. We remain on track to have every employee-facing SAP SuccessFactors experience unified with the theme by the end of 2023.</li>
    <li><strong>SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone guided onboarding experience:</strong> By bringing together SAP SuccessFactors solutions and third-party integrations, organizations can more efficiently handle an array of complex onboarding processes. This new feature helps ensure that employees receive individualized experiences, even before their first day. Covering key phases of the new hire journey, the guided onboarding experience for <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/workzone-hr.html">SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone</a> helps provide the tools and information employees need, both before and after hiring.</li>
    <li><strong>Cross-system workflow capability:</strong> We are unveiling a new cross-system workflow capability for processes that involve multiple users from multiple systems, such as SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and the payroll component of SAP ERP Human Capital Management. A guided activity framework for key processes enables our on-premise customers to more rapidly unlock the value of the cloud with SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and the latest HXM innovations while maintaining and progressively moving on-premise processes to the cloud over time.</li>
    <li><strong>Time management enhancements:</strong> We are continuing to <a href="/2022/09/sap-industry-leading-time-management-suite">enhance our capabilities in time management</a> with the much-anticipated ability to export leave events into calendar applications along with better support for public holidays and handling of grace rules. Time administrators can now copy time-related configuration objects, reducing the need for manual duplication during configuration. In addition, temporary work schedules and absence information on a per day basis will now be available for reporting in SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>All these and many more exciting features will be available in our 2H 2022 release, in preview today and production on Friday, December 9. Please watch our <a href="https://dam.sap.com/mac/app/p/video/asset/preview/KvodB4Q?ltr=a&#x26;rc=10">second half 2022 release highlights video</a> for more information.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Amy Wilson is senior vice president of Products and Design for SAP SuccessFactors.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/dynamic-teams</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-erp-hcm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investments in People Sustainability Drive Positive Business Outcomes, Says New SAP Research]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/people-sustainability-investment-sap-research</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/people-sustainability-investment-sap-research</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[By focusing on people sustainability, organizations can drive positive results for their organization and the environment. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Five Highlights from SuccessConnect 2022]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/five-takeaways-from-successconnect-2022</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/five-takeaways-from-successconnect-2022</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SuccessConnect was finally back in person after three years! Here are five key takeaways if you missed the in-person event.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Job Seekers Rush to Find New Opportunities with Better Pay and Work-Life Balance]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/job-seekers-new-opportunities-better-pay-work-life-balance</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/job-seekers-new-opportunities-better-pay-work-life-balance</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Research from Qualtrics and SAP shows job seekers are rushing to look for new jobs amid inflation and recession concerns. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Surprising Truth about Workers Who Can Be Productive Anywhere]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/surprising-truth-workers-productive-anywhere</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/surprising-truth-workers-productive-anywhere</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A study by Accenture identified valuable resources that enable employees in a hybrid workforce to be productive anywhere. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Employee Trust: The Key to a Successful Strategy for Diversity, Equity, Inclusion, and Belonging]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/employee-trust-key-to-deib-data-strategy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/employee-trust-key-to-deib-data-strategy</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To promote diversity, equity, inclusion, and belonging (DEIB), organizations must build trust with employees to collect truthful data.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/data-privacy</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[TUMO Labs Students Put Their Skills to Work in Innovation Challenges]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/tumo-labs-students-put-their-skills-to-work-in-innovation-challenges</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/tumo-labs-students-put-their-skills-to-work-in-innovation-challenges</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A program from SAP and TUMO Labs supports university students in understanding, utilizing, and shaping digital technologies. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-innovation-center-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unleashing Human Potential to Change Work for Good]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/unleashing-human-potential-change-work-for-good</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/unleashing-human-potential-change-work-for-good</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A Global Thought Leaders documentary on CBSNews.com features SAP SuccessFactors' strategic vision to unleach human potential.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Named a Leader in IDC MarketScape for Worldwide Modern Talent Acquisition]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/idc-marketscape-modern-talent-acquisition-sap-successfactors-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/idc-marketscape-modern-talent-acquisition-sap-successfactors-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In the IDC MarketScape for Worldwide Modern Talent Acquisition Suites 2022 Vendor Assessment, SAP SuccessFactors is a Leader!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/recruiting</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Holistic Future of Work Agenda for SAP: Mission and Vision of Chief Future of Work Officer Christian Schmeichel]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/christian-schmeichel-sap-chief-future-of-work-officer</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/christian-schmeichel-sap-chief-future-of-work-officer</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[What kind of work environment can SAP employees expect in the future? SAP's Chief Future of Work Officer Christian Schmeichel explains.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/pledge-to-flex</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychologists Say Your Flex Work Desires Are Perfectly Normal. But Does Your Boss Agree?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/psychologists-say-flex-work-perfectly-normal-does-boss-agree</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/psychologists-say-flex-work-perfectly-normal-does-boss-agree</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Psychologists agree the optimal work model for the average global employee is hybrid. But it's not necessarily the best model for every one.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Designing SAP SuccessFactors Products with Intentional, Scalable Inclusivity]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/designing-sap-successfactors-products-inclusivity</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/designing-sap-successfactors-products-inclusivity</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We are building inclusivity at scale to help customers create a sustainable workforce where employees and business can thrive. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/pridesap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Employees Worldwide Take a Day Off for Their Mental Health]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sap-mental-health-day-2022</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sap-mental-health-day-2022</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Mental Health Day 2022 an additional paid day off for all employees to take space for reflection and collectively recharge.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Earns Top Rated Awards from TrustRadius in Eight Categories]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sap-successfactors-top-rated-awards-trustradius</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sap-successfactors-top-rated-awards-trustradius</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[TrustRadius has recognized SAP SuccessFactors with eight Top Rated Awards this year. Read to learn more about this recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-compensation</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incorporating Expressive States into the Human Experience at Work]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/expressive-states-human-experience-at-work</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/expressive-states-human-experience-at-work</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Expressive states are critical to realizing the whole self model, a framework to understand how employees experience change and opportunity.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Great Resignation Compels Companies to Make a Great First Impression]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/great-resignation-companies-first-impression</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/great-resignation-companies-first-impression</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Great Resignation left thousands of companies with job openings to fill. When competing for top talent, a smoother hiring process helps.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/recruiting</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Flexibility Is Non-Negotiable When It Comes to the Employee Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/flexibility-non-negotiable-employee-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/flexibility-non-negotiable-employee-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Leading experts discuss how organizations are reinventing flexibility as a core part of transforming the employee experience.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_104d736bffd16956b265815dcd608601c0138cc0d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_104d736bffd16956b265815dcd608601c0138cc0d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_104d736bffd16956b265815dcd608601c0138cc0d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Flexibility Is Non-Negotiable When It Comes to the Employee Experience" src="./media_104d736bffd16956b265815dcd608601c0138cc0d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="flexibility-is-non-negotiable-when-it-comes-to-the-employee-experience">Flexibility Is Non-Negotiable When It Comes to the Employee Experience</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The future of work is unfolding as we speak and it’s more flexible than we could have ever imagined when the global <a href="/topics/covid-19">pandemic</a> hit two years ago. A recent Mercer <a href="https://www.mercer.com.au/what-we-do/workforce-rewards-and-talent/rewards-and-employee-experience/salary-benchmarking-surveys/au-benefits-hr-policies-practices.html">research</a> report found that almost 60% of organizations in Australia were reinventing flexibility as a core part of transforming the employee experience.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Employee benefits around health and well-being are a major topic within the Australian culture because people in this country expect more work-life balance,” said Chi Tran, head of Workforce Market Insights and Data at Mercer. “Organizations want to make sure they have the flexible programs in place to attract and retain people. We see well-being benefits becoming increasingly non-negotiable as a core component of an organization’s ability to deliver an effective employee experience.”</p>
  <p>The same study also showed that 97% of organizations had a health and wellness benefits program in place, and employees were more attracted to organizations that have a sense of purpose.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="workforce-trends-2022-how-companies-are-building-digital-dream-teams">Workforce Trends 2022: How Companies Are Building Digital Dream Teams</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2022/02/workforce-trends-2022">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="pandemic-puts-employee-wellness-at-center-stage">Pandemic Puts Employee Wellness at Center Stage</h2>
  <p>Like everything else, the pandemic has fast-tracked the future of work. Another Mercer poll revealed that respondents from one in two companies in Asia-Pacific saw indications of worsening employee burnout and pandemic fatigue. As a result, Tran said many organizations are taking a risk-based approach with data-driven prevention programs to reduce insurance premiums while addressing worker well-being, particularly mental health.</p>
  <p>“In addition to keeping responsive employee assistance programs in place, many companies are shifting to proactive strategies that bring people in with virtual wellness workshops on a more regular basis,” she said. “There’s no one-size-fits-all program. Organizations need to listen to their different employee cohorts, investing in benefits that will resonate with everyone’s unique needs.”</p>
  <h2 id="personalized-flexible-benefit-programs">Personalized, Flexible Benefit Programs</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="turn-employees-into-ambassadors-with-employee-experience-management">Turn employees into ambassadors with employee experience management</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/employee-experience-management.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>One example is SAP’s global “Pledge to Flex” program designed to fit every​ employee’s ​role, style, and location while continuing to meet business and customer needs. At <a href="/australia/2021/12/01/lets-talk-how-to-find-and-keep-great-staff">SAP ANZ</a>, where the pandemic’s impact was nascent in 2020 but revved up through 2021, the company established a framework for employees to consider when determining their work style preferences.</p>
  <p>“We want people empowered to find the ideal working style that will meet their individual, team, and customer success responsibilities,” said Debbie Rigger, head of HR at SAP Australia and New Zealand “We have parents with young children or other caregiving responsibilities. We have early talent working at home out of their bedroom. We want them to ask themselves, ‘What is my role? Who are my stakeholders and what are their expectations? What family-related and other personal commitments do I have? Given all these factors, what do I need to do my best work?'”</p>
  <p>Looking ahead, Rigger expects to see the unexpected, meaning employee requests for things HR has never thought of before. In the meantime, the SAP ANZ team as doubled down on creating a safe in-person reentry experience for employees based on legislation and government guidance, as well as the company’s global policies.</p>
  <p>“This has been more of a re-education for employees about the options they have and being transparent about what’s possible when it comes to working schedules that span full-time, part-time, compressed hours, job sharing, and even geographies,” said Rigger. “Given the border closures, people have been interested in traveling within the country while also being able to work remotely for a specified time period. Through candid conversations with managers, employees determine how, when, and where they work based on their personal circumstances and the needs of the business.”</p>
  <h2 id="organizations-adjust-employee-experience-to-the-new-normal">Organizations Adjust Employee Experience to the New Normal</h2>
  <p>Flexible working practices are likely here to stay. <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US47290521">IDC</a> analysts predicted that by 2023, digital transformation and business volatility would drive 70% of G2000 organizations to deploy remote or hybrid-first work models, redefining work processes and engaging diverse talent pools. The beauty of being flexible is obvious during these times of rapid change and market uncertainty.</p>
  <p>Rigger said SAP ANZ was already exploring how to make the most of the company’s office spaces in compliance with local legislation guidance. Hybrid work models might demand new spacial configurations, not just for social distancing but for fundamentally changed workplace norms. From impermanent individual workstations to virtual tools that let people effectively brainstorm when they aren’t in the same room, organizations need to create that employee community again, bringing people back into a space so they can continue to be more productive.</p>
  <p>Companies still struggling with remote versus in-person work mandates are missing the point about addressing the opportunities the global pandemic continues to reveal. Innovative organizations will jump at this historic inflection point to redefine the future of work with benefits for both organizations and their employees.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler.</em><br><em>This also appeared on <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2022/01/25/flexibility-is-non-negotiable-when-it-comes-to-the-australian-employee-experience/?sh=ec159d522f5e">SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Ideal Work Environment: What Is It and How to Deliver It]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/ideal-work-environment-what-is-it-how-to-deliver-it</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/ideal-work-environment-what-is-it-how-to-deliver-it</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Workers today expect more flexibility in their work environment. How can businesses provide the right tools, experiences, and capabilities?]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e5a7f7b4548009f6307ffbd3d0fa8ada45c8d093.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e5a7f7b4548009f6307ffbd3d0fa8ada45c8d093.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e5a7f7b4548009f6307ffbd3d0fa8ada45c8d093.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Ideal Work Environment: What Is It and How to Deliver It" src="./media_1e5a7f7b4548009f6307ffbd3d0fa8ada45c8d093.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-ideal-work-environment-what-is-it-and-how-to-deliver-it">The Ideal Work Environment: What Is It and How to Deliver It</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The hiring market continues to heat up, anxious employees are making retention more challenging, and workers expect more flexibility in their work environments. How can businesses provide the right tools, experiences, and capabilities necessary to create a workplace in which employees can thrive?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In today’s changing world of work, employees expect better experiences – especially when it comes to their learning, development, and growth. However, employees struggle with multiple outdated or inadequate systems and tools that create a fragmented digital experience at work.</p>
  <p>The pressure is undoubtedly on executives, organizational leaders, and their HR teams to fill those gaps to create a workplace culture that is motivating, empowering, and fulfilling. They are expected to provide personalized work experiences that include access to individualized learning and growth, guided and simplified technology interfaces, continuous process improvements, embedded listening, and increased productivity and efficiency.</p>
  <p>Organizations that deliver on these promises exceptionally well are usually more effective in attracting, retaining, and developing the best talent. However, this is easier said than done because no single definition of an ideal workplace meets everyone’s expectations. To create a truly empowering, engaging, and enriching environment, decision-makers must consider the unique locations, job roles, personal responsibilities, and situations that each employee faces daily.</p>
  <p>At SAP SuccessFactors, we understand the importance of fostering an environment where people are thriving, collaborating, and ready to succeed today and tomorrow – no matter where they work. And in virtually every case, that experience begins with technologies that cater to each employee’s whole self even as they evolve, making everyone consistently feel valued, heard, and recognized.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="provide-an-employee-centric-hr-user-experience-with-sap-successfactors-work-zone">Provide an employee-centric HR user experience with SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/workzone-hr.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="personalized-integrated-experience">Personalized, Integrated Experience</h2>
  <p>A good starting point is giving employees the freedom to reimagine their work experience with hyper-personalized, team-centric, and project-focused workspaces created through the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/workzone-hr.html">SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone solution</a>. This integrated digital experience connects the entire SAP software landscape and third-party applications to help streamline work and intelligently surface relevant content, recommendations, insights, and actions.</p>
  <p>By providing employees with a more simplified and unified digital experience tailored to their unique needs, SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone can enable companies to increase employee productivity and efficiency.</p>
  <p>For example, <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/11/90572075-047e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">AKT Solutions Limited</a> (AKT Global) resolved the presence of inefficient communication and collaboration across borders and time zones to improve productivity and lower employee stress. As a result, its employees work smarter and faster now that they have 24/7 access to everything they need to keep up with changes – no matter where they work, what device they use, or where they are based.</p>
  <h2 id="culture-of-continuous-and-agile-learning">Culture of Continuous and Agile Learning</h2>
  <p>Employees need on-demand access to individualized and engaging learning programs as part of their everyday experience. With learning established as a priority in the workspace, they are empowered to develop skills at their convenience and participate in opportunities to further develop their expertise and leadership abilities.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/corporate-lms.html">SAP SuccessFactors Learning</a> helps to foster a continuous and agile culture with learning that is personalized and relevant for each employee while being embedded into daily activities. Through learning workspaces employees can get access to relevant learning applications, information, collaboration tools, and content from any source – all through a single entry point and embedded into the flow of work – to be able to benefit from a more simplified and contextual way of learning. Organizations can then help ensure their people feel empowered to own their career path and growth while helping them become more engaged and develop the skills that align with current and future business needs.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/10/90d46430-007e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Rich Products Corporation</a> (Rich’s) is taking advantage of the solution to support a culture of continuous learning. The family-owned food company sought to elevate its training and development program with a modern, consumer-grade learning experience for its associates. By mapping and enabling access to learning content with individualized recommendations, Rich’s offers its associates a customized view of their development plans and objectives and connects them to integrated external content libraries and resources on demand.</p>
  <h2 id="employees-retained-with-opportunities-they-want">Employees Retained with Opportunities They Want</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="turn-employees-into-ambassadors-with-employee-experience-management">Turn employees into ambassadors with employee experience management</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/employee-experience-management.html?sort=title_asc&#x26;tab=all">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>According to joint research from <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/insights/focus/technology-and-the-future-of-work/importance-of-investing-in-employees.html">Deloitte Consulting and the MIT Sloan Management Review</a>, making job opportunities visible and accessible in the workforce helps improve retention by aligning employee interests with strategic priorities. But first, most companies require a conscious shift that embraces each employee’s whole self – who they are today, who they are becoming, and the value they bring as individuals.</p>
  <p>By adding the <a href="/2021/10/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace-drives-internal-mobility-and-upskilling-to-help-organizations-future-proof-their-business">SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace</a> solution to their workspace, employees can find short-term assignments, fellowships, learning recommendations, and mentors. The solution can empower everyone across the organization to pursue multiple opportunities for professional development, networking, and project participation.</p>
  <h2 id="meaningful-work-shaped-by-real-time-feedback">Meaningful Work Shaped by Real-Time Feedback</h2>
  <p>Measuring work experiences helps businesses remain agile and strive to give employees what they need to feel supported, productive, and engaged. With <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/employee-experience-management.html?sort=title_asc&#x26;tab=all">Experience Management solutions from SAP and Qualtrics</a>, organizations can evaluate how employees are doing, listen to their feedback, and respond to their concerns quickly and effectively.</p>
  <p>To enable a people-centric business transformation, luxury retailer <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2019/12/de86ec87-767d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Chalhoub Group</a> combines employee experience data with operational HR data. This approach allows the business to gain new insights, identify areas for improvement, and foster a culture where all employees are engaged and fully equipped to provide exceptional customer service. Chalhoub uses Experience Management solutions from SAP and Qualtrics to actively listen to its workforce and provide the right training, processes, and tools. The company is capturing feedback at every interaction touchpoint and discovering new ways to meet unique employee needs and continuously improve everyday work experiences.</p>
  <p>As a result, the company is redesigning and optimizing key aspects of the employee journey. For example, its HR transformation priorities are supported by hard data on the issues that employees really care about, driving greater emphasis on employee well-being and recognition as top strategic goals.</p>
  <h2 id="all-wrapped-with-a-human-experience">All Wrapped with a Human Experience</h2>
  <p>HR organizations are constantly challenging their business executives and organizational managers. They know that seemingly adequate access to technology is no guarantee that an employee’s specific needs are met. Meanwhile, it is understood that remote and <a href="/2021/08/essential-but-under-supported-improving-deskless-worker-experience">deskless workers</a> face even more complexity in their experiences, such as limited bandwidth and privacy controls, as they juggle work with their personal circumstances.</p>
  <p>With SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone, SAP SuccessFactors Learning, SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace, and Experience Management solutions from SAP and Qualtrics, organizations can deliver engaging, individualized experiences that enable everyone to thrive.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Stephanie Craig is global director of Solution Marketing for SAP SuccessFactors.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>