<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-ns2/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Innovative Cloud ERP at Department of Defense Agencies with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/dod-agencies-sap-ns2-innovative-cloud-erp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/dod-agencies-sap-ns2-innovative-cloud-erp</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP NS2 can now officially deploy SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition within the DoD IL4 secure cloud environment. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17fe6b9f04141be0d0702008e758517683085fbcd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17fe6b9f04141be0d0702008e758517683085fbcd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17fe6b9f04141be0d0702008e758517683085fbcd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Innovative Cloud ERP at Department of Defense Agencies with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition" src="./media_17fe6b9f04141be0d0702008e758517683085fbcd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="innovative-cloud-erp-at-department-of-defense-agencies-with-sap-s4hana-cloud-private-edition">Innovative Cloud ERP at Department of Defense Agencies with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Over the past several years, defense agencies in the United States have become increasingly cloud-centric. The cloud has proven its ability to streamline operations, empower real-time decision making, and support mission success.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/sap-ns2-achieves-disa-provisional-authorization-pa-of-sap-s4hana-cloud-to-support-enterprise-cloud-operations-for-defense-agencies-302130501.html?tc=eml_cleartime">announced May 2,</a> SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition has received a provisional authorization from the Defense Information and Systems Agency (DISA). This means SAP NS2, an independent subsidiary of SAP that facilitates the adoption of SAP cloud solutions for customers who require enhanced compliance, can officially deploy SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition within the Department of Defense FedRAMP+Impact Level 4 (DoD IL4) secure cloud environment.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="cloud-erp-for-every-business-need-from-mission-critical-operations-to-business-model-innovation">Cloud ERP for every business need: from mission-critical operations to business model innovation</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition enables a cloud experience with the same functional scope and upgrade flexibility that SAP S/4HANA Cloud offers, but with added security and compliance that allows Department of Defense customers a quick adoption of cloud solutions.</p>
  <p>With this new certification, defense customers can choose to adopt a secure cloud ERP solution that supports mission-critical operations in real time, from any location. Once limited to on-premise solutions, which exhausted budget and resources, defense agencies can now migrate operations to the cloud where data is stored on cloud servers and resources can be reallocated to support defense workforces and alternative needs.</p>
  <p>“Obtaining our FedRAMP+DoD IL4 authorization was a tremendous step in supporting our defense and federal agency customers,” said Amy Spruill, senior vice president and general manager of Regulated Industries at SAP. “SAP S/4HANA Cloud will provide the commercial cloud capabilities our customers are looking for while improving their security perimeter and mitigating attacks on critical data.”</p>
  <p>The FedRAMP+DoD IL4 secure cloud environment is dedicated to defense agencies and protected with continuous monitoring, vulnerability scanning, and intrusion detection to ensure Controlled Unclassified Information (CUI) is safeguarded. <a href="https://www.sapns2.com/security-and-trust/">SAP NS2 adheres</a> to National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) 800-53, FedRAMP®, International Traffic and Arms (ITAR), and FedRAMP+Impact Level 2 (DoD IL2).</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Harish Luthra is CEO of SAP NS2.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/defense-security</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ns2</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Can Highly Regulated Organizations Benefit from Business Networks?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/highly-regulated-organizations-benefit-from-business-networks</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/highly-regulated-organizations-benefit-from-business-networks</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Deploying SAP Business Network with SAP NS2, regulated organizations can benefit from the network's capabilities while remaining protected.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b6cad246411400921e0967e98c5c7a9f0d1498a7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b6cad246411400921e0967e98c5c7a9f0d1498a7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b6cad246411400921e0967e98c5c7a9f0d1498a7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How Can Highly Regulated Organizations Benefit from Business Networks?" src="./media_1b6cad246411400921e0967e98c5c7a9f0d1498a7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-can-highly-regulated-organizations-benefit-from-business-networks">How Can Highly Regulated Organizations Benefit from Business Networks?</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>No matter the industry, digital business networks are transforming the way organizations work. Connecting people, processes, and systems across multiple enterprises, solutions such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">SAP Business Network</a> help automate transactions and create transparent, resilient, and sustainable supply chains.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-sap-business-network">Learn more about SAP Business Network</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://dam.sap.com/mac/app/e/video/embed/Q3LwTGv?ltr=a&#x26;rc=10">Watch a video</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But if an organization operates in a regulated environment, it may face considerable obstacles in establishing these digital business networks. When organizations are involved in the purchasing and manufacturing of goods related to national security or provide services to local constituents, they have heightened security constraints that can make digital connections with third parties problematic.</p>
  <p>Despite this need for extra security, their objectives are similar to commercial organizations. They need to achieve closer connectedness with external supply chain partners to help ensure smooth product supply.</p>
  <h2 id="adhering-to-stringent-security-standards">Adhering to Stringent Security Standards</h2>
  <p>Organizations handling highly classified information, such as aerospace and defense companies, must comply with cloud security directives such as International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR), the Defense Federal Acquisition Regulation Supplement (DFARS), and the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) 800-53 regulations. These directives set out stringent security standards for the hosting and support of digital business networks, as well as robust rules for managing access to sensitive data.</p>
  <p>However, with security requirements set so high, regulated organizations often fail to establish a digital business network at all. And without one, they must instead adopt a far less efficient point-to-point approach involving e-mails, phone calls, and numerous spreadsheets for communicating with business partners and suppliers.</p>
  <h2 id="missing-out-on-effective-supplier-collaboration">Missing Out on Effective Supplier Collaboration</h2>
  <p>Without the ability for all parties, whether internal or external to the organization, to see real-time information stored in one location, effective collaboration is a challenge – to put it mildly. A lack of integration and transparency makes processes slow and cumbersome. What employees using a digital business network can achieve in hours can take days or weeks if they must make phone calls or send e-mails to request information or initiate a task. The result is a fundamental inability to execute tasks accurately and quickly. And this leads to all the things that supply chain professionals work diligently to avoid: stockout situations on materials they need, overstock on materials they don’t need, poor customer service, and higher supply chain costs.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-network-powers-transparency-resiliency-and-sustainability">SAP Business Network powers transparency, resiliency, and sustainability</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The COVID-19 pandemic created a long-lasting effect on supply chain processes, and many organizations are still impacted today. Collaboration and resiliency across an enterprise are key to remaining proactive in unprecedented situations that could result in lasting negative effects to an organization.</p>
  <h2 id="how-can-sap-help">How Can SAP Help?</h2>
  <p>Established to help protect the mission-critical operations of highly regulated organizations, SAP National Security Services (SAP NS2) can enable customers, such as security contractors and government and defense agencies, to run SAP applications without sacrificing security. By deploying <a href="/topics/business-network">SAP Business Network</a> through SAP NS2, organizations can benefit from the capabilities of SAP’s commercial offering for SAP Business Network while remaining protected by the required U.S. security regulations. The SAP NS2 sovereign deployment model uses U.S.-based support teams to help control how SAP Business Network is governed and how its data is secured.</p>
  <p>In addition to the SAP NS2 Secure Data Cloud service, access to SAP’s vast network of trading partners can help organizations connect new suppliers and expand their supply chain operations. Organizations can connect with supply chain partners digitally to break down siloed business processes and eliminate data visibility barriers. As a result, they can make decisions in real time, providing transparency to all those that need to know what’s happening and why. Through the shared visibility of critical business information, organizations can quickly adapt to change, drive reliable and resilient product flow across their supply chain, and ensure high customer service and on-time delivery of goods and services.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">Visit us online</a> to find out more about how you can deploy SAP Business Network.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Lillian Chang is senior vice president at SAP National Security Services (SAP NS2).</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ns2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP to Support Enterprise Transformation at L3Harris]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/l3harris-enterprise-transformation-rise-with-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/l3harris-enterprise-transformation-rise-with-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[L3Harris Technologies has selected RISE with SAP for its enterprise transformation initiative to streamline its ERP systems.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ns2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Fieldglass: Cloud Innovation for Commercial Regulated Industries]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sap-fieldglass-sap-ns2-cloud-innovation-commercial-regulated-industries</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sap-fieldglass-sap-ns2-cloud-innovation-commercial-regulated-industries</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP Fieldglass at SAP NS2, government agencies and highly regulated industries in the U.S. can adopt market-leading cloud applications.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ns2</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP NS2 Accelerates Plan to Offer SAP Ariba Solutions to Government and Regulated Industries Customers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/sap-ns2-sap-ariba-solutions-government-regulated-industries</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/sap-ns2-sap-ariba-solutions-government-regulated-industries</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To support government organizations, SAP NS2 and SAP are accelerating plans to add SAP Ariba solutions to the SAP NS2 portfolio.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ns2</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>