<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Nonprofits Use AI to Find and Keep Good Donors]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-nonprofits-use-ai-to-find-and-keep-good-donors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-nonprofits-use-ai-to-find-and-keep-good-donors</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Squeezed by a drop in donations, nonprofits are turning to artificial intelligence tools to increase efficiency, improve donor engagement, and boost their mission.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14d314daf26ef5c134b215e5cf30b3247b7bdf780.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14d314daf26ef5c134b215e5cf30b3247b7bdf780.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_14d314daf26ef5c134b215e5cf30b3247b7bdf780.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Close-up of a digital screen with data superimposed on a businessperson working at an office." src="./media_14d314daf26ef5c134b215e5cf30b3247b7bdf780.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-nonprofits-use-ai-to-find-and-keep-good-donors">How Nonprofits Use AI to Find and Keep Good Donors</h1>
        <p>Squeezed by a drop in donations, nonprofits are turning to artificial intelligence tools to increase efficiency, improve donor engagement, and boost their mission.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By Dante Ricci and Lauren Gibbons Paul</p>
  <p>Charities everywhere are feeling pinched. It’s a condition that is part economics and part donor fatigue. The U.S. economy, for example, is growing <a href="https://www.commerce.gov/news/blog/2024/01/numbers-us-economy-grows-faster-expected-year-and-final-quarter-2023#:~:text=Today%2C%20the%20U.S.%20Commerce%20Department%27s,Americans%20making%20and%20spending%20more">faster than expected</a> but Europe and Japan remain flat. After a drop in U.S. charitable giving in 2022 – only the fourth time in 40 years, according to a Giving USA <a href="https://www.charitynavigator.org/about-us/news-thought-leadership/2023-holiday-giving-insights/#:~:text=Charitable%20Giving%20in%202023%20is%20Down%20Year%2Dto%2DDate&#x26;text=We%27re%20hearing%20similar%20reports,%2Dto%2D%20date%20in%202023">report</a> – donations in 2023 plunged further, by <a href="https://www.charitynavigator.org/about-us/news-thought-leadership/2023-holiday-giving-insights/#:~:text=Charitable%20Giving%20in%202023%20is%20Down%20Year%2Dto%2DDate&#x26;text=We%27re%20hearing%20similar%20reports,%2Dto%2D%20date%20in%202023">as much as 30%</a>.</p>
  <p>All of this makes new donor acquisition and donor retention, key imperatives, according to <a href="https://afpglobal.org/news/donor-retention-and-acquisition-key-challenges-social-sector-q3-2023">the Fundraising Effectiveness Projec</a>t. According to NonProfitPRO, a resource for nonprofits, even recurrent donors <a href="https://www.nonprofitpro.com/post/reality-donor-fatigue-strategies-overcome-it/#:~:text=Donor%20fatigue%20is%20a%20real,how%20fundraisers%20can%20overcome%20it">feel fatigued</a> and are keeping their wallets shut as they are hit with increased communications through different channels from individual charities and appeals from additional organizations. Given these trends, nonprofits can reasonably expect lower donation numbers, at least for the near future.</p>
  <p>Ashutosh Nandeshwar, a consultant who advises nonprofits, sees limitless potential for artificial intelligence as a means to mitigate and reverse these trends. Nandeshwar, SVP of data science and analytics at CCS Fundraising, says nonprofits can use both traditional AI (including machine learning, natural language processing, and predictive analytics) and modern AI (including natural language generation and generative AI) to make more strategic use of limited resources.</p>
  <p>Money – fundraising – is a core function of a nonprofit, like revenue generation in the private sector. However, these organizations face additional challenges beyond retaining generous donors and attracting new ones. Aligned with this need is the drive to strengthen the efficiency of their business processes and improve their mission performance. Leaders working to address these challenges are finding encouraging signs that AI tools, from machine learning algorithms to ChatGPT, can help.</p>
  <p>“Especially with generative AI, not only can it be a lever for becoming more efficient, but [nonprofits] can also free up time to do the things they do best, which is being donor-centric, stewarding and cultivating those donors,” says Nandeshwar. “AI can help elevate philanthropic outcomes and, ultimately, better mission fulfillment.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15e32d174964567f77aeda2de45a3558e6dcfdf90.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15e32d174964567f77aeda2de45a3558e6dcfdf90.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_15e32d174964567f77aeda2de45a3558e6dcfdf90.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Close- up of four business people all holding and looking at their digital devices" src="./media_15e32d174964567f77aeda2de45a3558e6dcfdf90.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Artificial intelligence tools in a variety of forms can increase efficiency (save money) by quickly identifying potential new donor pools, analyzing past giving behavior, and zeroing in on the specific individuals and foundations who are most likely to donate. Nonprofits are also using AI for robotic process automation to eliminate costly and time-consuming manual processing of tasks, such as extracting data and filling in forms. Another important advantage: The ability to create personalized donor experiences that cut through cluttered inboxes and limited attention spans goes a long way toward perking up donors.</p>
  <p>Charities may recognize AI’s potential, but we’re still in the early days of adoption, according to a survey by NonProfitHR, a talent advisory service. Its 2024 <a href="https://www.nonprofithr.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/2023-Social-Impact-AI-Survey_Nonprofit-HR.pdf">survey of</a> 250 social sector organizations found respondents viewed generative AI as a useful tool for everything from taking meeting notes to writing job descriptions and drafting social media posts. Still, 45% of respondents said they did not yet use generative AI, with 14% planning to begin using it within the next 12 months.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="prepping-the-business-for-an-ai-world">Prepping the business for an AI world</h3>
        <p>A comprehensive guide on how AI is reshaping industries and powering innovation.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/prepping-the-business-for-an-ai-world">Dive in</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For those getting started on AI projects, the opportunities are there and likely will grow with experience. To get the benefit of using AI tools, there are legal considerations to plan for, including privacy, regulatory issues, and insurance (see sidebar) But there is no question: AI can help nonprofits better manage their money, mission, and people.</p>
  <p>Nonprofits have begun pursuing a range of projects in the past year-plus since ChatGPT and other widely available generative AI tools emerged in late 2022. Among the opportunities they have identified: AI helps nonprofits better understand their donors’ giving patterns.</p>
  <p>Nonprofits are increasingly using <a href="/resources/eight-examples-of-artificial-intelligence-in-action">generative AI</a> to analyze donor data and predict giving patterns, resulting in more targeted and effective fundraising campaigns. For example, the American Cancer Society applied machine learning in a 2022 project to pinpoint which of its digital advertising campaigns generate the most revenue, as well as raise general awareness.</p>
  <p>The program has generated impressive results, according to <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/adtheorent-uses-machine-learning-powered-predictive-advertising-to-boost-donations-and-drive-awareness-for-american-cancer-society-301525751.html">a press release</a> from an advertising technology company working with the cancer charity. “Every bit of our campaign spend needs to be optimized for the best possible performance, so our key advertising goal was to reach the most probable donors, and then engage them in a way that would drive donations,” says Ben Devore, director of media strategy for the American Cancer Society. The program generated donation revenue that came in at 117% over its benchmark and a donor engagement rate of nearly 70% throughout the campaign. The click-through rate on interactive banners was 1.5%, 87.5% above the charity’s benchmark.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ac8d711495cd4b091b76b8631798e7400f5789c5.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ac8d711495cd4b091b76b8631798e7400f5789c5.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1ac8d711495cd4b091b76b8631798e7400f5789c5.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Man standing in front of a big screen presenting graphs and charts to two seated colleagues with a video conferencing system on the table." src="./media_1ac8d711495cd4b091b76b8631798e7400f5789c5.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="opportunities-to-better-understand-and-communicate-with-donors">Opportunities to better understand and communicate with donors</h2>
</div>
<div>
  <h2 id="learn-more-about-implementing-ai">Learn More About Implementing AI</h2>
  <p>“<a href="/resources/eight-examples-of-artificial-intelligence-in-action">8 Examples of Artificial Intelligence in Action</a>.” Enterprise use of AI is growing fast. Here are eight examples with lessons for businesses of all kinds.</p>
  <p>“<a href="/blogs/a-playbook-for-machine-learning-projects-that-work">A Playbook for Machine Learning Projects That Work</a>.” Author Eric Siegel says most leaders miss the boat when it comes to deploying the biggest breakthrough technology to date.</p>
  <p>“<a href="/resources/prepping-the-business-for-an-ai-world">Prepping the Business for an AI World</a>.” In this collection of SAP Insights articles, we reveal how AI is changing business and what it takes to realize its full potential.</p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>Style</div>
      <div>Additional Reading</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <h2 id="ai-powered-chatbots-can-streamline-communications-and-increase-donor-engagement">AI-powered chatbots can streamline communications and increase donor engagement.</h2>
  <p>Generative AI can seamlessly create new content (such as e-mails, press releases, appeal letters, blogs, and social media posts) and foster creativity. The key is to keep a human involved for oversight of the tone and to ensure accuracy. This basic risk-reduction strategy is a good rule of thumb for all AI use.</p>
  <h2 id="ai-chatbots-can-help-guide-potential-donors-through-the-donation-process">AI chatbots can help guide potential donors through the donation process.</h2>
  <p>And they can help in designing and delivering personalized donor experiences. The tools make this quick and cost-effective to do.</p>
  <h2 id="generative-ai-can-fill-in-as-your-grant-writing-co-pilot">Generative AI can fill in as your grant writing “co-pilot.”</h2>
  <p>Tools like ChatGPT are famously helpful as a starting point for communications of all types. But they are useful for higher octane work such as grant proposals, too. Services such as grantboost.io have emerged specifically geared to help nonprofits with grant writing.</p>
  <h2 id="let-generative-ai-help-you-cast-a-wider-foreign-language-net">Let generative AI help you cast a wider (foreign language) net.</h2>
  <p>The translation capabilities in ChatGPT and other tools make it easy and fast to engage with nonnative English speakers. Just be sure you understand the regulations when operating in a new jurisdiction (see below for more information).</p>
  <h2 id="machine-learning-tools-can-help-nonprofits-unearth-useful-nuggets-from-the-trove-of-data-they-possess">Machine learning tools can help nonprofits unearth useful nuggets from the trove of data they possess.</h2>
  <p>This includes how their organization is meeting its mission and making a difference. Donors increasingly want to know more about where their donations go; insights driven from machine learning (ML) can provide the proof points they seek. This style of increased transparency should help decrease donor fatigue.</p>
  <p>ML can point to receptive new audiences. St. Jude Children’s Research Hospital, which funds close to 80% of its US$1 billion operating budget through individual donors, was driven to find new ways to interact with existing donors and identify new ones. According to a story on the Future of Marketing site, St. Jude integrated ML into its emotionally engaging donor appeal videos and offered easy ways to donate in the moment and engage new, younger, and more diverse audiences, according to <a href="https://www.thinkwithgoogle.com/future-of-marketing/digital-transformation/future-proofing-business/">an article</a> at Google’s Future of Marketing.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="a-playbook-for-machine-learning-projects">A playbook for machine learning projects</h3>
        <p>Unlock the potential of machine learning with Eric Siege’s six-step methodology.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/blogs/a-playbook-for-machine-learning-projects-that-work">Read the Q&#x26;A</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="ml-can-boost-the-efficacy-of-a-charitys-mission">ML can boost the efficacy of a charity’s mission.</h2>
  <p>Perhaps the most exciting use of AI and ML is to help the nonprofit more effectively carry out its core mission.</p>
  <p>Case in point: the Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS), uses ML to pinpoint the best location for <a href="https://www.ox.ac.uk/news/2018-10-02-using-ai-improve-refugee-integration">refugee resettlement</a> while accounting for a refugee’s ability to speak the local language and find a job. A study found the tool could increase the refugee employment rate by as much as 40%.</p>
  <p>"AI can help elevate philanthropic outcomes and, ultimately, better mission fulfillment."</p>
  <p><em>– Ashutosh Nandeshwar, SVP of data science and analytics for CCS Fundraising</em></p>
  <p>In another example, Breastcancer.org – a leading digital resource for people affected by breast cancer – uses ML to personalize the patient education journey, <a href="https://www.nonprofitpro.com/article/how-nonprofits-are-using-machine-learning-to-support-those-in-need/">according to</a> a NonProfitPRO article. The same article cites Polaris, a 150-person nonprofit that operates the U.S. National Human Trafficking Hotline, providing 24/7/365 support for survivors of human trafficking. With the number of calls from other agencies and survivors themselves increasing thousands of percentage points from 2008 to 2021, the nonprofit implemented a voice bot powered by ML to direct nonurgent general information requests (over 1,700 in the first six months) to informational resources, leaving staff free to engage with more urgent calls.</p>
  <h2 id="gain-insights-into-donor-sentiment">Gain insights into donor sentiment</h2>
  <p>Tools that incorporate natural language processing (NLP) and ML can sift through social media posts and reams of other structured and unstructured data to analyze how members of the public think and feel about relevant issues.</p>
  <p>For example, the White Ribbon Alliance, a Washington, DC-based global women’s health advocacy group, used NLP to analyze findings in “What Women Want,” a survey of one million women from eight countries that asked about their reproductive healthcare priorities.</p>
  <p>Responses from women in Mexico, Cameroon, Nigeria, India, Pakistan, Malawi, Uganda, Kenya, and Tanzania came back as unstructured data: text formats, using open-ended questions in a variety of languages, which made the survey difficult to analyze on a global scale. NLP made manageable the task of sorting through and understanding the responses to questions such as “What is your one request for quality reproductive and maternal healthcare services?” (Manual tabulations would have been unworkable with this number of respondents.) The White Ribbon Alliance shared the key concerns with case workers on the ground in respondent countries, and they were surprised by the depth of the data, which they were then able to use to help local constituencies, according to a <a href="https://fastdatascience.com/natural-language-processing-for-non-profit/">blog post</a> on Fast Data Science.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10e47f193bfd72a5b0ecf5263b25b88f2a3275942.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10e47f193bfd72a5b0ecf5263b25b88f2a3275942.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_10e47f193bfd72a5b0ecf5263b25b88f2a3275942.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Close-up image of a lock on top of an electric circuit board representing data security." src="./media_10e47f193bfd72a5b0ecf5263b25b88f2a3275942.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
</div>
<div>
  <h2 id="legal-considerations-to-nonprofits-use-of-ai">Legal Considerations to Nonprofits’ Use of AI</h2>
  <p>Are you fired up to use generative AI or other tools to increase efficiency and donor engagement? Not so fast. First, there’s a host of legal issues you’ll need to consider. According to an article in the <em>NonProfit Times</em>:</p>
  <p>Data privacy regulations that predate the debut of the newest AI tools are a top concern with AI use for nonprofits as they need to ensure compliance related to fundraising activities (for example, GDPR and the California <a href="https://oag.ca.gov/privacy/ccpa">Consumer Privacy Act</a>), consent, safeguarding data, and providing individuals with rights regarding their personal information and restrictions on solicitation practices.</p>
  <p>Intellectual property becomes an issue when AI systems create new works that need to be protected (such as software, content, and images). You will also need to take steps to ensure the AI system is not infringing on another intellectual property (IP) owner’s rights.</p>
  <p>Discrimination can inadvertently be introduced by AI, either by perpetuating pre-existing biases into the system or by introducing new biases from the AI system itself. Either way, you’ll need to <a href="/blogs/thinkers-unmasking-unconscious-bias-in-ai">guard against unfair bias</a>.</p>
  <p>Tort liability can arise if the AI system emits inaccurate, negligent, or biased results that harm donors or prospects (or anyone else who is harmed by the content). Use human gatekeepers to ensure the accuracy and reliability of the AI system’s output.</p>
  <p>Insurance is needed to reduce the legal risks identified above. Traditional directors and officers insurance is likely to be insufficient to cover these risks.</p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>Style</div>
      <div>Additional Reading</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <h2 id="rewards-but-not-without-risk">Rewards, but not without risk</h2>
  <p>Along with the opportunities offered by AI technologies come challenges, including legal considerations and regulatory risk, especially in regions with strong privacy laws like Europe’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). The requirements to maintain data anonymity are growing, even in the United States, and that will affect your ability to leverage donor data.</p>
  <p>Data quality is another challenge. Quality and availability of data are imperative. AI is only as good as the data it uses to learn and refine its outputs. Organizations often run into roadblocks with an inability to pull out data from old systems or difficulties embedding AI into legacy systems.</p>
  <p>Equally important are the algorithms used to process and analyze the data. Plan to put a lot of consideration into the choice of algorithm.</p>
  <p>You should also consider the possibility of unwittingly injecting bias into your use of AI and the unintended consequences that could result. It is important to fully understand the system’s limitations and to ensure AI algorithms are transparent and explainable. Ensure that the security capabilities provided by vendors provide appropriate encryption and access controls and that you can adhere to applicable data protection regulations.</p>
  <p>You also need to make sure your organization has the right skill sets for the type of AI. Even if you are purchasing and using pre-built products, you should have some internal people with AI skill sets to be able to govern its use.</p>
  <p>Managing these risks is prudent – but doing so should not close the door on the promise that AI tools have to help nonprofit organizations reverse recent trends.</p>
  <p>“We have observed philanthropic trends for generations,” says Greg Hagin, principal and managing director for CCS Fundraising. “Over the last twenty years, donors down, dollars up. More recently, donors down, dollars down, factoring inflation. Whether a crisis or concern, we do believe these AI-enabled technologies can help address the challenge by strengthening connection and commitment with personalized messaging and tailored offering.”</p>
  <h2 id="where-to-begin">Where to begin</h2>
  <p>For nonprofits interested in using AI to reap benefits relating to money, mission, and people, consider these starting points:</p>
  <p><strong>Start with small projects.</strong> Test the feasibility and benefits of the technology and then increase use as you become more comfortable. Jump-start the use of AI with pre-trained programs by investing in pre-built products to test out narrow use cases.</p>
  <p><strong>Collaborate cross-functionally.</strong> Include a cross-functional team in all the decisions and implementation to ensure the use of technology aligns with your mission and benefits the communities you serve. Don’t forget to engage with other nonprofit organizations to share knowledge, benchmark, and understand lessons learned.</p>
  <p><strong>Safeguard.</strong> Allow for learning and adjustments along the way, which will help minimize risks. Fully understand the systems’ limitations and ensure AI algorithms are transparent and explainable.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[7 Due Diligence Steps for the Four-Day Workweek]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/7-due-diligence-steps-for-the-four-day-workweek</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/7-due-diligence-steps-for-the-four-day-workweek</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[From employee visas to overtime requirements, ironing the devil out of these details will help you to avoid legal issues and hit your goals.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Five Ways That AI Is Changing Finance]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/research/five-ways-that-ai-is-changing-finance</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/research/five-ways-that-ai-is-changing-finance</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[AI tools are changing the focus of finance work. Human roles will change – to varying degrees – but remain important.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Revamping Sales Processes for Consumption Pricing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/revamping-sales-processes-for-consumption-pricing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/revamping-sales-processes-for-consumption-pricing</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A consumption-based sales model requires looking at the entire business with a new lens.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bb4fc748beb0ebc85bf3a07e3187d1b073bc57bf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bb4fc748beb0ebc85bf3a07e3187d1b073bc57bf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1bb4fc748beb0ebc85bf3a07e3187d1b073bc57bf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="A White person with their hands on a laptop keyboard. The laptop screen shows the words &#x22;Transaction completed,&#x22; along with a green checkmark and a blue button." src="./media_1bb4fc748beb0ebc85bf3a07e3187d1b073bc57bf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="revamping-sales-processes-for-consumption-pricing">Revamping Sales Processes for Consumption Pricing</h1>
        <p>A consumption-based sales model requires looking at the entire business with a new lens.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Consumption-based pricing (CBP), also known as usage-based pricing (UBP), seems straightforward at first blush. Instead of paying a set price up front for a software or service subscription, customers only pay for what they consume, a.k.a. pay-as-you-go. And rather than earn commissions when deals close, sales reps earn compensation that typically <a href="/resources/compensating-sales-for-consumption-based-pricing">is tied to how much the customer actually consumes</a>.</p>
  <p>But when a company rushes into this enticing model too quickly, chaos can ensue.</p>
  <p>Case in point: a company that sells software as a service (SaaS) to energy businesses was tired of losing deals to the same competitor. As many SaaS businesses do, the company licensed its software based on subscriptions, but the competitor offered a CBP model, with its software at a quarter of the normal up-front costs and with more flexible pricing. The energy company was being pushed into the CBP pool – and seeing the potential for more wins, it jumped right in.</p>
  <p>The company came up with new product usage prices and software packaging options, and tweaked the underlying data pipeline to make sure it could accurately meter customers’ usage for billing purposes. This created an option for customers to prepay for their expected software use. Otherwise, though, customers still had the option to stick with purchasing the software at an annual subscription rate.</p>
  <p>The company soon learned this wasn’t enough to consistently win competitive deals.</p>
  <p>The pricing change was clearly a step in the right direction, providing customers with better flexibility in the products they used and when, over the course of the contract. But in the following months, the company still struggled to beat the competitor, which offered much more flexibility in committed contract size for a highly commitment-phobic customer base.</p>
  <p>Without changing the sales team’s key performance indicators (KPIs) to reorient from up-front commitments toward CBP, nothing changed in how the sales team structured its proposed contracts. Salespeople continued to press customers for maximum commitment amounts, while offering aggressive discounts to counteract concerns about accurately forecasting future demand. They continued to lose deals as a result.</p>
  <p>The company realized it needed to embrace the strategy it had put on its pricing page – and take a closer look at how this strategy should affect the entire sales process.</p>
  <p>It’s a familiar dilemma for many organizations beginning their CBP journeys: there’s more to it than just changing the pricing terms.</p>
  <p>The <a href="/resources/compensating-sales-for-consumption-based-pricing">consumption-based pricing model</a> is a no-brainer for consumers because they know their bills match their actual use of the products. Software vendors like CBP because it brings new customers in the door faster – due to little or no up-front commitment – while opening the door wider for long-term potential growth, since they can continue to up-sell new features or encourage more usage over time.</p>
  <p>Sounds like a win-win – but creating a new pricing option is just the tip of the iceberg. A consumption-based sales model requires looking at the entire business with a new lens. It’s no longer a sales process but an end-to-end business process, from sale through data collection all the way to payment. Every piece of the business has to support that consumption-based economy. With that said, the underlying sales processes that are needed to maintain a CBP model are still in a state of flux. A lot of companies are still trying to figure it out, and no single solution fits all organizations.</p>
  <p>Navigating the right path could mean the difference between success and failure. Answering three critical questions will help you find that path.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b2b0676663ad0c58668262b1e7a98c0c7db34907.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b2b0676663ad0c58668262b1e7a98c0c7db34907.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1b2b0676663ad0c58668262b1e7a98c0c7db34907.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="A young professional Black woman looks at a financial business analytics data dashboard on two monitors." src="./media_1b2b0676663ad0c58668262b1e7a98c0c7db34907.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="what-new-data-will-we-need-to-collect">What new data will we need to collect?</h2>
  <p>Determining customers’ rate of “consumption” may involve transforming data you already have but it also may require collecting new data entirely.</p>
  <p>“It’s hard to offer a consumption product if you don’t have a metering system. It’s foundational,” says Chris Semain, principal and tech practice leader at Alexander Group. It’s similar to a meter in a cab; you pay depending on how far you go. Metering solutions ensure that both customers and software vendors have near-real-time information on how much they’re using the product.</p>
  <p>But there’s a lot of company-by-company uniqueness to data collection because there are many forms of consumption or usage, Semain says. “The unit of measurement for consumption is a variety of types of measurements. Some companies have tokens, like popping in a quarter into a video machine, where you can pay for 100 tokens to use the product. In other cases, usage is based on defining the number of ‘workloads,’ or it might be the number of software modules you’re using,” he adds.</p>
  <p>As the SaaS provider, of course, you’ll want the customer’s cost for each unit to accurately reflect how your own infrastructure costs increase as your users require more computation, storage, or seat management.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="xaas-and-subscription-business-models">XaaS and subscription business models</h3>
        <p>Subscription-based business models are helping many companies increase profits.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/business-model-innovation-xaas">Find out how</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Many organizations don’t yet track and report granular product usage data or trends to help inform and prioritize their sales teams’ activities. But the high-tech, insurance, and telco industries are among the best-positioned for data use tracking and consumption-based sales models.</p>
  <p>Telcos are well positioned for usage-based sales models because they have long monitored minutes spent on phone calls and specific apps as well as amounts of data used with streaming, downloads, backhauling data, and related services.</p>
  <p>Examples in the insurance industry show how this idea is expanding. Insurance companies collect data through GPS to offer a type of CBP. For instance, U.S.-based insurer Progressive offers Snapshot, a consumption-based model that measures not just how much customers drive but how well they drive. It monitors driver behavior through GPS and its mobile app; presumably, the customer gets a better insurance rate for being a safe driver. The data is tracking the driver’s actual exposure to risk in order to determine the rate.</p>
  <p>Health insurance companies are also trying to use GPS for data collection. In India, for example, some offer customers <a href="https://www.indiatimes.com/worth/news/health-insurance-companies-encourage-fitness-through-low-premiums-600815.html">discounts on insurance if they exercise</a> a certain number of days per month. To validate this, at least one company tracks customers by GPS to fitness clubs (with permission), although they don’t know if the customer is actually working out, Semain says.</p>
  <p>Organizations that can collect vital usage data and track customer behavior have the foundation for a consumption-based sales model; they will be able to compensate sales reps, come up with innovative sales models, and better forecast usage and revenue.</p>
  <p>The pipelines that deliver the collected data throughout an organization will need considerable reengineering too. You’ll see why this is necessary in the next question.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ae1b7f1802b610e98446be17ba5d6c551be06d69.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ae1b7f1802b610e98446be17ba5d6c551be06d69.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1ae1b7f1802b610e98446be17ba5d6c551be06d69.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="A businessperson seated at a conference table with other professionals, using a laptop that displays several sales-related charts." src="./media_1ae1b7f1802b610e98446be17ba5d6c551be06d69.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="how-will-we-measure-and-forecast-future-revenue">How will we measure and forecast future revenue?</h2>
  <p>Revenue predictability is the biggest challenge for any sales organization. Companies take different approaches to the extra uncertainty that comes with fewer up-front commitments, but it’s going to affect everything from data pipeline engineering to how salespeople are compensated.</p>
  <p>Historically, SaaS models were architected around the “deal” or the opportunity. Deals being closed were the singular catalyst for change in recognized revenue – the natural unit of measurement for tracking and planning revenue growth.</p>
  <p>In usage-based models, revenue growth could happen before, during, and after a deal cycle. Customers can buy more up front to get a better price – but, for example, if they anticipate just a one-time spike in their usage needs, they might be inclined to risk paying a premium for any overruns rather than overcommitting up front.</p>
  <p>A 2022 study by consulting firm Bain shows that more than 90% of users who prefer subscription models to consumption models <a href="https://www.bain.com/insights/topics/technology-report/2022/">cite a lack of predictability</a> as the main downside of the latter. So the challenge becomes rethinking and rearchitecting how to predict the flow of future revenue.</p>
  <p>At Datadog, a SaaS-based monitoring and analytics software provider, UBP has been a part of the business since its inception and has led to much of the company’s success, according to former VP of finance Scott Buxton. Its infrastructure monitoring product is still sold on a “price per host monitored” basis, and this model also accounts for discounts based on annual commitment, volume, and tier. But Buxton acknowledges in an OpenView Partners <a href="https://openviewpartners.com/blog/implementing-usage-based-pricing-what-your-financial-teams-need-to-know/">blog post</a> that sales predictability was a lot more challenging with UBP.</p>
  <p>Datadog implemented a drawdown model option that allowed a customer to adapt their usage pace according to the needs of their business. This helped balance the business’s need for predictability with the customer’s need for flexibility.</p>
  <p>With this drawdown model, “Customers can commit a certain sum, say $1 million, pick a term, and draw down on their sum over that time period. They could use zero dollars in the first six months of their three-year term to account for business delays… and as soon as they’re up and ready, they can go as fast as they want,” Buxton writes.</p>
  <p>Having commitment built into the pricing model can certainly mitigate some of these concerns about predictability, but it’s far from perfect, Buxton says. “First of all, not all customers elect this type of plan. Second, relying exclusively on monthly commitments in your calculations will lead to pretty inaccurate numbers.”</p>
  <p>The energy company found other ways to tackle its predictability challenges.</p>
  <p>First, the company ditched overage fees. In the original pricing model, it had maintained overage charges when customers finished their commitments (at the “rack rate” or standard pricing). Terms like “overage” turned off customers, so the company moved to a utility-based charge on par with the unit-based prices that customers were paying on their committed contracts.</p>
  <p>Next, they redefined core business KPIs. They devised different ways to define revenue events and architect sales plans around them.</p>
  <p>Establishing what those KPIs should be is all about priorities, says Ben Chambers, a consultant specializing in consumption-based sales models. Some companies want to solve for simplicity and choose the path that’s most comfortable to veteran sales reps: subscriptions. Others opt for more nuanced, usage-based measures of incremental sales performance. If product usage is seasonal (such as in the retail industry) or erratic and spiky (as with project-intense organizations), that likely influences the design of the KPI. For instance, it might make sense for a non-seasonal type of business to create a usage-based annual recurring revenue (ARR) metric that takes recent usage from the last one to three months and annualizes it to come up with ARR. However, that type of KPI would present more challenges and issues for companies with erratic or seasonal usage patterns.</p>
  <p>The energy company also chose to define revenue events in a fairly straightforward way – total billable usage, regardless of whether or not it’s precommitted. Every quantity of product usage was translated into a dollar amount and attributed back to the user.</p>
  <p>Once the core KPIs were defined, the energy company began architecting the data pipeline for this new KPI usage value – translating product usage into a dollar amount and thinking about all the legacy contracts that would be affected before it rolled out pricing changes. The company also attributed every dollar of usage to the responsible salesperson to determine their quota.</p>
  <p>The new data pipeline requires not only new data but determining where it goes and how it’s combined and transformed. When switching from subscription to CBP models involved only a pricing and packaging change, the in-product and customer-facing billing systems needed this usage data pipeline, while the internal business and go-to-market systems simply continued to manage the business around contracted ARR. In this case, a standard customer relationship management (CRM) system is generally well equipped to manage a fixed-subscription business model.</p>
  <p>But when flipping to a dedicated usage-based model, many more internal parties need their systems, processes, and reporting on the product usage data, as this is now the direct basis for revenue recognition, quota crediting, and commissions, Chambers says. CRM tends not to be the most logical or natural source of truth for tracking and reporting daily updates to product usage, he adds.</p>
  <p>Chambers has seen a shift toward the enterprise data warehouse developing into the source of truth for internal reporting. Product usage data from product and billing systems could be integrated with sales territory and attribution data or contract specifics from CRM and fed into business intelligence dashboards for field-facing reporting, revenue forecasting systems, and commission calculations.</p>
  <p>With usage now taking precedence over revenue commitment, a company’s primary metric becomes <em>how much</em> the accounts in a territory are using the product, not what they’re committed to. Usage-based KPIs can keep customers from being oversold or underutilized, and the KPI becomes the primary measure for how organizations define territories.</p>
  <p>With the data collection and data pipeline in place, the energy company is now building a compensation plan for sales and customer success teams. This process has its own complexities and decision points, which we previously discussed in <a href="/resources/compensating-sales-for-consumption-based-pricing">Compensating Sales for Consumption-Based Pricing</a>.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19acd9e985f649cd0f0e1cea3a6aae86812283904.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19acd9e985f649cd0f0e1cea3a6aae86812283904.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19acd9e985f649cd0f0e1cea3a6aae86812283904.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Sales and support teams discuss business results shown onscreen in a boardroom." src="./media_19acd9e985f649cd0f0e1cea3a6aae86812283904.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1493" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="how-will-revenue-generators-sales-and-revenue-enhancers-service-support-and-customer-success-teams-work-together">How will revenue generators (sales) and revenue enhancers (service, support, and customer success teams) work together?</h2>
  <p>CBP requires more cooperation between sales and customer success managers, and rethinking how you want sales spending their time is a top priority. The good news: CBP presents a huge opportunity for customer success functions to own a metric that more naturally reflects the impact of their efforts than booking-oriented metrics.</p>
  <p>In traditional go-to-market models in the software sales world, teams adhere to swim lanes. The sales team, or revenue generator, is accountable for leading new business acquisition and growth. The customer success team or another account management function, the revenue enhancer, is responsible for client retention.</p>
  <p>Those roles will remain, but they’ll need to collaborate when engaging with the client after the sale – including onboarding, monitoring usage, and scrutinizing consumption patterns at the end of a term commitment so they can forecast more accurately at renewal time, Semain says. The day-to-day activities of these roles need to focus on improving the adoption and value realization stages of the customer journey.</p>
  <p>“Your customer success managers and sales reps need to stay on clients, because if they don’t and the client isn’t consuming, they’ll probably cancel,” Semain says. “There need to be resources holding their hands to make sure they’re getting value from the products.”</p>
  <p>But how much time should a salesperson spend on building customers’ usage? On the one hand, organizations could determine what tools and dashboards are needed to best improve how they spend their time to maximize product usage. “That may be a little different from a traditional fixed-subscription model where their activities were around identifying potential opportunities and swooping in on a new account to generate a commercial transaction,” he says.</p>
  <p>Sales reps could spend 40 hours a week trying to identify where their customers are going to use more software, but is that the best use of their time? “Probably not,” Chambers says. “Primarily, they should be using their skill sets to unlock demand and identify and win new business – things that take persuasion and selling skills.”</p>
  <p>Many organizations, including the energy company, are still figuring this out. Sales compensation models still haven’t caught up with UBP in most organizations, so they’re sticking with more familiar models, Semain says.</p>
  <p>When it comes to compensating those teams, he says, “A lot of companies want to compensate their customer success managers and potentially their sales reps on usage, adoption, and/or value realization. But because of the difficulty with tracking usage or defining the right metric, they’ve decided just to compensate customer success managers and reps on renewals because they haven’t quite figured out what ‘good’ usage is.”</p>
  <p>While the consumption-based sales process is still in nascent stages, CFOs are warming to the idea that it is essentially the future. “It may be choppier waters than subscription-based models, but it's a better path to revenue growth, especially in competitive environments where core competitors are also offering usage-based pricing arrangements,” Chambers says.</p>
  <p>“Companies are getting pushed into the pool. If they don’t start swimming, they won’t be able to win against the competitor that designs and delivers a lower-friction sales cycle requiring far less money up front.”</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Upskilling Your Workforce for the AI Era]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/upskilling-your-workforce-for-the-ai-era</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/upskilling-your-workforce-for-the-ai-era</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get advice on how companies and employees can incorporate AI into existing work and seizing opportunities to elevate skills.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prepping the Business for an AI World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/prepping-the-business-for-an-ai-world</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/prepping-the-business-for-an-ai-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how AI is changing business, and what it takes to realize its full potential.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_176d65207aa8d830870be460910ae57fb38db1892.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_176d65207aa8d830870be460910ae57fb38db1892.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_176d65207aa8d830870be460910ae57fb38db1892.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="A robot with human face structure." src="./media_176d65207aa8d830870be460910ae57fb38db1892.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="prepping-the-business-for-an-ai-world">Prepping the Business for an AI World</h1>
        <p>In this collection of SAP Insights articles, we reveal how AI is changing business, and what it takes to realize its full potential.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By SAP Insights</p>
  <p>Everyone, it seems, is implementing artificial intelligence, whether it’s developing a proof of concept or pilot, or moving to full-on adoption. Along the way, leaders are learning valuable lessons about using AI throughout the organization, such as:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Innately human capabilities like collaboration and empathy have never been more important – and important to teach.</li>
    <li>It’s never sufficient to just “turn on” AI and let it work. Governance is crucial for rooting out harmful bias and other negative effects.</li>
    <li>AI will touch many areas of the business, from HR to the C-suite.</li>
    <li>Successful AI implementers approach AI as a business project, not a technology one.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>You can learn more about how to reap AI’s benefits while avoiding its pitfalls in the SAP Insights articles below.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13200c7a5384cba5e7c225a26b5740eb8dcf715c1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13200c7a5384cba5e7c225a26b5740eb8dcf715c1.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_13200c7a5384cba5e7c225a26b5740eb8dcf715c1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Woman engineer seated in front of a computer station, working on a robot head next to her." src="./media_13200c7a5384cba5e7c225a26b5740eb8dcf715c1.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="relationshipgoals-for-ai-and-humans">#RelationshipGoals for AI and humans</h2>
  <p><strong>Calling all humans.</strong> AI – and especially generative AI – is taking on more activities formerly in the human domain, like creating new content. But there are still lots of things it can’t do, like imagine new business models or recognize abstract concepts such as humor or irony.</p>
  <p>As AI takes hold, creativity and critical thinking skills will become increasingly valuable because these are things only a human can bring to the table. Uniquely human traits like emotional intelligence, cross-cultural awareness, curiosity, critical thinking, and persistence can and should be taught and cultivated, as opposed to expecting these qualities to develop on their own, as if by magic.</p>
  <p>Reevaluate what makes humans human in “<em><a href="https://www.sap.com/insights/viewpoints/the-human-factor-in-an-ai-future.html">The Human Factor in an AI Future</a></em>”.</p>
  <p><strong>Emotion commotion.</strong> Meanwhile, a phenomenon called “affective computing” uses machine learning to teach computers how to understand and project human emotions based on input from gestures, facial expressions, text, and tone of voice. This is important for businesses that want to use AI to engage people, as humans are known to respond to emotionally resonant experiences.</p>
  <p>Sensitivity to ethical considerations is key. For instance, the privacy implications of detecting employee frustration with a process or task are very different from the concerns raised when monitoring consumer mood changes in a retail setting.</p>
  <p><em>Read about computerized emotional awareness and how to use this superpower in “<a href="/blogs/empathy-affective-computing-ai">E mpathy: The Killer App for AI</a>”.</em></p>
  <h2 id="ai-behave-yourself">AI, behave yourself!</h2>
  <p><strong>Warning: bias ahead.</strong> Most business leaders know by now that AI tools can unwittingly introduce bias into processes. And when they do, suffering ensues, both for people harmed by bad decisions and for companies whose reputations crater when these decisions become known.</p>
  <p>Why is it so difficult to know when AI is biased? Data scientist and author Cathy O’Neil says it comes down to the harmful and widespread misconception that algorithms are neutral. Business leaders need to create processes to consider and mitigate against potential bias.</p>
  <p><em>Read our Q&#x26;A with O’Neil to discover where bias lurks in “<a href="/blogs/thinkers-unmasking-unconscious-bias-in-ai">Unmasking Unconscious Bias in AI</a>.”</em></p>
  <p><strong>Here’s the rub: It’s hard to tell what AI is doing.</strong> Many companies just set up AI systems and let them run without understanding why a particular decision was made. This is problematic, particularly in regions like the EU, which require businesses to be able to explain the decisions their systems make (such as denying a consumer’s loan application). Business and technology leaders alike need to start treating AI as a new source of risk that needs to be managed.</p>
  <p><em>If you’re not already worried, read “<a href="/resources/ai-buyer-beware-ai-liability">AI Buyer Beware: Know How Your AI Works</a>."</em></p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_139f785aa01b8865d2e2343008788c3e52a1fc031.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_139f785aa01b8865d2e2343008788c3e52a1fc031.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_139f785aa01b8865d2e2343008788c3e52a1fc031.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="A woman with glasses with data from monitors reflected in her glasses" src="./media_139f785aa01b8865d2e2343008788c3e52a1fc031.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><strong>And AI won’t exactly curb its own behavior.</strong> By neglecting AI risks, you can expose your organization and people to many types of harm – harm that can spiral out of control very quickly. In this Q&#x26;A, ethicist and former philosophy professor Reid Blackman gives pointers for what businesses should think about as they define the ethical boundaries for their AI systems and create the processes and quantitative metrics to support and enforce those boundaries.</p>
  <p><em>Read why Blackman says ethical AI is not a technology problem in “<a href="/blogs/giving-ai-a-moral-compass">Giving AI a Moral Compass.”</a></em></p>
  <p><strong>The risk is real.</strong> When it comes to who would be held accountable both for safeguarding the use of AI and for dealing with its potential negative consequences, most fingers point in one direction: the businesses who choose to use it. But don’t be tempted to drop this on your chief information officer’s or chief risk manager’s desk and call it a day.</p>
  <p>Ensuring AI behaves responsibly is a team effort, involving everyone from technology and data executives to legal and business execs, and everyday users of the AI system. The goal is to create a multilayered governance system for AI use that fills all the gaps.</p>
  <p><em>Get started on creating a responsible AI framework with five action items in “<a href="/blogs/no-more-excuses-for-irresponsible-use-of-ai">No More Excuses for Irresponsible Use of AI</a>."</em></p>
  <h2 id="from-hr-to-the-supply-chain-ai-is-everywhere">From HR to the supply chain, AI is everywhere</h2>
  <p><strong>AI’s effect on jobs? It’s complicated.</strong> HR professionals are the front-line warriors for managing AI-driven changes to the workforce. But there’s a big gray area between job apocalypse and full-employment nirvana. As such, people managers will need to accommodate many different potential outcomes, from increased automation displacing workers to the need for more human-centric roles created in the wake of AI.</p>
  <p><em>Learn more about possible AI workforce scenarios and how HR should respond in <a href="/research/three-hr-strategies-for-managing-ai-disruption">Three HR Strategies for Managing AI Job Disruption</a>.</em></p>
  <p><strong>HR as AI whisperer.</strong> HR leaders need to play a bigger role in how AI tools like ChatGPT are used in the workplace. Let’s start with training. Employees need help understanding how to use generative AI productively, accurately, equitably, and ethically, along with guarding against the potential for the technology to do damage.</p>
  <p>Additionally, HR could play a huge role in helping to redesign jobs and workflows to take advantage of AI efficiency gains, thereby enhancing the employee experience and furthering AI adoption. HR professionals need to be more assertive about convincing their organizations that HR expertise is key to making AI work.</p>
  <p><em>Learn about HR’s strategic role with generative AI in “<a href="/resources/how-hr-can-direct-use-of-ai">How HR Can Direct Use of AI and ChatGPT</a>.”</em></p>
  <p><strong>Supply and demand shocks, be gone.</strong> Long-lasting disruptions to global supply chains (we’re looking at you, COVID-19 pandemic) have forever put an end to traditional demand forecasting, with its reliance on historical data. With the increased frequency, scope, and scale of catastrophes – from global climate change and cyberterrorism to rolling pandemics – businesses are now turning to AI-based predictive modeling.</p>
  <p>This method incorporates real-time demand signals (such as point-of-sale data, weather forecasts, social media feeds, competitive intelligence, and macroeconomic indicators) and AI-driven analytics to anticipate and respond to unexpected shifts in demand. If you want a durable supply chain, this is the way to go.</p>
  <p><em>See how companies are moving from forecast to foresight in “<a href="/resources/new-era-of-demand-planning">The New Era of Demand Planning</a>.”</em></p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="what-is-supply-chain-planning">What is Supply Chain Planning?</h3>
        <p>Learn about demand forecasting for the modern supply chain.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/integrated-business-planning/what-is-supply-chain-planning/demand-forecasting.html">Read more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>AI with a corner-office view.</strong> AI is even coming to the hallowed halls of the C-suite. At this level, AI will become a tool for inquiry rather than action, helping CXOs prove or dispel hunches and gut instincts with extensive data and analysis. No more relying solely on personal experience or counsel from trusted advisors.</p>
  <p><em>Read how AI and machine learning (ML) will profoundly change how companies are led in “<a href="/blogs/the-c-suite-gets-an-ai-upgrade">The C-Suite Gets an AI Upgrade</a>.”</em></p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cdad9aafb436a68adcd2279e4215bbec6943a751.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cdad9aafb436a68adcd2279e4215bbec6943a751.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1cdad9aafb436a68adcd2279e4215bbec6943a751.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="White person in a field of tall grass using a digital tablet with a virtual overlay of data." src="./media_1cdad9aafb436a68adcd2279e4215bbec6943a751.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="ai-in-the-wild">AI in the wild</h2>
  <p><strong>Business use of AI is growing fast.</strong> Companies are ditching the endless cycle of proofs of concept and are now moving to actual implementation. AI is being used for everything from speeding up drug development and designing toy cars to pollinating crops and increasing efficiency in large-scale manufacturing.</p>
  <p>However, there are still as many ways to get it wrong as get it right. Much can be learned from those who’ve rolled up their sleeves and moved forward with AI.</p>
  <p><em>For inspiration and insight into your own AI use cases, read “<a href="https://www.sap.com/insights/viewpoints/eight-examples-of-artificial-intelligence-in-action.html">8 Examples of Artificial Intelligence in Action</a>.”</em></p>
  <p><strong>We can do hard things.</strong> It’s all too easy to get your head turned by the glittery object that is ChatGPT. But former Columbia University professor and best-selling author Eric Siegel says the real breakthroughs are tied not to generative AI but to machine learning. All too often, however, businesses get ML wrong because successful ML projects are notoriously difficult.</p>
  <p>Siegel says the key is viewing each ML project as a business project, and not becoming enchanted by the technology itself. His book provides a six-part framework for implementing ML to drive operational gains.</p>
  <p><em>Read our Q&#x26;A with Siegel to get your AI projects grounded in reality in “<a href="https://www.sap.com/insights/viewpoints/a-playbook-for-machine-learning-projects-that-work.html">A Playbook for Machine Learning Projects That Work</a>.”</em></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/responsible-ai</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Great Data-Driven Auto Distribution Rally]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/the-great-data-driven-auto-distribution-rally</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/the-great-data-driven-auto-distribution-rally</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To keep up with customers, automakers need to up their data game. Vehicles are changing, but the sales model is stuck in neutral.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1354ead36c3a8ed04a5ef33f01c05c22da44f4ae1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1354ead36c3a8ed04a5ef33f01c05c22da44f4ae1.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1354ead36c3a8ed04a5ef33f01c05c22da44f4ae1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Car Workers Inspecting Production Line" src="./media_1354ead36c3a8ed04a5ef33f01c05c22da44f4ae1.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-great-data-driven-auto-distribution-rally">The Great Data-Driven Auto Distribution Rally</h1>
        <p>Vehicles are changing, but the sales model is stuck in neutral. To keep up with customers, automakers need to up their data game.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By Randy Garrison and Chuck Mazurek</p>
  <p>A few of Ford Motor Company’s recent recruits are a good indication of where the legacy auto company is headed. The <a href="https://www.detroitnews.com/story/business/autos/ford/2022/02/10/ford-hires-away-tesla-engineering-director-work-advanced-evs/6739919001/">hirings</a> of former Apple and Tesla execs lay bare the company’s ambition to move away from internal combustion engines (ICEs) and to electric vehicles (EVs) – and even more so, to a technology- and software-focused company. Ford’s head, Jim Farley, says the <a href="https://www.latimes.com/environment/newsletter/2023-09-14/ford-ceo-jim-farley-talks-up-the-companys-ev-future-boiling-point">changes</a> he’s implementing – such as developing a new EV platform for release in 2025 – are “not an EV revolution” but instead are “a digital shift to a digital product.”</p>
  <p>But already in 2024, the company has <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-reduce-f-150-lightning-production-2024-01-19/">cut back production</a> of their flagship electric truck, the <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-reduce-f-150-lightning-production-2024-01-19/">F-150 Lightning</a>, because of lower-than-predicted demand.</p>
  <p>In their cohort of older original equipment manufacturers (OEMs), Ford is far from alone in struggling to remake its business.</p>
  <p>The automotive industry can be divided into two eras: Before Tesla and During Tesla. That’s a reflection of how much has changed in auto-land in the past two decades. Consumer buying habits, vehicles technology, and mobility options – Uber, car sharing, e-bikes – have all changed, and Tesla stands as the leading example of how automaking and marketing are also changing. As a vertically integrated, direct-to-consumer (DTC), native electric company, Tesla is currently the <a href="https://money.usnews.com/investing/articles/the-10-most-valuable-auto-companies-in-the-world">most valuable</a> vehicle manufacturer in the world. Its valuation in 2023 rose to as much as three times that of Toyota – long in the top spot, but now in second place – despite Toyota selling roughly five times as many cars as Tesla in the first half of that year. Farley noted that Ford’s current distribution model costs an estimated $2,000 more per vehicle versus Tesla’s integrated approach, with most of that extra cost attributed to advertising and inventory.</p>
  <p>For traditional automakers, as Ford’s experience shows, keeping up has been a challenge. The fragmentation of every step of the old-school process, including the relationship structure between OEMs and dealers, means siloed systems and data, which hamper automakers’ abilities to adapt and compete.</p>
  <p>Thriving in this new era of electrical vehicles and other modes of transportation requires new ways of making, selling, and servicing cars. Accepting these changes first and foremost means getting a better handle on the data. With that data, they’ll be able to make informed business model choices, streamline production, understand who is buying their product and why, and how it’s being used. Oh, and of course, all of that will add up to making more money. Making these changes won’t be easy, but there are strategies to make it more efficient.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_135e58689f6e6c5e54d774c7463839586a88ae866.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_135e58689f6e6c5e54d774c7463839586a88ae866.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_135e58689f6e6c5e54d774c7463839586a88ae866.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="White, young salesman talking to a middle-aged white couple in a car showroom." src="./media_135e58689f6e6c5e54d774c7463839586a88ae866.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1493" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="stuck-in-neutral">Stuck in neutral</h2>
  <p>In the United States, the traditional dealership system hasn’t changed much over the years from what’s considered to be the <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/30/cars/why-we-buy-cars-this-way/index.html">first-ever dealership in Detroit in 1898</a> to the <a href="https://www.newsweek.com/why-cant-you-buy-car-way-buy-computer-453657">legal morass</a> that exists today. Florida, for example, recently banned DTC sales, but only for legacy automakers; non-dealership brands are allowed. Adherence to this model differs around the world. For example, many Asian countries, such as Malaysia, have long allowed direct sales; Japan sees a mixed model, with OEMs owning varying stakes in dealerships. But for the largest Western brands, changing the established, independent dealer-distribution model has been challenging.</p>
  <p>In the late-2000s, Tesla rolled up with its completely owned DTC sales model, with fixed prices and Tesla-employed sales staff. It’s a streamlined, vertically integrated operation in which Tesla has access to all the data about all their vehicles and customers.</p>
  <p>Other upstarts in the automotive space, such as electric truck pioneer Rivian and China’s fast-growing BYD, are also DTC. DTC auto companies don’t work with independent dealerships, so they don’t have that extra dealership margin on top of the cost. They have stores (Tesla), “hubs” and “spaces” (Rivian), and “studios” (Lucid) – all names for brand-owned places where vehicles are displayed. Plus, they have data.</p>
  <p>“That ownership of the customer experience, it’s the ownership of the customer preferences, the demand profiles, patterns, the market insights,” says Neil Ganguli, senior managing director at U.S.-based FTI Consulting.</p>
  <p>Not that Tesla is without its own challenges and, to be fair, it did start up in a vastly different auto environment in which it was almost the only game in town for a premium EV, points out Steve Young, managing director at UK-based automotive consultancy ICDP. Young says the comparison between old and new isn’t fair. Tesla had a cost advantage because it was spending less money – on advertising, for example, and as much as $35 less per employee hour in labor costs, <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/ford-gm-stellantis-pay-raise-uaw-contract-tesla-labor-costs-2023-10">according to reports</a>. But for years, it also <a href="https://jalopnik.com/tesla-loses-a-lot-of-money-selling-cars-but-makes-it-a-1846768094">lost money</a> on each vehicle sold. Tesla’s competition has increased even as the company added capacity, Young notes, leading to price discounts, lower third- and fourth-quarter 2023 earnings, and a big market capitalization hit. Then there was that end-of-<a href="https://apnews.com/article/tesla-autopilot-recall-driver-monitoring-system-8060508627a34e6af889feca46eb3002">2023 recall</a> of almost all Teslas sold in the U.S. to address autopilot problems.</p>
  <p>Nevertheless, Tesla owns the customer data and, in that vital regard, older companies are playing catch-up. OEMs don’t have the “muscle memory, this is not DNA that they have already,” Ganguli says, whereas the newer automakers have DTC built into their standard operating procedures and are strategizing completely differently. “Their systems, their processes, their governance are wired that way. There is no legacy and changing the mentality and needing new skills,” he says.</p>
  <p>To illustrate the extreme silo-fication conventional OEMs must combat, consider the issue of sales incentives.</p>
  <p>Anyone who’s shopping for wheels is aware of incentives for lease or purchase. Auto companies budget billions of dollars every year for those incentives, which are often stacked (i.e., offered one on top of the other). OEMs lacking full visibility across the sale process may end up selling the car at a loss and not even realize it. And they don’t understand the customer network because they don’t have access to the data about their customers. But the dealerships do.</p>
  <p>OEMs making gas vehicles also have the pressure of <a href="https://electrek.co/2023/10/20/colorado-partially-adopts-californias-ev-rules-but-falls-short-of-2035-ban/">EV deadlines</a> in several states in the United States, in <a href="https://www.canada.ca/en/environment-climate-change/news/2022/12/let-it-roll-government-of-canada-moves-to-increase-the-supply-of-electric-vehicles-for-canadians.html">Canada</a>, and <a href="https://ec.europa.eu/commission/presscorner/detail/en/IP_22_6462">in the EU</a>, where most countries are mandating 100% EV new car sales by 2035. So they’re adopting aggressive changes to transform their businesses into leaner, meaner, greener machines that can compete with Tesla and its DTC kin.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://thedriven.io/2023/05/24/volvo-to-end-uk-dealerships-as-it-transitions-to-tesla-style-sales-model/">Volvo</a> is going all in with a full DTC sales model like Tesla’s, starting in the UK, to be followed by Sweden, then other European countries.</li>
    <li>Volkswagen’s parent company, VW Group, is aiming for major operational changes to <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/11/27/business/volkswagen-brand-no-longer-competitive/index.html">improve competitiveness</a>.</li>
    <li>GM wants to be considered a <a href="https://insideevs.com/news/537914/gm-tech-company-tesla-value/">tech company</a> – a refrain heard from CEO Mary Barra <a href="https://www.detroitnews.com/story/business/autos/general-motors/2018/10/29/ceo-mary-barra-wants-people-think-gm-tech-company/1808690002/">as early as 2018</a> – by providing software platforms and more EV models.</li>
    <li>Ford’s Jim Farley, speaking at a June 2022 strategy conference, also <a href="https://www.thedrive.com/news/ford-ceo-jim-farley-says-direct-sales-no-ads-will-sell-future-evs">said</a>, “We’ve got to go to non-negotiated price. We’ve got to go to 100% online … no inventory, it goes directly to the customer, 100% remote pickup and delivery.”</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Unfortunately, inefficient infrastructure and systems mean they’re driving uphill.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ffa3770f80a6b9f5d5ff739c47bd56ba9c435149.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ffa3770f80a6b9f5d5ff739c47bd56ba9c435149.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ffa3770f80a6b9f5d5ff739c47bd56ba9c435149.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Robotic arms assembling a line of pickup trucks on a production line" src="./media_1ffa3770f80a6b9f5d5ff739c47bd56ba9c435149.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1669" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="tech-in-park">Tech in park</h2>
  <p>Underpinning these business model challenges is a high degree of technical debt. OEMs are relying on decades-old technology systems that are on their last legs – if they’re walking at all.</p>
  <p>“The issue is that the legacy manufacturers have got legacy – it’s in the label,” as Steve Young puts it. Legacy covers a lot of ground in this case: products, production equipment, distribution agreements, and IT systems. “They’ve got existing networks, they’ve got combustion engine product lines still and they need to have them because that’s what’s funding their EV development, and still what consumers want to buy,” says Young.</p>
  <p>And buying trends, changed by e-commerce and accelerated by the pandemic, have meant an increase in the number of car and truck buyers who are fine with doing the entire transaction online. Instead of wandering through a dealer lot to see what’s available, shoppers do their research online, test drive one or two of the best options, then go back online to configure and finalize the sale, notes Peter Wells, professor at Cardiff University’s <a href="https://www.cardiff.ac.uk/research/explore/research-units/centre-for-automotive-industry-research">Centre for Automotive Industry Research</a> (CAIR). “They know what they want; they don’t need to be ‘sold’ in that sense. And I think a lot of U.S. dealerships are still selling,” he says.</p>
  <p>“It’s going to be more and more prevalent that, at least for software-defined vehicles (SDVs), sales are going to be more DTC-oriented," says Ganguli, noting that SDVs are basically computers with wheels, which supports a simpler buying process: the customer chooses a few options and that’s it, because a single car can be customized, and later upgraded, quite easily via software updates. It’s the proverbial win-win: simpler for the customers, much more efficient for the OEMs. <a href="https://www.wardsauto.com/industry-news/wards-intelligence-unveils-automakers-sdv-rankings-tesla-bev-oems-take-lead">According to Wards Auto</a>, the only established automakers that are making a showing in that regard are Mercedes-Benz, Volvo, and BMW. When OEM systems can’t meet customer expectations, or keep up the pace of software development, it leaves the door open for even more competition. Even Amazon is getting in on the act with a recent agreement to sell Hyundai cars through Amazon.com.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1932cc003e34bc28ee14e6c871a54923a072a552d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1932cc003e34bc28ee14e6c871a54923a072a552d.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1932cc003e34bc28ee14e6c871a54923a072a552d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="In a data center full of monitors, a businessman stands before a big screen with an interactive world map on it." src="./media_1932cc003e34bc28ee14e6c871a54923a072a552d.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="racing-to-resiliency">Racing to resiliency</h3>
        <p>Learn how automotive suppliers can drive new growth amid disruption.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/grow/industry/automotive.html">Read more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="driving-modernization">Driving modernization</h2>
  <p>To keep up, automakers must speed up the modernization process, taking better advantage of the data they have while making changes to get their hands on more. They will need to take simultaneous steps in changing internal processes and IT systems, while exploring options for new distribution models. The following are key ideas and options in each of these areas.</p>
  <h2 id="change-strategies">1. Change strategies</h2>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Put change management first</strong></li>
  </ul>
  <p>Auto companies might think modernizing is an IT project, says Steve Young, but that’s the wrong approach: it’s really a gigantic change-management project. Large, outdated legacy systems can’t be changed at the flick of a switch, he says, and neither can the behaviors of thousands of employees across OEMs and dealerships. “To get that degree of data and process integration and the alignment of objectives, the alignment of goals, the lines of thinking, is a huge change-management program,” he says.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Prepare for privacy and the Right to Repair</strong></li>
  </ul>
  <p>“It’s Official: Cars Are the Worst Product Category We Have Ever Reviewed for Privacy,” is the title of a Mozilla Foundation 2023 vehicle <a href="https://foundation.mozilla.org/en/privacynotincluded/articles/its-official-cars-are-the-worst-product-category-we-have-ever-reviewed-for-privacy/">privacy report</a>. There’s a <a href="https://theconversation.com/the-battle-over-right-to-repair-is-a-fight-over-your-cars-data-213052">massive amount of data</a> being brokered back and forth between the vehicle and the OEM, and there are no fully developed <a href="https://jalopnik.com/massachusetts-is-trying-to-protect-data-privacy-in-cars-1850849741">privacy standards</a> applicable to this data yet. OEMs will need to make this issue a priority so changes to systems and dealer models don’t run into roadblocks later on.</p>
  <p>Vehicle data is also part of the conversation <a href="https://www.wired.com/story/fight-right-repair-cars-turns-ugly/">around the Right to Repair Act</a>. Currently, repair data is completely separate from vehicle data, which includes personal info such as driver behavior, subscription choices, and connected cellphone data, along with more general data such as road and weather conditions. Dealers have their own systems to get data, and OEMs have theirs.</p>
  <p>Additionally, vehicle data needs to be available to independent repairers so they can fix a vehicle. In the U.S., if a repairer isn’t sponsored by an OEM or OEM certified (which is expensive for the repair shop), they won’t have that data. In Europe, they have the right to that data, but that doesn’t mean they’re able to get it easily.</p>
  <p>One solution is to create applications that keep personal data and vehicle performance data entirely separate. Then privacy considerations for the former won’t impede upon using the latter for maintenance.</p>
  <h2 id="change-technology">2. Change technology</h2>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>The one-application-at-a-time approach</strong></li>
  </ul>
  <p>This method means building around the exterior of existing technology systems. Companies first identify specific problems, then those problems are separated and updated. That way, particular processes can be modernized without disturbing the integrity of the remaining legacy environment, which can shuffle along until all of it has been replaced or retired.</p>
  <p>This cautious approach results in a long path of interoperability between old and new, but it’s the most cautious approach. On the other hand, it buffers – but doesn’t really reduce – legacy technology. The idea is that it will see itself out eventually.</p>
  <p>Nobody’s doing wholesale revamp, says Ganguli, but they are milking their legacy technology. “[They’re] harvesting it until it’s not needed, and then building this new capability on the back of the new business,” he says.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_165e099889971565f99d9ddc159777d8e374b9df4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_165e099889971565f99d9ddc159777d8e374b9df4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_165e099889971565f99d9ddc159777d8e374b9df4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="A high-level view of a road running through a green field." src="./media_165e099889971565f99d9ddc159777d8e374b9df4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>The greenfield approach</strong></li>
  </ul>
  <p>Another option OEMs can choose is the greenfield approach, which is treating a new plant – for EV batteries or semiconductors, for example – like a startup, where they can build new systems and experiment with new operating models.</p>
  <p>In this way, companies reduce their technical debt not by rewriting old systems, but by gradually making them less of the overall portfolio as new assets come online. Unlike the one-at-a-time approach, integration with older systems is minimized. It’s a gradual approach, but reduces the risk associated with turning off manufacturing lines and systems to do hard switchovers.</p>
  <p>In a variation of this idea, some OEMs are increasingly partnering with specialist companies, not just for automotive parts but for software components and platforms. They won’t own the entire vehicle ecosystem, and farming some of that out is a quicker path to modernizing.</p>
  <p>“They do need to keep a foot in both camps – the ICE world and the EV world – for at least some time to come,” says Young. “I think that the way to handle the ICE world as that declines within their total portfolio is probably more through joint ventures and alliances.”</p>
  <h2 id="explore-dealership-and-distribution-models">3. Explore dealership and distribution models</h2>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Dealers as service centers</strong></li>
  </ul>
  <p>Because of the steady increase in DTC sales, the data roles of the OEM and the dealership will likely be switched. The dealer will be the customer-facing contact, but the OEMs will have the data, which it will share (or not) with their dealer network, says Young.</p>
  <p>Ganguli notes that disruption is inevitable and expects some dealerships will close up shop. There will be a bifurcation, he says; sales and advertising will happen at OEM-owned showrooms, and former dealerships will operate mostly as independent service centers.</p>
  <p>The fee-based agency model – which means a single fixed price and a fixed dealer fee for every car – is gaining some popularity, particularly in Europe. But it also has a data problem, says Young. The OEMs don’t have the skills or relationship with customers to customize deals, he says, so they end up painting with a very broad brush in terms of promotions, incentives, and customer communications. “Everybody gets $5,000 off, but actually half of them would have bought with $1,000 off,” Ganguli offers as an example.</p>
  <p>“Dealership salespeople today are practicing dynamic pricing on a deal-by-deal basis, pitching an offer at the highest [price] level they think the customer will accept.” Under the agency model, OEMs take on that responsibility, but will be challenged to do a better job than the dealers – without the benefit of being face to face, he says.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="racing-into-a-new-world">Racing into a new world</h3>
        <p>Learn how to unlock brand value with mobility services</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/03/962c14d3-687e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Read the whitepaper</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Dealerships-as-a-service</strong></li>
  </ul>
  <p>This isn’t necessarily a bad thing for dealers, however. Consider the EV: compared to the thousands of moving parts in an ICE vehicle, EVs have just a handful. A Tesla car, for example, has about 24 parts – total. While that means less work and money for <em>maintenance</em>, EV <em>repairs</em> could be more expansive and expensive. According to a joint SAP/Reuters report, <em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/na-dealer-of-the-future-reuters-events-report/index.html">The Dealer of the Future</a></em>, almost half a dealer’s revenue already comes from service and parts.</p>
  <p>“This is a case where tighter alignment between OEM and dealer could benefit both. If OEMs can share connected-car data on performance with their dealers, dealers could offer predictive maintenance to their customers before a fault or breakdown occurs,” says the report.</p>
  <p>And, ironically, this is also a case in which old meets new: GM dealers have been <a href="https://jalopnik.com/gm-dealers-have-been-quietly-repairing-teslas-for-over-1849803291">repairing Teslas</a>. If vehicle data is portable, as suggested by the Right to Repair discussion, then dealerships may become less obligated to a single automotive brand and may switch allegiances or add new brands in a fluid manner.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c86737418265e86ad3d450790da5ef3a3f16d6ea.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c86737418265e86ad3d450790da5ef3a3f16d6ea.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1c86737418265e86ad3d450790da5ef3a3f16d6ea.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Illustration of a car in a wind tunnel." src="./media_1c86737418265e86ad3d450790da5ef3a3f16d6ea.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3198" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="driving-into-the-future">Driving into the future</h2>
  <p>How the industry will shake out is very much still to be determined. As car brands plan for the future, sustainability is, of course, a prime consideration. Volkswagen, for example, is aiming for a complete circular strategy, says Peter Wells of CAIR. The company’s goal is to maintain ownership of their cars beyond the first lease term and through the vehicle’s entire lifecycle – from manufacturing through to sales, aftercare, and beyond. At the end of a vehicle’s usefulness, it gets deconstructed – also by Volkswagen.</p>
  <p>“What the Volkswagen Group is currently trying to do is basically own the circle,” says Wells. “They’re trying to control the entire lifecycle of the vehicle. That’s a huge kind of data exercise there because they’ve got to track those vehicles.”</p>
  <p><a href="/resources/digital-twins-at-work">Digital twins</a>, autonomous vehicles, networked roadway infrastructure, even <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Terrafugia">flying vehicles</a> – whatever current or future technologies you can envision, odds are someone is exploring it.</p>
  <p>“The underpinning technologies are changing really fast,” Wells says. “That’s an extra layer of uncertainty on top of the global restructuring that’s going on. And so you have this perfect storm of electrification, digitalization, and global restructuring, and a huge uncertainty as to the future kind of role of the car in our lives.”</p>
  <p>Better collection, use, and sharing of data is the way forward for all automotive companies. The old-school OEMs need to address their data deficiencies to be competitive in this new world. And they need to step on it.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Building the Future Factory: A Special Report]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/building-the-future-factory-a-special-report</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/building-the-future-factory-a-special-report</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Dive beneath the buzzwords to find profitable steps forward for manufacturers, from sustainability to security to supply chain.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e319dcec96d029e6ff75199d1249eaa1b8d4741c.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e319dcec96d029e6ff75199d1249eaa1b8d4741c.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1e319dcec96d029e6ff75199d1249eaa1b8d4741c.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="A factory roof covered with solar photovoltaic panels" src="./media_1e319dcec96d029e6ff75199d1249eaa1b8d4741c.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="building-the-future-factory-a-special-report">Building the Future Factory: A Special Report</h1>
        <p>Dive beneath the buzzwords to find profitable steps forward for manufacturers, from sustainability to security to supply chain.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By Derek Slater</p>
  <p>The factory of the future will be more:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Modular, flexible, and agile</li>
    <li>Efficient and profitable</li>
    <li>Interconnected, both internally and to business partners</li>
    <li>Sustainable, for both its environment and community</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Easy to say, but ever so complicated to do?</p>
  <p>Plenty of companies struggle with the capital investments, workforce requirements, and the data-savvy to build a factory of <em>today</em>, let alone <em>tomorrow</em>.</p>
  <p>Further, to try to decipher future developments is to wade smack into a jungle of jargon and “consultantese,” from industry 4.0 and software-defined factories to analog front ends (AFEs) and 4D printing. (Yes, 4D – that’s not a typo.)<a href=""><sup>1</sup></a></p>
  <p>Nevertheless, business as usual won't cut it. Today's environment of “permacrisis,” as SAP's Richard Howells says in <a href="/resources/supply-chain-innovation-whats-next">an expert panel discussion</a> – wars, pandemic hangover, shipping backups, extreme weather events, energy costs, unstable countries – stresses traditional factories and supply chains to the breaking point. And the planetary reverberations of manufacturing, its by-products, its resources, and energy use, are existential.</p>
  <p>Fortunately, “in manufacturing, sustainability is profitability,” SAP's Mike Lackey notes in the same discussion. Increasing efficiency and agility while decreasing waste <em>will</em> feed the bottom line. In other words, building the future factory is about making goods and making money. And not just in this quarter, but for decades to come.</p>
  <p>Delving into the concrete topics underneath the pie-in-the-sky vision and through the jargon jungle, it's clear that technical progress is happening on all fronts, at a dizzying rate. Forward-looking manufacturers can take advantage of those developments now, to profit despite permacrisis challenges, while building toward tomorrow.</p>
  <p>Here are key takeaways from our special report, with links to further details in nine in-depth articles exploring the future factory. Learn how to make smart workforce and technology investments on the way there, and how to create more value beyond the factory walls in your broader supply chain.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15a56767d95d6e6b71b3c4377faaa4965c6ac597e.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15a56767d95d6e6b71b3c4377faaa4965c6ac597e.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_15a56767d95d6e6b71b3c4377faaa4965c6ac597e.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Two men wearing hardhats and looking at a laptop on the factory floor." src="./media_15a56767d95d6e6b71b3c4377faaa4965c6ac597e.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="the-regenerative-factory">The regenerative factory</h2>
  <p>What might a factory look like in a decade or two? Let's start by looking at <strong>how sustainability will shape tomorrow’s factories</strong>, because sustainability equals profitability, as <a href="/resources/profitable-purpose-the-future-of-business-sustainability">SAP Insights research has confirmed</a>.</p>
  <p>The lead article of our special report, “<a href="/blogs/the-sustainable-factory-of-the-future">The Sustainable Factory of the Future</a>,” sounds a perhaps counterintuitive note: the average factory footprint may be much smaller than today’s.</p>
  <p>For decades, manufacturing has focused on repeatable efficiency at an ever-greater scale. Today’s driving force, on the other hand, is increasingly a demand for more agility: for example, the ability to shift manufacturing from one place to another based on demand, capacity, or disruptive events, as well as the need to produce more customized products, rather than identical widgets. Moving to a smaller form factor also has positive implications for sustainable – or, better, regenerative – operations.</p>
  <p>“The regenerative principle is to return things better than before,” says Stanford researcher Trond Undheim. “The larger the scale, the more steel and carbon you are using, and the more difficult it becomes to disassemble. Regeneration is all about disassembly, leaving no trace, actually leaving it better.”</p>
  <p>It’s not just about disassembly; today’s ongoing operations benefit too. The use of smaller facilities requires greater efficiency, using less space and power. It also suggests multiple, dispersed production points located closer to where the manufactured goods will be used, reducing the financial and environmental costs of delivery.</p>
  <p>Whatever the size and scale, prominent manufacturers such as Interface, Siemens, and Tesla offer strategies for future factories to address all these areas:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Carbon:</strong> Cut emissions faster. Spot issues and prioritize improvements by using Internet of Things (IoT) data. Store (sequester) carbon in products, as well as in the factory itself (in cement and other building materials).</li>
    <li><strong>Waste:</strong> Use analytics to find advanced ways to reduce waste. Additive manufacturing yields less scrap. Reduce raw material use; recycle waste on site; think “circularly” about products through end-of-life.</li>
    <li><strong>Power:</strong> Go beyond solar with renewable sources, low-emissivity windows that reduce heating and cooling costs, green hydrogen power, and improved battery and passive energy-harvesting technology for local power storage.</li>
    <li><strong>Water:</strong> Capture and use rainwater; detect leaks with digital twins; treat and reuse wastewater on-site; use green and blue roofs to reduce or manage runoff.</li>
  </ul>
</div>
<div>
  <h2 id="dive-beneath-the-buzzwords-to-find-profitable-steps-forward-for-manufacturers-from-sustainability-to-security-to-supply-chain">Dive beneath the buzzwords to find profitable steps forward for manufacturers, from sustainability to security to supply chain.</h2>
  <p>Factory</p>
  <ul>
    <li>“<a href="/blogs/the-sustainable-factory-of-the-future">The Sustainable Factory of the Future</a>”</li>
    <li><em><a href="/resources/profitable-purpose-the-future-of-business-sustainability">Profitable Purpose: The Future of Business Sustainability</a></em> – SAP Insights Research</li>
    <li>“<a href="/resources/production-logistics-and-the-new-ot">Production Logistics and the New OT</a>”</li>
    <li>“<a href="/resources/how-industry-4-0-factories-can-still-embrace-the-past">Retrofitting: How Industry 4.0 Factories Can Still Embrace the Past</a>”</li>
    <li>“<a href="/blogs/twelve-security-issues-for-evolving-factories">12 Security Issues to Address as Your Factories Evolve</a>”</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The workforce</p>
  <ul>
    <li>“<a href="/resources/advanced-manufacturing-skills-workers-will-need">Advanced Manufacturing Skills Workers Will Need</a>”</li>
    <li>“<a href="/resources/hunting-for-advanced-manufacturing-talent-four-moves">Four Steps for Hunting for Advanced Manufacturing Talent</a>”</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The supply chain and business networks</p>
  <ul>
    <li>“<a href="/resources/contract-manufacturing-supply-chains-blind-spot">Contract Manufacturing: Supply Chains’ Blind Spot</a>”</li>
    <li>“<a href="/resources/supply-chain-innovation-whats-next">Supply Chain Innovation: What’s Next?</a>”</li>
    <li>“<a href="/blogs/landscape-view-into-value-chain-relationships">A Landscape View into Value Chain Relationships</a>”</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The full manufacturing lifecycle</p>
  <ul>
    <li>“<a href="/resources/circular-path-to-sustainability-for-manufacturers">A Circular Path to Sustainability for Manufacturers</a>”</li>
    <li><em><a href="/research/capacity-capture-a-new-approach-to-discovering-business-value">Capacity Capture: A New Approach to Discovering Business Value</a></em></li>
    <li>– SAP Insights Research</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>Style</div>
      <div>Additional Reading</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1baba0487f6216dd702d52864638cddf23866002b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1baba0487f6216dd702d52864638cddf23866002b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1baba0487f6216dd702d52864638cddf23866002b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Person holding a tablet with performance check screen software, with an automated wireless robot arm in the background" src="./media_1baba0487f6216dd702d52864638cddf23866002b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1803" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="the-smarter-factory">The smart(er) factory</h2>
  <p>Now let’s turn to the <strong>rapid advance of industrial smarts</strong>, which is happening in both the IT arena and in shop floor operating technology (OT).</p>
  <p>Tomorrow’s factory will make those of yesterday, sit in the corner with a dunce cap.</p>
  <p>A raft of technologies are already converging, including both traditional IT elements (cloud computing, edge computing, artificial intelligence, augmented reality, 5G wireless) and new OT devices and capabilities (advanced robots, cobots, autonomous transport, additive manufacturing machines, computer vision). This convergence is what many describe as “<a href="https://www.sap.cn/products/scm/industry-4-0/industry-4-0-strategy.html">industry 4.0</a>” – technologies that make possible “<a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/what-is-a-smart-factory.html">smart factories</a>” with new levels of process automation, greater efficiency and utilization, right-time right-place inventory, and increased safety.</p>
  <p>This much, you already know. And some of the near-term possibilities are easy to envision. Already in 2024, a humanoid-style robot built by Figure.ai learned, reportedly in 10 hours of training time, how to make coffee <a href="https://twitter.com/adcock_brett/status/1743987597301399852">by watching humans do it</a>, then trying, failing, and improving. The distance between that extremely expensive prototype Keurig-butler and a robotic system that learns complex assembly line tasks through computer vision isn’t far.</p>
  <p>But you also know that other, currently unforeseen smart-factory advances will lurk further over the horizon.</p>
  <p>So how to be prepared to assimilate new technology constantly, rather than seeing each wave render current machines or whole factories obsolete? That’s one motivator behind the idea of software-defined factories, where more flexible, programmable shop floor equipment can add features, change configurations, and connect to new systems with software updates rather than hardware swaps.</p>
  <p>However, as “<a href="/resources/production-logistics-and-the-new-ot">Production Logistics and the New OT</a>” find, staying on top of changes in operational advances relies on process and personnel as much as on technology: <strong>The time for meaningful IT/OT collaboration is truly overdue</strong>.</p>
  <p>When these historically siloed teams cooperate effectively, their companies can get better end-to-end visibility of manufacturing processes, machine health, efficient staffing and inventory movement, and much more while building a flexible technical architecture that more readily absorbs change and integrates whatever’s next.</p>
  <p>Companies including Pfizer, Chobani, and Kohl's show ways to cross this long-standing divide:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Involve both functions earlier</strong> in each other’s projects.</li>
    <li><strong>Provide training and exposure</strong> for OT people in IT processes, and vice versa.</li>
    <li><strong>Set up CIOs</strong>, most often from an IT background, as leaders and learners-in-chief – actively diving into OT technology.</li>
    <li><strong>Create leadership development programs</strong> that bring IT and OT people together.</li>
    <li><strong>Address the divide head-on with humor and empathy.</strong> Try an exercise in which each side role plays the other.</li>
    <li>Consider <strong>using cybersecurity as a natural starting point</strong> for tighter IT/OT collaboration (see the next point).</li>
  </ul>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1932cc003e34bc28ee14e6c871a54923a072a552d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1932cc003e34bc28ee14e6c871a54923a072a552d.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1932cc003e34bc28ee14e6c871a54923a072a552d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="In a data center full of monitors, a businessman stands before a big screen with an interactive world map on it." src="./media_1932cc003e34bc28ee14e6c871a54923a072a552d.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="the-secure-factory">The secure factory</h2>
  <p>About <strong>that security thing, in this highly connected factory...</strong></p>
  <p>A shop full of networked, intelligent machines needs to rethink its approach to security. Ransomware attacks knocking over manufacturing operations in the past few years have made this abundantly clear. The so-called attack surface is expanding as more OT comes online and data drives more automated processes.</p>
  <p>In “<a href="/blogs/twelve-security-issues-for-evolving-factories">12 Security Issues to Address as Your Factories Evolve</a>,” our experts list key steps, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Increase visibility.</strong> “Manufacturers will need to clarify the data flows between the IT and OT networks, as well as the assets that bridge this gap – for example, addressing the Internet of Things (IoT), edge computing, and building automation systems.”</li>
    <li><strong>Protect power supplies and building automation systems.</strong> IT/OT security keeps adding more potential targets to defend. Local generation and storage create new challenges for safety, security, and reliability.</li>
    <li><strong>Consider mobile vulnerabilities.</strong> The fast-changing world of autonomous shop floor tools that use new communication protocols that aren't yet well tested for security.</li>
    <li><strong>Raise your threat awareness game.</strong> “Another strong pillar of defense is maintaining knowledge of the common tactics, techniques, and procedures enacted by adversaries and forming an accurate view of your organization’s posture relative to them,” says former chief information security officer Dawn Cappelli.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="converting-the-old-factory-into-a-new-factory">Converting the old factory into a new factory</h2>
  <p>Last but not least: <strong>retrofitting to bring older factories into the game</strong>.</p>
  <p>Elon Musk could scare up €5 billion to build Tesla’s “Gigafactory Berlin” from scratch, chock-full of automation and AI. Maybe your company doesn’t have that kind of money sitting around.</p>
  <p>Does that mean you stay on the sidelines? Do you need billions for a brand-new shop to even get into this smart-factory game? Do old factories <em>really</em> have to sit in the corner wearing a dunce cap?</p>
  <p>Happily, they don’t. “<a href="/resources/how-industry-4-0-factories-can-still-embrace-the-past">How Industry 4.0 Factories Can Still Embrace the Past</a><u>”</u> explains why and how modernization strategies can connect older machines and buildings to modern data-driven manufacturing operations.</p>
  <p>True, it’s not as simple as slapping sensors on everything; collecting terabytes of environmental and performance data doesn’t guarantee you’ll find the right signals needed for predictive maintenance or more efficient materials movement. However, careful analysis of likely areas of improvement, the data types needed, and cost-benefit tradeoffs can lead to targeted investment and big payoff.</p>
  <p>For example:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Shift-by-shift, smart sensor data can provide granular insights to increase throughput.</li>
    <li>Supply chain sensor data can improve the traceability of raw material flow, indicating if a manufacturer is spending unnecessary time sourcing and procuring raw materials.</li>
    <li>Correlating real-time environmental and machine performance data may indeed reveal risks for machine and assembly line downtime.</li>
    <li>Networking and geolocation technologies can help track the movement of materials and goods, spotting inefficiencies, low inventory levels, or misplaced palettes.</li>
    <li>Combining new data sources over time can help build an increasingly valuable digital twin of an older facility and its workflows.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The experience of companies like Spirit AeroSystems and Gary Works provides modernization guidance tips:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Ongoing employee training and assessment is vital.</li>
    <li>IT and OT teams need clear, shared goals (notice a theme here?).</li>
    <li>Top executives have to lead the change management charge.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_182a158f9d99affeb797faa6a70c25ffd02004499.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_182a158f9d99affeb797faa6a70c25ffd02004499.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_182a158f9d99affeb797faa6a70c25ffd02004499.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Four workers in hard hats talking by machinery in a modern factory" src="./media_182a158f9d99affeb797faa6a70c25ffd02004499.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1493" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="the-future-manufacturing-workforce">The future manufacturing workforce</h2>
  <p>New factories require new skills. In “<a href="/resources/advanced-manufacturing-skills-workers-will-need">Advanced Manufacturing Skills Workers Will Need,”</a> experts foresee how common roles will change. For instance:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Production planners</strong> will use predictive analytics to anticipate machine downtime or late-arriving materials; work out solutions, such as predictive machine maintenance or purchasing more materials in advance; and look for continuous improvement ideas to reduce waste.</li>
    <li><strong>Line leaders</strong> will spend less time creating reports and more time coaching and problem solving with their team members.</li>
    <li><strong>Machine operators</strong> will probably have more general training, oversee more machines at once, and work with AI tools for problem solving and light maintenance. They may rely on voice and gestural commands to operate the equipment.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>These changes put a premium on flexibility, continuous learning, and problem-solving skills for all manufacturing employees.</p>
  <p>Finding or creating the workforce for these challenges will involve a mix of strategies, as noted in “<a href="/resources/hunting-for-advanced-manufacturing-talent-four-moves">Four Steps for Hunting for Advanced Manufacturing Talent,”</a> including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Rewriting job descriptions.</strong> You may find help with this from industry associations or other groups. Research Institute AIM Photonics worked with MIT to develop advanced job descriptions specific to the photonics industry.</li>
    <li><strong>Reskilling current employees.</strong> Bosch plans to spend €1 billion over five years to reskill employees in advanced tech areas ranging from AI to electric vehicle engineering, <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/reskilling-employees-is-a-priority-for-companies-like-bosch-2022-3"><em>Business Insider</em> reports</a>.</li>
    <li><strong>Partnering with local educational institutions to expand the talent pool.</strong> In southern China, Guizhou Equipment Manufacturing Vocational College has created new courses covering digital process design, advanced machine tools, and debugging industrial robots. It provides specific retraining for workers in all career stages, including laid off and unemployed persons, as detailed in <a href="https://www.autodesk.com/design-make/articles/upskilling-employees">an Autodesk article</a>.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Refurbishing your workforce and investing in local education is also part of how the future factory provides regenerative benefits to its local community.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="how-manufacturing-adapts-to-disruption">How Manufacturing Adapts to Disruption</h3>
        <p>Learn how manufacturers are becoming more flexible without breaking the bank.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/hunting-for-advanced-manufacturing-talent-four-moves">Read the guide</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="beyond-the-factory--the-future-supply-chain">Beyond the factory – the future supply chain</h2>
  <p>Inevitably, the future factory will connect more directly to more partners – that's the only way to work toward real-time, decision-making, based on demand.</p>
  <p>Your <strong>contract manufacturers (CMs)</strong> may be your closest partners. Yet typically this is an area of limited (i.e., almost zero) visibility in manufacturers’ supply chains. “<a href="https://www.sap.com/insights/viewpoints/contract-manufacturing-supply-chains-blind-spot.html">Contract Manufacturing: Supply Chains’ Blind Spot</a><u>”</u> explains why: it's not fundamentally a tech issue, it's a problem of trust, trust, trust!</p>
  <p>Germany's LkSG law (also known as the Supply Chain Due Diligence Act) demands more visibility into a manufacturer’s supply chain – both EU- and worldwide – to help weed out labor abuse and similar problems. But whether you're solving for compliance or something else, every disruption or change can present a chance to improve supply chain performance too. Example: during the pandemic, Haier Group, based in China, mobilized its supply chain, including CMs, to share information through a homegrown cloud application. Its CM partners reported results, including a reduction in cycle time, reduced procurement costs, and increased customer orders.</p>
  <p>How to improve visibility and collaboration with CMs:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Communicate to partners that regulatory requirements are an opportunity</strong> to improve processes and profits for both OEMs and CMs.</li>
    <li><strong>You go first</strong> in sharing systems and data with your contract manufacturing partners. Show trust to earn trust and provide value to gain value.</li>
    <li><strong>Rework contracts</strong> to formally spell out how the parties will work together in a mutually beneficial way, as opposed to just defining a transactional model. For example, a <em>Harvard Business Review</em> article details a method of contracting that uses a “<a href="https://hbr.org/2022/11/3-ways-to-build-trust-with-your-suppliers">vested sourcing model</a>.”</li>
  </ul>
  <p>With trust improving, improved <strong>supply chain technology</strong> should surely yield better performance – right? But somehow, often, it doesn’t.</p>
  <p>In “<a href="https://www.sap.com/insights/viewpoints/supply-chain-innovation-whats-next.html">Supply Chain Innovation: What’s Next?</a><u>,”</u> three experts explore why roughly eight out of 10 supply chain tech projects fail, and how to flip that ratio.</p>
  <p>Their recommendations include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Innovation benefits from <strong>a digital officer</strong> who can “paint a picture of the possible” to secure investment in pilot projects.</li>
    <li>However, they then have to let go of successful pilots and <strong>hand ownership over to the business.</strong></li>
    <li>Innovators and project leads should <strong>“show return over and over.”</strong></li>
    <li><strong>Get your innovation funding model right.</strong> Pilots are often funded from centralized technology budgets, but then quickly the model should shift to the infrastructure budget plus co-funding from business lines and factories.</li>
    <li><strong>Shared goals</strong> help get the plants to invest.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12c9be569b9e544b90067c1078fcc44a42a41a702.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12c9be569b9e544b90067c1078fcc44a42a41a702.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_12c9be569b9e544b90067c1078fcc44a42a41a702.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Businesspeople having a roundtable discussion" src="./media_12c9be569b9e544b90067c1078fcc44a42a41a702.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="beyond-the-factory--understand-the-value-you-create">Beyond the factory – understand the value you create</h2>
  <p>As we said at the outset – there’s a lot of detail to consider and work through. Here’s a parting idea to help clear the mind and prioritize decisions: <strong>start by reexamining how your company creates value</strong>.</p>
  <p>A factory is one link in a chain, and (ostensibly) the whole chain is designed to deliver something of great value to a customer who really needs it. Consultant Simon Wardley argues that a better understanding of how value is created in, and by, the product should yield smarter business decisions, resulting in better factory design and use.</p>
  <p>Seems obvious? Wardley contends most companies fail at this fundamental level: “My experience has been that organizations are not very strong at understanding users, they’re much poorer at understanding users’ needs, and they can be quite poor at understanding the chain of components required to meet those needs.”</p>
  <p>· He says lack of visibility beyond the next step in the value chain is one culprit.</p>
  <p>· Failure to map your competitive space is another – accounting for change over time, such as a gradual commodification of components.</p>
  <p>Test your future-factory assumptions with Wardley's insights in “<a href="https://www.sap.com/insights/viewpoints/landscape-view-into-value-chain-relationships.html">A Landscape View into Value Chain Relationships</a>.” You’ll gain a fresh outlook on familiar terrain.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>1 Analog front ends are sensors that can capture and digitize multiple types of analog signal. 4D printing creates products that change in response to time or conditions, for example, camouflage clothes that adjust hue or pattern to match their surroundings.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/trends-predictions</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No More Excuses for Irresponsible Use of AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/no-more-excuses-for-irresponsible-use-of-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/no-more-excuses-for-irresponsible-use-of-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how forward-thinking companies are showing the way to create a responsible AI framework]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bff5e2f948387e38673d75344d59bbd2b5ad396c.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bff5e2f948387e38673d75344d59bbd2b5ad396c.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1bff5e2f948387e38673d75344d59bbd2b5ad396c.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="woman studying 2 screens of ai driven dashboards" src="./media_1bff5e2f948387e38673d75344d59bbd2b5ad396c.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="no-more-excuses-for-irresponsible-use-of-ai">No More Excuses for Irresponsible Use of AI</h1>
        <p>When it comes to creating a responsible AI framework, the struggle is real. But forward-thinking companies are showing the way.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By Mathias Cellarius and Cindy Waxer.</p>
  <p>Artificial intelligence has always had equal shares of enthusiasts and detractors. But as AI establishes its place as an important business technology – especially with the rise of generative AI – both fans and naysayers are amping up the volume on questions about its ethical and responsible use.</p>
  <p>“With the increasing use of AI in high-stakes domains, we have witnessed a growing number of incidents and issues negatively impacting consumers,” says Hoda Heidari, the K&#x26;L Gates career development assistant professor in ethics and computational technologies at Carnegie Mellon University.</p>
  <p>Chief among these algorithmic landmines are the risk of perpetuating dangerous societal biases, dissemination of misinformation, and displacement of human beings from the workforce. <a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41599-023-02079-x">A recent study</a> published in <em>Nature,</em> for instance, found the combination of limited raw data sets and biased algorithmic designers can result in discriminatory hiring practices based on gender, race, color, and personality traits.</p>
  <p>Generative AI, in particular, poses the risk of spreading misinformation through error-prone large language models. Case in point: While representing a client in a lawsuit, attorney Steven Schwartz <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/05/27/business/chat-gpt-avianca-mata-lawyers/index.html">used ChatGPT to supplement his legal research</a>. However, at least six of his submitted cases were found to be nonexistent. <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.575368/gov.uscourts.nysd.575368.32.1_1.pdf">In an affidavit</a>, Schwartz said that he “was unaware of the possibility that its content could be false.”</p>
  <p>Meanwhile, A-list actors from Jane Fonda to Susan Sarandon <a href="https://www.castingnetworks.com/news/what-you-need-to-know-about-the-new-sag-aftra-agreement-artificial-intelligence/?utm_campaign=daily_roundup&#x26;utm_source=braze&#x26;utm_medium=email&#x26;utm_content=story_1">took to the picket lines</a> in July 2023 to call attention to key issues, including the degree to which Hollywood’s movie studios should be allowed to use the likeness of living actors in perpetuity, essentially using AI to replace actors entirely. In the end, the SAG-AFTRA national board voted to approve a new contract that includes guardrails against AI.</p>
  <p>High-profile events such as these have sparked “a newfound interest in responsible and ethical use of AI,” according to Heidari. In fact, as innovative use cases for AI multiply, on average, only one in two people believe the benefits of AI outweigh the risks, and three out of five people (61%) are wary about trusting AI systems, according to KPMG’s 2023 Trust in Artificial Intelligence <a href="https://assets.kpmg.com/content/dam/kpmg/au/pdf/2023/trust-in-ai-global-insights-2023.pdf">global study</a>.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1218ff1884ab5de1ab93c35907b396a5a3d3d04ac.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1218ff1884ab5de1ab93c35907b396a5a3d3d04ac.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1218ff1884ab5de1ab93c35907b396a5a3d3d04ac.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Close-up of clicking on computer screen" src="./media_1218ff1884ab5de1ab93c35907b396a5a3d3d04ac.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="ai-accountability-lies-with-ai-implementors">AI accountability lies with AI implementors</h2>
  <p>When it comes to who would be held accountable for both safeguarding the use of AI and dealing with its potential negative consequences, most fingers point in one direction: the businesses who choose to use it. In addition to existing or planned regulatory actions by the European Union, China, and the United States that subject AI to greater oversight, consumers also say it’s businesses themselves that need to mitigate AI risk. In <a href="https://www.accenture.com/us-en/services/applied-intelligence/ai-ethics-governance#:~:text=In%20fact%2C%20Accenture%27s%202022%20Tech,The%20pressure%20is%20on.">research conducted by Accenture</a>, 77% of global consumers think organizations should be held accountable for AI misuse.</p>
  <p>According to Ramayya Krishnan, a dean and professor of management science and information systems at Heinz College and a professor in the department of engineering and public policy at Carnegie Mellon University, “Responsible AI is about being transparent, being ethical in terms of what data will be used, and how it will be used and for what purpose.” Yet, he says, there are big challenges that require organizations to adopt tools in order to “move from policy to practice” when it comes to achieving responsible AI.</p>
  <p>And it shows. <a href="https://web-assets.bcg.com/37/87/33f2ee9d4e2281e792472f4ec1bf/to-be-a-responsible-ai-leader-focus-on-being-responsible.pdf">A study by Boston Consulting Group and MIT Sloan Management Review</a> finds that, although 84% of executives say that responsible AI (RAI) should be a top management priority, just 16% of companies have fully mature RAI programs. One explanation for this gap between aspiration and action, says Heidari, is the “layer of opacity” that can surround AI – a highly specialized technology that consumes vast volumes of data and utilizes complex statistical modeling techniques, such as deep learning, to produce capabilities including natural language processes and computer vision.</p>
  <p>“When even experts don’t fully understand the capabilities and limitations of the technology they’ve created or are using, it can be very challenging to foresee all that could go wrong when it is deployed in the real world,” she says.</p>
  <p>Despite these challenges, top organizations are moving forward with creating responsible AI governance structures and policies to help them make more informed decisions about how and where to use AI while minimizing its inherent risks – and thus avoiding reputational damage, employee backlash, or legal liabilities.</p>
  <p>A close look at these frameworks reveals five action items for any business striving to institute responsible AI: casting a wide net for stakeholder input, instituting strong leadership of the framework, creating and abiding by consistent metrics, ensuring transparency, and knowing where humans need to be kept in the loop.</p>
  <p>"When even experts don’t fully understand the capabilities and limitations of the technology they’ve created or are using, it can be very challenging to foresee all that could go wrong when it is deployed in the real world."</p>
  <p><em>- Hoda Heidari, Carnegie Mellon University</em></p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a670053ffcc2050c2bcf78c36704ee314c487633.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a670053ffcc2050c2bcf78c36704ee314c487633.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1a670053ffcc2050c2bcf78c36704ee314c487633.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Business people having meeting in board room" src="./media_1a670053ffcc2050c2bcf78c36704ee314c487633.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="gather-a-wide-range-of-input-including-diverging-views">#1: Gather a wide range of input, including diverging views</h2>
  <p>Although managing technology typically falls under the purview of IT, when it comes to responsible AI, “everybody in the organization has some responsibility,” Heidari says. “It takes, without a doubt, a multi-layer, multi-stakeholder approach to create and use AI responsibly.”</p>
  <p>For this reason, organizations would be wise to take a page from Carnegie Mellon University’s (CMU) <a href="https://www.cmu.edu/block-center/responsible-ai/cmu_blockcenter_rai-memo_final.pdf">responsible AI framework</a>. Created for the U.S. government, many of the framework’s recommendations apply to corporations, including the need for meaningful involvement from a wider set of stakeholders in the design, evaluation, and deployment of AI systems. By bringing these people together, organizations can account for new risks, ensure benefits are realized for key stakeholders, and devise an accountability framework.</p>
  <p>According to CMU’s policy brief on responsible AI, a key benefit of involving stakeholders with different domain expertise is that doing so can bridge the divide between those who design and deploy AI models and those who use them. By bringing AI makers together with AI users, businesses can build trust and ensure their AI systems satisfy real-world needs and risks. Multiple stakeholders should also weigh in on the objectives of the AI system, and monitor its development and behavior to ensure it continues to align with the goals of the business.</p>
  <p>A crucial way to invite a wide array of input is to create clear processes for employees and/or consumers to express their concerns if they feel there is an issue with an AI model, such as bias, without fear of repudiation. For example, through its AI4People initiative – aimed at creating “a good AI society” – think tank Atomium-European Institute for Science, Media, and Democracy recommends establishing “a redress process or mechanism to remedy or compensate for a wrong or grievance caused by AI.” This channel should be widely accessible and equip consumers, employees, or any stakeholder to report any damage done by an AI system, and determine accountability for grievances.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e3ad738323e29ca2256c835a1c36616cbff43c23.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e3ad738323e29ca2256c835a1c36616cbff43c23.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1e3ad738323e29ca2256c835a1c36616cbff43c23.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Woman standing in front of group discussing next steps." src="./media_1e3ad738323e29ca2256c835a1c36616cbff43c23.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="create-a-multi-layered-governance-mechanism-supported-by-strong-leadership">#2: Create a multi-layered governance mechanism, supported by strong leadership</h2>
  <p>Responsible AI should not be a stand-alone operation in an organization. “If there is a specific function within an organization, like an AI ethicist or ethics team, it’s often sitting in a vacuum from the rest of the organization,” says Merve Hickok, founder of AIethicist.org and a trainer and consultant on responsible development, use, and governance of AI. The problem with this organizational structure, she says, is, “the attitude becomes, ‘We already have an AI ethics team so it’s not our problem; they’re responsible for finding issues.’ There ends up being a lot of finger-pointing.”</p>
  <p>Instead, Hickok says responsible AI “needs to start with senior management – you need responsibility and accountability. You need effective oversight and governance mechanisms.”</p>
</div>
<div>
  <h2 id="perspectives-on-artificial-intelligence">Perspectives on Artificial Intelligence</h2>
  <p>Stay ahead of Artificial Intelligence in an increasingly automated world and discover how it can affect the future of business. <a href="https://www.sap.com/insights/ai.html">Find out more</a> from SAP Insights.</p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>Style</div>
      <div>Additional Reading</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p>To that end, SAP has instituted a three-layered approach for governing AI ethics within the company. The AI Ethics Steering Committee consists of senior leaders from different areas of the company. They are responsible for enforcing the company’s guiding principles and assessing high-risk use cases. Then, the AI Ethics Advisory Panel involves external experts who provide input on the guiding principles and regularly advise on their operationalization. Lastly, the Trustworthy AI Workstream is a group of interested employees who want to engage with trustworthy AI and build expertise. They create the means to implement the necessary processes for ensuring compliance of SAP’s AI development.</p>
  <p>The leadership team, meanwhile, should consist of people from a variety of functions, such as a chief AI officer, chief data officer, chief privacy officer, chief diversity and inclusion officer, or chief information officer. “You need to have capacity and expertise within the organization that spans technology and also understands and appreciates the business processes that are being reimagined or enabled with AI,” says Carnegie Mellon’s Krishnan.</p>
  <p>By involving multiple people from the C-suite, businesses can ensure they’ve covered the many areas of risk. For example, <a href="https://www.pwc.com/us/en/tech-effect/ai-analytics/managing-generative-ai-risks.html">as PwC points out</a>, a chief information security officer can protect an AI solution’s model, data, and content from threat actors. A chief privacy officer or a chief diversity and inclusion officer, on the other hand, can help an organization balance the rights and interests of potentially affected human beings.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fe5723c7cb511e79201941f4108481c2fd64135d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fe5723c7cb511e79201941f4108481c2fd64135d.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1fe5723c7cb511e79201941f4108481c2fd64135d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Businessman Checking Data" src="./media_1fe5723c7cb511e79201941f4108481c2fd64135d.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="establish-clear-and-consistent-metrics">#3: Establish clear and consistent metrics</h2>
  <p>The best way to assess the trustworthiness of AI products and services is to establish objective metrics that enable ongoing monitoring and measurement. As the AI4People initiative points out, such metrics would allow stakeholders to compare AI offerings in the marketplace, forming the foundation for a “trust comparison index” for AI.</p>
  <p>These metrics could include accuracy and reliability measurements of the AI model’s output, fairness metrics for determining impartiality and a lack of bias, and transparency and explainability metrics for justifying an AI model’s recommendations or decision-making.</p>
  <p>But the reality is, not all risks are equal for all companies. “Risk metrics or methodologies used by the organization developing the AI system may not align with the risk metrics or methodologies used by the organization deploying or operating the system,” reads a report entitled, “Artificial Intelligence Risk Management Framework,” published by the U.S. Department of Commerce’s National Institute of Standards and Technology.</p>
  <p>Rather than simply adopting a standard set of metrics that may not apply to the organization’s AI mandate, CMU’s proposed framework for responsible AI suggests a multi-pronged approach. Businesses should set clear expectations of performance of the AI system, develop “metrics for reliability and utility,” and ensure “continuous monitoring of standards based on the assessed risk of the application space or use case.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="ai-ethics-and-society">AI Ethics and Society</h3>
        <p>SAP’s Guiding Principles for Artificial Intelligence (AI)</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-ethics.html">Read more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="make-ai-transparent-and-explainable">#4: Make AI transparent and explainable</h2>
  <p>To trust AI, stakeholders need to understand how an AI model arrives at a particular decision and be able to determine whether that decision is accurate or not. At least <a href="https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/10447318.2023.2221605">that’s the finding of researchers</a> from Austria’s Johannes Kepler University in Linz, which had study participants play a virtual mushroom hunting game while walking through a highly immersive artificial indoor forest.</p>
  <p>Subjects were asked to pick edible mushrooms and leave the poisonous mushrooms behind. An AI app analyzed photos of the mushrooms and recommended classifications. One group saw the AI’s decisions only, while a second group also received visual explanations of the AI’s recommendation.</p>
  <p>The results: participants who received visual explanations outperformed those who didn’t receive explanatory evidence. In other words, visual explanations of how the AI determined which mushrooms were delicious – and which were lethal – significantly improved participants’ trust levels.</p>
  <p>But not all AI models are designed for mushroom picking, and oftentimes outputs can’t be fully explained. For the public to trust AI, Krishnan says transparency must exist “at each layer of the AI pipeline.” This means vetting the data fed to a model, as well as the accuracy and reliability of a model’s data output so there are “assurances that due diligence was exercised in the deployment of an AI application.”</p>
  <p>For the public to trust AI, Krishnan says transparency must exist “at each layer of the AI pipeline.” This means vetting the data fed to a model, as well as the accuracy and reliability of a model’s data output so there are “assurances that due diligence was exercised in the deployment of an AI application.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1071cbdcce8f416635d346d3e6b31b95bfc2906e2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1071cbdcce8f416635d346d3e6b31b95bfc2906e2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1071cbdcce8f416635d346d3e6b31b95bfc2906e2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="woman engineer looking at various information in screen of futuristic interface." src="./media_1071cbdcce8f416635d346d3e6b31b95bfc2906e2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1680" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="recognize-the-role-humans-play-in-responsible-ai">#5: Recognize the role humans play in responsible AI</h2>
  <p>Policies, governance structures, frameworks – these can all help organizations make more informed decisions about how to use AI responsibly and ethically. However, warns Krishnan, “When we talk about a responsible AI system, it’s not just about the AI. It’s about AI plus humans, plus the processes that come together to create the system.”</p>
  <p>After all, he adds, humans are not powerless to the AI models they design and deploy. For instance, if a hiring manager suspects that an AI-fueled human resources management system is inherently biased, he could “override the AI” and “refuse to accept its recommendation.”</p>
  <p>Humans also play a key role in ensuring the ongoing use of transparent and explainable algorithms, unbiased data, and compliance with ethical guidelines. Without this human oversight, a responsible AI framework is nothing more than a guideline.</p>
  <h2 id="real-world-impact-of-responsible-ai">Real-world impact of responsible AI</h2>
  <p>By establishing programs and policies for responsible use of AI, organizations can minimize risks, such as a damaged reputation, angry customers, frustrated employees, and government fines. But there’s also a flipside: Responsible AI can also drive business growth by building trust with stakeholders, enhancing brand reputation, improving accurate and speedy decision-making, and fostering a culture of innovation. After all, with business investment in AI growing at a rapid clip, responsible AI is no longer an aspirational goal but rather a corporate must-do.</p>
  <p>“If you’re an organization who is interested in improving the quality of your products, ensuring the sustainability of your organization, the loyalty of your customers, your market share, and leadership within the industry, then responsible AI is a key issue,” AIethicist.org’s Hickok says. “It can have a direct impact on your bottom line, on how you’re treating your customers, and how they perceive your company.”</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/responsible-ai</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Production Logistics and the New OT]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/production-logistics-and-the-new-ot</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/production-logistics-and-the-new-ot</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Orchestrate your production and supply chain to deliver next-level customer experiences by merging IT and OT functions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Measuring Social Impact – the S in ESG]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/measuring-social-impact-s-in-esg</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/measuring-social-impact-s-in-esg</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Defining terms, setting scope, tracking regulations – it’s messy. Here’s how to start measuring and managing social impact.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/environmental-compliance</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Manage Social Factors Like Other Governance Risks]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/manage-social-factors-like-other-governance-risks</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/manage-social-factors-like-other-governance-risks</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Unsafe factories and other social factors can fast become a liability. Learn how to put the issue on the board’s agenda.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/environmental-compliance</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Manufacturers Meet the Scalability Moment]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-manufacturers-meet-the-scalability-moment</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-manufacturers-meet-the-scalability-moment</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Enable fast pivots by investing in workers, deploying smart factory tech, and rethinking processes.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a5446ed7a5a187d3aaeec79265fc8f339e83a95d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a5446ed7a5a187d3aaeec79265fc8f339e83a95d.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1a5446ed7a5a187d3aaeec79265fc8f339e83a95d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Two employees checking inventory beside tall racks of boxes in a distribution warehouse." src="./media_1a5446ed7a5a187d3aaeec79265fc8f339e83a95d.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-manufacturers-meet-the-scalability-moment">How Manufacturers Meet the Scalability Moment</h1>
        <p>To enable fast pivots, product makers are investing in workers, deploying smart factory tech, and rethinking processes.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By Cindy Waxer</p>
  <p>Their circumstances vary, but each of these manufacturers achieved something crucial: the ability to react to changes in customer demand, changes to their operating conditions, even to a nation’s urgent call.</p>
  <p>German agricultural machinery manufacturer Fendt needed to meet rising consumer demand for larger and more powerful tractors. After a devastating earthquake and tsunami, automaker Toyota reimagined its supply chain. And a global pandemic prompted the United Kingdom’s Royal Mint to produce medical visors to protect the lives of frontline healthcare workers.</p>
  <p>These enterprises shared a common goal: scalability. Today’s manufacturers must be prepared to scale up – or down – to respond to market disruptions and take advantage of unexpected opportunities.</p>
  <p>Scalability involves streamlining production processes, optimizing the use of resources, and increasing capacity to handle varying volumes of work as needed. Today, advances in technology are upending entire product categories, challenging manufacturers to increase or decrease the volume of parts, subsystems, or products they make.</p>
  <p>Consider, for example, the explosive growth in demand for electronic vehicles and its effect on the auto industry. According to the 2023 edition of the International Energy Agency’s Global Electric Vehicle Outlook <a href="https://www.iea.org/news/demand-for-electric-cars-is-booming-with-sales-expected-to-leap-35-this-year-after-a-record-breaking-2022">report</a>, more than 10 million electric cars were sold worldwide in 2022. Sales are expected to grow by another 35% in 2023 to 14 million, amounting to 18% of the overall car market. In response, manufacturers like Audi, General Motors, and Ford Motor Company are retrofitting factories and overhauling production processes to assemble electric vehicles.</p>
  <p>Achieving greater degrees of scalability in manufacturing processes remains a stiff challenge. It’s like tasking a battleship to learn a new dance step, with workers doing new moves, machinery that can adjust to new inputs, and business processes that coordinate all of the above. It’s a large set of challenges that takes planning and investment.</p>
  <p>To tackle them, manufacturers are exploring innovative ways to reach greater degrees of scalability while managing costs. Strategies include investing in workers’ skills, capitalizing on smart manufacturing technologies, rethinking existing business processes, and factoring variability into manufacturing processes. Read on for more information about how manufacturers can improve their scalability.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aec77bd99a3b9e11aae994f99827ee391b381b5b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aec77bd99a3b9e11aae994f99827ee391b381b5b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1aec77bd99a3b9e11aae994f99827ee391b381b5b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Group of employees working around a transparent whiteboard with Post-it notes." src="./media_1aec77bd99a3b9e11aae994f99827ee391b381b5b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1680" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="invest-in-a-talented-workforce">Invest in a talented workforce.</h2>
  <p>In 2023, manufacturers face a problem of finding enough of the right people to work in their plants. In the United States, 74.4% of respondents to a National Association of Manufacturers <a href="https://www.nam.org/2023-second-quarter-manufacturers-outlook-survey/">survey</a> in the second quarter of 2023 said the top challenge facing manufacturers is attracting and retaining a quality workforce. Why? Working in today’s factories requires technology expertise in everything from knowing how to make a 3D-printed part to configuring sensors for proper data collection to allow sharing of data among people and machines.</p>
  <p>In response, manufacturers are investing in training and relationships. German automaker Audi has established a <a href="https://www.audi.com/en/company/profile/company-management/xavier-ros-hernandez/interview-ros-report-2022.html">training budget</a> of close to 500 million euros to prepare its staff for making electric vehicles at all of its production sites worldwide by 2025. U.S.-based food manufacturer General Mills is among a number of companies looking to hire retirees to help, the <em>Wall Street Journal</em> <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/food-companies-to-ex-employees-come-back-please-6498e88d">reported</a>. So is American defense missile maker Raytheon, <a href="https://www.defenseone.com/business/2023/06/raytheon-calls-retirees-help-restart-stinger-missile-production/388067/">reported</a> Defense One.</p>
  <p>It will take these types of commitments to build a workforce that can drive manufacturers’ scalability.</p>
  <p>Relying on its workforce is a key element in the UK Royal Mint’s shift to producing medical products. In a matter of days, the Mint began <a href="https://www.royalmint.com/stories/currency/the-royal-mint-to-manufacture-medical-visors-for-the-nhs-heroes/">mass manufacturing</a> medical visors for the UK National Health Service in response to the COVID-19 pandemic.</p>
  <p>“The Royal Mint, which normally makes billions of coins every year, pivoted overnight,” says Daniel Eyers, a lecturer in manufacturing systems management at Cardiff University in Cardiff, Wales. “They began making COVID visors because they could exploit flexibility within their workforce and within their processes. They completely changed the scale of their operation.”</p>
</div>
<div>
  <h2 id="skilled-workers-wanted">Skilled Workers Wanted</h2>
  <p>Read more at SAP Insights about how manufacturers can find the people they need to make their factories succeed.</p>
  <p><a href="/resources/hunting-for-advanced-manufacturing-talent-four-moves">Hunting for Advanced Manufacturing Talent: 4 Moves</a>. Companies can start with modernizing job listings and updating training. Also: consider remote roles.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/insights/viewpoints/advanced-manufacturing-skills-workers-will-need.html">Advanced Manufacturing Skills Workers Will Need</a>: Factories deploying more AI, digital twins, and robotics will value problem-solving, design thinking, coding, and creativity.</p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>Style</div>
      <div>Additional Reading</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <h2 id="capitalize-on-smart-manufacturing-technologies">Capitalize on smart manufacturing technologies.</h2>
  <p>Fluctuations in product demand require manufacturers to adjust their production volumes quickly. In <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/what-is-a-smart-factory.html">smart manufacturing</a>, factory operators analyze data from equipment sensors and automate production systems. Practitioners incorporate data from inventory warehouses and supply chain partners to coordinate the flow of materials.</p>
  <p>Smart manufacturing enables scalability by, for example, mitigating the risk of production disruptions. Unanticipated equipment failures prompted by sudden changes can cause significant production delays and product quality problems. Smart factory systems can generate insights that provide manufacturers “with a better understanding of what’s going on throughout their operations,” says Eyers. Smart sensors affixed to critical equipment and facilities provide real-time feedback on everything from the quality of parts being manufactured to potential equipment failures that could inhibit scalability.</p>
  <p>All data is not created equal, however. Eyers notes that manufacturers must be mindful that they are viewing the right quality data to glean useful information from sensors and other data-generating devices. “Some of the danger around smart manufacturing is that it gives us too much data and not enough information,” he says. It’s important that “individual manufacturing operations teams know what they’re looking for” before delving into the data, Eyers adds.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16a0c40a02a60fd4bb0c417d82b2e23d6b17c3949.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16a0c40a02a60fd4bb0c417d82b2e23d6b17c3949.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_16a0c40a02a60fd4bb0c417d82b2e23d6b17c3949.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Two female engineers discussing technology." src="./media_16a0c40a02a60fd4bb0c417d82b2e23d6b17c3949.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="reevaluate-existing-business-processes">Reevaluate existing business processes.</h2>
  <p>Another way manufacturers can overhaul their manufacturing processes for greater scalability is by adopting dynamic production planning. Static product planning assumes that the steps in a production process are set and not subject to change. Dynamic product planning, on the other hand, assumes that these processes will change, from how raw materials are received to the physical space where products are manufactured. Accounting for these unanticipated shifts in the planning stages, before manufacturing begins, can allow for greater supply chain flexibility and ease of production flows.</p>
  <p>The impetus for pursuing scalability can vary, too. While some events, like COVID-19, force organizations to scale temporarily, others call for a more permanent shift. Toyota’s wake-up call came in March 2011 in the form of a magnitude 9 earthquake. At the time, Toyota built 45% of its vehicles in Japan. So when a deadly earthquake and tsunami forced the automobile manufacturer to close its Japanese plants for nearly two months, it knew it had to react. A key decision was to create uniform parts, no matter where they were produced.</p>
  <p>“When it was hit by earthquakes in Japan, Toyota realized that it needed to standardize its products around the world so that it could have some slack and actually produce parts in other regions in the world,” says Arnd Huchzermeier, a professor at the WHU – Otto Beisheim School of Management in Germany.</p>
  <p>To accomplish this feat, Toyota began by standardizing parts across Japanese automakers so that common components could be shared and manufactured in several locations, as Reuters <a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-toyota/toyota-aims-for-quake-proof-supply-chain-idUSTRE7852RF20110906">reported</a> at the time. In the case of specialized parts that could not be built in multiple locations, Toyota worked with suppliers further down the supply chain to build redundant inventory that could be easily accessed in the event of another earthquake or natural disaster.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17517b7bab52c0a4989f6ed7d7b6305b2026bf686.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17517b7bab52c0a4989f6ed7d7b6305b2026bf686.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_17517b7bab52c0a4989f6ed7d7b6305b2026bf686.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Group of employees working on processes in an office space." src="./media_17517b7bab52c0a4989f6ed7d7b6305b2026bf686.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>"When it was hit by earthquakes in Japan, Toyota realized that it needed to standardize its products around the world so that it could have some slack and actually produce parts in other regions in the world."</p>
  <p><em>– Arnd Huchzermeier, professor, WHU – Otto Beisheim School of Management.</em></p>
  <p>In fact, according to Huchzermeier, “there’s a really big drive toward product and process standardization as manufacturers look to shift inventories around the world. If a pandemic hits in Mexico and you can’t manufacture a product, you can produce it in other regions.”</p>
  <p>The Toyota case is important because it highlights the efforts made by a company known for its lean manufacturing practices that seek to reduce waste while increasing productivity. Many manufacturers have relied on lean approaches for their production systems. But while lean manufacturing’s standardized work processes and procedures can contain costs, it can also “limit manufacturers in what they can offer” by preventing them from easily adding or changing product lines, warns Huchzermeier.</p>
  <p>Another tool in helping manufacturers adjust is 3D printing, also known as additive manufacturing. The technology can benefit a manufacturer’s scalability by quickly producing parts or components of a product using computer-aided designs.</p>
  <p>Because not all manufacturers are using 3D machines to increase internal capacity, it’s another opportunity to tap into supplier networks to scale up or down as parts are needed.</p>
  <p>Eyers says many manufacturers are choosing to tap into a global network of partners with additive manufacturing capabilities.</p>
  <p>“If I have an additive manufacturing machine and it’s full, or I need extra capacity, I can outsource that to a worldwide network of additive manufacturing machines,” he says. “These machines are general purpose. What I can print in the UK, I can print on a machine in Europe or the U.S. I can outsource demand so scaling up is quite easy.”</p>
  <p>Amnovis, for example, is a Belgium-based additive manufacturing production and engineering company that uses additive manufacturing to produce high-end medical devices for its partners. Medical device firm CairnSurgical recently partnered with Amnovis to 3D print a product designed to help surgeons accurately locate and remove cancerous breast tumors during lumpectomies, the 3D Printing Industry publication <a href="https://3dprintingindustry.com/news/amnovis-fda-master-file-simplifies-regulatory-submission-process-for-3d-printed-titanium-medical-implants-223416/">reported</a>.</p>
</div>
<div>
  <h2 id="takeaways-for-factory-leaders">Takeaways for Factory Leaders</h2>
  <p>Learn more about manufacturing trends and to-dos at SAP Insights.</p>
  <p><a href="/resources/the-future-of-manufacturing-business-models">How Manufacturing Adapts to Disruption</a>. Learn how manufacturers are adapting to be more flexible and greener without breaking the bank.</p>
  <p><a href="/resources/new-era-of-demand-planning">The New Era of Demand Planning</a>. Sensing and responding to fast-changing demand signals require analyzing more data – and more recent data.</p>
  <p><a href="/blogs/thinking-long-and-wide-horizon-scanning">The Value of Horizon Scanning</a>. Horizon scanning lets leaders evaluate fast-moving changes and risks of outlier events to prepare for their potential impact.</p>
  <p><a href="/resources/5-supply-chain-truths-post-covid-19-world">5 Supply Chain Truths for a Post-COVID-19 World</a>. New rules that prioritize risk are bringing big changes to traditionally long, lean, and low-cost global supply chains.</p>
  <p><a href="/blogs/augmented-reality-goes-to-work-on-the-factory-floor">Augmented Reality Goes to Work on the Factory Floor</a>. Augmented reality is helping manufacturing workers conduct assembly, repairs, and service quicker and more accurately.</p>
  <p><a href="/resources/how-digital-twins-are-driving-the-future-of-business">How Digital Twins Are Driving the Future of Business</a>. The uses for digital twins are expanding to improve factory processes and to offer predictive maintenance applications.</p>
  <p><a href="/blogs/the-sustainable-factory-of-the-future">The Sustainable Factory of the Future</a>. By seizing innovations in engineering and design, manufacturers can turn factories into forces of environmental repair.</p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>Style</div>
      <div>Additional Reading</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <h2 id="deploy-digital-twins-to-plan-production-and-pinpoint-areas-for-improvement">Deploy <a href="/resources/how-digital-twins-are-driving-the-future-of-business">digital twins</a> to plan production and pinpoint areas for improvement.</h2>
  <p>Consumers today expect some degree of personalization in the products they purchase. But satisfying these demands can place enormous pressure on assembly systems – and increase the need for scalability.</p>
  <p>“The challenge,” says Huchzermeier, “is if you have lots of different products that are highly customized, you must perform different tasks on different products all the time, which is highly demanding on workers and can create huge spikes in workloads.”</p>
  <p>Huchzermeier says digital twin technology can help manufacturers scale production up or down quickly to gain mass personalization in manufacturing. A digital twin works by serving as a virtual model of a physical product, process, or system. By mimicking the various aspects of the manufacturing process, including design, testing, and performance, in such accurate detail, a digital twin can identify areas where production should be increased or decreased to handle spikes in workloads. A digital twin can also flag areas where production processes can be improved. For example, manufacturers can run experiments on changing the sequence of products that go down the assembly line, making small adjustments that can create a less stressful sequence of tasks for workers.</p>
  <h2 id="factor-variability-into-manufacturing-processes">Factor variability into manufacturing processes.</h2>
  <p>Beyond virtual models and 3D printing machines, Huchzermeier says, “companies can’t have scalable manufacturing unless they pay attention to how they organize work.”</p>
  <p>It’s a lesson learned by Fendt at a time when the agricultural machinery manufacturer was facing greater customer demand for tractors of larger size and with more horsepower. Like many manufacturers, Fendt relied on a <em>fixed takt</em> or <em>fixed pulse</em> method to manufacturing in which changes in a product portfolio require rebalancing an assembly line and modifying product sequences – a detailed scheduling process that manufacturers use to order the production of purchase orders based on customer demand.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10842ce1cd88e51fe7387f770d3011b7c3899aec6.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10842ce1cd88e51fe7387f770d3011b7c3899aec6.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_10842ce1cd88e51fe7387f770d3011b7c3899aec6.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Worker at control panel operating machinery in factory." src="./media_10842ce1cd88e51fe7387f770d3011b7c3899aec6.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="by-adopting-a-scalable-method-to-manufacturing-fendt-can-assemble-all-10-of-its-product-series-on-a-single-assembly-line">By adopting a scalable method to manufacturing, Fendt can assemble all 10 of its product series on a single assembly line.</h2>
  <p>But these workarounds can be costly and lead to delays in production. In response, Fendt chose to abandon its fixed takt method and instead, <a href="https://www.farmprogress.com/farming-equipment/new-fendt-500-vario-tractor-born-from-state-of-the-art-manufacturing-facility">introduced</a> its VarioTakt system in its 900,000- square-foot tractor plant in Marktoberdorf, Germany.</p>
  <p>In a case study <a href="https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/epdf/10.1287/ited.2019.0224ca">published</a> by the Institute for Operations Research and the Management Sciences, Huchzermeier describes Fendt’s VarioTakt method, in which products are put onto the assembly line at varying rates rather than fixed rates. This not only allows the manufacturer to fulfill individualized customer requests, but also “mostly eliminates such labor inefficiencies as idle time and utility work” and reduces “the complexity of production planning – in particular, assembly line balancing and sequencing.”</p>
  <p>By adopting this scalable method to manufacturing, Fendt can assemble all 10 of its product series on a single assembly line. For example, Fendt’s 1000 Vario, one of its largest tractors on the market, is now assembled with its smallest tractor on the same assembly line – despite a 738% difference in horsepower.</p>
  <p>Refining existing operations to gain greater scalability takes planning and investment. That’s the plan Audi <a href="https://www.audi-mediacenter.com/en/press-releases/audi-presents-plan-for-the-production-of-the-future-15135">unveiled</a> in 2022: converting its entire network of global production factories and phasing out production of its combustion models by 2033. The German luxury automaker opted to invest in its existing plants rather than build new “production sites or greenfield plants” to accommodate its production needs. (This is in addition to the commitment to train its workforce.)</p>
  <p>To ensure the premium manufacturer will be able to respond more flexibly to fluctuations in customer demand or production program, Audi will make its manufacturing processes even more flexible. “We want to structure both product and production, so we get the optimum benefit for our customers,” says Gerd Walker, Audi’s board member for production and logistics, in a company statement. To this end, the new Audi Q6 e-tron, for example, will initially be made in Ingolstadt on the same line as the Audi A4 and A5. The electric models will then gradually replace the combustion cars on the lines.</p>
</div>
<div>
  <h2 id="pandemic-pivots">Pandemic Pivots</h2>
  <p>Production lines at the UK Royal Mint were not the only ones making fast pivots. Other manufacturers' adjustments during the pandemic were a dramatic illustration in scalability as companies rescheduled their operations and shifted capacity from one plant to another – sometimes with life-saving consequences.</p>
  <p>When COVID hit, General Motors tapped into its automobile manufacturing capabilities to produce 30,000 ventilators for the United States. That same year, Lamborghini’s upholstery department began making 1,000 surgical masks a day, and later used 3D printers to produce lung simulators to help test ventilator designs, according to a CBI Insights <a href="https://www.cbinsights.com/research/companies-startups-pivoting-covid-19-pandemic/">report</a>. And 3M manufactured more than four billion respirators in two years, the company’s 2021 annual report <a href="https://d1io3yog0oux5.cloudfront.net/_4402e38d0e58dcd9de0f824dacab5599/3m/db/3235/29849/annual_report/3M_2021_Annual_Report_Web-%283%29.pdf">notes</a>.</p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>Style</div>
      <div>Additional Reading</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/investment-value</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Contract Manufacturing: Supply Chains’ Blind Spot]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/contract-manufacturing-supply-chains-blind-spot</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/contract-manufacturing-supply-chains-blind-spot</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how to build trust with partners and not just demand it.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Keep Boomers, an Essential Talent Resource]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-to-keep-baby-boomers-an-essential-talent-resource</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-to-keep-baby-boomers-an-essential-talent-resource</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Effective moves: learn older workers’ specific needs. Embrace flexible scheduling. Foster older-younger collaborations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Industry 4.0 Factories Can Still Embrace the Past]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-industry-4-0-factories-can-still-embrace-the-past</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-industry-4-0-factories-can-still-embrace-the-past</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how retrofitting old equipment can help digitalize operations without breaking the bank.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Offset the Rise in Workplace Retaliation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-to-offset-the-rise-in-workplace-retaliation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-to-offset-the-rise-in-workplace-retaliation</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how to minimize workplace retaliation and have systems in place to deal with it effectively.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fdaca4b7993d1a2478e2398d027a8c5271fe2396.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fdaca4b7993d1a2478e2398d027a8c5271fe2396.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1fdaca4b7993d1a2478e2398d027a8c5271fe2396.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Woman seen from above sitting on a modern wood bench with a tablet on her lap having a difficult conversation on her cellphone." src="./media_1fdaca4b7993d1a2478e2398d027a8c5271fe2396.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-to-offset-the-rise-in-workplace-retaliation">How to Offset the Rise in Workplace Retaliation</h1>
        <p>79% of U.S. employees report experiencing some form of retaliation at work. Here’s how to minimize these occurrences and have systems in place to deal with them effectively.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By Caitlynn Sendra and Stacy Collett</p>
  <p>In the aftermath of two Boeing 737 Max airliner crashes in 2018 and 2019, investigations pointed to two reasons why the aircrafts’ catastrophic design flaw was not identified and resolved. Both underlying conditions were related to the manufacturer’s organizational culture: a hyper-focus on bottom-line business results over design safety and fear of retaliation for speaking up.</p>
  <p>“My pay was docked for putting quality concerns in writing,” says one Boeing quality manager, speaking in the Netflix <a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/81272421">documentary</a> <em>Downfall: The Case Against Boeing</em>. Whistleblowers at the company said anybody who reported a problem was either fired, let go, or moved on, according to aviation analyst Michael Goldfarb in the documentary.</p>
  <p>These experiences were emblematic of a retaliation culture that had infected the organization. “Boeing quit listening to their employees. So every time I would raise my hand, they would attack the messenger and ignore the message,” says yet another quality manager.</p>
  <p>The severity of the Boeing case may make workplace retaliation seem like a rare occurrence – something that many senior managers would attest “doesn’t happen here.” But retaliation at work – in various forms – is very much on the rise. Since 2019, incidents of retaliation at work skyrocketed globally. According to <a href="https://www.ethics.org/global-business-ethics-survey/">a study</a> by the Ethics and Compliance Initiative, a Vienna, Virginia-based nonprofit that helps organizations build and sustain high-quality ethics and compliance programs, 79% of U.S. employees and 61% of global employees reported experiencing some type of retaliation in the workplace in 2021. Additionally, more than half of cases (55.8%) formally filed with the U.S. Equal Employment Opportunity Commission in 2020 were for some form of retaliation.</p>
  <p>Granted, in most organizations, retaliatory action can be far more subtle than what Boeing’s employees experienced. It could come in the form of a supervisor withholding constructive feedback, or leaving an employee out of an important meeting after they disagree with a management decision, or exercising their rights in a way that goes against the grain of the culture. However, the negative effect on the victims of retaliation and the business itself can be just as serious.</p>
</div>
<div>
  <h2 id="more-on-how-leaders-can-build-better-workplace-cultures">More on how leaders can build better workplace cultures</h2>
  <p>Including <a href="/resources/how-to-repair-toxic-workplace-culture">how to combat workplace toxicity</a> , what to do about <em><a href="/resources/strategies-to-head-off-quiet-quitting">quiet quitting</a></em>, and how to view the forces that are redefining what it means to be <a href="/blogs/going-to-the-office-every-day-is-over">connected to an office</a>.</p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>Style</div>
      <div>Additional Reading</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p>Left unchecked, a culture of retaliation can spread throughout the organization, “creating entire climates of abuse,” says Villanova professor Manuela Priesemuth in <a href="https://hbr.org/2020/06/times-up-for-toxic-workplaces">her article</a>, “<a href="https://hbr.org/2020/06/times-up-for-toxic-workplaces">Time’s Up for Toxic Workplaces</a>.” “Because employees look to and learn from managers, they come to understand that this type of interpersonal mistreatment is acceptable behavior in the company.”</p>
  <p>Researchers attribute the rise in retaliation, in part, to increased pressure on employees to compromise business standards. Since 2020, such pressure is the highest it has ever been, according to ECI. Globally, 29% of employees reported pressure in 2020, up from 20% in 2019.</p>
  <p>For their part, employees are more willing to speak up about observed misconduct, thanks to heightened sensitivity following the Me Too movement, increased diversity and inclusion awareness, and a new age of employee empowerment brought on by the demand for workers. In 2020, 86% of employees were more likely to report misconduct, compared with 69% in 2017, according to ECI. The move to remote work in 2020 also created more opportunities for inappropriate behavior through digital channels. Inappropriate comments, jokes, GIFs sent through e-mail, chat messages, and texts could all be considered digital harassment with grounds for reporting.</p>
  <p>In this climate, businesses need to be alert to signs of a retaliation culture and stop retaliatory behavior before it starts. This starts with creating an environment of psychological safety and extends to middle management training. Companies also need to put mechanisms in place for employees to address concerns promptly and transparently and provide multiple reporting channels to any employee who feels the need to raise an issue or report on a retaliatory event.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="fundamentals-of-employee-experience">Fundamentals of employee experience</h3>
        <p>Everything you need to know about the employee journey and tools to support.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/workzone-hr/what-is-employee-experience.html">Get the guide</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="what-retaliation-actually-looks-like">What retaliation actually looks like</h2>
  <p>Although retaliation is defined in multiple ways, two basic elements are always present: an issue is raised, and the person who raised it suffers as a result. The suffering can be overt or subtle and can be triggered by management or peers.</p>
  <p>Often, retaliatory actions can be indirect or can even take the form of a lack of action. In fact, “exclusion is the number one form of subtle retaliation,” says Skip Lowney, senior researcher at ECI. For example, an employee who’s seen as too outspoken at meetings might find information being withheld that’s essential to them doing their job. Team members could also be discouraged from listening to an employee’s expertise or contributions after the employee challenges the direction a project is going. It could even be as subtle as an executive giving a disapproving look to a senior manager who speaks up at a meeting, signaling that they’re in trouble.</p>
  <p>Such subtle acts of retaliation can be difficult to recognize, but they can still have a devastating effect. Subtle retaliation destroys careers, erodes the targeted individual’s sense of worth, and damages workforce effectiveness and productivity. Further, retaliation can diminish business performance because it discourages employees from offering input that could lead to innovation or steer management away from making poor decisions.</p>
  <h2 id="the-reverberating-effect-of-a-culture-of-retaliation">The reverberating effect of a culture of retaliation</h2>
  <p>Even companies that don’t have a culture of retaliation may have to deal with its damaging effects. Employees who experienced retaliation at a previous employer may be extremely sensitive to any nuance of it at any new workplace, or suspicion may be raised by retaliation claims on social media. Some workers are so distrustful that they won’t complete employee surveys for fear it will be linked back to them and used against them.</p>
  <p>Jeffrey, a data scientist who asked that his real name not be used, is still haunted by the retaliation he suffered at a former employer. “It has shaped how I interact with everyone else for the rest of my career,” he says.</p>
  <p>While working remotely for a small company, he was locked out of the company’s network and communication tools after voicing his frustration to the CEO in a group email about the team’s health insurance that had been stopped and restarted repeatedly. He later learned he had been fired.</p>
  <p>“I was scared. My family is a single-income household,” he recalled. “Then I started spiraling. How am I going to pay for my wife’s meds? How do we not become homeless?” Jeffrey found a new job within weeks – but the experience had lingering effects on him and his former co-workers.</p>
  <p>“There was a lot of fear on the team after I was fired. They were afraid to speak out and get fired themselves,” Jeffery says.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15de7ef3b5018dbd66f539cc6427fa896c06ac485.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15de7ef3b5018dbd66f539cc6427fa896c06ac485.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_15de7ef3b5018dbd66f539cc6427fa896c06ac485.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Viewed from above, two people in a conversation, seated in leather lounge chairs at a small table in a corporate lounge setting." src="./media_15de7ef3b5018dbd66f539cc6427fa896c06ac485.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="psychological-safety--good-decision-making">Psychological safety = good decision-making</h2>
  <p>Organizational psychologists agree that the first step to avoiding or repairing a culture of retaliation is to promote and reinforce a culture of psychological safety. Psychological safety is grounded in an unwritten contract of behavior expectations between employer and employee. These expectations create an interpersonal climate where people feel free to speak up honestly and openly. The perception that there will not be consequences for taking interpersonal risks at work is at the core of psychological safety, says Amy Edmonson, professor at Harvard Business School.</p>
  <p>“The most important thing that psychological safety enables for executive teams is good decision-making,” Edmonson says in a <a href="https://512solutions.com/psychological-safety-podcast/">podcast</a>. “They will not fall prey to a very common trap, which is to make a consequential decision in a particular direction that one or more people had grave doubts about but didn’t feel safe to speak up about them.” This isn’t a rare occurrence, she adds.</p>
  <p>“Some of that is just slightly below conscious awareness. You sort of hold back,” Edmonson says. Even if it’s not a matter of feeling unsafe about speaking up, people may not want to come across as unpleasant, or they may doubt themselves because the area of discussion is somewhat outside of their area of expertise. “One executive described it as, ‘I didn’t want to be the skunk at the picnic,’” she says. “In an executive team of high psychological safety, that just doesn’t happen.”</p>
  <h2 id="the-vital-role-of-middle-managers-and-supervisors">The vital role of middle managers and supervisors</h2>
  <p>While executives set the cultural tone, middle managers and supervisors are central to avoiding a culture of retaliation or repairing one damaged by it. <a href="https://news.gallup.com/businessjournal/182792/managers-account-variance-employee-engagement.aspx">Data from Gallup</a> going back to 2015 indicates that managers account for 70% of the variances in employee engagement, which means a good manager can make a world of difference in every employee’s perception of the culture.</p>
  <p>On the flip side, middle managers and supervisors at every level in the organization can create distinctive microcultures, even when they are subject to the same corporate policies and organization-wide practices. Empowering managers has many advantages, but autonomy also leaves more space <a href="/resources/how-to-repair-toxic-workplace-culture">to create a toxic subculture</a>. <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-fix-a-toxic-culture/">In their research</a>, senior lecturer at the MIT Sloan School of Management, Donald Sull, and cofounder of Culture X, Charles Sull, found that middle managers were more than twice as likely to be the source of a toxic subculture compared with other companywide factors.</p>
  <p>To curb a culture of retaliation, executives and managers need the tools to deepen their self-awareness regarding the actions they take and their effect on the people who report to them. Education programs can help managers learn to identify mental patterns that block them from absorbing and accepting new ideas that allow them to change their behavior, says Robert Kegan, co-author of <em>Immunity to Change: How to Overcome It and Unlock the Potential in Yourself and Your Organization.</em></p>
  <p>Managers should also be encouraged to examine their conscious or unconscious ulterior motives. To what extent are their actions a result of ego, stress, or self-protection? What effect has that had on others?</p>
  <p>They must also examine their relationships with those around them and identify how they might treat their inner circle and outer circles differently. From here, managers can start to recreate a culture that is open and inclusive.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_190249664dedc86c74415791a01eb3f1c3a4bb6fd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_190249664dedc86c74415791a01eb3f1c3a4bb6fd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_190249664dedc86c74415791a01eb3f1c3a4bb6fd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Group of five colleagues in an open office setting, two are seated and three are standing, two that are standing are high-fiving" src="./media_190249664dedc86c74415791a01eb3f1c3a4bb6fd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1678" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="exposing-and-eliminating-retaliation-culture">Exposing and eliminating retaliation culture</h2>
  <p>As important as it is to discourage a culture of retaliation, it’s just as vital to have plans and mechanisms in place for when these transgressions occur. Organizations should consider the following when developing strategies and processes for managing instances of misconduct.</p>
  <h2 id="develop-clear-policies-and-communicate-them">Develop clear policies and communicate them</h2>
  <p>Employees need to be aware of the channels for reporting on both misconduct and retaliatory behaviors. Companies may use human resources, an anonymous hotline, supervisors, a complaint process, or a combination of these and other methods, to encourage employees to report concerns. The entire organization needs to know what retaliation looks like, and the definition needs to be shared repeatedly with all employees.</p>
  <h2 id="hear-out-employees">Hear out employees</h2>
  <p>Managers need to intentionally set aside time to talk with their direct reports and allow them to air out any concerns, says Dr. Anthony Klotz, an associate professor of organizational behavior at University College London School of Management. “But they’re so stretched, they usually don’t have time or feel stressed, and when they do have time, they’re usually in defensive mode.” Klotz suggests setting aside time weekly to hear how employees are experiencing work. “Then their job is to funnel that up to higher levels of the organization so they can make changes and adjust accordingly,” Klotz says.</p>
  <p>Managers should also be trained to recognize appearances of unfair behavior, including their own, and address it immediately, Lowney says. “If a problem comes to the supervisor, they are supposed to resolve it, but also report that to the ethics and compliance office to monitor and track it,” he says.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="how-to-support-stressed-workers">How to support stressed workers</h3>
        <p>Learn how managers can respond to employees’ mental health needs.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/how-managers-can-support-stressed-workers">Explore</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="set-manageable-expectations">Set manageable expectations</h2>
  <p>Employees need to understand what will happen once a report is made and how long it’s likely to take, from reporting through evaluation and investigation to potential disciplinary actions.</p>
  <p>It needs to be made clear that just because a report is made; it does not mean specific actions will be taken. If a formal investigation is to be launched, the employee should be notified and made aware of how long the investigation may take.</p>
  <p>Employees who file a complaint will likely be especially sensitive to others’ behavior – suddenly, even the most minor interactions can feel like retaliation, such as a boss who doesn’t say hello in the hallway, or their peers who suddenly seem quiet. To ameliorate such fears, employees should be made aware of what is and is not retaliation, so they know how to manage any heightened sensitivity while awaiting a response to their report and thereafter.</p>
  <h2 id="keep-the-lines-open">Keep the lines open</h2>
  <p>While it is not necessary or feasible for employees to be alerted to every step of the formal process, it is important for them to know there is a process and generally what it entails so they feel confident that something is being done, their allegations are being taken seriously, and their complaint is heading toward some type of conclusion. Employees should be told what leaders found in their examination of reported unethical or retaliatory behavior, what they’ve done with that information to resolve the problem, the progress made, and then follow through on changes leaders have identified as being necessary.</p>
  <p>All these steps can equip individuals to speak up for themselves and for the benefit of the organization. Employees who work in a culture of psychological safety feel valued and are more productive, and organizations benefit from better decision-making and, ideally, greater innovation.</p>
  <p>“You want a culture where people feel it is safe to speak up,” Klotz says. “If it’s a climate of support and psychological safety, having a voice leads to very positive outcomes for the organization.”</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Replacing Water Cooler Moments]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/replacing-water-cooler-moments</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/replacing-water-cooler-moments</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how hybrid companies can encourage greater innovation and new ideas by encouraging collaborative interactions no matter where employees work.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Currency of Customer Trust in Retail]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/the-currency-of-customer-trust-in-retail</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/the-currency-of-customer-trust-in-retail</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Building trustworthy customer experiences means sharing information and devoting resources to enhancing consumers’ trust.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why DEI Backlash Exists and What to Do About It]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/why-dei-backlash-exists</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/why-dei-backlash-exists</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn why clear, ongoing, two-way communication is the foundation for truly inclusive diversity and DEI programs that yield business payoff.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Compensating Sales for Consumption-Based Pricing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/compensating-sales-for-consumption-based-pricing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/compensating-sales-for-consumption-based-pricing</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Five key questions for CEOs, CFOs, and sales VPs to make the switch to consumption-based pricing models a success for your staff and customers.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Learning in the Flow of Work: A More Engaging Learner Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/learning-in-the-flow-of-work</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/learning-in-the-flow-of-work</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learning in the flow of work seamlessly incorporates learning into employees’ workdays through an LMS – boosting employee engagement and productivity.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What is Contingency Planning?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/contingency-planning</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/contingency-planning</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Creating an emergency-response framework results in retaining a healthy, motivated, dedicated workforce during crises – and better business after.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Sustainable Factory of the Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/the-sustainable-factory-of-the-future</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/the-sustainable-factory-of-the-future</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how the evolution of manufacturing processes and technology provides the opportunity to think differently about sustainable factory operations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-supply-chain</category>
            <category>content-type/trends-predictions</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How HR Can Direct Use of AI and ChatGPT]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-hr-can-direct-use-of-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-hr-can-direct-use-of-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn why as adoption of AI spreads, HR has an opportunity to shape how it is used to benefit the business and its employees.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>core-topic/responsible-ai</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Supply Chain Innovation: What’s Next? | SAP Insights]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/supply-chain-innovation-whats-next</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/supply-chain-innovation-whats-next</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Supply chains need innovation, but tech investments too often fall flat. Three experts offer insights on how to fix the problem.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/trends-predictions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Repair a Toxic Workplace Culture]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-to-repair-toxic-workplace-culture</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-to-repair-toxic-workplace-culture</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To fix a bad corporate culture, leaders must demonstrate that their actions match their words.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hiring Shouldn’t Feel as Bad as Firing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/hiring-shouldnt-feel-as-bad-as-firing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/hiring-shouldnt-feel-as-bad-as-firing</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how companies can streamline the hiring process to address worker shortages more quickly.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17bb3191c41b9ec73545b24b93d76b48cbdeb1b88.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17bb3191c41b9ec73545b24b93d76b48cbdeb1b88.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_17bb3191c41b9ec73545b24b93d76b48cbdeb1b88.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Male HR representative sitting in front of laptop looking very serious." src="./media_17bb3191c41b9ec73545b24b93d76b48cbdeb1b88.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="hiring-shouldnt-feel-as-bad-as-firing">Hiring Shouldn’t Feel as Bad as Firing</h1>
        <p>Too many application hoops. Too many interviews. With a worker shortage, how can companies fix a burdensome hiring process?</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Last fall, MBA graduate Janet fell into the abyss known as the interview process – with seemingly no end in sight. She applied for a newly created senior associate position at a private equity firm. Nine interviews, a list of references, and nearly three months later, the firm decided to nix the position.</p>
  <p>Janet estimates that she spent 12 hours in discussions with various executives over those months. “I was having to take time away from work and I was really, really busy with a project, so I would have to sneak away to go to interviews or call in sick.”</p>
  <p>“It’s fine for them to not want to hire me, but to drag it out over two and a half months I found to be very insulting, quite honestly,” she says.</p>
  <p>For professional jobs – engineers, paralegals, designers, consultants, and more – the hiring process takes way too long for everybody involved: candidates, hiring managers, and human resources. It’s ironic considering the tight job markets in many countries – for example, in the United States, there were 10.8 million job openings and 3.9 million employees who quit their jobs in January 2023 alone, <a href="https://www.roberthalf.com/blog/job-market/january-2023-jobs-report-employers-add-517000-jobs">according to stats</a> from the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics.</p>
  <p>Of the 1,657 hiring professionals worldwide <a href="https://www.hirevue.com/resources/report/report-hirevue-2022-global-trends-report">surveyed</a> by digital recruiting company HireVue, 68% said it takes three weeks or more to fill vacant jobs, up from 55% a year earlier. Hiring times have gone from 54 days on average in 2022 to 58 days for engineering and technology jobs, 62 days for executives and 65 days for public administration hires this year.</p>
  <p>What’s behind the lengthy hiring process? Job seekers blame a lack of communication and haphazard hiring processes on the employers’ part. In a quest to find a rock star who will dazzle on day one, hiring managers devise ever-higher hoops for candidates to jump through – personality and skills testing, multiple rounds of virtual and in-person interviews, and even mock presentations – for fear of making the wrong choice. Bungling the processes even further, companies are changing business strategies quickly in response to shifting market conditions, and open jobs may disappear midway through the hiring process.</p>
  <p>One line of thinking is that a detailed process is part of encouraging fewer but more qualified people to apply. Author and management professor Peter Cappelli, director of the Center for Human Resources at the Wharton School, questions that reasoning.</p>
  <p>“It’s certainly right that a longer process cuts down on the number of applicants. The important question is whether the ones who persist do so because they believe they are best suited for the job…or they can’t get a job anywhere else,” Cappelli says.</p>
  <p>Finding that perfect hire amid a sea of applicants is a delicate balancing act. Acting hastily risks choosing the wrong candidate; taking too long risks losing out on great candidates who get other offers sooner. One thing that’s clear is that greater transparency can make the process a lot less painful for everyone. Beyond that, improving the hiring process gets tricky – automation, for example, isn’t yet the solution it might appear to be. Here, experts diagnose the problems hiding below the surface of the hiring process, explain the real trade-offs involved in seemingly simple answers, and offer ideas to make hiring more effective.</p>
  <h2 id="whats-taking-so-long-and-why-doesnt-automation-fix-it">What’s taking so long, and why doesn’t automation fix it?</h2>
  <p>Mass resignations and “<a href="/resources/strategies-to-head-off-quiet-quitting">quiet quitting</a>” have hiring managers doubly concerned that they’ll make the wrong choices, which are costly and time-consuming. The average cost per hire was nearly $4,700 in 2022, <a href="https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/benefits/pages/shrm-hr-benchmarking-reports-launch-as-a-member-exclusive-benefit.aspx">according to</a> the Society for Human Resources Management (SHRM), but many employers say the total can be three to four times the position’s salary. That means it could cost $180,000 to fill a role that pays $60,000, Edie Goldberg, founder of E.I. Goldberg &#x26; Associates, <a href="https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/talent-acquisition/pages/the-real-costs-of-recruitment.aspx">tells SHRM</a>. Of those expenses, 30% to 40% are hard costs, and the other 60% are soft costs, including time departmental leaders and managers invest in supporting the HR-specific roles in the hiring process, she says.</p>
  <p>Automation currently may hurt as much as it helps. It can be helpful for compulsory things such as background checks or detecting embellished resumes. HR leaders also lean on automation and AI in efforts to avoid age, race, and gender biases by analyzing job descriptions to make them more inclusive or screening resumes and ranking candidates based on relevant skills and qualifications rather than personal details.</p>
  <p>However, tools that automate tasks for HR often create more work for the applicants. For example, some of the tools used for initial resume scans often require a candidate to first upload their résumé and information on the job board where they found the position, then apply again on the company site. A <a href="https://www.jobvite.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/2021-Jobvite-F500-Audit.pdf">JobVite analysis</a> last year of postings at Fortune 500 firms found that 83% required candidates to jump through both hoops rather than allowing them to just apply directly on the company’s career page.</p>
  <p>Further, every task assigned to AI still adds another step to the process. Hiring companies are using an array of AI tools to check backgrounds and evaluate candidates based on voice recognition, body language, and social media clues. Unfortunately, there’s little proof that this produces satisfactory hires. Only about a third of U.S. companies report that they monitor whether their hiring practices lead to good employees, Cappelli says.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12ccf2695e6609d195a1db70b8ccc2b821f9005cc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12ccf2695e6609d195a1db70b8ccc2b821f9005cc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12ccf2695e6609d195a1db70b8ccc2b821f9005cc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Close-up of a person impatiently checking their watch" src="./media_12ccf2695e6609d195a1db70b8ccc2b821f9005cc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1493" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Some online tests look to match personalities with the corporate culture. Maddie, a chemist, applied for a position at a chemical manufacturing company last August. She was asked to take an online assessment that compares a candidate’s personality, soft skills, and values to those of the employer. “The way they framed it, the results would not affect their decision process but indicate how I would work with the team,” Maddie says. The experience made her wonder whether this step was necessary so early in the process.</p>
  <p>Requiring job candidates to take myriad skills tests and <em>personality</em> assessments may be a waste of time. However, online <em>skills</em> assessments and quizzes, which may or may not involve automation, are a necessary step in this job market, according to many HR professionals. One recruiting firm uses AI in video interviews to assess verbal and non-verbal cues. A hiring software vendor uses <a href="/resources/when-microlearning-met-gamification">gamified</a> assessments to measure cognitive and emotional traits such as problem-solving, creativity, and resilience.</p>
  <p>“Companies are not finding qualified candidates, and someone who applies may think they’re qualified when they’re not,” says John Dooney, HR knowledge advisor at SHRM.</p>
  <p>Online skills assessments help measure basic skills before interviews and weed out unsuitable candidates earlier. In many cases, hiring managers don’t think they’ll find someone with the full range of required skills, “so they’re thinking maybe they can train them – and they take a certain number of candidates who score above a minimum,” Dooney says.</p>
  <p>These techniques can often turn off job candidates who feel they are spending time proving basic skills rather than displaying their talents for the specific position, but many companies still include these assessments. Beyond that concern, employers need to be wary when recruiting assessment tools promise that they can predict successful employees, Cappelli says. “The issue is not what data science could do in principle. The question is whether the solutions being offered can do a good job of it,” he says.</p>
  <p>A successful tool would gather information on thousands of past hires for various positions – all their attributes – and a good measure of their job performance and success on the job, he says. “Has the vendor done that? Will they show you how good a fit their model is? Do you believe that the job they profiled is really like yours? Will they validate their algorithm with your data? If the answer is <em>no</em>, don’t bother.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1130f7f07204819ebf1ae3d14f49e2f922d6ceaf8.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1130f7f07204819ebf1ae3d14f49e2f922d6ceaf8.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1130f7f07204819ebf1ae3d14f49e2f922d6ceaf8.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Man and woman shaking hands at a table, illustrating a more positive interview process" src="./media_1130f7f07204819ebf1ae3d14f49e2f922d6ceaf8.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="jumping-through-flaming-hoops--the-interview-process">“Jumping through flaming hoops” – the interview process</h2>
  <p>Those lucky candidates who survive the digital screening steps often run into an even more daunting obstacle: humans.</p>
  <p>Jessica was up for a job as a fundraiser at a large social services organization in New York, she <a href="https://www.vox.com/the-goods/2023/1/12/23546379/job-interviewing-applying-exhausting-tests-employment">says in an interview</a> with the Web site Vox. Over two months, Jessica took part in six separate interviews involving nine people, many of whom were present in multiple interviews. She put together a dummy presentation on a hypothetical corporate partnership program for interview number four.</p>
  <p>“It just gets really mentally exhausting, and it’s hard to manage your work schedule because obviously you don’t want your employer to know you’re interviewing,” she told Vox.</p>
  <p>Virtual interviews became the norm during the pandemic and gave hiring managers the time to do more frequent interviews with more candidates in less time and at very little cost. A bonus for them – but a bummer for job candidates.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Unstructured interviews, where employers just ask whatever they want... predict very little about who will succeed.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Peter Cappelli, The Wharton School Center for Human Resources</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“It’s unfair to make five candidates jump through flaming hoops and go through [multiple] rounds of interviews when four of them will be told <em>no</em>,” says Kelsey Collett, a former HR manager at a global consumer packaged goods company. Most candidates have other jobs, after all, and interviewers often ask the same questions. Collett suggests no more than three rounds of interviews.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.indeed.com/career-advice/interviewing/how-many-interviews-for-a-job">According to Indeed</a>, one to three interviews typically yield the best results, but no rule is true in every case. Organizations may sometimes justify using a fourth interview to make a final decision between two highly qualified candidates – but if the cycle repeats too many times, the candidate may question why the hiring manager hasn’t made a decision. They may also wonder if it’s still worth it to schedule time away from their current job to continue pursuing a new one.</p>
  <p>Cappelli finds today’s overwrought process a bit ridiculous and often the result of poor planning by the hiring company. “Unstructured interviews, where employers just ask whatever they want, are major sources of bias in the process and predict very little about who will succeed,” he says.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1994350c1911d4a239738f7546873b219741d1ffc.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1994350c1911d4a239738f7546873b219741d1ffc.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1994350c1911d4a239738f7546873b219741d1ffc.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Woman balancing on boulders" src="./media_1994350c1911d4a239738f7546873b219741d1ffc.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="how-to-strike-the-right-balance">How to strike the right balance</h2>
  <p>It’s a balancing act – companies stand to lose out on the best candidates when the process drags on, but going too fast risks hiring someone who turns out to be a bad fit. It also risks making job candidates feel like a commodity. “It may feel too fast and easy to get the interview because they’re so desperate,” Dooney says, “and the new hire thinks the company really wasn’t looking for that person long-term.”</p>
  <p>While the numbers have been trending in the wrong direction, per the HireVue study, companies still want to ensure that they choose the right, long-term employee. HR experts say there are ways to reconcile these conflicting interests and make the hiring process less painful for all. Here’s what to do.</p>
  <p><strong>Start with realistic job requirements</strong>. If you’re looking for a rock star, unicorn, or “purple squirrel,” a nickname for an impossible combination of sought-after skills for a given job, reset your expectations. “If your current employees don’t have those attributes, the candidates don’t need them either,” Cappelli says.</p>
  <p><strong>Make an actual hiring plan</strong>. At the outset, determine skills requirements, a maximum list of candidates, a maximum number of must-see interviewers, distinct roles and objectives for each interviewer, and a decision date. Having a clear timeline should also cut the chances of running into a sudden hiring freeze that can delay the process and leave the hiring manager trying to string along candidates.</p>
  <p><strong>Be transparent about the hiring process up front.</strong> Explain the process to candidates, including what to expect in terms of time to hire and rounds of interviews.</p>
  <p><strong>Add more human elements throughout.</strong> This doesn’t necessarily mean making everything in person – it could mean just having a real person send an email, make a follow-up phone call, let the candidate know how they were received by the interviewers, and discuss next steps. Don’t lead them on, but fill them in. This personal connection may also help reduce ghosting of the hiring team by candidates after getting an offer.</p>
  <p><strong>Consider returning to more in-person interviews.</strong> It won’t necessarily speed up the process, but it may ensure a better fit and help curb the impulse to do too many interviews.</p>
  <p><strong>Don’t let one employee hang up the process.</strong> “In terms of buy-in, make people who want a say in the decision sign up to meet only the short-listed candidates,” Cappelli says. “Don’t make it a requirement that no one can be offered a job until everyone has met them.”</p>
  <p><strong>Avoid redundant interview questions.</strong> Consider scheduling a small panel of interviewers in the room at the same time to avoid repetition of questions in multiple interviews. For one-on-one interviews, avoid general questions that are already answered on the candidate’s resume and ask questions about how the candidate would handle situations that are under the interviewer’s purview.</p>
  <p><strong>Break up quickly.</strong> If you don’t see a good fit or the right qualification, don’t waste everybody’s time. Case in point: Another job-seeker, Charles, applied for a marketing position at a digital security company, which abides by a 24-hour rule for making a decision after any interview and informing the candidate immediately – with either “You’re advancing, and here’s the next step” or a polite version of “Sorry, you’re out.” Like ripping off the Band-Aid, it stings at first, but, to the private equity candidate Janet’s point, it’s respectful and keeps the process moving.</p>
  <p><strong>Consider taking managers and/or leaders out of the hiring process.</strong> One reason for the lengthy process is that managers and leaders are too busy, and the hiring process is treated as a second job – so it stands to reason that companies should stop putting them in that position. “Drop all the rounds of interviews. Have them done by one expert who knows what they are doing,” Cappelli says.</p>
  <p>Companies have decimated their own recruiting offices to save money. They often turn to outsourcing or push the tasks onto line managers “who don’t know how to do it, who don’t do enough of it to get good at it, and who aren’t held accountable for it,” Cappelli says. “Bring back recruiters and let line managers focus on what they are supposed to do.”</p>
  <p><strong>Make offers quickly.</strong> All the preceding steps should allow you to make most offers more quickly than before. When companies do so, applicants are more likely to accept.</p>
  <p>It’s not just employers who must adapt to these labor market trends. Prospective employees are paying attention too. Bruised but not beaten by the process, Janet now goes into job interviews with a new perspective. “I know to ask for clarity and what I should expect. At the beginning, I ask what criteria they’re looking for in this role. If I had pushed for that and in the end they said no, I could look back and see where I fell short.”</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[12 Security Issues to Address as Your Factories Evolve]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/twelve-security-issues-for-evolving-factories</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/twelve-security-issues-for-evolving-factories</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how your company can keep up with changing cybersecurity demands for future factories.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>content-type/trends-predictions</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Business Value of Sustainability Is Here]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/the-business-value-of-sustainability-is-here</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/the-business-value-of-sustainability-is-here</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn why sustainable business practices are investments that pay, like R&D and customer relationships, from author Andrew Winston.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>