<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-original-series-forward/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Return of Forward Live: Can We Really Change Work for Good?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/the-return-of-forward-live</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/the-return-of-forward-live</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Forward Live video series features live interviews with some of today's most interesting personalities and brightest thinkers.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-original-series-forward</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How adidas Promotes Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion in the Workplace]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/how-adidas-promotes-diversity-equity-inclusion-in-workplace</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/how-adidas-promotes-diversity-equity-inclusion-in-workplace</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To promote equity, adidas is working to diversify its workforce and has set clear targets around ethnicity and gender. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cd48a968e30f278d08b59a1a7cb654ca34e7ec1e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cd48a968e30f278d08b59a1a7cb654ca34e7ec1e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1cd48a968e30f278d08b59a1a7cb654ca34e7ec1e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How adidas Promotes Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion in the Workplace" src="./media_1cd48a968e30f278d08b59a1a7cb654ca34e7ec1e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-adidas-promotes-diversity-equity-and-inclusion-in-the-workplace">How adidas Promotes Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion in the Workplace</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For global sports company <a href="https://adidas.com/">adidas</a>, ‘Impossible is nothing’ is much more than a tagline. As one of the most recognized and iconic brands in the world, adidas sees endless potential to transcend cultures – both on and off the field of play.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To be the best sports brand in the world, adidas needs to work with talent that reflects the diversity of its customers. In 2020, the company redefined its framework for diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) to clarify what DEI means to adidas as a company: championing individual uniqueness and cultivating a culture of belonging so that everyone can create at their best.</p>
  <p>“Diversity means ensuring that we have a plethora of people from different backgrounds,” said Amanda Rajkumar, executive board member, Global Human Resources People and Culture at adidas. “Equity means putting fair processes in place across the board, for all employees. And inclusion means ensuring that the environment at adidas is one where everyone feels welcome. As the first non-white member of our executive board, these topics are close to my heart.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-forward-a-new-series-about-a-better-human-experience-at-work">Watch Forward, a new series about a better human experience at work</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://www.sap.com/HXMForward">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="taking-a-data-driven-approach-to-dei">Taking a Data-Driven Approach to DEI</h2>
  <p>Historically, our society has been an unequal playing field, and that inequality is still present in our workplaces. To promote equity, adidas is working to diversify its workforce and has set clear targets around ethnicity and gender.</p>
  <p>For example, the company aims to fill at least 30% of new positions in the United States with Black and LatinX people. Globally, adidas is reforming its hiring and career development processes to increase representation of women and Black, Indigenous, and People of Color (BIPOC) at all levels.</p>
  <p>“We need to ensure that hiring managers and recruiters understand the importance of our DEI imperatives and take affirmative action to support underrepresented groups,” said Rajkumar. “We don’t see it as lowering the bar, but as widening the gate for those who have not had the same starting point in life.”</p>
  <p>adidas is one of the first companies on DAX (the German stock index) to collect data on DEI. It uses DEI insights not only to support decision-making, but also – crucially – to measure progress against its targets.</p>
  <p>“There’s no point in setting targets if we cannot accurately measure our progress against them,” said Rajkumar. “Line managers can see the current diversity status of their teams, so they can have meaningful conversations with HR about how to improve and to meet their targets. Data is essential to getting this right.”</p>
  <h2 id="creating-real-change">Creating Real Change</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-appoints-new-chief-diversity-and-inclusion-officer">SAP Appoints New Chief Diversity and Inclusion Officer</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/10/supriya-jha-sap-chief-diversity-and-inclusion-officer">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For too long, HR has been denied a seat at the executive table. The tumultuous events of 2020, including the Black Lives Matter movement and the <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19 pandemic</a>, have brought HR to the fore.</p>
  <p>“There’s no other department that can hold up a mirror to the organization,” said Rajkumar. “HR is the ombudsman between employer and employee. We represent the conscience of the firm, which is why HR has played such a crucial role in the last year.”</p>
  <p>That’s why, in the third quarter of 2020, adidas introduced mandatory anti-racism and unconscious-bias training worldwide. The company also defined strategic focus areas to attract, recruit, promote, and retain a diverse workforce at all levels and areas of the business.</p>
  <p>With <a href="https://www.successfactors.com/">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a> underpinning HR and talent processes at adidas across the entire employee life cycle, the company can measure progress against its ambitious DEI targets and create a work environment where all employees feel like they belong.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div><strong>To learn more, watch <a href="http://www.sap.com/hxmforwardadamgrant">Forward with Adam Grant in conversation with Amanda Rajkumar</a>.</strong></div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Deb Lyons is senior director of Global Marketing for SAP SuccessFactors. <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/11/10/how-adidas-promotes-diversity-equity-and-inclusion-in-the-workplace/?sh=39423b6e3349">This also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-original-series-forward</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scotiabank Empowers and Nurtures Employees with Better Learning Experiences]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/scotiabank-empowers-and-nurtures-employees-with-better-learning-experiences</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/scotiabank-empowers-and-nurtures-employees-with-better-learning-experiences</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Scotiabank employees are provided with cutting-edge learning and career opportunities that create a meaningful employee experience.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18efb1435db832c6b2cef28268c4569ca7fb99b4d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18efb1435db832c6b2cef28268c4569ca7fb99b4d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18efb1435db832c6b2cef28268c4569ca7fb99b4d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Scotiabank Empowers and Nurtures Employees with Better Learning Experiences" src="./media_18efb1435db832c6b2cef28268c4569ca7fb99b4d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="scotiabank-empowers-and-nurtures-employees-with-better-learning-experiences">Scotiabank Empowers and Nurtures Employees with Better Learning Experiences</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Thanks to its wide portfolio of personal and commercial banking services, <a href="https://www.scotiabank.com/">Scotiabank</a> is a preferred bank across Canada and around the world. But its true competitive advantage lies in its 90,000 employees, affectionately known as “Scotiabankers.” Every day at Scotiabank, employees are provided with cutting-edge learning and career opportunities that create a meaningful employee experience.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a result, not only do customers prefer to do business with Scotiabank, but the company’s own employees see Scotiabank as an employer of choice too, according to Barb Mason, group head and chief human resources officer at Scotiabank.</p>
  <h2 id="empowering-employees-with-better-learning-experiences">Empowering Employees with Better Learning Experiences</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="upskill-and-reskill-your-workforce-to-adapt-to-change-with-sap-successfactors-learning">Upskill and reskill your workforce to adapt to change with SAP SuccessFactors Learning</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/corporate-lms.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Should employers hire candidates with a strong desire to learn, or try to nurture this quality in all its employees? According to Mason, it’s a bit of both. Too often, employees aren’t afforded the opportunity to learn on the job and grow their skill set – especially women and people of color.</p>
  <p>“For us, it is all about ensuring that we have systemically equitable processes in the bank to allow everyone to have the same opportunities and understand what they need to do to be able to get these opportunities,” Mason said.</p>
  <p>Scotiabank embraces equitable hiring processes that set a standard for equity for the rest of the employee life cycle. This begins with diverse interview teams who strive to ask unbiased interview questions and follow other best practices for inclusive recruitment.</p>
  <p>From the start, Scotiabank lets its employees know it is dedicated to providing next-level learning and skill-building experiences. Throughout the recruitment and interview process, HR leaders open the door to a world of on-the-job learning for candidates. With a modern learning experience similar to employees’ favorite video streaming services, Scotiabank’s workforce can tap into on-demand learning and training built on Blend by TalenTeam powered by <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/corporate-lms.html">SAP SuccessFactors Learning</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="creating-the-highest-performing-workforce-to-date">Creating the Highest Performing Workforce to Date</h2>
  <p>Mason knows that learning doesn’t do any employees – or the business – any good if people don’t know how to access learning resources. In addition to making these resources readily available to employees as part of the company’s next-generation HR experience, Scotiabank also readily provides opportunities for experiential learning for directors and above.</p>
  <p>During hypothetical scenarios, employees have the chance to tackle new tasks set at a level above their current role at Scotiabank. For instance, a mid-level bank officer may have to resolve a simulated customer challenge that is usually handled by a senior officer. Employees get to learn new skills on the fly, and the company gets to see employees’ aptitude for performing in a new role. “It’s not a pass or fail,” said Mason. “It’s an experience.”</p>
  <p>Meanwhile, the Scotia Inspire program, enabled by <a href="https://www.sap.com/programs/experience-wins.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a>, empowers women in senior positions to participate in mentoring and sponsorship for the next level of women at Scotiabank. This begins at the very top, with women in the executive suite enabling leaders to mentor women in every other role across the business.</p>
  <p>“We now have the highest caliber performance of women that we’ve ever had in the history of the organization, and I don’t see that ever changing,” said Mason.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-forward-a-new-series-about-a-better-human-experience-at-work">Watch Forward, a new series about a better human experience at work</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://www.sap.com/HXMForward">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="to-learn-more-watch-barb-masons-interview-in-an-episode-of-forward-with-adam-grant">To learn more, <a href="https://www.sap.com/HXMForwardAdamGrant">watch Barb Mason’s interview</a> in an episode of Forward with Adam Grant.</h3>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Carolyn Judge Phillip is vice president of Corporate Marketing for SAP SuccessFactors.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/10/27/scotiabank-empowers-and-nurtures-employees-with-better-learning-experiences/?sh=436ae7e83464">This also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-original-series-forward</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Deloitte Is Beating Burnout at Scale]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/how-deloitte-is-beating-burnout-at-scale</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/how-deloitte-is-beating-burnout-at-scale</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In trying to address overwork issues before they impact mental health, professional services company Deloitte is a pioneer. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/deloitte</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-original-series-forward</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Five Dimensions to Create a Robust Employee Well-Being Strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/five-dimensions-to-create-robust-employee-well-being-strategy-telus</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/five-dimensions-to-create-robust-employee-well-being-strategy-telus</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[TELUS has developed a strategy that includes five interlocking dimensions that align with emerging industry best practices. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e9ef10a46e14836a5b028351769a9327d59a02b0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e9ef10a46e14836a5b028351769a9327d59a02b0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e9ef10a46e14836a5b028351769a9327d59a02b0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Five Dimensions to Create a Robust Employee Well-Being Strategy" src="./media_1e9ef10a46e14836a5b028351769a9327d59a02b0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="five-dimensions-to-create-a-robust-employee-well-being-strategy">Five Dimensions to Create a Robust Employee Well-Being Strategy</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>What does it mean to have a robust employee well-being strategy?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Just ask TELUS, a leading communications and information technology company with $16 billion in annual revenue and 15.2 million customer connections spanning wireless, data, IP, voice, television, entertainment, video and security, healthcare, and agriculture. TELUS connects people to what matters most to improve lives and build a better future – and it starts with supporting and enabling its employees.</p>
  <p>TELUS’ employees have long depended on the company’s technology, devices, and services to work from home – well before remote work became all the rage. Since 2006, TELUS’ employees have enjoyed flexible work arrangements, with approximately 75% of its Canadian workforce spending a portion of time working remotely.</p>
  <p>In response to the global health <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, 95% of TELUS employees work from home, including 99% of domestic call center employees. As a result, the company has achieved higher levels of workplace satisfaction and productivity, as employees are empowered to find new ways to fit work into their evolving lives.</p>
  <p>Just as TELUS was ahead of its time with its flexible work styles, the company is proving to be a pioneer in supporting employee well-being.</p>
  <p>According to Sandy McIntosh, TELUS’ executive vice president, People and Culture, and chief human resources officer, “without a robust people strategy, you won’t have a business that will thrive or succeed.”</p>
  <p>Under McIntosh’s leadership, well-being has become an ongoing cultural commitment and business imperative. TELUS has developed a strategy that recognizes the whole person and includes five interlocking dimensions that align with emerging industry best practices from the National Standard for Psychological Health and Safety in the Workplace, the Mental Health Commission of Canada, and the World Health Organization:</p>
  <ol>
    <li><strong>Physical</strong>: The company offers physical fitness and well-being centers, as well as virtual fitness classes and apps, virtual care solutions, nutritional counseling, health coaching, and more. TELUS also hosts biannual well-being challenges for employees and household family members to promote healthy habits.</li>
    <li><strong>Psychological</strong>: TELUS understands its employees are all somewhere on the well-being continuum and that each person’s situation is dynamic. The company offers industry-leading benefits coverage for mental health support and 24/7 support to mental health counselors and therapists through its Employee and Family Assistance Program and virtual care. In 2020, TELUS launched custom mental health training for leaders and over 90% have completed it. In May 2021, the company extended the reach by introducing similar training to all employees.</li>
    <li><strong>Social</strong>: TELUS creates opportunities to connect employees at work, home, and in the community through initiatives like TELUS Days of Giving, as well as supportive resources, collaboration tools, and employee resource groups that offer mentoring, networking, peer support, volunteering, and coaching.</li>
    <li><strong>Environmental</strong>: TELUS helps employees maintain healthy workspaces at home and in offices. In fact, TELUS is reimagining its offices for the future of work with work styles and well-being top of mind, offering a mix of private and collaborative spaces to support whitespace and brainstorming.</li>
    <li><strong>Financial</strong>: TELUS supports all aspects of its employees’ financial well-being, offering competitive salaries and benefits and financial literacy resources, including a financial well-being hub where employees can find tools to help them reach their financial and life goals.</li>
  </ol>
  <p>“Our job as leaders is to come at well-being from all five dimensions because well-being is not just mental and it’s not just physical,” said McIntosh. “Leaders have a responsibility to make sure that employees understand their financial situation, that the environment is appropriate, and their social connections are healthy. If you understand all of that and keep pressing the gas on all levers, you create a magical place where people want to be,” McIntosh explained.</p>
  <p>For TELUS, it’s deeper than providing technology and tools. The company is working to create a common language, build leadership competencies and practices, and use data insights to shift mindsets and behaviors.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/hxm-suite.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a> provides TELUS with the technology to create a company culture dedicated to flexible work that in turn supports employee well-being. With cloud-based tools, employees can tap into engaging, individualized experiences. The company knows that a better employee experience will empower the workforce to provide better experiences to customers.</p>
  <p>Very rarely does a superior or business leader say an employee must give up the things they love. But McIntosh says that employees often feel this way, especially after they have been promoted or move into a new role. Employees who quit a beloved hobby or stop exercising because they feel they don’t have the time may soon see the rest of their lives – including their performance at work – begin to free-fall.</p>
  <p>“Nobody explicitly says to you, ‘Stop doing these things,’” said McIntosh. “But also, unfortunately, nobody explicitly says to you, ‘Keep doing these things.’ We have to, as leaders, overtly come out and say, ‘Is your self-care in check?’”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-forward-a-new-series-about-a-better-human-experience-at-work">Watch Forward, a new series about a better human experience at work</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://www.sap.com/HXMForward">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="making-good-on-a-commitment-to-employee-well-being">Making Good on a Commitment to Employee Well-Being</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="put-employees-at-the-heart-of-everything-you-do-with-sap-successfactors">Put employees at the heart of everything you do with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/hxm-suite.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At TELUS, team member well-being initiatives aren’t designed to simply make the company look good. Rather, they exist to make employees feel good and perform at their best.</p>
  <p>“We’re really focused on helping leaders understand we don’t mean fluffy stuff,” said McIntosh. “We don’t mean every Friday we’re having a pizza party. We mean that you understand that you’re leading other human beings.”</p>
  <p>Take, for example, one TELUS benefit that provides employees, including their dependents, with up to CAD5,000 per year to spend on psychologists, psychotherapists, and social workers – a benefit unmatched by its peers. TELUS also enables its team members to connect with registered mental health clinicians through a range of virtual care solutions and provides a free, unlimited subscription to the leading mental fitness app Calm.</p>
  <p>“Human beings are complex, and we need to look at all five dimensions and put all of these ingredients together,” said McIntosh.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>To learn more, <a href="https://www.sap.com/HXMForwardAdamGrant">watch Sandy McIntosh’s interview</a> in an episode of Forward with Adam Grant.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Carolyn Judge Phillip is VP of Corporate Marketing for SAP SuccessFactors. <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/10/14/5-dimensions-to-create-a-robust-employee-well-being-strategy/?sh=3d0c882a5e18">This also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-original-series-forward</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chobani Creates Positive Change for Its Dynamic and Diverse Workforce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/chobani-creates-positive-change-for-dynamic-and-diverse-workforce</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/chobani-creates-positive-change-for-dynamic-and-diverse-workforce</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Empowered by an integrated suite of SAP solutions, Chobani is even better equipped to continue to lead in making the world a healthier place.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b683315f4787218c78d03bb6eaa883935b3f2b30.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b683315f4787218c78d03bb6eaa883935b3f2b30.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b683315f4787218c78d03bb6eaa883935b3f2b30.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Chobani Creates Positive Change for Its Dynamic and Diverse Workforce" src="./media_1b683315f4787218c78d03bb6eaa883935b3f2b30.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="chobani-creates-positive-change-for-its-dynamic-and-diverse-workforce">Chobani Creates Positive Change for Its Dynamic and Diverse Workforce</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Founded in 2005 when Hamdi Ulukaya brought together a small group of passionate individuals to make the real, wholesome yogurt he remembered from his childhood, Chobani now produces the top-selling Greek yogurt brand in the United States. The company’s yogurt, oat milk, dairy and plant-based creamers, ready-to-drink coffee, and plant-based probiotic drinks are made with natural ingredients and without artificial preservatives, keeping with its mission to make “good food for all.”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Chobani prides itself on being a values-driven, people-first food and wellness company. Employees describe it as “One Chobani – we work in different places and do different things, but we are one.” Its energetic work environment comprises diverse backgrounds and cultures, with tight-knit teams that feed off innovation and creativity.</p>
  <p>This unity is reflected in Chobani’s efforts to reduce inequities in the workplace by offering programs that benefit the entire workforce, regardless of job title.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1320c990b64986b59a05e760b3d1133d364f1b49a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1320c990b64986b59a05e760b3d1133d364f1b49a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1320c990b64986b59a05e760b3d1133d364f1b49a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Chobani employee in PPE giving thumbs-up" src="./media_1320c990b64986b59a05e760b3d1133d364f1b49a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="300" height="259">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Photo courtesy of Chobani</em></p>
  <p>“Chobani is fundamentally about access to delicious, nutritious, natural, and affordable food,” said Grace Zuncic, chief people officer, Chobani. “But it also stands for access to a living wage, good benefits, and a workplace that lifts you up, makes you feel appreciated and welcome for who you are, and where you can really be yourself. Our values are simple: people, integrity, leadership, giving back, innovation, and craftsmanship.”</p>
  <p>But merely expressing these values is not enough: Zuncic says it’s important how these words are enacted across the entire organization and how they make employees feel. The company strives to transform employees’ lives through the experience employees have from their first day.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-forward-a-new-series-about-a-better-human-experience-at-work">Watch Forward, a new series about a better human experience at work</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://www.sap.com/HXMForward">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="putting-its-values-into-practice">Putting Its Values Into Practice</h2>
  <p>According to Zuncic, <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> gave Chobani an opportunity to show its workforce how much it cares. While Chobani’s executive leadership team always led in service of essential workers – who comprise the majority of its workforce – during the pandemic, the company offered financial incentives for employees to get tested and vaccinated.</p>
  <p>It was one of the first companies in the United States to offer paid leave for vaccination. It also opened up discussions about mental health among frontline employees and implemented new policies to help ensure employees at all levels have access to the right mental health support and resources.</p>
  <p>In addition, Chobani introduced a US$100 daily subsidy to help cover the cost of childcare. This financial support helped the company keep production moving in the face of extremely high demand while supporting employees during a difficult and uncertain time.</p>
  <h2 id="delivering-an-exceptional-people-experience">Delivering an Exceptional People Experience</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="deliver-engaging-individualized-experiences-that-enable-employees-to-be-their-best-with-sap-successfactors">Deliver engaging, individualized experiences that enable employees to be their best with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/hxm-suite.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In order to help power its people and workforce strategies, Chobani relies on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/hxm-suite.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a> to provide a robust experience across the entire employee life cycle, help upskill and reskill its people, and deliver the data and insights to further the company’s mission.</p>
  <p>“SAP SuccessFactors HXM Suite has helped us deepen engagement for both managers and employees and strengthen their understanding of our people strategy as well as the tools and resources we offer,” said Zuncic. “Eliminating barriers between management and employees enables meaningful conversations around goals, performance, learning, career development, and succession.”</p>
  <p>Empowered by an integrated suite of SAP solutions, Chobani is even better equipped to continue to lead in making work better for all, elevate communities, and make the world a healthier place.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div><strong>To learn more, <a href="https://www.sap.com/HXMForward">watch “Forward with Baratunde Thurston” and Grace Zuncic</a>.</strong></div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Deb Lyons is senior director of Global Marketing for SAP SuccessFactors. <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/10/07/learn-how-chobani-creates-positive-change-for-its-dynamic-and-diverse-workforce/?sh=7f82450214ed">This also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a> Top image courtesy of Chobani.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-original-series-forward</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Introducing Forward, an SAP Original Series with Baratunde Thurston, Adam Grant, and Leading Brands]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/introducing-sap-original-series-forward</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/introducing-sap-original-series-forward</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The new SAP original series Forward offers the chance to learn how leading companies are grappling with trending issues. Learn more here.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-original-series-forward</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>