<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Leveraging SAP SuccessFactors Solutions: Five Ways User Experience Drives DEI&B Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/five-ways-sap-successfactors-ux-drives-deib</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/five-ways-sap-successfactors-ux-drives-deib</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactor's focus on UX helps businesses advance DEI&B by offering an interface that can address employee needs in the flow of work.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-performance-goals</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Great Resignation Points to a Serious Sustainability Issue]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/great-resignation-serious-sustainability-issue</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/great-resignation-serious-sustainability-issue</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Great Resignation is a sustainability warning to companies that have not focused on culture and leadership for a while. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Measuring the Carbon Footprint of Employees Can Help You Make More Informed and Strategic Business Decisions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/measuring-employee-carbon-footprint-business-decisions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/measuring-employee-carbon-footprint-business-decisions</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Executives can make informed decisions when considering the social and actual carbon footprint of employees in planning. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/experience-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How HR Professionals Can Get Past Data Overload and Analysis Paralysis]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/hr-professionals-get-past-data-overload-and-analysis-paralysis</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/hr-professionals-get-past-data-overload-and-analysis-paralysis</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The best decisions are made when you look at the right data at the right time and analyze it with the right tools. HR data is no exception.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Solving Diversity Problems: One Dream and A Lot of Data]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/solving-diversity-problems-dream-data</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/solving-diversity-problems-dream-data</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how people analytics, like SAP SuccessFactors solutions, can help HR to solve diversity problems through a data-driven HR culture.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Solving Diversity Problems: One Dream and A Lot of Data" src="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="solving-diversity-problems-one-dream-and-a-lot-of-data">Solving Diversity Problems: One Dream and A Lot of Data</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>On the third Monday of January each year, Martin Luther King Jr.’s birthday is honored in the U.S. King was an American Baptist minister and activist in the American civil rights movement. At the age of 35, he was the youngest man to have received the Nobel Peace Prize.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For many, Martin Luther King Jr.’s name is synonymous with his dream of a United States void of segregation and racism. And while his dream has been recognized globally, there is still much work to do to realize it.</p>
  <p>I recently sat down with <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/nigeldias/">Nigel Dias</a> to discuss how people analytics can support organizations’ diversity, equity, and inclusion (DE&#x26;I) strategy. Dias is the managing director of <a href="https://www.3nstrategy.com/">3n Strategy</a> as well as the chair and founder of the <a href="https://www.hranalyticsthinktank.com/">HR Analytics ThinkTank research</a>. He specializes in supporting businesses to make better HR decisions using people analytics and enabling data-driven HR culture.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="drive-performance-and-results-with-data-driven-insights-across-all-your-hr-processes-in-the-cloud">Drive performance and results with data-driven insights across all your HR processes in the cloud</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/workforce-planning-hr-analytics.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="q-how-does-people-analytics-help-hr-to-solve-diversity-problems">Q: How does people analytics help <a href="/topics/human-resources">HR</a> to solve diversity problems?</h2>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> What areas of your business have the lowest levels of diversity and inclusion, and how bad is the imbalance? Over the years, which HR decisions have caused and added to that inequality? Do different types of employees get promoted differently? Rewarded differently? Hired and retained faster or slower? If you do not change anything, how much worse will the inequality get? If you want to reduce inequality within five years, what HR strategies are most likely to achieve that goal?</p>
  <p>With or without data, organizations are making decisions to try to become fairer and more equal. The purpose of people analytics is to enable organizations to make better people decisions; in this case, about achieving diversity goals and solving inequality. By using HR data to answer questions, people analytics helps organizations to make better decisions increasing the likelihood of achieving diversity outcomes across the entire employee experience.</p>
  <h2 id="what-types-of-diversity-questions-are-sap-successfactors-customers-answering-using-their-data">What types of diversity questions are SAP SuccessFactors customers answering using their data?</h2>
  <p>In the 2020 Benchmarking study by the HR Analytics ThinkTank, <a href="https://www.hranalyticsthinktank.com/news-and-updates/hr-analytics-thinktank-benchmark-2020-release-r30/">93% of people analytics functions said they were actively working with diversity data</a>, which is no surprise given DE&#x26;I is a priority for most organizations.</p>
  <p>These people analytics functions are empowering their HR leaders to solve diversity problems by supplementing HR expertise with answers gleaned directly from data. From day one, people analytics teams can answer descriptive questions, providing facts about what happened in the past and over time. For example, within a particular job family or location, a specific minority group was three times more likely to be promoted than another. Other functions may go one step further, answering questions that diagnose a problem and use data to answer why an outcome has occurred in the past. For example, they might be able to answer why minority groups are more like to resign in particular locations.</p>
  <p>The more advanced functions, which research shows take two to three years to build, will create even more value. Some will be asked to spend more time answering critical questions, predicting how the gender equity gap will increase if nothing changes. The most advanced will provide answers to questions by prescribing what should be done; for example, what strategies are most likely to achieve 25% ethnic minority representation at board level within six years.</p>
  <h2 id="how-are-sap-successfactors-customers-using-workforce-analytics-and-report-stories-to-tackle-diversity-problems">How are SAP SuccessFactors customers using Workforce Analytics and Report Stories to tackle diversity problems?</h2>
  <p>The SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics solutions has the functionality to support organizations to tackle their diversity issues.</p>
  <p>In order to support strategic decision-making, they use SAP SuccessFactors Workforce Analytics to transform HR data into metrics and dashboards, showing end users the answers to questions about what has happened in the past, displaying insights and trends over time. For example, where is minority representation worsening? In particular grades, job families or geographies is there a difference in the way in which different workers are promoted or hired? Using SAP SuccessFactors Workforce Analytics, HR leaders can create better strategies and track progress over time.</p>
  <p>Using report stories, SAP SuccessFactors software can provide anyone in the entire business with a snapshot view of their business area. Stories will allow end users to check an answer at any given moment; for example, whether their recruitment pipeline contains a diverse selection of candidates or if all the resignations in the last month have been women.</p>
  <h2 id="what-steps-can-sap-successfactors-customers-take-to-prepare-for-diversity-analytics">What steps can SAP SuccessFactors customers take to prepare for diversity analytics?</h2>
  <p>The first thing that organizations should do is confirm the objectives that leaders are trying to achieve and identify the questions they need answered to make better choices. In our 2020 study, 94% of SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics leaders said their function was directly sponsored by an HR executive but only 32% were positive that they knew what their leader’s goals were. HR leaders need to clearly articulate what their diversity goals are and establish what questions they would like answered by the people analytics team.</p>
  <p>The second thing they should do is audit the foundations for data-driven HR success and prepare for the journey. According to the same study, only 42% of SAP SuccessFactors customers had a plan for what data to capture, only 16% were sure they knew how the people analytics team should be structured, and only six percent were confident that decision-makers understood how to use their insights in decision-making. A lot of diversity questions can be answered on day one using standard SAP SuccessFactors data, but a plan will be required to provide more complex answers over time.</p>
  <p>The final tip is to provide answers with evidence to help ensure that decision-makers are empowered to actually use the insight. If given the option, most HR and business professionals will welcome evidence that helps them achieve their goals, but they will only use the evidence if it is easy to access and formatted in a way that makes it easy to use in the context of their job. The organizations most successful with data-driven HR make sure that decision-makers are enabled with the right skills, and their dashboards create the best experience for users to find the answers they are looking for.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>To hear more on this topic, <a href="https://gateway.on24.com/wcc/eh/1892128/lp/3582695/jan-2022-solving-diversity-problems-using-your-successfactors-data">register</a> for the upcoming webinar (or listen to the recording), “<a href="https://gateway.on24.com/wcc/eh/1892128/lp/3582695/jan-2022-solving-diversity-problems-using-your-successfactors-data">Solving Diversity Problems using Your SAP SuccessFactors Data</a>” on January 26, or visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/workforce-planning-hr-analytics.html">the HR Analytics and Workforce Planning area of sap.com</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[People Analytics: Why Every HR Professional Needs to Be a Myth Buster]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/people-analytics-hr-myth-busting</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/people-analytics-hr-myth-busting</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read to learn how SAP SuccessFactors Workforce Analytics uses people analytics and data to test common HR assumptions and gut instincts.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aaaf9c57957ab674c85c85d0ed6f285fe279ebc0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aaaf9c57957ab674c85c85d0ed6f285fe279ebc0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1aaaf9c57957ab674c85c85d0ed6f285fe279ebc0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="People Analytics: Why Every HR Professional Needs to Be a Myth Buster" src="./media_1aaaf9c57957ab674c85c85d0ed6f285fe279ebc0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="people-analytics-why-every-hr-professional-needs-to-be-a-myth-buster">People Analytics: Why Every HR Professional Needs to Be a Myth Buster</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>HR professionals make countless decisions every day, and each one can have far-reaching consequences for both individuals and organizations alike. And like all of us, they tend to rely on their experience and gut instinct to make decisions. As people, we gain wisdom through experience, so why not use it, right?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The problem is that every organization is unique in ways that are often not appreciated. Each business has its own culture, strengths and weaknesses, geographic context and impacts, internal and community dynamics, and more that influence what works – and what doesn’t – from an HR perspective. Equally important, organizations continuously evolve, so strategies and actions that worked yesterday may not work in the future.</p>
  <p>The big “so what” is this: When HR professionals make their decisions based solely on their training and experience – even when tempered by the recommendations of others – it can lead to unintended outcomes. <strong>Experiences and assumptions must be tested within the current context in each unique business using people analytics</strong>.</p>
  <p>I like to think of this testing process as “myth busting,” which was popularized by the beloved show that goes by a similar name. In the HR world, this means using models of actual employee and organization data to test assumptions and gut instincts. The results are often surprising – and lead to different decisions and better outcomes for employees and the business.</p>
  <p>If this sounds like a lot of work, it’s not. The SAP SuccessFactors Workforce Analytics solution is so incredibly intuitive that just about anyone in HR can use it – no analytics training or expertise required. Plus, it comes with more than 2,000 prebuilt HR metrics. To help focus on the metrics that matter most, the “<a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/03/8254c834-d67d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">100 Critical People Analytics Questions: How Well Do You Really Know Your Workforce?</a>” brief includes a series of questions designed to help you and your organization understand HR metrics and help you make decisions that will support your executive strategy, drive revenues, manage costs, and mitigate human capital and business risks.</p>
  <p>To understand the power of people analytics and why myth busting is more important than ever, consider the findings uncovered by an SAP customer using SAP SuccessFactors Workforce Analytics. We showed them how to test widely embraced assumptions and preconceived notions within the HR department against actual business data. Here are just a few examples.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="tap-into-the-power-of-people-analytics">Tap into the power of people analytics</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/workforce-planning-hr-analytics.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="assumption-the-best-source-of-new-hires-is-your-current-employees-through-employee-referrals">Assumption: The Best Source of New Hires Is Your Current Employees Through Employee Referrals</h3>
  <p>When we looked at the data for this company, this was not necessarily the case. The best referrals came from top performers only; people referred from average performers did not typically become top performers and turned over at twice the typical rate.</p>
  <h3 id="assumption-commute-time-is-a-key-driver-of-turnover">Assumption: Commute Time Is a Key Driver of Turnover</h3>
  <p>This assumption did prove to be true. The data showed that for this business, turnover correlates to both commute time, travel cost, and geographic location, but not directly to distance. Using SAP SuccessFactors Workforce Analytics, the business was able to filter for various variables and identify real drivers of turnover as it relates to commuting.</p>
  <h3 id="assumption-employee-equity-awards-of-any-size-increase-retention">Assumption: Employee Equity Awards of Any Size Increase Retention</h3>
  <p>At this company, this proved to be true. Giving employees equity in the business through stock, for example, was highly correlated to employee retention.</p>
  <h3 id="assumption-industry-experience-is-a-key-factor-in-successful-salespeople">Assumption: Industry Experience Is a Key Factor in Successful Salespeople</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="how-well-do-you-really-know-your-workforce">How well do you really know your workforce?</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/03/8254c834-d67d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At this company, this long-held assumption did not prove to be true. In some positions studied, salespeople with little or no industry sales experience outperformed seasoned salespeople. This freed HR and hiring managers to focus on a new set of candidates for sales positions and increase the likelihood of having high performers.</p>
  <h3 id="assumption-previous-work-experience-can-be-an-indication-of-a-candidates-future-performance-and-expected-tenure">Assumption: Previous Work Experience Can Be an Indication of a Candidate’s Future Performance and Expected Tenure</h3>
  <p>This is a logical and common assumption that did not prove to be true at this business. SAP SuccessFactors Workforce Analytics revealed that, for this company, previous work experience is not an indicator of future performance or even tenure.</p>
  <h3 id="assumption-the-longer-a-person-is-with-the-company-the-better-their-performance-will-be">Assumption: The Longer a Person Is with the Company, the Better Their Performance Will Be</h3>
  <p>Again, this is a logical and common assumption, as employees tend to know their job better over time. But SAP SuccessFactors Workforce Analytics revealed that for this business, this is not true. The analytics showed that Millennials reach peak performance at one year in a position; after that, boredom sets in and they are ready to change jobs and learn something new. For older workers such as Baby Boomers, they reach peak performance at three years in a role. HR was able to use these data-driven insights to help create an evolving job program for Millennials and Baby Boomers that timed job changes around their respective peak performance timeframes.</p>
  <p>It’s important to note that these analytics results are unique to this business. Another firm in the same industry or other geographic location may uncover very different findings, which would in turn result in very different decisions by HR professionals. Every business needs to understand their own people-related data using people analytics.</p>
  <p>Did any of these findings surprise you and challenge your assumptions and experience? What kinds of assumptions and preconceived notions – many based on logic and past experience – might you be bringing to your decision-making process? I encourage you to become an HR myth buster by adopting SAP SuccessFactors Workforce Analytics. To learn more, visit us online at <a href="http://www.sap.com/people-analytics">www.sap.com/people-analytics</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Tammie Eldridge is in Solution Marketing at SAP SuccessFactors.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mirror, Mirror on the Wall: What the Heck Happened?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics-mirror-mirror-what-happened</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics-mirror-mirror-what-happened</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Workforce Analytics offers the insights HR needs to lead the workforce, accelerate change, and drive results.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1974d56d391031ac88bc9704aed317c0d03024efc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1974d56d391031ac88bc9704aed317c0d03024efc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1974d56d391031ac88bc9704aed317c0d03024efc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Mirror, Mirror on the Wall: What the Heck Happened?" src="./media_1974d56d391031ac88bc9704aed317c0d03024efc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="mirror-mirror-on-the-wall-what-the-heck-happened">Mirror, Mirror on the Wall: What the Heck Happened?</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In my conversations with HR executives, I often hear the same issue raised: Their talented team of HR professionals aren’t data scientists, and probably never will be, yet they really <em>need</em> to be today. For HR to deliver more value in today’s digital enterprises, they must be using data to make faster, more informed, and more strategic decisions.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The funny thing is, in most cases, HR staff already has all the data they need, lots of it. They just don’t know how to turn it into insights when they need them most – in the course of their day-to-day work. In recent years, organizations have made vast improvements in collecting and managing their data, including HR and people data. But most of it is stored in silos, making it almost impossible to provide the holistic view of how the organization is doing and what actions to take in the future to realize business goals.</p>
  <p>And without these insights, they are back to making countless decisions based on gut instinct, intuition, and habit. This can lead to less-than-optimal outcomes not just for the business, but for employees as well. For example, an HR professional may assume the best recruits come from employee referrals, which may not be true, or falsely assume that industry experience is a key factor in hiring successful salespeople.</p>
  <p>There’s a sign I have that captures the gist of this problem very well. It reads, “Mirror, mirror on the wall, what the heck happened?” When people make decisions based on the insights they’ve gleaned off the surface of things and the habits they’ve developed over the years, they are making decisions based on their intuition, not the hard evidence data can provide. Their insights and habits form the edges of the mirror, constraining their view and limiting their insight to only what they can see in front of them: themselves, their knowledge, and their gut instinct. When their decisions don’t yield what they expected, they say, “What the heck happened?” Even the outcomes can be hard for them to explain.</p>
  <p>HR analytics vastly expand what HR professionals can see and understand. In fact, with the right solutions, they can even get 360-degree views of their workforce, departments, teams, individual employees and contractors, and more. When built-for-purpose HR algorithms crunch all this data, the constraints of the mirror’s edges are gone. HR staff and executives can see and understand things that their natural mind and eyes would never be able to discern. They can make data-driven, unbiased decisions by looking at metrics, running scenarios, and predicting expected outcomes. And this empowers them to be more effective, unbiased, and strategic decision-makers who are not only more effective HR professionals, but better strategic advisors to the business. For example, they can:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Identify the promotion rate of minority employees at different levels.</li>
    <li>Monitor employee engagement to see if it increased or decreased in the last 12 months, six months, or three months.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The challenge, however, is making it easy for HR professionals to access and consume HR analytics – without having to bother IT for custom reports, data models, and other costly resource- and time-intensive requests. They need analytics at their fingertips, all the time.</p>
  <p>At SAP, we work to solve this with the SAP SuccessFactors Workforce Analytics solution. SAP SuccessFactors Workforce Analytics connects your people, data, and ideas from multiple sources to help enable fast and confident decision-making. It allows users to discover, visualize, plan, and predict, all in one place. And it works to democratize analytics so that anyone – even nontechnical HR professionals – can access and use it with ease, every day.</p>
  <p>SAP SuccessFactors Workforce Analytics helps you gain the insights you need to lead your workforce, accelerate change, and drive results with:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Standardized HR metrics</strong>: Take advantage of an extensive catalog of more than 2,000 pre-delivered HR and talent metrics. Each metric is described in terms HR professionals understand so they can interpret outputs with ease and make faster decisions.</li>
    <li><strong>Data trending</strong>: Track trends through time and across different periods, such as annual, quarterly, monthly, and seasonal time models.</li>
    <li><strong>Actionable analytics</strong>: Answer key questions about your workforce and spot risks and opportunities rapidly with visual, interactive HR analytics.</li>
    <li><strong>Integrated data foundation</strong>: Integrate data from multiple systems to create a solid data foundation and rely on SAP software to help manage data quality.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>I invite you to explore the “<a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/03/8254c834-d67d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">100 Critical People Analytics Questions: How Well Do You Really Know Your Workforce?</a>” whitepaper, which includes a series of questions designed to help you and your organization understand HR metrics and help you make decisions that will support your executive strategy, drive revenues, manage costs, and mitigate human capital and business risks. This document provides helpful tips to avoid one of the biggest risks in deploying a workforce metrics capability: “information overload.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="make-hr-decisions-based-on-accurate-workforce-intelligence-not-guesswork">Make HR decisions based on accurate workforce intelligence, not guesswork</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/workforce-analytics.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="find-more-information-on-this-topic-on-the-sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics-area-of-sapcom">Find more information on this topic on the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/workforce-analytics.html">SAP SuccessFactors Workforce Analytics area of sap.com</a>.</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-paper-how-well-do-you-really-know-your-workforce">Read the paper: How Well Do You Really Know Your Workforce?</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/03/8254c834-d67d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>