<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/talent-acquisition/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Building a Dynamic Organization with a Skills-Based Approach to Talent]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/building-dynamic-organization-skills-based-approach-to-talent</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/building-dynamic-organization-skills-based-approach-to-talent</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A skills-based approach to talent management can help organizations build a dynamic and resilient workforce. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/recruiting</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coles Reimagines Volume Hiring with AI and Automation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/coles-reimagines-volume-hiring-with-ai-and-automation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/coles-reimagines-volume-hiring-with-ai-and-automation</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Coles uses an AI-powered solution integrated with SAP SuccessFactors to help revolutionize its hiring process and gain speed and efficiency.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_149ed3b06f07dcdc3485b441db14e19620bea42c6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_149ed3b06f07dcdc3485b441db14e19620bea42c6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_149ed3b06f07dcdc3485b441db14e19620bea42c6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Coles Reimagines Volume Hiring with AI and Automation" src="./media_149ed3b06f07dcdc3485b441db14e19620bea42c6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="coles-reimagines-volume-hiring-with-ai-and-automation">Coles Reimagines Volume Hiring with AI and Automation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.colesgroup.com.au/home/">Coles Group</a>, one of Australia’s most trusted and iconic brands, is steadfast in delivering on its purpose to help Australians eat and live better every day. Through its core business as a full-service supermarket retailer, Coles engages with millions of customers every week in its 860 supermarkets throughout Australia. The group’s other areas of business include its Click &#x26; Collect online platform, network of liquor stores, and financial services with nearly 1,000 additional retail outlets.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Guided by the organization’s clear <a href="https://colescareers.com.au/au/en/culture">vision, purpose, and strategy</a>, Coles’ team of 120,000 employees is dedicated to making a difference in the lives of customers and the local communities it serves.</p>
  <p>In fiscal year 2020/21, Coles Group hired nearly 30,000 people to deliver on its business needs. Mike Virgo, head of Talent Acquisition for Coles Group, said this hiring volume was necessary to make sure the company was “positioned well to support our customers.”</p>
  <p>The business environment, however, dramatically shifted as the public health crisis of the pandemic unfolded, resulting in repeated lockdowns and restrictions. As a neighborhood retailer dependent on in-person interaction to deliver most of its services, Coles found its workforce impacted by the pandemic. Faced with supply chain disruptions, panic buying behaviors by consumers, high employee absenteeism, and increased turnover, Coles urgently needed to step up its volume and pace of hiring to support its customers.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="create-ai-powered-experiences-that-drive-real-competitive-advantage-with-sap-successfactors">Create AI-powered experiences that drive real competitive advantage with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Around 2020-2021, we started to experience one of the most significant shifts in the employment market we’d ever seen,” Virgo said in a <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1693098679863001ykJ6">session</a> at <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/successconnect/virtual.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SuccessConnect Virtual</a>. “It started to create huge challenges for organizations around the world – around how we attract, retain, and hire talent.”</p>
  <h2 id="catalyst-for-change-and-a-new-way-of-working">Catalyst for Change and a New Way of Working</h2>
  <p>To meet pressing business demands, Coles doubled its hiring volume from 30,000 to 60,000 people and increased recruitment advertising spend by a factor of three. Its talent acquisition team grew proportionally to manage the increased workload – but then labored under manual transactional activities that slowed processing times. As a result of the huge strain, variability in the candidate and hiring manager experience became noticeable.</p>
  <p>Due to the volume of work, Coles looked for ways to evolve its system to create more speed, efficiency, and scalability. With a list of criteria, Coles began to review technology solutions on the market to find one that could support its vision for a new way of working. “We wanted to reimagine how we recruit for our stores,” Virgo said. “We needed automation and AI to remove a lot of the manual work in our systems. We wanted to create more consistency and uplift the experiences we were giving our candidates and our hiring managers. And ultimately, [the solution] needed to drive commercial benefit for us.”</p>
  <p>As a key requirement, the new solution needed to integrate with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/what-is-hxm-suite.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a>. In 2020, as part of an organization-wide <a href="/australia/2021/09/08/how-coles-group-is-transforming-hr-during-the-global-pandemic">digital transformation</a> that introduced SAP S/4HANA and SAP Ariba solutions, Coles modernized its HR and payroll processing, replacing a patchwork of outdated systems with SAP SuccessFactors solutions. It became the first organization in the southern hemisphere to launch all modules of the SAP SuccessFactors portfolio in one go. With all HR processes unified on a single platform, Coles benefits from having a single source of truth for people data that is accurate and available in real time for the entire organization.</p>
  <h2 id="two-way-integration-ensures-single-source-of-truth-in-data">Two-Way Integration Ensures Single Source of Truth in Data</h2>
  <p>To help with the project, Coles chose <a href="https://www.phenom.com/">Phenom</a>, an SAP partner whose AI-powered Intelligent Talent Experience platform provides two-way integration with SAP SuccessFactors solutions. Virgo said the two-way integration “allows us to have a holistic view of the candidates that progress through the process, no matter whether the team is operating in Phenom or SAP SuccessFactors, and it allows SAP SuccessFactors to be our single source of truth.”</p>
  <p>There are several key benefits of Phenom’s solution at Coles. One is candidate attraction and engagement, which is achieved primarily through the Coles career site and chatbot. Another is recruiter automation and interview management, which provides automation and process efficiencies from when a job requisition is created in SAP SuccessFactors solutions and replicated into Phenom until a hiring manager chooses a candidate for the job. Once a candidate is chosen, the two-way integration enables the HR team to access the data in SAP SuccessFactors solutions and complete all compliance aspects, such as working rights, contract generation, and onboarding.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-how-phenom-can-compliment-sap-successfactors-recruiting">Learn how Phenom can compliment SAP SuccessFactors Recruiting</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-2001007992_live_v1">Find out</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The Coles team gains additional efficiencies in its onboarding programs through the application of robotic process automation (RPA) powered by two bots that work in the background: <em>Ashbotty</em> processes the working rights and <em>Usain Bot</em> processes onboarding and manages pending recruits. “They take a lot of the transactional, manual work that we used to have team members doing. It can do that quickly, accurately, and it can do that 24/7 – which is particularly important for us as a seven-days-a-week business,” Virgo said.</p>
  <h2 id="ai-powered-experiences-for-candidates-and-recruiters">AI-Powered Experiences for Candidates and Recruiters</h2>
  <p>Coles reimagined the candidate experience to launch a modern, tech-enabled career site – which has been chosen as a two-time winner of Australia’s Best Careers Site. The site includes an AI-powered chatbot to guide candidates as they look for information, search relevant job postings, and submit their applications. It also includes Coles’ Expression of Interest, always-on advertising that drives the growth of its talent pool and advances its talent marketing by reducing the need to advertise every role. A Hosted Apply process, facilitated by integrations with Phenom, presents a consistent candidate experience and increases the conversion rate on applications.</p>
  <p>Phenom AI Scheduling, a key part of Coles’ hiring experience, enables candidates to book themselves an available interview slot and automates the coordination of hiring team calendars. The new solution provides a fully mobile-enabled experience to meet the demands of candidates for an omni-channel, real-time experience where they can learn, read, and apply for jobs where and when they want.</p>
  <p>Inundated by nearly 1 million applications each year to review, Coles also took steps to elevate the recruiter experience and increase the speed and accuracy of candidate screening and job matching. It implemented Phenom Fit Score, an AI-powered feature that assesses a candidate’s suitability for an open role, based on location and optimal travel distances, availability, and working rights; then, assigns a fit score and surfaces the most closely matched candidates to the recruiters. In addition, the new solution empowers in-store managers to collaborate with recruiters to review candidates and make quick hiring decisions with confidence.</p>
  <h2 id="talent-pools-grow-with-improvements-to-hiring-speed-and-efficiency">Talent Pools Grow with Improvements to Hiring Speed and Efficiency</h2>
  <p>With the new augmented solution, Coles is experiencing tangible benefits across multiple categories and key metrics for success: time-to-fill is down six days; time-to-hire is down two days, which is impressive considering candidates can book the in-store interview up to two weeks in advance; and advertising spend is down 50%.</p>
  <p>Most notably for Coles as a people-centric organization is the development of its talent pool, now numbering 2 million potential candidates. It achieves an 85% application conversion rate on up to 1 million applications per year. Through its <a href="https://www.colesgroup.com.au/media-releases/?page=coles-group-ranked-1-for-recruitment-of-aussies-with-disabilities">commitment</a> to be a safe, inclusive, and diverse workplace, Coles has applied the new solution to provide greater accessibility for more diverse candidates, resulting in an increase of 24% more hiring for people who identify as having a disability.</p>
  <p>Virgo said that the talent acquisition team will continue to evolve its solution and assess more opportunities for AI and automation to bring value to the recruitment process. Although these technologies are not cure-alls for every recruitment scenario, they can save recruiting teams precious time and resources to focus on more high-touch interactions further down the recruiting funnel. In sharing lessons learned, Virgo noted, “I think the important call out is the level of automation you can inject in your process will likely diminish as the seniority, complexity, and requirements of your roles increase because they are likely to be more high touch, perhaps need more interpretation or judgment calls from your recruiters to identify who the right talent is for your organization.”</p>
  <p>Watch <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/successconnect/virtual.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SuccessConnect Virtual</a> on demand.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-sap-news-on-linkedin-to-stay-up-to-date">Follow SAP News on LinkedIn to stay up-to-date</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/recruiting</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cybersecurity a Top Priority at SAP, Early Talent Program Recognized by U.S. Government]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/cybersecurity-top-priority-sap-global-early-talent-program</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/cybersecurity-top-priority-sap-global-early-talent-program</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The two-year Global Security Early Talent program offers young professionals entry into the cybersecurity space at SAP. Learn more about it.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/cybersecurity</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Talent Strategies Procurement Leaders Can Employ to Lead Through the Polycrisis]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/talent-strategies-procurement-polycrisis</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/talent-strategies-procurement-polycrisis</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read about three key actions procurement leaders can take to address talent strategies in turbulent times, like a polycrisis.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[San Pablo Farmacia: Realizing the Power of Customer-Facing Employees as Brand Ambassadors]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/san-pablo-farmacia-employees-brand-ambassadors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/san-pablo-farmacia-employees-brand-ambassadors</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To become an employer of choice in Mexico, San Pablo Farmacia set out to improve its employee experience with SAP SuccessFactors solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Helping SAP Partner Delaware Meet Its Recruiting Needs]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/partner-talent-initiative-delaware-recruiting-needs</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/partner-talent-initiative-delaware-recruiting-needs</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Partner Talent Initiative helped Delaware UK find, recruit, and retain knowledgeable, skilled individuals to bolster its success.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Named a Leader in IDC MarketScape for Worldwide Modern Talent Acquisition]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/idc-marketscape-modern-talent-acquisition-sap-successfactors-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/idc-marketscape-modern-talent-acquisition-sap-successfactors-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In the IDC MarketScape for Worldwide Modern Talent Acquisition Suites 2022 Vendor Assessment, SAP SuccessFactors is a Leader!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/recruiting</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Without More Flexible Hours and Locations, 54% of Workers to Quit]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/without-flexibility-54-percent-to-quit</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/without-flexibility-54-percent-to-quit</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Global talent marketplaces help business and HR leaders head off tech worker shortages and power massive growth from digitalization.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1de65b4f8c903741801eae2d7b08e181383eefa42.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1de65b4f8c903741801eae2d7b08e181383eefa42.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1de65b4f8c903741801eae2d7b08e181383eefa42.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Without More Flexible Hours and Locations, 54% of Workers to Quit" src="./media_1de65b4f8c903741801eae2d7b08e181383eefa42.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="without-more-flexible-hours-and-locations-54-of-workers-to-quit">Without More Flexible Hours and Locations, 54% of Workers to Quit</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>On the cusp of economic growth fueled by a huge wave of digitalization, organizations in Australia and New Zealand (ANZ) are transforming talent management strategies to find the tech workers they need.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>A recent EY study found that nine out of 10 respondents worldwide, including workers from ANZ, wanted flexibility in their working hours and location. Fifty-four percent of employees were prepared to quit if they weren’t offered some form of flexibility. According to Thomas Barlow, head of SAP Fieldglass Centre of Excellence, Australia and New Zealand, the talent challenge is acute when it comes to tech employees.</p>
  <p>“Technology permeates every part of an organization, requiring people with new skills in areas like data science, artificial intelligence (AI), machine learning, blockchain, robotics, and the Internet of Things (IoT). Organizations need to build a global workforce that meets digitalized business demands,” said Barlow. “Workers with specialized expertise typically operate in a highly flexible, agile way. They’re likelier to be more mobile, in charge of managing their own learning experiences and careers. They also may not be located nearby.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="put-employees-at-the-heart-of-everything-you-do-with-sap-successfactors-software">Put employees at the heart of everything you do with SAP SuccessFactors software</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="complete-talent-pool-data-creates-business-resilience">Complete Talent Pool Data Creates Business Resilience</h2>
  <p>The latest data from the <a href="https://www.abs.gov.au/">Australian Bureau of Statistics</a> revealed how <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> lockdowns have accelerated the skills shortage. <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com.au/australia-skills-shortage-wage-growth-2021-6">Business Insider Australia</a> reported one in four Australian businesses were struggling to find suitable staff to fill job vacancies. In a recent COVID-19 Resilience Ranking from <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/graphics/covid-resilience-ranking/">Bloomberg</a>, Australia dropped 21 points compared to over 50 other major economies worldwide. To meet this workforce challenge, leaders are turning to connected data.</p>
  <p>“As companies build more flexible, cross-border workforces, they need full transparency of all employees, including permanent and external workers,” said Barlow. “With complete workforce data, companies are better prepared to identify and deploy the right people with the right skills to support growth forecasts, or pivot quickly in case of unexpected disruptions like the pandemic.”</p>
  <p>AI-based talent pools like <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-0000056483_live_v1">WillHire</a> have emerged to help organizations quickly match open positions with pre-qualified candidates from the global external labor pool. Integrated with <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/">SAP Fieldglass solutions</a> and available on <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/">SAP Store</a>, WillHire curates emerging talent who have the niche skills that support digital transformation.</p>
  <h2 id="global-people-strategy-is-core-to-business-execution">Global People Strategy Is Core to Business Execution</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="five-workplace-norms-innovative-hxm-leaders-are-replacing-right-now">Five Workplace Norms Innovative HXM Leaders Are Replacing Right Now</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/11/five-workplace-norms-innovative-hxm-leaders-are-replacing">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Historical talent strategies distinguished between permanent full-time employees and external workers who were typically hired to pitch in as a short-term business fix. With the advent of global marketplaces, talent strategies have transformed to flex with changing business demands.</p>
  <p>“Companies need to embrace fluidity, looking at talent from the perspective of business results, as opposed to permanent versus contract workers,” said Marc Havercroft, global chief customer officer at SAP SuccessFactors. “For example, organizations using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a> and SAP Fieldglass solutions can easily see how many people work for the company irrespective of an end date on their contract. Data reveals where people are, what skills they have, and their work quality over time. Organizations can quickly identify gaps and find the additional specialists with the latest skills anywhere in the world.”</p>
  <p>One SAP customer, an established ANZ-based financial services organization, needed to digitally transform to attract the next generation of customers. Using both SAP SuccessFactors and SAP Fieldglass solutions, leaders sourced external tech experts to build digital services, pairing them with existing employees who shared their business knowledge while gaining new skills.</p>
  <p>At the other end of the spectrum, a native digital banking startup in ANZ relied on both SAP solutions to help guide talent investments in business specialists with go-to-market and customer upselling and engagement capabilities. These experts rounded out the existing team’s tech-centric skills.</p>
  <h2 id="employee-experience-attracts-global-talent-pool">Employee Experience Attracts Global Talent Pool</h2>
  <p>The same EY study found that worldwide, 72% of respondents believed remotely working would likely have a negative impact on their career opportunities. That percentage was higher (82%) among employees in Asia-Pacific. With greater visibility across the entire workforce, companies can create a strong employee experience in a hybrid ‘work-from-anywhere’ world.</p>
  <p>“Full transparency into an organization’s workforce capabilities and recruitment needs allows leaders to adopt a continuous learning culture with benefits to the business and employees,” said Havercroft. “People want to learn, making their work enjoyable and career secure. They want to be valued globally for their skills and knowledge, which is probably the biggest benefit of a global talent marketplace.”</p>
  <p>Business resiliency demands new talent management strategies to match recruitment programs with forecasted growth opportunities, factoring in skills and roles that might not exist yet but are surely on the horizon. For example, SAP’s recent acquisition of <a href="/2021/08/sap-acquires-swooptalent-intellectual-property-to-boost-talent-data-intelligence">SwoopTalent’s IP</a>, an AI-based talent data platform, will allow companies to explore ‘what-if’ scenarios, combining real-world total workforce data to improve ROI on talent investments and other decisions as businesses evolve. Massive growth from digitalization is all well and good. Just make sure you have the business and tech experts on hand to power it.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler.</em><br><em>This also appeared on <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/10/05/54-percent-of-workers-plan-to-quit-without-more-flexible-hours-and-locations/?sh=1148b4b83bab">SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intelligent Internal Recruitment Powered by SAP Business Technology Platform]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/intelligent-internal-recruitment-powered-by-sap-business-technology-platform</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/intelligent-internal-recruitment-powered-by-sap-business-technology-platform</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Doosan and SAP developed an internal job posting platform to hire employees from within the company through intelligent data screening.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c53d3fd0eba13a082df86a6b743cdf6d80b501a4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c53d3fd0eba13a082df86a6b743cdf6d80b501a4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c53d3fd0eba13a082df86a6b743cdf6d80b501a4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Intelligent Internal Recruitment Powered by SAP Business Technology Platform" src="./media_1c53d3fd0eba13a082df86a6b743cdf6d80b501a4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="intelligent-internal-recruitment-powered-by-sap-business-technology-platform">Intelligent Internal Recruitment Powered by SAP Business Technology Platform</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Doosan is a multinational conglomerate founded in 1896 with more than 30,000 employees spread across the globe today. The highly diversified manufacturing and service companies operate worldwide, offering services such as electronic components production or logistics equipment manufacturing.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Doosan’s business portfolio consists of diverse industries, including the heavy industry that mainly focuses on power plants generated by fuel, nuclear, or sustainable resources such as solar and wind, the construction equipment industry that is renowned for Bobcat compact tractors and Doosan forklifts, as well as the high-tech industry that includes robotics, electronic components, and network equipment manufacturing.</p>
  <p>The goal of the human resources department of Doosan Holdings was to maximize work engagement level. Doosan improved individual employee satisfaction by providing opportunities for self-driven career development. The company provided HR applications for co-growth, both on the employee and corporate side, such as through matching talented employees with appropriate job opportunities across the company. This transparency allowed employees to be aware of vacant positions.</p>
  <p>The newly designed internal job posting process spans from internal job search and application to screening and anonymized reporting. After a review is conducted through the anonymized blind report and the document screening is completed, the selected applicants can be interviewed.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-the-innovation-culture-toolkit">Explore the Innovation Culture Toolkit</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://experience.sap.com/designservices/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/InnovationCultureToolkit_forVirtualCollaboration.pdf">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="defining-the-scope-with-all-relevant-stakeholders">Defining the Scope with All Relevant Stakeholders</h2>
  <p>After defining the broad scope of the use case, the so-called exploration phase of the joint project began, aiming to clarify the purpose of the project together with all relevant stakeholders. The project team conducted a virtual exploration workshop, using the collaboration tool <a href="https://www.mural.co/playmakers/sap-apphaus">MURAL</a> and the <a href="https://experience.sap.com/designservices/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/InnovationCultureToolkit_forVirtualCollaboration.pdf">Innovation Culture Toolkit for virtual collaboration</a> by SAP AppHaus. Based on interviews with relevant stakeholders from Doosan, objectives, expectations, the scope, as well as roles and responsibilities, could be clarified.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d306f135ab9697818039de1b965741ac43d7403d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d306f135ab9697818039de1b965741ac43d7403d.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1d306f135ab9697818039de1b965741ac43d7403d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1d306f135ab9697818039de1b965741ac43d7403d.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="447">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Click to enlarge.</em></p>
  <h2 id="prototyping-and-iteration-based-on-the-needs-of-end-users">Prototyping and Iteration Based on the Needs of End Users</h2>
  <p>In the discovery phase, the project team conducted end-user interviews with HR managers from Doosan to identify their needs and pain points related to the internal recruitment process. After synthesizing the gained insights, the <a href="/topics/sap-apphaus">SAP AppHaus</a> team created a rapid user interface (UI) design prototype.</p>
  <p>End-user insights and needs served as valuable assets in deciding which features were needed and what exactly had to be prioritized in the development of the solution. Low-fidelity prototypes could be iterated regularly so that a user-friendly, tailored solution would be developed.</p>
  <p>“In working with Doosan, we developed a use case along SAP’s human-centered approach to innovation. We decided to implement an enhanced job candidate screening through specific job requisitions,” said Kay Schmitteckert, developer, SAP Strategic Customer Engagements. “I really enjoyed working together with SAP AppHaus and Doosan Digital Innovation.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_162ff9925ba12502deb5484a6795aacffc46bdac0.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_162ff9925ba12502deb5484a6795aacffc46bdac0.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_162ff9925ba12502deb5484a6795aacffc46bdac0.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_162ff9925ba12502deb5484a6795aacffc46bdac0.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="430">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Click to enlarge.</em></p>
  <h2 id="the-enabler-of-the-use-case-sap-business-technology-platform">The Enabler of the Use Case: SAP Business Technology Platform</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-btp-the-platform-for-the-intelligent-enterprise">SAP BTP: The platform for the Intelligent Enterprise</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The core of the use case is the candidate screening functionality for the internal hiring process, built with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a>. Its technological capabilities allowed Doosan to transform into an intelligent enterprise using customized functions on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/extension-suite.html">SAP Extension Suite</a> as well as SAP SuccessFactors solutions.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12d41132d29ce8ea0d2372a1687754b1e0ac7295f.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12d41132d29ce8ea0d2372a1687754b1e0ac7295f.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_12d41132d29ce8ea0d2372a1687754b1e0ac7295f.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_12d41132d29ce8ea0d2372a1687754b1e0ac7295f.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="457">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Click to enlarge.</em></p>
  <p>It automatically generates candidate scores based on the results of the past competency evaluation and provides appropriate recommendations, priorities, and anonymous reports.</p>
  <p>The anonymized reports created enhance the applicants’ experience and avoid exposure during the internal recruitment process. Finally, HR managers can quickly assess the suitability of multiple candidates through the in-depth evaluation of candidate information provided.</p>
  <h2 id="an-intelligent-and-cutting-edge-hiring-platform">An Intelligent and Cutting-Edge Hiring Platform</h2>
  <p>Doosan’s internal job posting project is a prime use case for future HR management, unfolding its strengths in two dimensions:</p>
  <ol>
    <li>At the process level, the developed solution represents a cutting-edge increase in HR process efficiency leading to high time and cost savings.</li>
    <li>At the cultural level, the platform contributes to a culture underlining the possibility of internal job transfers, which ultimately leads to more diversified employee skill sets, highly engaged employees, and lower fluctuation.</li>
  </ol>
  <p>“It was a great opportunity to experience the whole process from UX to design thinking, development, and collaboration. It was a delightful experience as an SAP Fiori developer due to the strong backup of UX designers that made such development possible,” said Minchoul Jung, project manager and SAP Fiori developer l, Doosan Digital Innovation. “We will develop the last components on this basis and create value when set in production.”</p>
  <p>The integration and extension capabilities of SAP Business Technology Platform are the key foundation of the use case. The solution provides a suitable candidate list through data screening based on the existing data on SAP Success Factors solutions. The more data evaluated, the more intelligent and effective the HR process will finally become.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Esther Lee is a project lead and senior UX design specialist at SAP AppHaus Seoul.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>