<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/microsoft/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Joule to Integrate with Microsoft Copilot for a Unified Work Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/joule-microsoft-copilot-unified-work-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/joule-microsoft-copilot-unified-work-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is bringing its generative AI copilot Joule together with Microsoft Copilot for Microsoft 365 for deep bi-directional integration.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/microsoft</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Concur Enriches Travel and Expense Experiences with Generative AI at SAP Concur Fusion 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-concur-enriches-travel-and-expense-experiences-with-generative-ai-at-sap-concur-fusion-2024</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-concur-enriches-travel-and-expense-experiences-with-generative-ai-at-sap-concur-fusion-2024</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP Concur Fusion 2024, SAP announced new updates reimagining travel and expense management and new capabilities powered by generative AI.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/microsoft</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI Built for Business]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-sapphire-business-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-sapphire-business-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Turning AI technology advancement into business impact remains a challenge for many companies, SAP's unique approach to AI can help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/microsoft</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-digital-assistant</category>
            <category>product/sap-extended-warehouse-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-signavio-process-manager</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-transportation-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Microsoft Collaborate on Joint Generative AI Offerings to Help Customers Address the Talent Gap]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-microsoft-joint-generative-ai-offerings-talent-gap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-microsoft-joint-generative-ai-offerings-talent-gap</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Together, SAP and Microsoft are using the latest in enterprise-ready generative AI innovations to help customers conquer the talent gap.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/microsoft</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Next-Level ERP Collaboration: The Evolution of SAP S/4HANA Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/next-level-erp-collaboration-sap-s-4hana-cloud-microsoft</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/next-level-erp-collaboration-sap-s-4hana-cloud-microsoft</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Microsoft are taking ERP collaboration to the next level with SAP S/4HANA Cloud and Microsoft Teams. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/microsoft</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microsoft Selects RISE with SAP to Drive Business Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/microsoft-selects-rise-with-sap-business-innovation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/microsoft-selects-rise-with-sap-business-innovation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Microsoft selects RISE with SAP to deploy new capabilities and technologies faster and run on a flexible cloud-first solution. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/microsoft</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-erp</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kick Start for the First Sovereign Cloud Platform for the Public Sector in Germany: SAP and Arvato Systems Announce Partnership]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/sap-arvato-systems-partnership</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/sap-arvato-systems-partnership</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Arvato Systems intend to invest in a new company that will provide a sovereign cloud infrastructure for the German public sector.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b7aaad0a3370f26330596ee7a95766f2be5855bd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b7aaad0a3370f26330596ee7a95766f2be5855bd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b7aaad0a3370f26330596ee7a95766f2be5855bd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Kick Start for the First Sovereign Cloud Platform for the Public Sector in Germany: SAP and Arvato Systems Announce Partnership" src="./media_1b7aaad0a3370f26330596ee7a95766f2be5855bd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="kick-start-for-the-first-sovereign-cloud-platform-for-the-public-sector-in-germany-sap-and-arvato-systems-announce-partnership">Kick Start for the First Sovereign Cloud Platform for the Public Sector in Germany: SAP and Arvato Systems Announce Partnership</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) and Arvato Systems today announced the intent to invest in a new German company that will provide a sovereign cloud infrastructure for the German public sector.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This cloud infrastructure is designed to meet the unique national requirements set out in the German cloud strategy. There will be no network dependencies on systems outside Germany, and the independent operation of all services is ensured. All data will be processed and stored in Germany, and all services will be delivered from within Germany.</p>
  <p>A completely new company is to be established to provide a sovereign cloud for the public sector in Germany. The aim of the new company is to drive digital transformation in Germany. It is planned that, in addition to SAP, Arvato Systems will also become a shareholder and additionally will take over operations.</p>
  <p>The offering will be based on the broadly adopted Microsoft Azure platform and related Microsoft services, including cutting-edge collaboration and productivity solutions of Microsoft 365 along with industry-leading SAP® business applications and tools. Approved third-party providers can also offer their applications on the platform.</p>
  <p>The planned new company will provide a broad catalog of digital solutions to support the digitalization efforts of the German government to accelerate the use of cloud technology in the German public sector and will meet the strict requirements put in place by the Bundesamt für Sicherheit in der Informationstechnik (BSI).</p>
  <p>The offering of this new company will be a vendor-neutral stack built on an open platform based on Microsoft’s secure cloud technology, and it will offer full interoperability with other tools. With that, the infrastructure can support a variety of cloud solutions from independent vendors including open source software. Already today, 60% of the workloads on Azure are Linux-based.</p>
  <h2 id="a-sovereign-cloud-platform-from-a-technical-operational-and-legal-perspective">A Sovereign Cloud Platform from a Technical, Operational and Legal Perspective</h2>
  <p>This offering is designed to meet the technical, operational and legal sovereignty requirements of the German government. It will be governed by German law and address the data sovereignty needs of the German public sector.</p>
  <p>The cloud infrastructure will be owned by the new German entity. Furthermore, it is planned that the technical operation will be taken over by Arvato Systems as an experienced infrastructure operator. The infrastructure will be strictly separated from Microsoft’s global data center infrastructure and the existing public cloud infrastructure in Germany.</p>
  <p>“This partnership represents a breakthrough approach for cloud-based innovation,” said Christian Klein, CEO of SAP. “Together we’ll provide a unique solution that not only meets the highest standards of cloud-based technology but also meets the strictest requirements of data sovereignty. This one-of-a-kind collaboration unlocks the potential of digital transformation for the German government and beyond.”</p>
  <p>“We are very pleased about the expansion of our partnership and the joint plans with SAP,” said Matthias Moeller, CEO of the Arvato Systems Group and CIO of Bertelsmann. “At Arvato Systems, we have been supporting large infrastructures, including those in the public sector, for many years and understand their unique requirements. The intended partnership offers the best outcome from various perspectives: to use the best available technology and secure German sovereignty interests while accelerating digitalization for citizens and employees alike.”</p>
  <p>“As digital technology continues to rapidly transform work and life, we have a critical opportunity to ensure these advancements benefit people and organizations everywhere, including in Germany,” said Satya Nadella, Chairman and CEO, Microsoft. “Together with SAP and Arvato Systems, we will create a cloud platform that meets the requirements of the German public sector to help drive digital transformation across the country.”</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-power-of-partnership-with-sap">Learn more about the power of partnership with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/partner.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="about-arvato-systems">About Arvato Systems</h3>
  <p>Global IT specialist Arvato Systems supports major companies in Digital Transformation. About 3,000 staff in over 25 locations stand for in-depth technology expertise, industry knowledge, and focus on customer requirements. Working as a team, we develop innovative IT solutions, transition our clients into the Cloud, integrate digital processes, and take on IT systems operation and support. As a part of the Bertelsmann-owned Arvato network, we have the unique capability to work across the entire value chain. Our business relationships are personal; we work with our clients as partners so that together we can achieve long-term success. <a href="https://arvato-systems.com/">arvato-systems.com</a></p>
  <h3 id="about-sap">About SAP</h3>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want — without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong> To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Marcus Winkler, SAP, +49 6227 7-67497, <a href="mailto:marcus.winkler@sap.com">marcus.winkler@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a><br>Marcus Metzner, Arvato Systems, +49 5241 80-88242, <a href="mailto:press@arvato-systems.de">press@arvato-systems.de</a>, CET</p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2020 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2022 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>industry/public-sector</category>
            <category>news-tag/microsoft</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Sales Cloud and Microsoft Teams Help Businesses Grow by Removing Barriers to Remote Selling]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-sales-cloud-and-microsoft-teams-remote-selling</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-sales-cloud-and-microsoft-teams-remote-selling</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The integration of SAP Sales Cloud and Microsoft Teams is now available to all customers. Read the announcement.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17b8952c43a637b0afef6fb6de63bf78b580e5e7d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17b8952c43a637b0afef6fb6de63bf78b580e5e7d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17b8952c43a637b0afef6fb6de63bf78b580e5e7d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Sales Cloud and Microsoft Teams Help Businesses Grow by Removing Barriers to Remote Selling" src="./media_17b8952c43a637b0afef6fb6de63bf78b580e5e7d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-sales-cloud-and-microsoft-teams-help-businesses-grow-by-removing-barriers-to-remote-selling">SAP Sales Cloud and Microsoft Teams Help Businesses Grow by Removing Barriers to Remote Selling</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-whats-happening-at-sap-customer-experience-live-unplugged">Learn more about what's happening at SAP Customer Experience LIVE: Unplugged</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-cx-live-2021/en/home">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that the integration of the SAP Sales Cloud solution with Microsoft Teams is now available to all customers. SAP made this announcement at the <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-cx-live-2021/en/home">SAP Customer Experience LIVE: Unplugged</a> event being held October 26–27, 2021.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In today’s world, “remote selling” is no longer an exception, it has become the norm. Sales professionals across the globe use Microsoft Teams to meet with customers and engage in sales activities. The integration of SAP Sales Cloud and Microsoft teams enables users to access customer and sales information instantly from Microsoft Teams. While in customer meetings, they can update records in real time without ever leaving the Microsoft Teams environment.</p>
  <p>“Traditional sales automation solutions are record-keeping tools that focus on performing administrative tasks,” said Sameer Patel, chief marketing and solutions officer of Customer Experience at SAP. “They can distract sales professionals from high-value activities. SAP Sales Cloud is different because it removes complexities, adapts to changing needs of sales professionals and strives to make it easier for them to focus on customers and closing deals. The integration with Microsoft Teams is another great example of how SAP makes it easier for sales professionals to engage with customers and grow revenues.”</p>
  <p>“Microsoft Teams is the new way people and sales professionals connect, collaborate and stay in the flow of work in today’s hybrid world,” said Nicole Herskowitz, Microsoft Teams general manager. “We are excited that partners like SAP are building Teams Apps and native integration to enable collaborative solutions that help our mutual customers improve team productivity and better serve customers.”</p>
  <p>“It is more important than ever to eliminate friction in the sales process, remove administrative tasks and provide our sales professionals with the right sales solutions that help them focus on our customers and engage with them anywhere and anytime,” said Gamze Senkal, manager of Information Technology at <a href="https://www.eczacibasi.com.tr/en/brands/companies-building-products">Eczacıbaşı Building Products</a>, part of one of the leading industrial holding companies in Turkey. “With the integration of SAP Sales Cloud and Microsoft Teams, our sales professionals can access the latest customer information with one click from Microsoft Teams and are able to update sales records in real time without ever leaving Microsoft Teams. By eliminating duplicate data entry and record keeping, SAP Sales Cloud helps ensure that our sales professionals are focusing on our customers and value-added activities.”</p>
  <p>To attend <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-cx-live-2021/en/home">SAP Customer Experience LIVE: Unplugged</a>, please check out the <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-cx-live-2021/en/home#agenda">agenda</a> and <a href="https://vshow.on24.com/clients/SAP/3309743/">register</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-sales-cloud-connect-with-every-customer">SAP Sales Cloud: Connect with every customer</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/sales.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong></p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as a sustainable intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into sustainable intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want — without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Samantha Finnegan, +1 (415) 377-0475, <a href="mailto:samantha.finnegan@sap.com">samantha.finnegan@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/microsoft</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-customer-experience-live</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microsoft Moves HR to the Cloud with SAP SuccessFactors]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sap-successfactors-at-microsoft-hr-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sap-successfactors-at-microsoft-hr-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Microsoft has been on a journey to transform its people strategy. Learn more about SAP SuccessFactors at Microsoft.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10721d47f45f641339803a1b91af08b8c6a41dad7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10721d47f45f641339803a1b91af08b8c6a41dad7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10721d47f45f641339803a1b91af08b8c6a41dad7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Microsoft Moves HR to the Cloud with SAP SuccessFactors" src="./media_10721d47f45f641339803a1b91af08b8c6a41dad7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="microsoft-moves-hr-to-the-cloud-with-sap-successfactors">Microsoft Moves HR to the Cloud with SAP SuccessFactors</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-the-hr-track-at-sapphire-now">Explore the HR track at SAPPHIRE NOW</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapphirenow2021/portal/page/track-hr">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Microsoft has successfully completed the implementation of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/employee-central-hris.html">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</a> for its 140,000 employees in 109 countries. For the first time, Microsoft now has all of its employees on a single human resources (HR) platform, which runs on Microsoft Azure.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Microsoft has been on a journey to transform its people strategy in order to better understand the behaviors, pain points and motivations of its employees, and attract skilled, curious, and passionate talent.</p>
  <p>After decades of running its HR operations on the on-premise SAP ERP Human Capital Management solution and multiple homegrown applications, the company needed a cloud platform that could deliver on its mobile-first, cloud-first philosophy and provide a foundation for future transformations. It selected <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a> for the global and local reach that it provides in both data and regulatory needs and an open platform that can easily be integrated with other solutions in its larger ecosystem.</p>
  <p>With many Microsoft employees continuing to work remotely or in a <a href="https://blogs.microsoft.com/blog/2021/03/22/the-philosophy-and-practice-of-our-hybrid-workplace/">hybrid model</a>, it is even more important today that it has the technology to connect a distributed workforce, encourage collaboration, and keep employees engaged and inspired. Since implementing SAP SuccessFactors HXM Suite, including <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/products.html#active_tab=item_1602592257238">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</a>, Microsoft can provide a consistent employee experience for its entire global workforce – regardless of location or role. SAP SuccessFactors solutions will serve as the foundation for the innovations Microsoft is developing to manage the changes and impacts of the hybrid workplace</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="create-a-more-flexible-engaged-workforce-and-a-more-resilient-business">Create a more flexible, engaged workforce and a more resilient business</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Since migrating to cloud-based HXM solutions from SAP, Microsoft has increased the quality of data in its HR system, thus increasing the efficiencies in payroll and other critical processes. It also has the ability to extend and create delightful experiences for their employees. With solutions including <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/employee-onboarding.html">SAP SuccessFactors Onboarding</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/corporate-lms.html">SAP SuccessFactors Learning</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/succession-development.html">SAP SuccessFactors Succession &#x26; Development</a>, and now <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/employee-central-hris.html">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</a>, the company has also simplified and unified its HR processes and can access data faster. Not only has this improved visibility into the workforce, it has elevated HR’s ability to provide timely, accurate insights in real time.</p>
  <p>“As we continue Microsoft’s HR transformation journey, it’s been critical to have a cloud platform that can adapt and grow with our needs, especially as the needs of the workforce change,” said Rajamma Krishnamurthy, senior director of HR Technology, Microsoft. “In fact, we completed the implementation of SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central in more than 90 countries in a completely virtual environment due to the global <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> by adopting an agile approach. Moving forward, SAP will continue to be a critical partner in helping use data to design engaging, inclusive experiences for all of our global employees.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Angelique Slagle is head of SAP SuccessFactors for North America.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/microsoft</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Microsoft: How We Simplify Business Collaboration]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/02/microsoft-teams-sap-solutions-simplify-business-collaboration</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/02/microsoft-teams-sap-solutions-simplify-business-collaboration</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[By integrating SAP solutions with Microsoft Teams, the companies are lifting collaboration to the next level. Learn more about what's planned.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>news-tag/microsoft</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Microsoft Expand Partnership and Integrate Microsoft Teams Across Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/sap-and-microsoft-expand-partnership-integrate-teams</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/sap-and-microsoft-expand-partnership-integrate-teams</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Expanding the SAP and Microsoft partnership includes integrating Microsoft Teams with SAP solutions and accelerating SAP S/4HANA on Microsoft Azure.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_187aeff3904fd1189128bc0a8dc382d908b9af431.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_187aeff3904fd1189128bc0a8dc382d908b9af431.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_187aeff3904fd1189128bc0a8dc382d908b9af431.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP and Microsoft Expand Partnership and Integrate Microsoft Teams Across Solutions" src="./media_187aeff3904fd1189128bc0a8dc382d908b9af431.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-and-microsoft-expand-partnership-and-integrate-microsoft-teams-across-solutions">SAP and Microsoft Expand Partnership and Integrate Microsoft Teams Across Solutions</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-expanding-the-sap-and-microsoft-partnership">Read more: Expanding the SAP and Microsoft Partnership</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/01/expanding-microsoft-sap-partnership">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF and REDMOND, Wash.</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) and Microsoft Corp. announced plans to integrate Microsoft Teams with SAP’s intelligent suite of solutions. The companies also formalized an extensive expansion of an existing strategic partnership to accelerate the adoption of SAP S/4HANA on Microsoft Azure. This builds on a <a href="/2019/10/sap-microsoft-partnership-cloud-migration-offerings">joint commitment by the companies</a> to simplify and streamline customers’ journeys to the cloud.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“New ways of working, collaborating and interacting completely transform how we operate,” said Christian Klein, SAP CEO and member of the Executive Board. “By integrating Microsoft Teams across our solution portfolio, we will bring collaboration to the next level, jointly determining the future of work and enabling the frictionless enterprise. Our trusted partnership with Microsoft is focused on continuously advancing customer success. That’s why we are also expanding interoperability with Azure.”</p>
  <p>Much has changed in the last year as work has become more virtual, increasing reliance on Microsoft Teams for meetings, communication and collaboration. To facilitate these business and societal changes, SAP and Microsoft are building new integrations between Microsoft Teams and SAP solutions, such as SAP S/4HANA, SAP SuccessFactors offerings, and SAP Customer Experience. This can enable innovation, increase employee productivity and engagement, deliver collaborative learning and support global growth. These integrations are planned for delivery in mid-2021.</p>
  <p>“The case for digital transformation has never been more urgent,” Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella said. “By bringing together the power of Azure and Teams with SAP’s solutions, we will help more organizations harness the power of the cloud so they can more quickly adapt and innovate going forward.”</p>
  <p>The companies also are expanding their <a href="http://www.sap.com/microsoft">endorsed cloud partnership</a> announced in 2019, to introduce new offerings in cloud automation and integration for SAP S/4HANA on Microsoft Azure. Together, Microsoft and SAP are expanding the ability to run a mission-critical intelligent enterprise on Azure while helping customers modernize their enterprise applications. SAP and Microsoft will provide customers with:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Simplification</strong> when moving on-premise editions of SAP ERP to SAP S/4HANA in the cloud. In addition to the industry-specific journey maps to the cloud and reference architectures, SAP and Microsoft will continue to co-innovate around SAP S/4HANA on Azure.</li>
    <li><strong>Expanded joint engagements with customers and partners.</strong> In addition to product integration work, SAP, Microsoft and system integrator partners will continue to provide digital enterprise road maps for customers. This includes immediate and actionable reference architectures and technical guidance to help customers on their journey to the cloud.</li>
    <li><strong>Increased investments in platform and infrastructure</strong>. The companies will further develop automated migrations, improved operations, monitoring and security.</li>
  </ul>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/01/ca0f4c25-c87d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Customers</a> broadly favor Azure when moving on-premise SAP S/4HANA to the cloud.</p>
  <p>“As part of our overall transformation, we transitioned to SAP S/4HANA,” said John Hill, <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/01/5ae05150-c87d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Carhartt’s</a> chief information officer and senior vice president of Business Planning. “Running it on Microsoft Azure provides the velocity, availability, scalability and elasticity we need for more visibility and better efficiency across our business. The pandemic struck as we were in the middle of our SAP implementation, so by using Teams, we were able to continue to work on the project, stay on schedule and keep everyone informed. The combination of SAP and Microsoft was especially helpful during a challenging time.”</p>
  <p>“SAP S/4HANA has given us real-time visibility into our inventory, which is crucial for us as a pharmacy and healthcare retail company during the pandemic,” said Francesco Tinto, Walgreens Boots Alliance’s senior vice president and global chief information officer. “We chose to run SAP S/4HANA on Azure because of its agility and flexibility to scale up and out quickly to meet our business needs. Now we have access to our data in one place so we can offer the best possible customer experience online and in our stores. Microsoft Teams coupled with SAP solutions helped us overcome business continuity challenges and enabled our employees to collaborate very effectively despite the shift from office to remote work.”</p>
  <p>“When it comes to our customers delivering personal protective equipment, we can’t be late, so we rely on SAP and Microsoft to provide the digital backbone that’s essential to keeping our supply chain running smoothly,” said Helge Brummer, <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/01/ec91671f-c87d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Coats’</a> vice president of Technical Infrastructure, Support &#x26; Operations. “The combination of Microsoft Teams with our SAP solutions has given our employees the ability to work from anywhere while ensuring orders are delivered on time to our customers, supporting the people putting their lives at risk working on the front line.”</p>
  <p>SAP’s endorsement of Azure for ERP cloud migration is reflected in positive customer feedback on the collaboration between the companies. SAP and Microsoft will continue to make migration simpler and increase customers’ confidence in running their digital enterprises in the cloud. At the same time, many customers express a desire to maintain multi-cloud environments. SAP continues with its long-standing policy of supporting choice for those customers who request alternatives based on business requirements.</p>
  <p>SAP and Microsoft <a href="/2020/12/sap-and-microsoft-supply-chain-industry-40-cloud">recently announced an update</a> to enable customers to design and operate intelligent digital supply chain and Industry 4.0 solutions in the cloud and at the edge.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-sap-and-microsoft-partnership">Learn more about the SAP and Microsoft partnership</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://discover.sap.com/microsoft/en-us/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>About Microsoft</strong></p>
  <p>Microsoft (Nasdaq “MSFT” @microsoft) enables digital transformation for the era of an intelligent cloud and an intelligent edge. Its mission is to empower every person and every organization on the planet to achieve more.</p>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong></p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: 77% of the world’s transaction revenue touches an SAP system. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT) and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong> Susan Miller, SAP, +1 (610) 570-6845, <a href="mailto:susan.miller@sap.com">susan.miller@sap.com</a>, EST<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a><br>Microsoft Media Relations, WE Communications for Microsoft,<br>+1 (425) 638-7777, <a href="mailto:rrt@we-worldwide.com">rrt@we-worldwide.com</a>, PST</p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="e-book-how-sap-and-microsoft-are-working-together">E-Book: How SAP and Microsoft are Working Together</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/01/ca0f4c25-c87d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/microsoft</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microsoft and SAP: Expanding Our Partnership]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/01/expanding-microsoft-sap-partnership</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/01/expanding-microsoft-sap-partnership</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Microsoft will expand integration scenarios with Microsoft Teams and SAP solutions and improve SAP S/4HANA on Microsoft Azure. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1876d61f48b27527d21736c822aacc4a0e62dbb6c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1876d61f48b27527d21736c822aacc4a0e62dbb6c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1876d61f48b27527d21736c822aacc4a0e62dbb6c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Microsoft and SAP: Expanding Our Partnership" src="./media_1876d61f48b27527d21736c822aacc4a0e62dbb6c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="microsoft-and-sap-expanding-our-partnership">Microsoft and SAP: Expanding Our Partnership</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Our world is becoming more digital every day, with an increasing number of people working remotely. The <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> pandemic has only accelerated these trends.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Efficient virtual collaboration has never been more important, and we want to provide our customers with solutions that help them cope with business disruptions. When done right, these can be powerful tools to increase workplace productivity, raise flexibility, and foster agility within and across organizations.</p>
  <p>One key aspect to this is the integration of business software applications with business collaboration tools. <a href="/">Together with Microsoft</a>, we want to better support end users in their daily work and bridge the gap between enterprise software and collaboration tools more effectively and efficiently. Our two companies combine the market-leading business software applications from SAP with the market-leading business collaboration tools from Microsoft.</p>
  <p>Together with Microsoft, we will drive joint innovation to integrate Microsoft Teams and SAP’s business software applications. By doing so, we aim to simplify processes, enable collaboration without switching applications, and guide users of the solutions intuitively. Ultimately, the integration scenarios can help to achieve enhanced workplace productivity by offering our customers significant value to work better together with their employees, customers, and partners—anywhere and anytime.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="press-release-sap-and-microsoft-expand-partnership">Press Release: SAP and Microsoft Expand Partnership</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/01/sap-and-microsoft-expand-partnership-integrate-teams">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="bringing-together-microsoft-teams-and-sap-solutions">Bringing Together Microsoft Teams and SAP Solutions</h2>
  <p>We are looking to expand the integration scenarios with Microsoft Teams and SAP solutions in the following areas to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Effectively collaborate with business partners:</strong> Especially in the case of disruptions in business, fast communication with clients and partners is imperative. One of our first integration scenarios relates to <strong>SAP S/4HANA and Microsoft Teams</strong>. With the solution alignment, customers will be able to identify their business partners easily and initiate contact directly from SAP S/4HANA—with no need to switch between applications or devices. This will help customers swiftly react to business situations based on real-time data and constant communication with relevant stakeholders.</li>
    <li><strong>Simplify and modernize the remote sales experience:</strong> Today, remote selling has become an imperative for companies across the globe. Integrating <strong>SAP Sales Cloud</strong> with <strong>Microsoft Teams</strong> simplifies the remote selling process and removes barriers to customer engagement through an embedded in-app integration of the two solutions. For example, without switching applications, customer calls can be initiated directly from the customer experience application—helping ensure transparency and consistency within customer relationship management (CRM) and saving time through user-friendly workflows.</li>
    <li><strong>Foster collaboration and build learning communities:</strong> Organizations have realized the necessity of providing simple, intuitive, and engaging ways for employees to learn new skills, share knowledge, and stay informed—all in a virtual environment. Bringing together <strong>SAP SuccessFactors solutions</strong> and <strong>Microsoft Teams</strong> will support learning experiences that enable collaboration, social learning, and remote conferencing.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>This news makes one characteristic of the two companies’ enduring alliance very clear: the ability and commitment to continually evolve to make our customers even more successful. Every time an end user works with SAP solutions, there is an opportunity for real-time collaboration such as chats, conference calls, alerts, and so much more. It is exciting to see the opportunities for collaboration culture and frictionless enterprises that our partnership with Microsoft creates for our customers.</p>
  <h2 id="accelerating-migration-and-increasing-operational-efficiencies">Accelerating Migration and Increasing Operational Efficiencies</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-sap-and-microsoft-partnership">Learn more about the SAP and Microsoft partnership</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://discover.sap.com/microsoft/en-us/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In addition, SAP and Microsoft are further simplifying and improving the experience for customers running SAP S/4HANA on Microsoft Azure. Together, we will continue to make our customers’ migration from SAP ERP to SAP S/4HANA in the cloud simpler, while at the same time ensuring choice for customers that prefer multi-cloud environments in their enterprise IT landscapes.</p>
  <p>This means that our customers will see more guidance from SAP and Microsoft on the initial setup and architecture design of SAP S/4HANA on Microsoft Azure.</p>
  <p>We also plan to collaborate with Microsoft to enhance SAP Cloud Appliance Library, a tool that makes it easier for users to quickly provision SAP applications for immediate use in the cloud, and offer automated SAP system installations for SAP S/4HANA. Customers can also subscribe to SAP Landscape Management Cloud, improving scalability and operation efforts, and benefit from an SAP system-centered view of their Microsoft Azure landscape. Additionally, we are working on a more guided approach for customers to quickly deploy SAP S/4HANA directly into Microsoft Azure. For better transparency within the transformation process, we will provide guidance on data migration tool usage for the transition of SAP workloads from on premise to SAP S/4HANA on Microsoft Azure.</p>
  <h2 id="bringing-platform-services-closer-together">Bringing Platform Services Closer Together</h2>
  <p>We will also continue to expand the global availability of SAP solutions on Microsoft Azure during 2021. Together, we will drive co-innovation between <a href="https://www.sap.com/germany/products/business-technology-platform.html?campaigncode=CRM-DE20-PPC-DDE_PLTTA0&#x26;source=ppc-mee-ao-dg_PT_x_DE_x_x-GOO-x-x&#x26;DFA=1&#x26;gclid=EAIaIQobChMIy-qk-YOR7AIVRM3tCh2oqQtUEAAYASAAEgIwa_D_BwE&#x26;gclsrc=aw.ds&#x26;pdf-asset=fa09d6fc-4b7d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff&#x26;page=7&#x26;btp=18743a19-5b7f-4397-aa1d-2a1ccc3c4142">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP) and Microsoft Azure services to deliver business outcomes to our customers. The range of capabilities includes event integration based on open standards, single sign-on and provisioning of users between Microsoft and SAP, secure network connectivity, and improved application development experience on SAP BTP. My SAP Executive Board colleague and our Chief Technology Officer Juergen Mueller will give more insight on the role of SAP BTP in the upcoming days.</p>
  <p>With our partnership, we bring together Microsoft Teams with SAP solutions, accelerate migration and improve operational efficiencies, and bring platform services closer together. We are working on making these enhancements and integrations of SAP solutions with Microsoft a reality for our customers soon. You can find the latest status of our joint work in <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/01/ca0f4c25-c87d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">this e-book</a>, which we will update regularly. I look forward to more joint innovation to come.</p>
  <p>The next generation of enterprise software is intelligent and integrated, networked, sustainable, and collaborative.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Thomas Saueressig is a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE, Product Engineering.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sign-up-for-the-weekly-sap-news-center-newsletter">Sign up for the weekly SAP News Center newsletter</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>news-tag/microsoft</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>