<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/idc/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Industry Analysts Say About SAP Sustainability]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/what-industry-analysts-say-about-sap-sustainability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/what-industry-analysts-say-about-sap-sustainability</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Industry analysts assess the sustainability performance of companies across industries. Learn about what they had to say about SAP.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e36ed2496934d2a62eef72bc90f762db5c48d221.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e36ed2496934d2a62eef72bc90f762db5c48d221.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e36ed2496934d2a62eef72bc90f762db5c48d221.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="What Industry Analysts Say About SAP Sustainability" src="./media_1e36ed2496934d2a62eef72bc90f762db5c48d221.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="what-industry-analysts-say-about-sap-sustainability">What Industry Analysts Say About SAP Sustainability</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For nearly 15 years, SAP has committed to being a <a href="/topics/sustainability">sustainability</a> leader both in our operations and through our sustainability product offerings for customers. Industry analysts review and assess the sustainability performance of companies across industries. SAP has recently been assessed by some of the most important analyst firms for both our own sustainability performance and the sustainability solutions we offer customers.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner, an independent analyst firm, recently published a report titled “<a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/sap-rated-positively-in-sustainability/index.html">Sustainability Assessment: SAP</a>.” A report from analyst firm IDC earlier this year, “Sustainability Index for Software Providers: SAP”, noted SAP performed “exceptionally well.” The published <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/05/d2950cf3-737e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.rc.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y23-IMM-21123823">IDC report</a> highlights how SAP is leading by example as a sustainable vendor.</p>
  <p>It’s abundantly clear that businesses need to urgently address sustainability challenges. Companies are adopting new technology solutions to help them manage sustainability across many different dimensions, from environmental issues like energy, water, and waste, to social issues like diversity and human rights, to governance and reporting issues.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d31b118dcbe3ac649ef3a08129aad3c3e6a33702.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d31b118dcbe3ac649ef3a08129aad3c3e6a33702.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d31b118dcbe3ac649ef3a08129aad3c3e6a33702.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1d31b118dcbe3ac649ef3a08129aad3c3e6a33702.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="986">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Source: Gartner. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Business leaders are looking for the best tools that allow them to quantify, analyze, and act on real-time, accurate, and shareable sustainability data throughout their end-to-end operations. With SAP’s ERP-centric solutions, financial and non-financial data can be brought together for holistic decision-making. Business leaders can not only manage their productivity and operating results but connect that information with sustainability-related data to help make climate protection measurable, diversity and inclusion visible, and ethical responsibility transparent.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="record-report-and-act-with-sap-sustainability-solutions">Record, report, and act with SAP Sustainability solutions</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP has a unique role to play in supporting our customers’ sustainability efforts. SAP customers produce 87% of the world’s global commerce. That means our products and services can help the vast majority of companies driving the global economy organize their supply chains, transportation, and financial data in a way that can enable an equitable, circular economy and net-zero emissions.</p>
  <p>Sustainability data in ERP is the foundation for holistic, integrated sustainability management. As the leader in enterprise resource management, SAP has more than 50 years of experience helping businesses across 25 industries optimize resources.</p>
  <p>Our comprehensive portfolio is designed to help customers find the solutions they need to run their business processes and enterprise more efficiently, with offerings such as SAP Business Network, business process transformation solutions, SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP), and the SAP Customer Experience portfolio. Our solutions, increasingly powered with AI capabilities, can help customers not only in their own operations, but across their entire value chain – from calculating product-level carbon footprints, to ensuring diversity and inclusion, to protecting human rights. In addition, SAP’s broad ecosystem of partners can support customers with industry- and technology-specific consulting and implementation, advancing SAP’s “sustainable by design” approach.</p>
  <p>SAP leads by example as well, having committed to net-zero emissions across our entire value chain by 2030. We also <a href="/2021/12/sap-leads-sustainability-rankings">have been recognized</a> as the leading software firm in the Dow Jones Sustainability Indices for 15 years and as a leader in environmental transparency and action by CDP, an international organization considered the gold standard of environmental reporting.</p>
  <h2 id="whats-next">What’s Next</h2>
  <p>Sustainability is not an end state, it’s a state of being. In that respect, companies should adopt an approach that constantly evolves and adapts to remain sustainable. SAP is dedicated to advancing sustainable business through our own operations and our comprehensive portfolio of solutions that can help other companies with their end-to-end sustainability management. Across the business network and our wide solution portfolio, SAP supports our customers in tackling their biggest sustainability challenges.</p>
  <p>Try the free <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/sap-rated-positively-in-sustainability/index.html">SAP Sustainability Navigator</a> tool, and read the full <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-2FWN452Z&#x26;ct=231213&#x26;st=sb">complimentary Gartner Sustainability report</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Daniel Schmid is chief sustainability officer at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Follow us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner, Sustainability Assessment: SAP, 11 December 2023, Ed Anderson, Fabio Di Capua<br>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally and is used herein with permission. All rights reserved. This graphic was published by Gartner, Inc. as part of a larger research document and should be evaluated in the context of the entire document. The Gartner document is available upon request from SAP.<br>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Multi-Enterprise Supply Chain Commerce Network Report]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-leader-idc-worldwide-multi-enterprise-supply-chain-commerce-network</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-leader-idc-worldwide-multi-enterprise-supply-chain-commerce-network</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been recognized as a Leader in the IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Multi-Enterprise Supply Chain Commerce Network 2023 Vendor Assessment.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_135f4226168fd5f6686d7e1a231112cde982b97a7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_135f4226168fd5f6686d7e1a231112cde982b97a7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_135f4226168fd5f6686d7e1a231112cde982b97a7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named a Leader in IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Multi-Enterprise Supply Chain Commerce Network Report" src="./media_135f4226168fd5f6686d7e1a231112cde982b97a7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-a-leader-in-idc-marketscape-worldwide-multi-enterprise-supply-chain-commerce-network-report">SAP Named a Leader in IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Multi-Enterprise Supply Chain Commerce Network Report</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP continues to act on our vision of enabling companies to create transparent, resilient, and sustainable supply chains across a massive amount of trading partners. We’re being recognized as a Leader in the <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/12/02200664-9f7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Multi-Enterprise Supply Chain Commerce Network 2023 Vendor Assessment</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="why-sap-is-a-leader">Why SAP Is a Leader</h2>
  <p>In an increasingly digitalized world, it is imperative that companies stay connected via a business network. I believe SAP was selected as a Leader because <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-SAPLeaderinIDCMarketScape">SAP Business Network</a> – our entry into the Multi-Enterprise Supply Chain Commerce Network space – can successfully drive buyer-supplier collaboration across procurement, supply chain, logistics, and asset management by providing a digital platform for trading partners to collaborate externally and exchange data just as, if not more, efficiently as their own internal processes.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_187994eca96ea26313df6a84f0d5d56cfe3bbffac.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_187994eca96ea26313df6a84f0d5d56cfe3bbffac.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_187994eca96ea26313df6a84f0d5d56cfe3bbffac.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_187994eca96ea26313df6a84f0d5d56cfe3bbffac.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="620" height="615">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Source: “IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Multi-Enterprise Supply Chain Commerce Network 2023 Vendor Assessment,” by Simon Ellis, December 2023, IDC #US49948423.* Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The IDC MarketScape report notes these competitive strengths of SAP Business Network:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Depth and breadth</strong> of product features and functionalities, as well as a future road map covering all major B2B collaboration categories (indirect, direct material, MRO logistics, financial, services, and sustainability) and scenarios in an end user, persona-based manner.</li>
    <li><strong>Integration and extensibility capabilities</strong> include integration between SAP ERP, SAP procurement modules, other applications like ERP, SCAM, and customer applications, and technologies such as machine learning, AI, and blockchain through SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP).</li>
    <li><strong>Global adoption and breadth of collaboration</strong> makes SAP among the industry’s largest, highly adopted B2B collaboration platforms enabling trading partners to collaborate in real time. Ongoing efforts to harmonize commerce, asset intelligence, and logistics continue to enhance the power of the connected economy.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The IDC MarketScape report notes, “Manufacturers and retailers looking for a vendor of both a multi-enterprise network and supply chain procurement application should consider SAP,” citing the “breadth and depth of [its] business network capabilities, strategic road map vision, and unmatched integration with core SAP and non-SAP supply chain and procurement applications,” making SAP a strong choice.</p>
  <h2 id="charting-the-evolution-of-sap-business-network">Charting the Evolution of SAP Business Network</h2>
  <p>I’m so pleased that as a pioneer in business networks, we continue to be recognized for our commitment to executing our vision. As we’ve continued to evolve our road map, I’m reflecting on how far we’ve come and paved the way for the future of intelligent business networks. From the founding of Ariba Supplier Network in 1996 to what we’ve become today, SAP Business Network touches US$4.9 trillion in commerce annually across many business processes and industries and has over 2 million active users on the network.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-network-powers-transparency-resiliency-and-sustainability">SAP Business Network powers transparency, resiliency, and sustainability</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Recent years have shown us that intelligent, digital business networks are essential to supporting an agile supply chain. SAP Business Network is a comprehensive platform that helps connect people, processes, and systems across multiple enterprises, ultimately creating transparent, resilient, and sustainable supply chains that can span the globe and be tailored to each line of business, helping to drive partner collaboration beyond a company’s own four walls and spanning the entire value chain.</p>
  <p>I’m proud to say that SAP Business Network can provide best-in-class supply chain collaboration, helping companies adhere to legal mandates, scale with confidence, and automate repetitive tasks, leaving more time for strategic decision-making informed by patterns gleaned from vast amounts of data. Our vision – what so many talented people at SAP are working towards every day – is to create the world’s best and largest B2B marketplace to help our customers meet their business goals.</p>
  <h2 id="recent-advancements-continue-to-revolutionize-b2b-collaboration">Recent Advancements Continue to Revolutionize B2B Collaboration</h2>
  <p>If you know SAP, you know about our commitment to continuous innovation. In 2023, we announced many exciting innovations around SAP Business Network, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Build on artificial intelligence in SAP Business Network.</strong> My colleague Muhammad Alam <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/11/40a14527-977e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-SAPLeaderinIDCMarketScape">announced our plans</a> to further integrate generative AI in spend management at SAP Spend Connect Live. Customers can look forward to enriched supplier responses to SAP Business Network Discovery postings, helping to facilitate more transparent communication between buyers and suppliers. Generative AI improvements can give suppliers the ability to generate clear, concise catalog descriptions, as well as summarize common errors for users so buyers can find exactly what they’re looking for.</li>
    <li><strong>Tackle industry-specific challenges with SAP Business Network for Industry.</strong> We’ve combined our more than 50 years of industry knowledge with the power of business networks to help customers address industry-specific supply chain challenges. Take a look at <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/industries.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-SAPLeaderinIDCMarketScape">how companies across industries use SAP Business Network</a> to help predict and respond to disruptions, comply with industry regulations, and meet sustainability goals.</li>
    <li><strong>Learn more with trading partner insights.</strong> Account managers struggle with obtaining comparative measures to assess the performance of trading partners. New KPIs and benchmarks, presented in a streamlined dashboard, can allow suppliers to evaluate customer transaction performance of orders, invoices, and payments with automatically generated KPIs and SAP Business Network community benchmarks. These insights can support collaborative dialogues with customers to help reduce transaction costs and mitigate business risk. <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/05/44712fba-737e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-SAPLeaderinIDCMarketScape">Watch the demo to learn more</a>.</li>
    <li><strong>Draw insights from data with component planning collaboration.</strong> With component planning collaboration, buyers and suppliers can view the forecast planning data for a finished good together with its components. Armed with this visibility, buyers and suppliers can respond to material shortages and adjust production accordingly, making supply more predictable. <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/05/585c0fc7-737e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-SAPLeaderinIDCMarketScape">Learn more in this demo</a>.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Stay tuned for more exciting innovations this year. Stay up-to-date about recent and upcoming innovations and explore road maps <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/innovations.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-SAPLeaderinIDCMarketScape">here</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="transforming-the-future-of-business-networks">Transforming the Future of Business Networks</h2>
  <p>I am proud that SAP is being recognized as a leader in delivering solutions that connect people, processes, and systems, enabling trading partners to collaborate effectively. I can’t wait to see our road map continue to come to life as we collaborate with our customers to develop innovations that help them achieve their business objectives by automating tasks, scaling efficiently, and operating sustainably.</p>
  <p>To learn more, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-SAPLeaderinIDCMarketScape">the SAP Business Network product page</a> and read the full IDC MarketScape report <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/12/02200664-9f7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">here</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Tony Harris is senior vice president and chief marketing and solutions officer for SAP Business Network.</p>
        <p>*IDC MarketScape vendor analysis model is designed to provide an overview of the competitive fitness of ICT suppliers in a given market. The research methodology utilizes a rigorous scoring methodology based on both qualitative and quantitative criteria that results in a single graphical illustration of each vendor’s position within a given market. The Capabilities score measures vendor product, go-to-market and business execution in the short-term. The Strategy score measures alignment of vendor strategies with customer requirements in a 3-5-year timeframe. Vendor market share is represented by the size of the circles. Vendor year-over-year growth rate relative to the given market is indicated by a plus, neutral or minus next to the vendor name.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc-marketscape</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network-for-industry</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why SAP Is a Leader in the IDC MarketScape for Enterprise Treasury and Risk Management Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-leader-idc-marketscape-treasury-risk-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-leader-idc-marketscape-treasury-risk-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been recognized in the 2023 IDC MarketScape: Worldwide SaaS and Cloud-Enabled Enterprise Treasury and Risk Management Applications.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc-marketscape</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-treasury-and-risk-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Get to the Next Level of Supplier Collaboration with a Robust Business Network]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/supplier-collaboration-with-sap-business-network</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/supplier-collaboration-with-sap-business-network</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[An IDC research study, sponsored by SAP, reveals how businesses can achieve next-level supplier collaboration with business networks.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Rated Top Three in IDC’s Sustainability Index]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-rated-top-three-idc-sustainability-index</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-rated-top-three-idc-sustainability-index</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP placed in the top three of 23 software vendors that were assessed for the IDC Sustainability Index for Software Providers. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sustainability-solutions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Awarded the IDC SaaS Customer Satisfaction Award for Talent Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-successfactors-idc-saas-customer-satisfaction-award</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-successfactors-idc-saas-customer-satisfaction-award</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors was awarded the 2022 IDC SaaS Customer Satisfaction Award for Talent Management, receiving top ratings in every metric.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Six Ways Growth-Focused Organizations Power Reskilling and Upskilling Initiatives with SAP SuccessFactors]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/six-ways-power-reskilling-upskilling-initiatives-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/six-ways-power-reskilling-upskilling-initiatives-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[An IDC survey sponsored by SAP reveals six ways midsize organizations use SAP SuccessFactors solutions to power reskilling and upskilling.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-performance-goals</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP a Leader in Procurement Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-leader-in-procurement-applications</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-leader-in-procurement-applications</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been named a Leader in the IDC MarketScape: Worldwide SaaS and Cloud-Enabled Procurement Applications 2023 Vendor Assessment.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc-marketscape</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IDC Research Shows Intellectual Property Drives SAP Partner Growth]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/idc-intellectual-property-research-sap-partner-growth</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/idc-intellectual-property-research-sap-partner-growth</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Per new intellectual property research from IDC, making a 20% revenue investment can lead to 60% higher revenue growth than average.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP a Leader in New IDC MarketScape for Worldwide Enterprise Planning]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/idc-marketscape-worldwide-enterprise-planning-sap-a-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/idc-marketscape-worldwide-enterprise-planning-sap-a-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is a leader in the IDC MarketScape for Worldwide Enterprise Planning, Budgeting, and Forecasting Applications 2022 Vendor Assessment.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-performance-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Is a Leader in the IDC MarketScape for Worldwide Enterprise Subscription and Usage Management Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/idc-marketscape-enterprise-subscription-and-usage-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/idc-marketscape-enterprise-subscription-and-usage-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is a Leader in the IDC MarketScape for Enterprise Subscription and Usage Management Applications. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/quote-to-cash</category>
            <category>news-tag/recurring-revenue-models</category>
            <category>product/sap-billing-and-revenue-innovation-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/subscription-billing</category>
            <category>news-tag/xaas</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Business Value of SAP BTP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2022/12/the-business-value-of-sap-btp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2022/12/the-business-value-of-sap-btp</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP CTO and Executive Board Member Juergen Mueller explains the true business value of SAP BTP. Learn more here.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Industry 4.0 Attracts Workers Whose Entire Lives Are on Their Mobile Device]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/industry-4-0-attracts-workers-whose-entire-lives-are-on-their-mobile-device</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/industry-4-0-attracts-workers-whose-entire-lives-are-on-their-mobile-device</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Manufacturers are transforming factories, hoping next-generation workers come for the cool factor and stay for career-building innovations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-4-0</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/mobile</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Recognized as Leader in IDC MarketScape for Worldwide Holistic Supply Chain Planning 2022]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/idc-marketscape-worldwide-holistic-supply-chain-planning-sap-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/idc-marketscape-worldwide-holistic-supply-chain-planning-sap-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is a Leader in strategy and capabilities in the IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Holistic Supply Chain Planning 2022 Vendor Assessment.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fa5ae196539d080edf29895e6ce0f91da35a0c2e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fa5ae196539d080edf29895e6ce0f91da35a0c2e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1fa5ae196539d080edf29895e6ce0f91da35a0c2e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Recognized as Leader in IDC MarketScape for Worldwide Holistic Supply Chain Planning 2022" src="./media_1fa5ae196539d080edf29895e6ce0f91da35a0c2e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-recognized-as-leader-in-idc-marketscape-for-worldwide-holistic-supply-chain-planning-2022">SAP Recognized as Leader in IDC MarketScape for Worldwide Holistic Supply Chain Planning 2022</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-customer-centric-products-to-market-faster-and-at-less-cost-with-global-supply-chain-management-software-from-sap">Get customer-centric products to market faster and at less cost with global supply chain management software from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>IDC Manufacturing Insights has recognized SAP as a Leader in strategy and capabilities in the IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Holistic Supply Chain Planning 2022 Vendor Assessment.*</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>According to Simon Ellis, program vice president, IDC Manufacturing Insights, “Growing complexity in the supply chain, particularly increasingly diverse outsourcing, has made supply planning much more challenging. Combined with larger forecast error and a lack of complete insight into supply opportunities and constraints, the need for a competent supply planning application is central to the success of the broader supply chain.”</p>
  <p>At SAP, we see planning as a process. The market of vendors in this space is evolving, fueled by new technology and planning approaches that put customer experience at the center. We continue to set the pace with the market-leading <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/integrated-business-planning.html">SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain</a> solution as well as cloud-native innovations that have been adopted by more than 1,200 customers worldwide.</p>
  <p>SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain is a key element of the <a href="/topics/supply-chain-management">SAP Digital Supply Chain</a> portfolio, which helps companies:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Create continuously learning, resilient, and responsive supply chains</li>
    <li>Synchronize strategic and operational supply chain decisions in a single solution</li>
    <li>Ingest real-time data from external and internal sources to provide more intelligent visibility across the supply chain</li>
    <li>Connect trading partners digitally with the internal plan via SAP Business Network</li>
    <li>Enable planners to make business decisions rooted in real-time facts</li>
    <li>Infuse decision processes with intelligent technologies like machine learning and artificial intelligence (AI)</li>
    <li>Execute supply chain planning decisions with confidence from a modern and simplified user experience</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Ellis also states, “SAP has extensive experience in almost all industries, with notable engagements in consumer products, retail, high tech, automotive/heavy equipment, pharma/life sciences, and wholesale distribution. Supply chains looking for a comprehensive supply chain planning offering that provides a seamless, user-friendly planning platform with embedded analytics that is tightly integrated to manufacturing, operational planning, and supply chain execution should consider SAP.”</p>
  <p>We are excited for companies to consider SAP as a partner in the work to build risk-resistant and resilient supply chains.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><em>David Vallejo is global head of Supply Chain Solution Management at SAP.</em></p>
        <p>*Doc #US49578717, September 2022</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Digital Innovations Behind the Booming Life Sciences Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/digital-innovations-life-sciences-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/digital-innovations-life-sciences-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The pandemic has irrevocably disrupted the life sciences industry, revealing a new vision for innovation from cloud-based collaboration.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[If The Pandemic Was Their Wake-Up Call, This Is How Employers Are Reacting]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/pandemic-wake-up-call-workforce-resiliency</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/pandemic-wake-up-call-workforce-resiliency</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Organizations are devising new strategies to increase workforce resiliency in the wake of the pandemic and the Great Resignation. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/contingent-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Is Your Factory Intelligent Enough to Withstand the Next Business Crisis?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/is-your-factory-intelligent-enough-to-withstand-the-next-business-crisis</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/is-your-factory-intelligent-enough-to-withstand-the-next-business-crisis</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Manufacturers are embracing Industry 4.0 and intelligent factories to anticipate and respond faster to market demands. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-4-0</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/machine-learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Procurement Solutions Hit New Heights]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/sap-procurement-solutions-hit-new-heights</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/sap-procurement-solutions-hit-new-heights</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Ariba solutions have received honors from IDC, Supply Chain Digital and Procurement Magazine, and TrustRadius. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/taulia</category>
            <category>news-tag/trustradius</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Named a Leader in IDC MarketScape for Worldwide Modern Talent Acquisition]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/idc-marketscape-modern-talent-acquisition-sap-successfactors-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/idc-marketscape-modern-talent-acquisition-sap-successfactors-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In the IDC MarketScape for Worldwide Modern Talent Acquisition Suites 2022 Vendor Assessment, SAP SuccessFactors is a Leader!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/recruiting</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[For High-Tech Supply Chains, CO2 Emission Tracking Is Sustainable Business Currency]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/high-tech-supply-chains-co2-emission-tracking</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/high-tech-supply-chains-co2-emission-tracking</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[High-tech industry leaders are making sustainability a core commitment, and it is transforming business models to address climate change.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>industry/high-tech</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/net-zero</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Manufacturers Supercharge Massive Supply Chain Advantage with Industry 4.0]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/manufacturers-supply-chain-advantage-industry-4-0</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/manufacturers-supply-chain-advantage-industry-4-0</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Industrial manufacturers can gain a competitive advantage with digitalized supply chains to understand and respond to market demands faster.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-4-0</category>
            <category>news-tag/internet-of-things</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in IDC MarketScapes for Cloud-Enabled Manufacturing and Operational ERP Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sap-named-leader-idc-marketscapes-cloud-manufacturing-operational-erp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sap-named-leader-idc-marketscapes-cloud-manufacturing-operational-erp</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[IDC has positioned SAP as a Leader within the 2022 IDC MarketScape for worldwide SaaS and cloud-enabled operational ERP applications.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc-marketscape</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preventing Cybercrime with a Solid Security Culture]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/preventing-cybercrime-solid-security-culture</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/preventing-cybercrime-solid-security-culture</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Building a security culture with shared responsibility and accountability company-wide is the best defense against cybercrime. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ed0db808ab7bc42e8ffe4aeb17d137cd686d0b64.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ed0db808ab7bc42e8ffe4aeb17d137cd686d0b64.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ed0db808ab7bc42e8ffe4aeb17d137cd686d0b64.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Preventing Cybercrime with a Solid Security Culture" src="./media_1ed0db808ab7bc42e8ffe4aeb17d137cd686d0b64.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="preventing-cybercrime-with-a-solid-security-culture">Preventing Cybercrime with a Solid Security Culture</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Cybercrime is not inevitable. With a <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/trust-center/security.html?pdf-asset=c8573354-f87d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=1">security culture</a>, meaning a rigorous, people-first risk management strategy, organizations can muster the vigilance to head off threats.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the wake of <a href="https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/the-log4j-software-flaw-is-christmas-come-early-for-cybercriminals/">Log4j</a> vulnerabilities, massive breaches like <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/thomasbrewster/2021/02/03/severe-solarwinds-vulnerabilities-allow-hackers-to-take-over-servers-update-now/?sh=4966e1ae687c">SolarWinds</a>, and the <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/18/business/cream-cheese-cyberattack-schreiber-foods/index.html">cream cheese shortage</a> during the 2021 holiday season, organizations are changing up security strategies to mitigate <a href="https://cybersecurityventures.com/cybercrime-damages-6-trillion-by-2021/">cybercrime</a> damages that are predicted to total US$10.5 trillion annually by 2025.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-the-security-culture-toolkit">Explore the Security Culture Toolkit</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/trust-center/security.html?pdf-asset=c8573354-f87d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=1">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="security-cultures-prioritize-new-business-practices">Security Cultures Prioritize New Business Practices</h2>
  <p>As every company becomes technology-driven, risks are escalating, pushing security much closer to the top of business priorities. <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/articles/the-top-8-cybersecurity-predictions-for-2021-2022">Gartner</a> researchers said that by 2025, 70% of CEOs will mandate a culture of organizational resilience to survive coinciding threats from cybercrime, severe weather events, civil unrest, and political instabilities. Meanwhile, security cultures will have changed numerous business practices. By next year, <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US47193621">IDC</a> analysts said that 80% of organizations faced with complex global regulations will increase security compliance automation investments by 25% to consistently meet policies and regulations. In the same time frame, IDC predicted 25% of G2000 public cloud customers will subscribe to integrated risk management and cyber-insurance policies through shared fate/risk programs to protect against sophisticated cyberattacks.</p>
  <h2 id="make-security-a-company-wide-responsibility">Make Security a Company-Wide Responsibility</h2>
  <p>Security and risk leaders who responded to a recent Gartner <a href="https://www.gartner.com/smarterwithgartner/develop-a-security-strategy-for-cyber-physical-systems/">survey</a> ranked the Internet of Things (IoT) and cyber-physical systems as their top concerns for the next three to five years. <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/information-technology/trends/the-it-roadmap-for-cybersecurity">Gartner</a> analysts predicted that by 2023, 75% of organizations will restructure risk and security governance to address the widespread adoption of advanced technologies, an increase from less than 15% today.</p>
  <p>In a world where just about every organization is in the computer industry, embedded secure practices across the organization are table stakes. For example, SAP follows the NIST (National Institute of Technology in North America) cybersecurity framework, a holistic security strategy based on repeatable processes. This approach harmonizes controlled security company-wide, including product development and operations.</p>
  <p>“Security has always been our number one concern,” said Tim McKnight, executive vice president and chief security officer at SAP. “With the acceleration of digitalization, organizations have embarked on a massive cloud-based computing transformation that extends to security. We’ve undergone a multi-year security transformation backed by the commitment of our Executive Board and real-time input from customers.”</p>
  <p>A security culture comes down to a shared vision that’s carried out by leaders who make security a priority and teams who participate in ongoing trainings that celebrate success and learn from failures. People in any sector can take a page out of the software applications industry playbook.</p>
  <p>“We’ve set cybersecurity goals for all of our executives,” said McKnight. “We present these measures to the Board on a regular basis, reviewing progress against security initiatives. With open conversations around security, we reinforce priorities while driving accountability from each department. Whether you’re an executive, team lead, or individual contributor, you need to understand your role in driving a security culture with a security-first mentality. After all, the vast majority of security incidents are the result of human error.”</p>
  <h2 id="dont-let-other-business-demands-supersede-security-resources">Don’t Let Other Business Demands Supersede Security Resources</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="secure-your-intelligent-enterprise-with-sap">Secure your intelligent enterprise with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/trust-center/security.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While just-in-time supply chains boost business agility in a <a href="/topics/covid-19">post-pandemic</a> environment, having more partners also increases risk. <a href="https://www.forrester.com/predictions/">Forrester</a> researchers predicted that 60% of security incidents will involve third parties in 2022. Maybe that’s why <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US47193621">IDC</a> researchers said that by next year, 55% of organizations will allocate half of their security budgets to cross-technology ecosystems and platforms designed for rapid consumption and unified security capabilities to drive agile innovation.</p>
  <p>Companies need to allocate sufficient resources to prioritize security across the entire product life cycle, from development through go-live and support. With intelligent capabilities from artificial intelligence (AI), machine learning, robotic process automation (RPA), and other technologies, products and services increasingly require advanced security measures.</p>
  <p>“An effective culture makes security everyone’s responsibility,” said Wiebke Thelo, senior vice president and head of SAP Quality, Application Security, and Production. “For example, business information security officers at SAP report directly into business unit leaders. They work together, making sure that security is embedded into product design, development, and operation.”</p>
  <h2 id="educate-employees-now-for-a-trusted-future">Educate Employees Now for a Trusted Future</h2>
  <p><a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US48154621&#x26;pageType=PRINTFRIENDLY">IDC</a> research showed that close to 25% of organizations report ransomware infections weekly. Human judgment is core to preventing these incidents. However, <a href="https://www.forrester.com/blogs/predictions-2022-continued-uncertainty-forces-attention-on-securing-relationships/">Forrester</a> analysts warned about the “security brain drain” as one in 10 experienced professionals have exited the industry during the past year. These analysts advised security executives to address burnout and team culture problems and use succession planning to build a pipeline of security leaders.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div><a href="/2022/02/sap-teams-with-hbcus-next-generation-cybersecurity">SAP Teams Up with HBCUs to Attract Talent to the Cybersecurity Curriculum</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/2022/02/sap-teams-with-hbcus-next-generation-cybersecurity/embed/#?secret=KrZWqWNpab#?secret=TP1q2sHDbR">“SAP Teams Up with HBCUs to Attract Talent to the Cybersecurity Curriculum” — SAP News Center</a></p>
  <p>“A security culture requires significant learning and development, which is why we’ve professionalized security,” said McKnight. “The human element is critical – we position people first, process second, and technology third. We start with our people and make sure they have the skills they need.”</p>
  <p>As remote working, just-in-time supply chains, and tech innovations continue, companies have to think and act faster than the criminals. There’s never a good time for a cyberattack. Just ask the people who suffered through the cream cheese shortage. Criminals don’t take holidays and a security culture is the best protection.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2022/01/20/preventing-the-next-log4j-with-a-solid-security-culture/?sh=297049942c43">This also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/cybersecurity</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Retail Trends 2022: In Search of the Ultimate Customer Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/retail-trends-2022</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/retail-trends-2022</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[What retail trends can we expect in 2022? The right combination of digital and physical CX, sustainability, and great employee experiences.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Workforce Trends 2022: How Companies Are Building Digital Dream Teams]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/workforce-trends-2022</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/workforce-trends-2022</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Analysts identify incoming workforce trends, revealing how employers are revamping HCM norms to improve the employee experience. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e7a28fd0b82c4064c764164f31084da5ca03f255.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e7a28fd0b82c4064c764164f31084da5ca03f255.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e7a28fd0b82c4064c764164f31084da5ca03f255.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Workforce Trends 2022: How Companies Are Building Digital Dream Teams" src="./media_1e7a28fd0b82c4064c764164f31084da5ca03f255.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="workforce-trends-2022-how-companies-are-building-digital-dream-teams">Workforce Trends 2022: How Companies Are Building Digital Dream Teams</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>While employees have their say about where, when, and how they want to work, company leaders are just as busy creating the post-pandemic workplace.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>From work anywhere flexibility to technology-driven individual and team augmentation, these are some of the top workforce predictions about how companies can craft the ideal employee experience (EX) for increasingly digitalized, sustainable business models.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="put-employees-at-the-heart-of-everything-you-do-with-sap-successfactors-software">Put employees at the heart of everything you do with SAP SuccessFactors software</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="hybrid-work-upheaves-workplace-norms">Hybrid Work Upheaves Workplace Norms</h2>
  <p>Conversations about remote versus on-site work erroneously position these decisions as an either/or choice. <a href="https://www.forrester.com/blogs/future-of-work-predictions-2022-eu/">Forrester</a> data revealed that in Europe, “skilled employees will force employers to grant them greater flexibility – or leave.”</p>
  <p>Similarly, <a href="https://www.forrester.com/blogs/predictions-2022/">Forrester</a> Analyst Sharyn Leaver predicted that 60% of organizations will shift to a hybrid model in 2022, but one-third will fail in their first attempt at anywhere work. It’s not enough to simply announce flexible work anywhere policies. Organizations also have to restructure expectations around meetings, job roles, and promotion opportunities so they no longer reflect face-to-face experiences. And don’t even consider demanding that everyone return to the office. Forrester warns that the 30% of companies expected to mandate fully in-office work will experience monthly employee quit rates as high as 2.5% “until executives feel the pain and finally commit to making hybrid work…work.”</p>
  <p>Worker location is a business decision predicated on productivity realities as well as competitive market demands. In a recent <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/webinars/4003227/5-digital-dexterity-enablers-to-support-a-hybrid-workforce">Gartner</a> survey, 64% of workers said they would only consider a new position or job if it allowed for flexible hours. In fact, they cited having flexible work hours as the main reason for their increased productivity.</p>
  <p>Another major issue is upskilling managers. <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/articles/you-ll-be-breaking-up-with-bad-customers-and-9-other-predictions-for-2022-and-beyond">Gartner</a> analysts predicted that by 2024, 30% of corporate teams will be without a boss due to the agile and hybrid nature of work. They reasoned that agility, by definition, requires “an environment of trust that doesn’t lend itself to traditional hierarchies.” Many managers lack the skills to manage employees in remote or hybrid situations, and only 47% of employees believed their manager capable of leading the team to future success.</p>
  <p>“Managers are on the ground every day, coaching and inspiring their people, driving execution, and ensuring transformation efforts are successful,” said Jill Popelka, president of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">SAP SuccessFactors</a>. “As workplace and business needs continue to shift, we will need strong, people-focused managers leading the way. Their development must be a top priority for organizations and is critical to business success.”</p>
  <h2 id="technology-changes-the-employee-experience">Technology Changes the Employee Experience</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="five-workplace-norms-innovative-hxm-leaders-are-replacing-right-now">Five Workplace Norms Innovative HXM Leaders Are Replacing Right Now</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/11/five-workplace-norms-innovative-hxm-leaders-are-replacing">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As digitalization transforms business models, it also changes how work gets done. <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US47290521">IDC</a> analysts said by next year, 60% of G2000 businesses will deploy artificial intelligence (AI)- and machine learning-enabled platforms to support the entire employee life cycle experience from onboarding through retirement.</p>
  <p>Digital intelligence will permeate the workplace with profound consequences. <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US47290521">IDC</a> predicted that 70% of connected workers in task-based roles will use intelligence embedded in adaptive digital workspaces from anywhere to engage clients and colleagues and drive enterprise productivity by 2023. These <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US48360721">analysts</a> said that “companies with cross functional leadership – a digital dream team – will enjoy faster rates of innovation, higher market share gains, and greater operational efficiencies than their contemporaries by 2025.”</p>
  <p>Data-driven businesses also need to give employees the right information, recognizing those who apply data across their decision-making. <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US47913321">IDC</a> researchers warned that the lack of a “meritocracy-based data culture” will erode trust in management, reducing employee satisfaction and increasing turnover in two-thirds of midsize to large enterprises by 2024, exacerbating skills gaps.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.forrester.com/predictions/">Forrester</a> was most optimistic about the combined value of people and technology. It predicted leading organizations will “unlock the creativity of their employees and surround them with intelligent technologies such as automation and prediction engines that focus on outcomes, not just financial results.” This heralds a new era of transformation featuring “human-centered technology initiatives” that connect customer experience (CX) and EX “to drive competitive advantage and deliver a 3% to 5% net gain in productivity.”</p>
  <p>These researchers also predicted a <a href="https://www.forrester.com/blogs/nomorejobs/">“no more jobs”</a> framework where “employees will become more peripatetic, taking their skills to contribute to project-based work and swarm teams, rather than sitting still in a fixed role…The world of no more jobs employs a dynamic mix of full-time employees, internal and external talent marketplaces, on-demand and contingent labor, and bots.”</p>
  <h2 id="sustainable-recruitment-and-business-performance-metrics">Sustainable Recruitment and Business Performance Metrics</h2>
  <p>As employees raise their voices for corporate accountability across a range of diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) topics, leading organizations have no choice but to respond. <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US47290521">IDC</a> predicted that 70% of enterprise businesses will have extensively invested in DEI data, tools, and benchmarking by 2024 to define recruitment and human capital strategies. These <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US48300021">researchers</a> predicted two-thirds of organizations worldwide will track their DEI performance using ESG (environmental, social, and corporate governance) metrics and KPIs in the same time frame.</p>
  <p>DEI isn’t just about metrics. Instead of focusing on corporate culture and a shared mission during a disruption, like <a href="/topics/covid-19">COVID-19</a>, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/smarterwithgartner/3-lessons-to-sustain-workforce-resilience-through-disruption">Gartner</a> analysts advised HR to give employees a personal sense of purpose, writing that, “when employees believe that their work is personally relevant, there is a 26% increase in the likelihood of sustained workforce health.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2022/01/18/workforce-trends-2022-how-companies-are-building-digital-dream-teams/?sh=27a661e84394">This also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Consumer Products Trends 2022: Can Your Brand Deliver Instant Happiness and Comfort?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/consumer-products-cpg-trends-2022</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/consumer-products-cpg-trends-2022</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Leading CPG brands package up superior customer experiences using tech innovation and sustainable business strategies to transform industries.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d70b1fb78d02205a4c7b6a0a2b435d4d5e086f4f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d70b1fb78d02205a4c7b6a0a2b435d4d5e086f4f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d70b1fb78d02205a4c7b6a0a2b435d4d5e086f4f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Consumer Products Trends 2022: Can Your Brand Deliver Instant Happiness and Comfort?" src="./media_1d70b1fb78d02205a4c7b6a0a2b435d4d5e086f4f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="consumer-products-trends-2022-can-your-brand-deliver-instant-happiness-and-comfort">Consumer Products Trends 2022: Can Your Brand Deliver Instant Happiness and Comfort?</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Underneath all the visionary aspirations for digital transformation, consumer packaged goods (<a href="/topics/cpg">CPG</a>) brands are grappling with a triumvirate challenge: how to balance bottom- and top-line business demands with sustainable practices that will take them into the future.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“CPG companies are moving systems to the cloud to gain business agility by connecting data to actions company-wide,” said Stuart Wilkinson, industry director of CPG and Life Sciences at SAP. “They want best practices to standardize business processes because that’s how they’ll achieve operational excellence, increasing efficiencies that lower costs. With centralized data visibility, they can measure, monitor, and reduce the environmental impact of their product supply chain from sourcing through distribution and after.”</p>
  <p>Here’s a quick roundup of some of the latest industry analyst predictions for the consumer products industry.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="with-sap-solutions-deliver-personalization-with-a-purpose">With SAP solutions, deliver personalization with a purpose</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://www.sap.com/industries/consumer-goods-cpg.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="intelligent-data-sharing-and-protection">Intelligent Data Sharing and Protection</h2>
  <p>Personalization may be the watchword for CPG companies aiming to delight their customers, but it’s fraught with land mines. For example, <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US48297321">IDC</a> analysts predicted 35% of brands will openly incentivize consumers to share personal data in exchange for cash rewards, services, and exclusive experiences by 2024. Yet <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/articles/you-ll-be-breaking-up-with-bad-customers-and-9-other-predictions-for-2022-and-beyond">Gartner</a> analysts predicted that 40% of consumers in the same time frame will trick behavior tracking metrics to intentionally devalue the personal data collected about them, making it difficult to monetize. It’s not surprising that <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US48300021">IDC</a> analysts expected companies to extend their data privacy initiatives to surpass compliance requirements, with 60% of enterprises establishing KPIs regarding the ethical use of data by 2023.</p>
  <p>These challenges are important for consumer brands companies regardless of where they are on the value chain. <a href="https://cache.webcasts.com/content/citr003/1494846/content/fc92275950c5a6a53c52ee6105409576a5a0a524/pdf/secured/IDC_Future_of_Digital_Innovation_Futurescape_2022_Draft2.pdf">IDC</a> researchers forecast that as early as next year, traditional distribution models will crumble as 20% of businesses in some sectors use technology to go direct to customers, seeking to improve customer satisfaction and product development.</p>
  <p>“Consumer brand awareness and selling is nontraditional territory for CPG companies,” said Wilkinson. “Organizations are scrambling to attract employees with B2C skills in the middle of a worker shortage, making cultural shifts along with new technologies to capture these new opportunities.”</p>
  <p>In fact, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/webinars/4007946/the-future-of-cloud-prepare-for-2025">Gartner</a> analysts position cloud as the key driver for business innovation across all industries. As cloud-based platforms become the norm, industry networks will be instrumental for every sector. <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US47219421">IDC</a> predicted that by 2024, 40% of manufacturers will share data in their ecosystems (partners, customers, suppliers), improving OEE (operational equipment efficiency) of their factory operations, on average, by 10%.</p>
  <h2 id="go-digital-with-cx-no-more-excuses">Go Digital with CX: No More Excuses</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="ai-trends-2022-spare-us-the-hype-we-want-business-results">AI Trends 2022: Spare Us the Hype, We Want Business Results</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2022/01/ai-trends-2022-spare-us-the-hype-we-want-business-results">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>According to some analysts, customers will reward brands that relieve their stress. <a href="https://www.forrester.com/blogs/predictions-2022-consumer-behavior/">Forrester</a> researchers predicted that, “In 2022, consumers will turn to uplifting, pleasing products and experiences that offer reprieve from the fatigue of ongoing uncertainty.” If these analysts are correct, this could be a boon for “physical goods that spark joy – from comfort food to at-home spa kits,” as well as “experiential consumption, like prioritizing time for personal care or IRL face time with friends and family.”</p>
  <p>Customers definitely have little patience for anything less than stellar experiences. <a href="https://www.forrester.com/predictions/">Forrester</a> found that about six in 10 U.S. and UK consumers believed companies “should have figured out how to handle <a href="/topics/covid-19">pandemic-related disruption</a> by now.” These <a href="https://www.forrester.com/predictions/">analysts</a> saw brands investing in “the commerce building blocks of their experience architectures; order management, payments, and inventory control will make every touch a shoppable moment; investments in immersive experiences will turn browsing into virtual inhabiting; and subscription billing will make loyalty a business model pivot.”</p>
  <p>Gaining insights from connected data makes the biggest business difference. By 2024, <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US48297321">IDC</a> forecasted 30% of Fortune 2000 companies will deploy next-best action across their omni-channel environment, driving demand for customer data platforms, omni-channel management, and customer service solutions.</p>
  <h2 id="sustainable-business-is-a-priority">Sustainable Business Is a Priority</h2>
  <p>It’s impossible to separate the intertwined strands of customer experience, tech innovation, and sustainable business, especially when it comes to supply chains.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US48298220">IDC</a> analysts predicted that by 2023, 50% of all supply chain forecasts will be automated through artificial intelligence (AI), improving accuracy by five percentage points. <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/articles/gartner-predicts-the-future-of-supply-chain-technology">Gartner</a> analysts said 50% of global product-centric enterprises will have invested in real-time transportation visibility platforms by 2023. By the following year, IDC researchers saw 70% of manufacturers in global supply chains improving long-term supply chain profitability with investments in software tools to support sustainability and circular economy business models.</p>
  <p>To improve delivery speed, agility, and visibility for B2B and B2C customers, <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US48298220">IDC</a> analysts said 35% of manufacturers will invest in order management software by 2024, resulting in a 25% improvement in OTIF (on-time, in-full) fulfillment. By 2025, <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US48298220">IDC</a> researchers predicted that 40% of G2000 organizations will invest in supply chain systems to increase information and inventory velocity to improve last-mile delivery efficiency and boost customer experience.</p>
  <p>What’s striking about these predictions is that they’re expected to radically change the CPG sector in just a couple of years. The future has never been more transformational.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2022/01/11/consumer-products-trends-2022-can-your-brand-deliver-instant-happiness-and-comfort/?sh=2e30f5f5421b">This also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enterprise Content Management: A Pivotal Step to End-to-End Digitalization]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/enterprise-content-management-ecm-digitalization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/enterprise-content-management-ecm-digitalization</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[According to an IDC whitepaper, SAP ECM solutions by OpenText can help businesses go paperless, resulting in greater efficiency. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_184c064ceef0464e02871782164bc5c9529c8989b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_184c064ceef0464e02871782164bc5c9529c8989b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_184c064ceef0464e02871782164bc5c9529c8989b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Enterprise Content Management: A Pivotal Step to End-to-End Digitalization" src="./media_184c064ceef0464e02871782164bc5c9529c8989b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="enterprise-content-management-a-pivotal-step-to-end-to-end-digitalization">Enterprise Content Management: A Pivotal Step to End-to-End Digitalization</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Work patterns may have changed over the years, but surprisingly most workplaces have yet to make any meaningful progress toward becoming paperless. Is this resistance to content digitalization and integration holding businesses back from becoming resilient and sustainable enough to stay competitive?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While the concept of the paperless workplace is nothing new, the opportunity to achieve this vision is quickly approaching as businesses advance their transformation strategies. Over the past year, companies have invested in software-as-a-service (SaaS) and cloud-enabled systems, new methodologies such as process automation, and network-wide collaboration to keep employees productive, update suppliers, and deliver on customer expectations.</p>
  <p>Now, some organizations are looking to go even further in their business transformation journey by digitalizing and integrating content with a comprehensive enterprise platform.</p>
  <p>According to an IDC whitepaper sponsored by SAP and OpenText, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2022/01/629d79f0-127e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">The Business Value of SAP Enterprise Content Management Solutions by OpenText in the Digital-First World</a>,” implementing solutions ‒ such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/enterprise-content-management.html">SAP enterprise content management (ECM) solutions by OpenText</a> ‒ can quickly yield a 288% three-year ROI. And at the center of this effective transformation is fast and efficient document migration, intake, processing, and auditing with fewer errors and higher productivity.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="discover-enterprise-content-management-solutions-to-help-your-business-become-an-intelligent-enterprise">Discover enterprise content management solutions to help your business become an intelligent enterprise</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/oth/enterprise-content-management/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="capturing-us7-million-in-revenue-growth">Capturing US$7 Million in Revenue Growth</h2>
  <p>The benefits of content digitalization, integration, and automation with <a href="/2020/05/study-ecm-and-mdg-solution-extensions-opentext-utopia">enterprise content management can be combined to increase revenue</a> by more than $7 million per year. By increasing efficiency, reducing errors, and accelerating processes, organizations surveyed by IDC reported an average gain of 4,794 productive hours each ‒ a 21% increase in gross user productivity.</p>
  <p>This improvement allowed respondents to avoid the hiring of 2.6 full-time employees to accomplish equivalent workloads, resulting in approximately $178,000 in enhanced user productivity value per organization. Additionally, enhanced interdepartmental document sharing and the automation of manual processes boosted profitability even further by driving $3.82 million in savings per one million documents.</p>
  <h2 id="migrating-documents-with-more-efficiency">Migrating Documents with More Efficiency</h2>
  <p>Migrating millions of documents that have been created, managed, and stored on paper to digital is a daunting task during any change initiative, especially when moving to a modern enterprise resource planning (ERP) system, such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a>. However, document-related migration is not just a one-time effort; it’s a project that can happen as regularly as organizations continue to evolve throughout their digital transformation.</p>
  <p>Interviewed organizations that use solutions for enterprise content management cited considerable migration efficiencies and cost reductions. For example, some respondents required 24% fewer full-time employees to complete migration projects, from 128.6 to 97.3 on average. The duration of the migration was also shortened from 12.2 months to only seven months, a 43% improvement. As a result of these efficiencies gain, the cost of document-related migration became 24% more affordable.</p>
  <p>As one manufacturing executive noted, “Doing data migration is easier if you minimize the number of applications. SAP ECM solutions by OpenText helped us put building blocks in place. Our knowledge has increased, and the learning curve is less steep. We know more about what is required country to country.”</p>
  <h2 id="decreasing-invoice-errors">Decreasing Invoice Errors</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-a-snapshot-of-the-idc-whitepaper">Get a snapshot of the IDC whitepaper</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/10/3ede3947-027e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>When the volume of paper invoices increases, manual processes become too time-consuming and risk-prone to maintain. For one of the survey participants, the lack of history tracking, trend analysis, and currency distinction led to €300,000 lost on paying invoices because the organization missed out on receiving discounts upwards of two percent. And in some cases, IDC reported that many respondents also paid interest and penalties on late payments that they could have avoided.</p>
  <p>After automating invoicing tasks with enterprise content management, organizations realized a 35% drop in delayed payments and paid 36% less on penalties and interest. The system immediately validates and approves incoming invoices, improving overall invoice performance and decreasing errors by 43% on average.</p>
  <p>A participating executive from an industrial chemicals company remarked on the tremendous value of digitalizing invoice management: “From the moment the organization moved toward less touching, it saw a 70% improvement over paper.”</p>
  <h2 id="boosting-organizational-efficiency">Boosting Organizational Efficiency</h2>
  <p>As digital transformation becomes synonymous with business growth, executives must consistently consider new capabilities and enhancements to improve their operations, employees’ lives, desired outcomes, and customer experiences. In fact, this mindset is bringing forth a new focus on business efficiency and resiliency.</p>
  <p>From invoice intake and processing, accounts payable, and auditing teams to areas outside of finance, solutions for enterprise content management can have an impressive impact on organizational efficiency, ranging from 24% to 41%. This outcome is largely due to allowing multiple users to obtain documents with greater ease. Organizations can work independently of an office location and still have secure access to content from a single centralized environment.</p>
  <p>In return, users who work from remote locations can work more effectively, which is a tremendous benefit for businesses with most of their workforce still working from home and in the field. Companies can support employees from more geographic regions and across all process streams and operational areas ‒ all without shuttling physical documents back and forth in e-mail.</p>
  <p>In addition, since their content is archived and stored in a centralized process and database, organizations can stay compliant with regulatory and business requirements with minimal or no effort. A surveyed healthcare executive noted this advantage’s value: “We can see content now, whereas the older way we had to search. We can now look at transactional records, so compliance is handled on the schedule.”</p>
  <h2 id="gaining-the-full-potential-of-content-management">Gaining the Full Potential of Content Management</h2>
  <p>The deeper companies transform into digital-first enterprises, the closer they get to operate at a level of efficiency, intelligence, and speed that rivals their competitors. And the first place to gain that edge is best found in digitalization through enterprise content management that removes the complexity of siloed information, spreadsheets, data extractions, and manipulations.</p>
  <p>Explore the calculated cost savings and business benefits of SAP enterprise content management solutions by OpenText, which support enterprise content management. Read the IDC whitepaper, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2022/01/629d79f0-127e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">The Business Value of SAP Enterprise Content Management Solutions by OpenText in the Digital-First World</a>,” commissioned by SAP and Open Text.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/opentext</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Icertis Expand Partnership to Deliver Enterprise Contract Intelligence]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/sap-icertis-expand-partnership</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/sap-icertis-expand-partnership</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[An expanded cooperation with Icertis will help SAP customers take advantage of market-leading innovations for contract management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_138c442285c71c51b7df821b9cafb8724bb18d76f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_138c442285c71c51b7df821b9cafb8724bb18d76f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_138c442285c71c51b7df821b9cafb8724bb18d76f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP and Icertis Expand Partnership to Deliver Enterprise Contract Intelligence" src="./media_138c442285c71c51b7df821b9cafb8724bb18d76f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-and-icertis-expand-partnership-to-deliver-enterprise-contract-intelligence">SAP and Icertis Expand Partnership to Deliver Enterprise Contract Intelligence</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF and BELLEVUE, Wash.</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com">SAP SE</a> (NYSE:SAP) and <a href="http://www.icertis.com">Icertis</a> today announced an expanded partnership for enhanced contract management to help companies increase efficiency, minimize risk and realize the full intent of their agreements.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The partnership, which includes a financial investment from SAP in Icertis, will lead to a joint product road map and deeper technological integration to deliver enterprise-wide value, including faster negotiations, greater compliance and AI-powered business insights and automation.</p>
  <p>“The expanded cooperation with Icertis will help our customers take advantage of market-leading innovations for contract management from Icertis while managing core business processes with SAP solutions,” said Christian Klein, CEO and member of the Executive Board, SAP SE. “This partnership is a great complement to our portfolio, with multiple touchpoints to SAP systems across ERP, finance, procurement, sales and HR.”</p>
  <p>This expanded partnership builds on the existing relationship between SAP and Icertis, which began in 2020 to transform the <a href="https://www.icertis.com/news/icertis-integrates-with-sap-ariba/?utm_source=hootsuite&#x26;utm_medium=&#x26;utm_term=&#x26;utm_content=&#x26;utm_campaign=Increase%20CLM%20Leadership">source-to-pay</a> and <a href="https://www.icertis.com/news/icertis-partners-with-sap-sales-cloud/">lead-to-cash</a> processes through the integration of Icertis Contract Intelligence (ICI) with SAP Ariba and SAP Customer Experience solutions. The enhanced partnership further leverages each company’s technology to deliver even more value to a growing list of joint customers. Customers will have the opportunity to benefit from ICI capabilities for smart contract creation, online negotiation, AI-assisted risk identification, obligation management and contract-driven insights for decision support while operating their core source-to-pay and lead-to-cash processes within SAP solutions.</p>
  <p>“With this partnership, SAP and Icertis customers will be able to derive end-to-end value across the enterprise, so the intent of every contract is correctly memorialized and fully realized,” said Samir Bodas, CEO of Icertis. “Partnering with SAP to bring our AI-powered, best-of-breed contract intelligence to the market is another affirmation of Icertis’ strategy to become the contract intelligence platform of the world. It is also a testament to SAP’s forward-looking vision for the intelligent and networked enterprise.”</p>
  <p>As part of the expanded partnership, Icertis Contract Intelligence (ICI) for SAP Ariba solutions and ICI for SAP Customer Experience solutions are now SAP Endorsed Apps, premium certified by SAP with added security, in-depth testing and measurements against cloud operations best practices.</p>
  <p>“SAP’s focus on the intelligent enterprise has enabled many organizations to move into the digital-first world, and the contracting process in SAP Ariba solutions has done much for the buying community,” said Mickey North Rizza, Program Vice President Enterprise Applications and Digital Commerce, IDC. “Icertis is named a leader in the IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Contract Life-Cycle Management Software for Corporate Legal 2021. With Icertis’ flexible platform and enhanced CLM capabilities, SAP can now manage the trading partner relationship for the enterprise in a much more integrated, innovative and tailored manner.”</p>
  <p>Contracts are the foundation of commerce, governing the rights and obligations between parties. Traditional contract management is often manual and siloed, creating inefficiency and risk while leaving value unrealized. ICI helps structure and connect data within contracts across an enterprise, enabling businesses to increase efficiencies, identify and mitigate potential risk, and drive bottom-line value throughout the contract lifecycle.</p>
  <p>Icertis solutions including <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-0000055732_live_v1/Icertis%20Contract%20Intelligence%20%28ICI%29%20for%20SAP%20Ariba">ICI for SAP Ariba solutions</a> and <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-0000059213_live_v1/Icertis%20Contract%20Intelligence%20%28ICI%29%20for%20SAP%20Customer%20Experience">ICI for SAP Customer Experience solutions</a> are available in <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/">SAP Store</a>, the digital marketplace for solutions from SAP and its partners. SAP Store provides customers with real-time access to more than 1,800 innovative solutions from SAP as well as partner solutions that complement and extend their SAP applications.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a> and follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="standardize-source-to-contract-processes-across-the-organization">Standardize source-to-contract processes across the organization</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/strategic-sourcing-and-contracts.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="about-icertis">About Icertis</h3>
  <p>With unmatched technology and category-defining innovation, Icertis pushes the boundaries of what’s possible with contract lifecycle management (CLM). The AI-powered, analyst-validated Icertis Contract Intelligence (ICI) platform turns contracts from static documents into a strategic advantage by structuring and connecting the critical contract information that defines how an organization runs. Today, the world’s most iconic brands and disruptive innovators trust Icertis to govern the rights and commitments in their 10 million+ contracts worth more than $1 trillion, in 40+ languages and 90+ countries.</p>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong></p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want — without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong>:<br>Kelly Sheldon Murray, SAP, +1 (978) 708-6821, <a href="mailto:kelly.murray@sap.com">kelly.murray@sap.com</a><u>,</u> ETGeraldine Lim, SAP, +1 (415) 418-0945, <a href="mailto:geraldine.lim@sap.com">geraldine.lim@sap.com</a>, PT<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a><br>Liza Colburn, Director of Corporate Communications, Icertis,<br><a href="mailto:CorpComm@icertis.com">CorpComm@icertis.com</a>, +1 (781) 562-0111</p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2020 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2022 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI Trends 2022: Spare Us the Hype, We Want Business Results]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/ai-trends-2022-spare-us-the-hype-we-want-business-results</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/ai-trends-2022-spare-us-the-hype-we-want-business-results</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The latest industry analyst predictions on AI trends show how smart, creative, and sincere artificial intelligence will become. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c8d8a4bb0d40b93cde54c85cab62756d51ea01fc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c8d8a4bb0d40b93cde54c85cab62756d51ea01fc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c8d8a4bb0d40b93cde54c85cab62756d51ea01fc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="AI Trends 2022: Spare Us the Hype, We Want Business Results" src="./media_1c8d8a4bb0d40b93cde54c85cab62756d51ea01fc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="ai-trends-2022-spare-us-the-hype-we-want-business-results">AI Trends 2022: Spare Us the Hype, We Want Business Results</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>If you thought judgment, ethics, and even creativity were the unique purview of humans, think again.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The latest industry analyst predictions about artificial intelligence (AI) are out, and they’re certain to oust a ton of assumptions we’ve made to date. Read on to find out just how smart, creative, and sincere AI will become during the next few years.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="find-out-more-about-intelligent-technologies-from-sap">Find out more about intelligent technologies from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/intelligent-technologies.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="creative-machines-are-the-future">Creative Machines Are the Future</h2>
  <p>Noting that South Africa granted the first patent to a creative AI system in 2021, <a href="https://www.forrester.com/predictions/">Forrester</a> researchers predicted creative AI systems will win dozens of patents in 2022. They were quick to point out that “AI will not own the products in the traditional sense – the developers of the AI systems…will still enjoy commercial benefits. But companies will experiment with creative AI, knowing that these innovations may be legally protected.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.forrester.com/blogs/meet-the-new-demand-for-creativity-with-ai/">Forrester</a> Analyst Diego Lo Giudice looked ahead to “AI 2.0,” which he saw fueling the development of new creative business applications, exceeding basic expectations of AI to free up workers for greater creativity. He predicted that AI would connect business processes across silos to boost business creativity and wrote that “AI’s new business models can optimize the convergence of the digital world with the physical world and drive the ‘anything as a digital service’ trend. The impact on customer experience could be huge.”</p>
  <h2 id="explainable-ai-is-not-your-typical-it-project">Explainable AI Is Not Your Typical IT Project</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-the-entire-sap-institute-for-digital-government-research-series">Explore the entire SAP Institute for Digital Government research series</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://discover.sap.com/sap-institute-digital-gov/en-us/publications.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Explainability and ethics were among the most widely discussed AI-related issues. <a href="https://www.forrester.com/blogs/predictions-for-2022-successfully-riding-the-next-wave-of-ai/">Forrester</a> Analyst Srividya Sridharan saw the market for responsible AI solutions doubling as industries adopt “responsible AI solutions that help companies turn AI principles such as fairness and transparency into consistent practices.” And for those who fear these algorithms will run amok, <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US47913321">IDC</a> analysts predicted that by 2025, to reduce reputational risks, 40% of G2000 companies will be forced to redesign their approaches to algorithmic decision-making, providing better human oversight and explainability.</p>
  <p>AI explainability is one of topics that Ian Ryan is exploring as global head of the SAP Institute for Digital Government. It’s part of a research series for the Australian public sector on the value and impact of technologies for employees, citizens, and society at large. Ryan said that AI can help deliver citizen services with that coveted Amazon-like experience, provided organizations set value-based, measurable objectives.</p>
  <p>“Applications of AI consist of the person using it, the AI model itself, and the information that comes from reality; these three pieces have to be in sync, targeted towards driving a particular outcome,” said Ryan. “You need to train the AI model continuously, keeping it updated so it can support workers as situations evolve, engineering out any bias while preserving data protection.”</p>
  <p>For business value, AI algorithms cannot function as an inscrutable black box or operate autonomously. Ryan said organizations need to build explainability into complex AI models and involve targeted employees in AI model development.</p>
  <p>“AI supports employees by taking tasks away, allowing people to be more productive and focus on high-value activities,” he said. “Al can access huge amounts of seemingly disconnected data from different places and identify patterns in seconds, far faster than humans. Explainability provides the transparency people can trust, so they’ll share their data knowing the organization will protect it and deliver value.”</p>
  <p>Indeed, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/information-technology/insights/top-technology-trends">Gartner</a> analysts warned that while AI will help companies emerge from the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> in a strong position, merely adopting AI won’t be enough. Companies need to operationalize updates to AI models, “using integrated data and model and development pipelines to deliver consistent business value from AI. It combines automated update pipelines with strong AI governance.”</p>
  <h2 id="ai-becomes-ubiquitous">AI Becomes Ubiquitous</h2>
  <p>Numerous analyst predictions tout the benefits of AI in strengthening human decisions. <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US48298421">IDC</a> researchers said that 85% of enterprises will combine human expertise with AI, machine learning, natural language processing, and pattern recognition to augment foresight across the organization, making workers 25% more productive and effective by 2026. <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US47913321">IDC</a> researchers saw 30% of organizations using forms of behavioral economics and AI- and machine learning-driven insights to nudge employees’ actions, leading to a 60% increase in desired outcomes by 2026.</p>
  <p>More near term, <a href="https://www.forrester.com/blogs/predictions-for-2022-successfully-riding-the-next-wave-of-ai/">Sridharan</a> expected traditional businesses will take a page out of digital-native practices during the pandemic with an AI-first approach to platform and digital transformation. He said that “the more AI inside, the more enterprises can shrink the latency between insights, decisions, and results.”</p>
  <p>Unlike many previous innovations, AI is not an isolated technology that organizations can surgically apply and wait for the magic to happen. AI is an extraordinarily powerful technology with profound ramifications for organizations and people as they discover its true business potential.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/12/08/ai-trends-2022-spare-us-the-hype-we-want-business-results/?sh=11dd0d96601a">This blog also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable Retail Business Solutions from SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/nrf-2022-sustainable-retail-business-solutions-from-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/nrf-2022-sustainable-retail-business-solutions-from-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[During NRF 2022, read how SAP solutions are helping retailers digitally transform and make their businesses sustainable.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a903832003837e34c273cbd6c0ea4f5745d5d107.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a903832003837e34c273cbd6c0ea4f5745d5d107.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a903832003837e34c273cbd6c0ea4f5745d5d107.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Sustainable Retail Business Solutions from SAP" src="./media_1a903832003837e34c273cbd6c0ea4f5745d5d107.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sustainable-retail-business-solutions-from-sap">Sustainable Retail Business Solutions from SAP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-sap-at-nrf-2022">Learn more about SAP at NRF 2022</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/noam/nrf/en/home">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong> — The <a href="https://cdn.nrf.com/sites/default/files/2020-06/RS-118304%20NRF%20Retail%20Impact%20Report%20.pdf">retail industry’s</a> $3.9 trillion contribution to the U.S. annual GDP makes it the nation’s leading industry for private sector employment and uniquely positioned to address climate change.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As recently as the 2021 United Nations Climate Change Conference (COP26) meetings, the <a href="https://nrf.com/blog/retailers-set-science-based-targets-address-climate-change">National Retail Federation (NRF)</a> stated, “Retailers will continue inventing and implementing pragmatic climate change solutions because the needs identified at COP26 demand nothing less.”</p>
  <p>To help retailers digitally transform to make their businesses sustainable, SAP is featuring a number of offerings, including these:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>The new <a href="/2021/07/sap-intelligent-returns-management-consumers-retailers-environment">SAP Intelligent Returns Management solution</a> was built to optimize the returns process for the retail industry. The solution uses routing and dispositioning decisions driven by artificial intelligence (AI) to guide products from customers’ hands to the final dispositioning steps, ultimately maximizing customer experience and company margins while also mitigating waste.</li>
    <li>The recently updated <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/09/a6120d2d-f87d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">SAP Assortment Planning application</a> now offers advanced category management capabilities. It uses customer data science, assortment strategies, business rules and AI to plan space-aware, localized assortments with a user experience designed for the needs of today’s category manager. Customer-centric, relevant assortments increase customer loyalty, boost profitability and support a more sustainable supply chain.</li>
    <li>The SAP.iO Foundries program is a network of startup companies with integrations to SAP solutions, including:
      <ul>
        <li><strong><a href="https://algramo.com/en">Algramo</a>,</strong> offering a circular platform that encourages consumers to buy in a more convenient, affordable way with zero waste and connects people, brands and retailers in an engaging way to change consumption habits</li>
        <li><strong><a href="https://ecocart.io/business/">EcoCart</a>,</strong> helping thousands of e-commerce brands offer carbon-neutral products</li>
        <li><strong><a href="https://everledger.io/">Everledger</a>,</strong> leveraging blockchain and the Internet of Things to offer transparency into supply chains for clarity on quality, origin, sustainability footprint and compliance standards</li>
        <li><strong><a href="https://evrythng.com/">EVRYTHNG</a>,</strong> helping customers run their businesses differently with real-time data intelligence from each of their products end to end, from factory to consumer and beyond</li>
        <li><strong><a href="https://inspectorio.com/">Inspectorio</a>,</strong> with a dynamic and risk-assessment-based quality compliance program that provides digitalization, automation, transparency and traceability</li>
        <li><strong><a href="https://thelimeloop.com/">LimeLoop</a>,</strong> offering a platform for sustainable shipping including reusable packaging, real-time tracking and predictive analytics</li>
        <li><strong><a href="https://specright.com/">Specright</a>,</strong> providing a purpose-built platform for specification management that fundamentally changes how brands, suppliers, manufacturers and retailers manage data and collaborate to bring products to market</li>
      </ul>
    </li>
  </ul>
  <p>In addition to these offerings, retailers can utilize SAP’s entire portfolio of <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html">sustainable business solutions</a>. Learn more in the blog “<a href="/">SAP Cloud for Sustainable Enterprises: Taking Action Together</a>.”</p>
  <p>SAP’s solutions enable retailers to integrate sustainable business practices smoothly, which is critical to a fast-paced industry such as retail. According to Leslie Hand, IDC Group Vice President, IDC Retail Insights, <a href="https://eur03.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.linkedin.com%2Fcompany%2Fidc_emea%2F&#x26;data=04%7C01%7Cstacy.comes%40sap.com%7C32f20fbd808e403ebab108d9c18832a2%7C42f7676cf455423c82f6dc2d99791af7%7C0%7C0%7C637753612987837002%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000&#x26;sdata=Avs0Ujbs1kRZqn0deU53aOOosGrbGrMddrMgbScdhSc%3D&#x26;reserved=0">IDC’s latest research</a> indicates that retail organizations report that, relative to political, social and economic risks, changing environmental targets and regulations will have the greatest impact on their digital transformation and tech investment plans in the next two years. Further, 80% (Asia Pacific) 59% (United States) and 64% (EMEA) of retail organizations agree that their digital technology strategy is an important enabler of their organization’s broader sustainability efforts.*</p>
  <p>For more information about SAP at NRF 2022, Retail’s Big Show, visit <a href="https://events.sap.com/noam/nrf/en/home">sap.com/nrf</a> and follow <a href="https://twitter.com/SAP_Retail">@SAP_Retail</a> on Twitter.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Stacy Ries, SAP Media Relations, +1 (484) 619-0411, <a href="mailto:stacy.ries@sap.com">stacy.ries@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p><em>*Source: IDC Retail Core Processes and Applications, May 2021.</em><br>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2022 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/nrf</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-assortment-planning</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises</category>
            <category>product/sap-intelligent-returns-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-io</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>