<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-erp-hcm/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/2023-gartner-mq-cloud-hcm-suites-1000-employee-enterprises</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/2023-gartner-mq-cloud-hcm-suites-1000-employee-enterprises</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is a leader in the Cloud HCM Magic Quadrant for the eight consecutive year as it continues to help drive change within workforces.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-erp-hcm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Second Half 2023 Release: AI-Driven Innovation to Ignite the Potential in Your Workforce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-successfactors-second-half-2023-release</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-successfactors-second-half-2023-release</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Our SAP SuccessFactors second half 2023 release is full of AI innovation. Read to learn how we are applying it in our solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-erp-hcm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[On-Premise Customers Realizing Benefits of Moving HR to SAP SuccessFactors]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/benefits-moving-on-premise-hr-to-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/benefits-moving-on-premise-hr-to-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP SuccessFactors, we continue to make investments to streamline the transition for our on-premise customers with focused initiatives]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cbfc53de6444e8aa82313cbc8457262f0c9abf49.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cbfc53de6444e8aa82313cbc8457262f0c9abf49.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1cbfc53de6444e8aa82313cbc8457262f0c9abf49.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="On-Premise Customers Realizing Benefits of Moving HR to SAP SuccessFactors" src="./media_1cbfc53de6444e8aa82313cbc8457262f0c9abf49.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="on-premise-customers-realizing-benefits-of-moving-hr-to-sap-successfactors">On-Premise Customers Realizing Benefits of Moving HR to SAP SuccessFactors</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Organizations are constantly looking for ways to enhance their operational efficiency and provide a better experience for their workforce.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>I spent many years of my career working on SAP ERP Human Capital Management (HCM) on-premise and it is very near and dear to my heart. But, I am also a big believer in using innovative modern technology to help organizations run their business as efficiently as possible and get the most out of their people. We are seeing an increased urgency for customers to transform their HR operations to improve agility and productivity in a constantly changing world.</p>
  <p>For Maryann Abbajay, chief revenue officer at SAP SuccessFactors, the readiness of many of our customers to begin their cloud HR journeys is accelerating. “So far in 2023, we are seeing increased momentum of SAP on-premise customers moving to the cloud. In the first half of the year, we saw well over 100 customers sign up to move their core HCM or payroll to the cloud,” she said. “We’re gearing up to increase this pace in the second half of the year as well.”</p>
  <p>More importantly, a move to the cloud is about achieving success and better business results, which includes large and complex businesses. Here are a few recent examples of customers that are realizing benefits with the move:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2022/11/80daf380-4d7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Microsoft</a> has been able to create consistent employee experiences worldwide for its 220,000 employees in over 100 countries. With a move to the cloud, it can create jobs much faster and become a more agile business.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/04/7a53dae4-6c7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Purolator</a> has created organizational agility while providing a better experience for employees. The integration of HR and finance is helping the company make better business decisions.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/roehm.html">Röhm</a> has been able to standardize its processes leading to significantly reduced HR IT costs. It can now better support and empower employees with a new digital HR experience.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>At SAP SuccessFactors, we continue to make a substantial investment to streamline the transition for our existing customers with focused initiatives. These include the introduction of the SAP Readiness Check tool for SAP SuccessFactors solutions, where we continue to see <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2023/02/17/sap-readiness-check-for-successfactors-customer-momentum/">increased adoption</a> with nearly 150 customers, including those with over 100,000 employees, running it to help jump-start a move to the cloud.</p>
  <p>We’ve also delivered product investments focused on meeting the business requirements of SAP ERP HCM based upon direct customer feedback. This includes enhancements to <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/employee-central-hris.html">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</a>, building a leading <a href="/2022/09/sap-industry-leading-time-management-suite">time management suite</a>, and an emphasis on hybrid customers by building enhanced data and process integrations for a best-in-class experience for customers that continue to use on premise along with SAP SuccessFactors solutions.</p>
  <p>A few years ago, I wrote an article on a dozen improvements in SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite, which had a direct comparison between on premise and the cloud. It becomes clear that there are a lot of advantages to moving to SAP SuccessFactors solutions, but in 2023 we face a complex economic landscape and many companies are being intentional about where to invest their time and resources.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="simplify-your-move-from-on-premise-hcm-to-the-cloud-with-sap-successfactors">Simplify your move from on-premise HCM to the cloud with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/hxm-move.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="building-a-business-case-to-support-moving-hr-to-the-cloud">Building a Business Case to Support Moving HR to the Cloud</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-infographic-moving-from-sap-erp-hcm-to-sap-successfactors-solutions">Read the infographic: Moving from SAP ERP HCM to SAP SuccessFactors Solutions</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/07/aa55462b-7e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To help customers make the business case, we recently worked with a third-party vendor, Enterprise Strategy Group (ESG) by TechTarget, to analyze the economic benefits of moving from SAP ERP HCM to SAP SuccessFactors HXM Suite. To complete the analysis, ESG conducted multiple customer interviews, used its industry knowledge, leveraged public data, and evaluated SAP SuccessFactors solutions to build a comprehensive model that compared the cost and benefits of HR operations of SAP SuccessFactors solutions versus continued use of SAP ERP HCM.</p>
  <p>The research contained four categories in which customers would expect to see a benefit: improved experience for all employees, more efficient HR and IT operations, improved business agility and enablement, and unique SAP advantages.</p>
  <p>The result of this analysis validated how organizations can realize over 100% ROI through increased organizational efficiency. Learn more: <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/hxm-move.html?pdf-asset=aa55462b-7e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=1&#x26;url_id=ctabutton-us-move-esginfographic">Analyzing the Economic Benefits of Moving from SAP ERP HCM to SAP SuccessFactors HXM Suite.</a></p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Imran Sajid is senior director of HXM Solution Marketing at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-erp-hcm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Second Half 2022 Release: Building a Future-Ready Workforce Today]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-successfactors-second-half-2022-release</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-successfactors-second-half-2022-release</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The SAP SuccessFactors second half 2022 release introduces new innovations around creating an agile and future-ready workforce. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1074c8b37f11498501b456579a1cc6d70dabc96f4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1074c8b37f11498501b456579a1cc6d70dabc96f4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1074c8b37f11498501b456579a1cc6d70dabc96f4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP SuccessFactors Second Half 2022 Release: Building a Future-Ready Workforce Today" src="./media_1074c8b37f11498501b456579a1cc6d70dabc96f4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-successfactors-second-half-2022-release-building-a-future-ready-workforce-today">SAP SuccessFactors Second Half 2022 Release: Building a Future-Ready Workforce Today</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In today’s business landscape, organizations must equip themselves to respond to workforce opportunities or challenges <em>before</em> they arise. If recent trends have taught us anything, it’s that by the time a business reacts to a market shift, a new one is already occurring. Staying a step ahead of workforce demands is no longer a step ahead – it’s step one.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The SAP SuccessFactors second half 2022 release, which is available for preview today, introduces new innovations focused on empowering organizations to create an agile and future-ready workforce in a rapidly changing workplace as well as further investments for individualized experiences and agile and compliant HR.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="realizing-a-people-centered-future-of-work-through-the-intelligent-enterprise">Realizing a People-Centered Future of Work Through the Intelligent Enterprise</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/06/people-centered-future-of-work-intelligent-enterprise-hxm">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="creating-a-future-ready-workforce">Creating a Future-Ready Workforce</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="change-the-world-of-work-for-good-with-the-next-generation-of-hcm-software-from-sap">Change the world of work for good with the next generation of HCM software from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the face of increasingly complex and more urgent transformations, organizations must accelerate their talent development at scale. At the core of such adaptability is an understanding of the skills organizations need to build and grow. As part of our early adopter care program, select customers will have access to skills ontology, growth portfolio, and dynamic teams, which work together to deliver greater intelligence on the skills and capabilities that currently exist and are needed within an organization.</p>
  <p><strong>The skills ontology</strong> is a major advancement for SAP SuccessFactors that’s connected to global skills databases to help ensure that organizations have a comprehensive and up-to-date view of the most important skills for their workforce. It delivers machine learning and artificial intelligence (AI) powered recommendations to employees about relevant and trending skills to prioritize for development.</p>
  <p><strong>The growth portfolio</strong>, also part of the early adopter care program, is how employees can reveal their skills, capabilities, education, language proficiencies, and certifications. In the second half release, this data will connect employees to the most relevant assignments in <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/opportunity-marketplace.html">SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace</a>. While the skills ontology gives organizations the ability to align talent development to the ambitions of the organization, the growth portfolio enables employees to align their own talent development to their ambitions.</p>
  <p><strong>Dynamic teams</strong> is also part of the SAP SuccessFactors foundation and available to all customers. Within organizations today, there are countless teams that exist outside of traditional organizational structures – groups of people that work cross-functionally on a project for a certain amount of time. The dynamic teams functionality can provide organizations with visibility into these teams as well as tools to help manage and assemble teams. Team progress can be measured using objectives and key results (OKRs) and employees can find a dynamic team within SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace to help learn new skills and continue to grow their career. This transparency within the organization levels the playing field and creates equal opportunity for employees.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11660a4ded960363037d3e57f808136c91669c786.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11660a4ded960363037d3e57f808136c91669c786.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11660a4ded960363037d3e57f808136c91669c786.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_11660a4ded960363037d3e57f808136c91669c786.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="534">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Click to enlarge</em></p>
  <p>With richer data and greater talent intelligence, organizations can help ensure that employees are connected to the most relevant talent development opportunities that are aligned to the ambitions of employees and the needs of the organization. Skills ontology, growth portfolio, and dynamic teams provide significant updates to the foundation of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/hxm-suite.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a> – built into what customers already have instead of requiring an entirely new solution.</p>
  <p>Some more exciting features for our second half 2022 release are around individualized experiences and agile and compliant HR, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Chosen name and personal pronouns:</strong> As part of our commitment to diversity, equity, and inclusion, we are taking important steps to help every individual be seen and valued. People can now indicate their chosen name, personal pronouns, and gender directly within the people profile. This information is displayed consistently across SAP SuccessFactors solutions – from recruiting to learning, helping to foster a greater sense of belonging.</li>
    <li><strong>End-to-end visual redesign:</strong> We are enhancing the overall look and feel of SAP SuccessFactors by implementing the Horizon visual theme for SAP Fiori. This new theme enhances consistency while delivering a more informed and streamlined product experience. Employees will find nearly every element of the solution updated with new colors, typography, iconography, layouts, and visual hierarchy focused on intent and success. We remain on track to have every employee-facing SAP SuccessFactors experience unified with the theme by the end of 2023.</li>
    <li><strong>SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone guided onboarding experience:</strong> By bringing together SAP SuccessFactors solutions and third-party integrations, organizations can more efficiently handle an array of complex onboarding processes. This new feature helps ensure that employees receive individualized experiences, even before their first day. Covering key phases of the new hire journey, the guided onboarding experience for <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/workzone-hr.html">SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone</a> helps provide the tools and information employees need, both before and after hiring.</li>
    <li><strong>Cross-system workflow capability:</strong> We are unveiling a new cross-system workflow capability for processes that involve multiple users from multiple systems, such as SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and the payroll component of SAP ERP Human Capital Management. A guided activity framework for key processes enables our on-premise customers to more rapidly unlock the value of the cloud with SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and the latest HXM innovations while maintaining and progressively moving on-premise processes to the cloud over time.</li>
    <li><strong>Time management enhancements:</strong> We are continuing to <a href="/2022/09/sap-industry-leading-time-management-suite">enhance our capabilities in time management</a> with the much-anticipated ability to export leave events into calendar applications along with better support for public holidays and handling of grace rules. Time administrators can now copy time-related configuration objects, reducing the need for manual duplication during configuration. In addition, temporary work schedules and absence information on a per day basis will now be available for reporting in SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>All these and many more exciting features will be available in our 2H 2022 release, in preview today and production on Friday, December 9. Please watch our <a href="https://dam.sap.com/mac/app/p/video/asset/preview/KvodB4Q?ltr=a&#x26;rc=10">second half 2022 release highlights video</a> for more information.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Amy Wilson is senior vice president of Products and Design for SAP SuccessFactors.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/dynamic-teams</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-erp-hcm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HR Transformation Is Changing in a New Hybrid Era]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/hr-transformation-is-changing-in-new-hybrid-era</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/hr-transformation-is-changing-in-new-hybrid-era</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The cloud can be a viable, long-term choice for HR transformation. Learn more about the deployment options to help you move to the cloud.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e958dd85b3014d05423ae9871982dcde5f562197.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e958dd85b3014d05423ae9871982dcde5f562197.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e958dd85b3014d05423ae9871982dcde5f562197.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="HR Transformation Is Changing in a New Hybrid Era" src="./media_1e958dd85b3014d05423ae9871982dcde5f562197.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="hr-transformation-is-changing-in-a-new-hybrid-era">HR Transformation Is Changing in a New Hybrid Era</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Most executives have a positive outlook on how their digital transformation plans can affect their business prospects. But HR leaders are, by far, the most optimistic when considering cloud technology to enable new opportunities to increase workplace flexibility, control costs, and accelerate strategic decision-making.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Unfortunately, frustration is growing on the other side of this cloud adoption boom. In a <a href="https://www.pwc.com/us/en/tech-effect/cloud/cloud-business-survey.html">PwC</a> survey, 53% of surveyed executives believe their organizations have yet to realize substantial value from their cloud investments, even though 56% view it as a strategic platform for growth and innovation.</p>
  <p>As with any digital business transformation, cloud technology is a critical enabler. It connects systems, data, devices, and emerging technology to allow companies to operate more quickly, innovatively, and with more agility. However, and more importantly, the cloud offers people and their organizations a gradual approach to creating and establishing lasting change in how they work.</p>
  <h2 id="closing-the-cloud-value-gap-to-drive-true-change">Closing the Cloud Value Gap to Drive True Change</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="join-the-sap-hxm-movement">Join the SAP HXM Movement</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hxm-move.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>There is great power in allowing people to choose how they transition to new technology – but not everyone is ready to take the leap all at once. Using technology to evolve how employees think, collaborate, and work enables organizations to align their digital strategy with business needs, address the next digital talent divide, and advance business goals as they shift. Then, ultimately, they build a level of trust that compels people to embrace change more openly.</p>
  <p>For that reason, some organizations view the cloud as a viable, long-term choice for HR transformation. The modular nature of cloud-based human experience management (HXM) technology, such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a>, allows organizations to take a step-by-step deployment approach. They can choose to deploy one module at a time, allowing users to adapt their work habits gradually. Then, adoption can be expanded slowly to eventually cover the entire employee life cycle fully in the cloud.</p>
  <p>Yet, one of the challenges most companies face is knowing and understanding which deployment options can best help them move at their pace to the cloud. In short, there are three to consider:</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="build-your-success-as-an-intelligent-enterprise-with-sap-services-and-support-offerings">Build your success as an intelligent enterprise with SAP Services and Support offerings</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="talent-hybrid">#1 Talent Hybrid</h3>
  <p>A first entry point for cloud adoption that delivers immediate value is running talent management in the cloud and maintaining processes for core HR, payroll, time management, and benefits on premise. By using talent management solutions and people analytics, HR organizations can adjust or completely reimagine recruiting, onboarding, performance and goals management, compensation, learning, and succession.</p>
  <h3 id="core-hybrid">#2 Core Hybrid</h3>
  <p>The core hybrid option is recommended for HR organizations that want to move their HR core processes to the cloud but keep payroll and time management on premise. This deployment approach allows HR leaders to rethink their talent management capabilities, as done with a talent hybrid. Organizations can add cloud-based personnel administration and organizational management solutions and integrate data with their existing instance of SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management Suite. Then, they can keep the payroll and time management solutions from the suite on premise without disruption.</p>
  <p>Often, organizations that embrace the talent hybrid or core hybrid approach will have further objectives related to the adoption of cloud infrastructure. In response, SAP has developed a hybrid transition scenario, the SAP Human Capital Management solution for SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition.</p>
  <p>When using the solution, SAP customers with complex time and payroll requirements are afforded the ability to move things stand-alone or embedded in their enterprise resource planning stack into SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition. Plus, they can realize the full benefit from cloud infrastructure and subscription-based licensing. Furthermore, their deployment of human capital management (HCM) applications for payroll, time, and attendance are left undisrupted.</p>
  <h3 id="full-cloud">#3 Full Cloud</h3>
  <p>The full cloud option is what most companies envision when considering true HR transformation through a move to the cloud. HR organizations can bring together all their core HR-related data and applications – including payroll and time management – and move them all at once with a modern, cloud-based solution.</p>
  <p>The move to a full cloud deployment approach for HR may seem daunting. But organizations can ease the transition by taking the time up front to identify the goals they wish to achieve through transformation and the value proposition associated with adopting cloud solutions, as well as consider risks realistically. These early measures can help ensure that the true benefits of “going to the cloud” are observed.</p>
  <p>Some of the key benefits of a full cloud transformation include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Innovating quickly, meaningfully, and with a low total cost of ownership innovation</li>
    <li>Reimagining business processes and taking advantage of standardized best practices</li>
    <li>Eliminating the need to convert outdated and legacy HCM processes and solution configurations</li>
    <li>Adopting a complete set of modern, cloud-native capabilities that improve the speed and scale of HR processes and application experiences</li>
  </ul>
  <p>While results such as immediate savings in operating costs and simplified contracting with the solution provider are compelling, users may need more time to fully accept the transition from on premise to the cloud before realizing additional value from the investment.</p>
  <h2 id="advancing-every-stage-of-an-evolving-hr-function">Advancing Every Stage of an Evolving HR Function</h2>
  <p>The more HCM-related processes managed in the cloud, the better the employee experience. Meanwhile, HR staff, organizational management, and executive leadership have the integrated employee data they need to make intelligent decisions in recruiting, skill development, future succession, and compensation competitiveness. This, in turn, enables businesses to better attract, engage, and retain top talent and inspire the entire workforce as HR evolves from managing people to optimizing the human experience of everyday work.</p>
  <p>This perspective demonstrates the advantages of slowly moving HR to the cloud. Every HR leader has a specific destination in mind for transforming the employee experience and supporting it. But choosing the right processes, applications, and experiences along the way is challenging when locked in a specific environment – regardless of employee readiness. Instead, their organizations need to plan, imagine, and design the HR landscape in ways that are relevant, engaging, and productive to the workforce.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_125aa883445723f33a570f14e3b06b7cbea74ec5c.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_125aa883445723f33a570f14e3b06b7cbea74ec5c.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_125aa883445723f33a570f14e3b06b7cbea74ec5c.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Figure showing how ease of digital transformation increase as you move to the cloud" src="./media_125aa883445723f33a570f14e3b06b7cbea74ec5c.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Figure: Transformation increases exponentially with gradual cloud adoption. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
  <p>To help our customers reframe their concept of the cloud, SAP offers the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hxm-move.html">SAP Human Experience Management Movement</a> program. It helps empower organizations with the on-premise SAP ERP Human Capital Management solution to transition to cloud-based SAP SuccessFactors solutions with a steady expansion of capabilities, as they are needed.</p>
  <h2 id="supporting-people-in-a-rapidly-changing-world">Supporting People in a Rapidly Changing World</h2>
  <p>Providing clear guidance, predictable outcomes, faster time to value, and access to tools, assets, and services helps ease and accelerate the complete migration journey with less complexity. Our customers can then advance their core HR capabilities with improved configurability and localization, such as supporting payroll innovation with little to no disruption and streamlining data integration between on-premise and cloud solutions.</p>
  <p>And whenever a migration to the cloud is simpler and faster, HR organizations open themselves to new possibilities to rethink, readjust, and drive HR transformation that is powerfully relevant, meaningful, and timely.</p>
  <p><strong>Let us help make your cloud HXM migration as easy as possible. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hxm-move.html">Learn more about the SAP HXM Movement program.</a></strong></p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-erp-hcm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-hxm-movement</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>