<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/learning-for-life/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Breaking Barriers Through Education: SAP's Partnership with University of the People]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/breaking-barriers-through-education-sap-university-of-the-people</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/breaking-barriers-through-education-sap-university-of-the-people</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has partnered with University of the People, helping provide global access to higher education. Read the stories of two refugee students.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
            <category>news-tag/ukraine</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Four Culture Keys for Unlocking Lifelong Learning]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/four-culture-keys-lifelong-learning</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/four-culture-keys-lifelong-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A thoughtful and data-driven learning and development strategy is essential to meet business priorities. Here are four culture keys to do so.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Some Organizations Have Successfully Changed Their Learning and Talent Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/organizations-successfully-changed-learning-culture</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/organizations-successfully-changed-learning-culture</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP customers have transformed their learning culture by leveraging SAP SuccessFactors Learning and SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why Building a Lifelong Learning Culture Is Challenging and How to Be Successful]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/building-lifelong-learning-culture-challenges</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/building-lifelong-learning-culture-challenges</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Building a culture of lifelong learning is key to an organization’s long-term viability and can ensure that your workforce is future ready.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Building a Lifelong Learning Culture Is More Important Than Ever]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/building-a-lifelong-learning-culture</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/building-a-lifelong-learning-culture</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Continuous learning options and a culture of lifelong learning will be critical to develop the workforce of the future. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-management-system</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[World Refugee Day: SAP Accelerates Global Partnerships to Boost Education for Displaced Youth]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/world-refugee-day-sap-partnerships-education-for-displaced-youth</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/world-refugee-day-sap-partnerships-education-for-displaced-youth</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[This World Refugee Day, SAP CSR shines a light on our strategic initiatives that power access to education for refugees and displaced youth.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and University of the People: Educate the Leaders of Tomorrow]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2022/02/sap-university-of-the-people-educate-leaders</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2022/02/sap-university-of-the-people-educate-leaders</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In partnership with University of the People, SAP is establishing 100 higher education scholarship for refugees and displaced youth.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[De-Coding the Classroom]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/science-on-stage-de-code-the-classroom</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/science-on-stage-de-code-the-classroom</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Supported by SAP, the European Code Leaguge and Science on Stage enable more students to gain digital skills needed for a challenging future.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10ef344527722252b1347bd697f9b1d41b88e24d6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10ef344527722252b1347bd697f9b1d41b88e24d6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10ef344527722252b1347bd697f9b1d41b88e24d6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="De-Coding the Classroom" src="./media_10ef344527722252b1347bd697f9b1d41b88e24d6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="de-coding-the-classroom">De-Coding the Classroom</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Teachers, along with their students, are shaping the future of education with Science on Stage’s European Code League. Meet this year’s inspiring 2021 winner.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the 1940s, Nobel Prize-winning Hungarian biochemist Albert Szent-Gyoergyi wrote: “The future will be like the schools are today.” In 2021, these words still ring true, even more so for the winners of the European Code League competition, Dr. Corina Toma and Mihaela Giurgea, along with their students from Tiberiu Popoviciu High School of Computer Science in Romania. Second and third place went to teams from Turkey and Greece.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="in-a-post-pandemic-world-youth-take-center-stage-and-lead">In a Post-Pandemic World, Youth Take Center Stage and Lead</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/07/possibilists-study-youth-lead-post-pandemic-world">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="change-is-the-only-constant-but-changemakers-are-ever-changing">Change Is the Only Constant, but Changemakers Are Ever Changing</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-sap4good-stories">Read more SAP4Good stories</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sap4good">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> has been quite a revelation in this aspect, with unexpected and seemingly limitless opportunities presenting themselves and youth grabbing them with both hands.</p>
  <p>According to a report by the World Economic Forum, around 65% of children who start primary school today will work in professions that do not even exist yet: their future lies in the hands of educators. To date, Science on Stage reaches about 100,000 teachers and teacher trainers in over 30 countries, providing a necessary network to exchange ideas and to scale them across Europe. And with 79% of participating teachers implementing the teaching ideas they’ve seen at Science on Stage festivals over the years, European Code League has proven that it’s possible for teachers and students to work together — even in the midst of a pandemic — to create inspiring, real-world science, technology, engineering, and mathematics (STEM) projects.</p>
  <p>Organized by Science on Stage with the support of the SAP Corporate Social Responsibility (SAP CSR) team in Middle Eastern Europe, the European Code League is a competition to which teacher-student teams with innovative coding projects can apply. It was launched in 2020 as a follow up to Science on Stage’s <a href="https://www.science-on-stage.eu/project/coding-stem-education">successful coding project for STEM education</a>.</p>
  <p>“Science on Stage gave me the opportunity to find new ways to motivate my students to learn physics using ICT,” says Dr. Toma, who became a teacher after 10 years working as a physicist. “Physics is everywhere and happens at any time. In the classroom, I am at home. I like to talk with my students and explain all kinds of topics.”</p>
  <p>Science on Stage Europe is a network for STEM teachers focusing on the exchange of best practice teaching ideas. The ultimate goal is to improve STEM teaching by supporting educators in their professional development and growth.</p>
  <p>“Teachers are often the ideas, the starting point. Students who finish high school do not know what their role in the world will be,” Dr Toma adds. “These projects show how important it is to code, and also to learn STEM subjects like mathematics, physics, chemistry, and biology.”</p>
  <p>CaeliBox, the winning coding project, used sensors to measure different air parameters such as concentration of CO2, humidity, pressure, temperature, noise, and other noxious substances in the studennts’ town. The data was transferred to a server so the students could access and work with it at any time.</p>
  <p>“My town in Romania used to be small but now it is very big. As a result, the air is polluted because we have so many cars. CaeliBox is a useful device for STEM education and our students were happy to combine coding with physics and technology,” explains Dr. Toma, who adds that she faced many challenges trying to complete the project, from broken sensors to realizing they needed more space and swapping out their Arduino Uno for an Arduino Mega.</p>
  <p>For Dr. Toma, Science on Stage is far more than a networking opportunity for teachers, it’s a community of like-minded educators: “At first, I saw that the education in Romania is very different from other countries, but then I realized that as teachers we have the same goals and can make the same activities. Science on Stage is a community to challenge our ideas and to understand that we are in the same place. SAP can be very proud for supporting STEM teaching training in Europe.”</p>
  <p>There is no one way to make the world a better place. By helping discover and promote innovative teaching concepts among Europe’s science teachers, Science on Stage and the European Code League enable more students to gain the digital skills they need for a challenging future and encourage them to consider a career in science, ICT or engineering to help the positively change the world.</p>
  <p>In a world shaped increasingly by technology and digitalization, teachers make the difference and the youth of today have so many more opportunities to learn and be the change.</p>
  <p>The 12th European Science on Stage festival takes place March 24-27, 2022, in Prague, Czech Republic. Stay tuned to see amazing youth in action, redefining how a career in science, ICT, or engineering can help make a positive change in the world.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>SAP is committed to helping the world run better and improve people’s lives, with youth playing a critical role. Join us in sharing good news by tagging your stories of inspirational youth or your actions inspiring youth with @SAP4Good on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/sap4good/">Instagram</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/sap4good">Twitter</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/sap4good">Facebook</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Empowering Equity in Education with Virtual Reality and Immersive Learning]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/skill-immersion-lab-education-equity</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/skill-immersion-lab-education-equity</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To support equity in education, SAP and JFFLabs have rolled out a Skill Immersion Lab program with high school-aged learners at three sites.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1af0df9b9b6da496f33f3d94554e2892a50ad3aaf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1af0df9b9b6da496f33f3d94554e2892a50ad3aaf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1af0df9b9b6da496f33f3d94554e2892a50ad3aaf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Empowering Equity in Education with Virtual Reality and Immersive Learning" src="./media_1af0df9b9b6da496f33f3d94554e2892a50ad3aaf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="empowering-equity-in-education-with-virtual-reality-and-immersive-learning">Empowering Equity in Education with Virtual Reality and Immersive Learning</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> has dramatically disrupted traditional learning. While that disruption has widened gaps in access to education that existed along racial, ethnic, and socioeconomic lines, it has also accelerated advances in innovation that could help close those gaps.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>More than a year after schools and training providers pivoted to remote learning, two trends have emerged. First, finding innovative ways to teach and learn is here to stay. Second, many educators who have gained a new appreciation for how technology can help students learn will forever be on the lookout for technical tools that support unique approaches to education. These tools will create pathways to new educational and career opportunities with students from under-resourced communities.</p>
  <p>JFFLabs is the <a href="http://www.jff.org/labs">innovative unit of JFF</a>, a national nonprofit that drives transformation in the American workforce and education systems. Kristina Francis, executive director of JFFLabs, believes that immersive learning currently represents one of the most promising options for changing traditional approaches to education and closing achievement gaps.</p>
  <p>Together, JFFLabs and SAP are piloting an effort to introduce immersive learning to classrooms across the country.</p>
  <p>“This time in history requires expanded access and new entry points for learning, education experiences, and innovation,” Francis said. “It requires corporations and school districts to partner to put resources and technology in the hands of our most marginalized and disadvantaged learners and, frankly, future leaders and innovators.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="in-a-post-pandemic-world-youth-take-center-stage-and-lead">In a Post-Pandemic World, Youth Take Center Stage and Lead</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/07/possibilists-study-youth-lead-post-pandemic-world">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="a-need-for-new-entry-points">A Need for “New Entry Points”</h2>
  <p>The program is called the Skill Immersion Lab. SAP and JFFLabs have rolled it out at three sites working with high school-aged learners: a high school in Queens, New York; a community center in St. Paul, Minnesota; and a workforce development center serving a rural area of Louisiana, which offers instruction to young people ages 16-24 who are unemployed and not in school.</p>
  <p>The importance of finding new ways to engage and motivate students became clear during the pandemic. A June 2020 <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/industries/public-and-social-sector/our-insights/covid-19-and-student-learning-in-the-united-states-the-hurt-could-last-a-lifetime">McKinsey report</a>, citing data from Curriculum Associates, revealed that student engagement rates at schools that serve low-income populations lagged behind those serving high-income students. The data suggested that 60% of students from low-income families were regularly logging on to online instruction, compared to 90% of high-income students.</p>
  <p>Students in the Skill Immersion Lab program are engaging in immersive experiences using desktop and virtual reality (VR) platforms to strengthen human skills, also called employability or “soft” skills, such as effective communication and leadership capabilities. The four-to-six-week courses feature curriculum from Talespin, a developer of a VR platform that learners can use to take part in interactive role-playing exercises, allowing them to practice interpersonal skills in virtual settings.</p>
  <p>Research has shown that immersive technology is a powerful educational tool. According to <a href="https://www.pwc.com/us/en/services/consulting/technology/emerging-technology/vr-study-2020.html#:~:text=In%20our%20study%2C%20VR%2Dtrained,training%20and%20have%20better%20outcomes.">PwC</a>, people who are taught using virtual reality tech are 3.75 times more emotionally connected to the content, four times more focused than their e-learning peers, and 275% more confident about applying the skills they learn after training. It’s also possible to train people more quickly and cost-effectively using VR.</p>
  <p>Educators at the Skill Immersion Lab sites, who have been working with learners in their communities for years, say they welcome the opportunity to offer immersive learning experiences with students.</p>
  <p>“A gap that we notice as mentors is the need for students to apply the skills they learn from seminar sessions into a real-world setting,” said a career readiness advisor at the Queens site. “Students learn a lot about the ‘what’ to communicate in a professional environment, but getting students to learn the ‘how’ and ‘why’ as they maneuver through multilevel relationships in the workplace is crucial to ensuring that they are prepared for the many types of communication scenarios they would experience in the workforce. Allowing students to engage in virtual reality experiences early on gives them a head start into building awareness through verbal and non-verbal communication, not only for themselves but also for others.”</p>
  <p>The Skill Immersion Lab is also a critical opportunity to listen to learners who bring important lessons and skills from past experiences. Their feedback and engagement will push the program to be more relevant and effective for their own education and career goals.</p>
  <h2 id="an-effective-tool-for-tough-topics">An Effective Tool for Tough Topics</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-student-and-graduate-programs-at-sap">Learn more about student and graduate programs at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/students-graduates.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“It’s all about giving learners access to technology that is proven to be an effective teaching tool for tough topics,” says Katie Booth, who leads the SAP Corporate Social Responsibility team in North America. “We want to give them the language to think about things differently — and understand that they have a place within any environment, whether it’s a corporate setting or a community one. These deep communication skills will help them succeed.”</p>
  <p>The Skill Immersion Lab holds significant promise, particularly with young learners located outside of wealthy, suburban, or urban areas. Young people are receiving early access to some of the most innovative and effective immersive learning tools on the market, and they’re using those tools to advance their communication skills and further the pursuit of their education and career goals.</p>
  <p>As chief customer innovation officer for SAP North America, I’ve seen firsthand how innovative technology can help transform our customers’ businesses. The potential impact of this initiative is tremendous. Not only can it help educators build a deeper understanding of how new technology can empower young people, it can teach young learners some of the most important skills they need to succeed in life — and not just young learners in well-to-do communities, but any student, anywhere in the country.</p>
  <p>It’s possible. As one of the nation’s first programs focused squarely on immersive learning experiences for this age group, the Skill Immersion Lab is paving the way.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Stephanie Nashawaty is chief customer innovation officer at SAP North America.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/05/25/empowering-equity-in-education-with-virtual-reality-and-immersive-learning/">This article originally appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In a Post-Pandemic World, Youth Take Center Stage and Lead]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/possibilists-study-youth-lead-post-pandemic-world</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/possibilists-study-youth-lead-post-pandemic-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is proud to support the Possibilists, youth working to solve the issues of the world and striving to maximize their agency and potential.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enabling an Innovative, Agile Culture with SAP Innovate to Win]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/sap-innovate-to-win-agile-culture</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/sap-innovate-to-win-agile-culture</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Newly expanded, the SAP Innovate to Win program helps customers build an internal culture around innovative and agility. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_185769a8bf884145887bfdb3c5602151d7f6c78db.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_185769a8bf884145887bfdb3c5602151d7f6c78db.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_185769a8bf884145887bfdb3c5602151d7f6c78db.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Enabling an Innovative, Agile Culture with SAP Innovate to Win" src="./media_185769a8bf884145887bfdb3c5602151d7f6c78db.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="enabling-an-innovative-agile-culture-with-sap-innovate-to-win">Enabling an Innovative, Agile Culture with SAP Innovate to Win</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>To become an intelligent enterprise in our increasingly digitized and rapidly evolving world, it is crucial to foster an engaged workforce that prioritizes innovation and agility. Employers foresee skills such as problem-solving, critical thinking, creativity, flexibility, and active learning increasing in demand moving forward, according to the World Economic Forum’s recent <a href="https://www.weforum.org/reports/the-future-of-jobs-report-2020">Future of Jobs Report</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP is committed to setting individuals and teams up for success by creating opportunities to develop and hone new capabilities and ways of thinking. As part of this mission, we’ve expanded <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/05/4a102369-e17d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?source=social-Global-SAPEDU-TWITTER-MarketingCampaign-Training_Enablement-unspecified-spr-4846849072&#x26;campaigncode=CRM-WX20-EDU-SOC">SAP Innovate to Win</a>, a service designed to help customers get enabled on innovation frameworks and mindsets and apply these to build an internal culture around innovative and agility.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="turn-learning-into-achieving-with-sap-training-and-adoption">Turn learning into achieving with SAP Training and Adoption</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/training-certification.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="empowering-new-ways-of-thinking">Empowering New Ways of Thinking</h2>
  <p>Available for companies of all sizes and from all industries, SAP Innovate to Win is an innovation enablement and coaching service that helps companies to tackle their individual business challenges. We piloted the program in the Middle East and North Africa region, and have now expanded to support enterprises around the globe with virtual, in-person, and hybrid format options.</p>
  <p>The customized service enables teams within organizations to adopt Design Thinking — defined by <a href="https://hpi.de/en/school-of-design-thinking/design-thinking/what-is-design-thinking.html">The HPI School of Design Thinking (HPI D-School)</a> as a human-centered, iterative, team-based mindset that leads to breakthrough innovations — and to build digital prototypes using SAP technologies. It also uniquely includes Business Model Innovation, Blue Ocean strategy, positive psychology, and creative coaching.</p>
  <p>The standard program is delivered in seven different modules over the course of six weeks. With an emphasis on learning by doing, users complete field work in between each module to apply their learnings. This culminates in the final module when they then pitch the concepts they’ve developed to be utilized in real-world situations. SAP also creates a “maturity assessment,” or checklist, to help teams stay on track to achieve their objectives.</p>
  <h2 id="supporting-it-and-business-professionals">Supporting IT and Business Professionals</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-more-detail-on-the-innovation-enablement-and-coaching-service-with-sap-innovate-to-win">Get more detail on the innovation enablement and coaching service with SAP Innovate to Win</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/05/4a102369-e17d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?source=social-Global-SAPEDU-TWITTER-MarketingCampaign-Training_Enablement-unspecified-spr-4846849072&#x26;campaigncode=CRM-WX20-EDU-SOC">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP Innovate to Win is also designed for different types of professionals. First, the programming can be geared to people specializing in IT who want to collaborate more efficiently with the business side of an organization. With SAP Innovate to Win, IT professionals are better equipped to communicate with different kinds of teams and move from conversations centered on tech requirements to those focused on outcomes.</p>
  <p>On the other hand, business professionals can leverage SAP Innovate to Win to build digital skills and IT-inspired mindsets. In doing so, both business and IT teams can speak the same language to foster an innovation culture across the broader company.</p>
  <h2 id="propelling-future-success">Propelling Future Success</h2>
  <p>As the <a href="https://hbr.org/2020/01/the-transformer-clo">Harvard Business Review</a> described, to achieve learning goals, there is now a greater focus on developing growth mindsets and capabilities, rather than role-specific training. With the coaching from SAP Innovate to Win, teams are prepared — and empowered — to creatively explore solutions to unique business challenges that arise down the line.</p>
  <p>We continue to see customers benefit from a personalized SAP Innovate to Win curriculum. Vicky Hasioti, SAP Innovate to Win program director, noted: “Through SAP Innovate to Win, we have already supported our customers to create more than 250 low-fidelity prototypes for new solutions and road maps in an effort to solve business challenges and improve their companies’ business models.”</p>
  <p>In one example, in the United Arab Emirates, Dubai Future Foundation utilized SAP Innovate to Win in a series of workshops. Yaqoob Al-Zaabi from the Strategy Department at Dubai Future Foundation said, “It’s been a surprisingly great experience! It really helped me think in ways that I have never thought before. It also gave me a sense of self-confidence to express myself and give feedback. The content was very clear and everything had a practical aspect and purpose which gave me actionable skills that I can take with me into my job.”</p>
  <p>With the expansion of SAP Innovate to Win, SAP will support more customers around the world in their journeys to cultivate thriving innovation cultures that ultimately generate greater value for stakeholders in the future.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Getting Ahead of the Skills Curve]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/getting-ahead-skills-curve</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/getting-ahead-skills-curve</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Businesses can get ahead of the skills curve by aligning strategic workforce planning and business strategy. Read to learn more!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be3fe31204da0bc2c881ee5a27f5a8d1f0bd6231.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be3fe31204da0bc2c881ee5a27f5a8d1f0bd6231.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1be3fe31204da0bc2c881ee5a27f5a8d1f0bd6231.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Getting Ahead of the Skills Curve" src="./media_1be3fe31204da0bc2c881ee5a27f5a8d1f0bd6231.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="getting-ahead-of-the-skills-curve">Getting Ahead of the Skills Curve</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>What’s the uber skill? The ability to constantly learn, evolve, update, or even un-learn relevant skills. Today, training workforces to acquire that mindset of continuous learning is everything. We spoke with Stefan Haenisch, senior vice president of SAP Learning Strategic Initiatives at SAP, to dive deeper into his perspective, especially as he comes out of the World Economic Forum’s summer event, <a href="https://www.weforum.org/events/the-jobs-reset-summit-2021">The Jobs Reset Summit</a>, and recently published an <a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2021/05/back-to-school-4-lessons-in-workforce-skilling/">article</a> for WEF about the critical lessons in workforce skilling and lifelong learning.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-the-skills-you-need-anytime-anywhere-with-sap-learning-hub">Learn the skills you need anytime, anywhere with SAP Learning Hub</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://learninghub.sap.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="q-in-your-article-for-the-world-economic-forum-you-discuss-the-importance-of-connecting-business-strategy-to-workforce-skills-can-you-share-what-this-looks-like-and-why-its-so-essential">Q: In your article for the World Economic Forum, you discuss the importance of connecting business strategy to workforce skills. Can you share what this looks like and why it’s so essential?</h3>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> Every company plots out its business strategy. But how often does it think about how this relates and aligns with its people strategy and strategic workforce planning and skill building?</p>
  <p>For example, if our strategy is to use <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-artificial-intelligence/">artificial intelligence (AI)</a> to make our products smarter, we must simultaneously be asking ourselves how we can <a href="https://insights.sap.com/importance-upskilling/">upskill the workforce</a> on the required skills to drive this vision.</p>
  <p>Skill training shouldn’t be an afterthought. Instead, by connecting skills and strategy from the very beginning, companies can proactively adapt and more effectively position themselves for long-term success.</p>
  <h3 id="how-does-an-organization-develop-skills-for-the-future-when-things-are-changing-so-frequently-and-we-cant-possibly-know-what-the-world-will-look-like-in-the-next-couple-of-years">How does an organization develop skills for the future when things are changing so frequently and we can’t possibly know what the world will look like in the next couple of years?</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="how-to-upskill-staff-from-strategy-to-practical-steps">How to Upskill Staff: From Strategy to Practical Steps</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://insights.sap.com/how-to-upskill-guide/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As we saw with <a href="http://news.sap.com/covid-19">the global pandemic</a>, things may go differently than predicted. Companies must embrace ambiguity and disruption when it comes to skills for the future. A recent article in the <a href="https://hbr.org/2020/01/the-transformer-clo">Harvard Business Review</a> noted, “If you focus on building individual micro skills, you may be missing the bigger picture.” Indeed, there are ‘expiration dates’ on technical skills as innovation emerges, so companies must establish a culture that encourages agility and experimentation in the workforce – and, not least, motivates continuous learning – in order to yield sustainable success. Soft skills like dealing with uncertainty, staying curious, as well as embracing and tolerating ambiguity are the foundation of employees being ready for the future. They can then quickly and continuously keep up the relevant hard skills.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/content/dam/Deloitte/global/Documents/HumanCapital/gx-the-future-of-work-post-covid-19-poc.pdf">A recent report from Deloitte</a> asserts that the <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-future-of-work/">future of work</a> in our technology-driven world is about “creating an environment where organizations can optimize human potential” and “empowering workers with agency and choice over what they do, unleashing their interests and passions.” What this means is that the ultimate skill is being able to continuously learn in a constantly changing business environment. Fostering agile, innovative mindsets and curiosity throughout the workforce – promoting not only the <em>need</em> to learn, but the <em>want</em> to learn – helps companies to think big and earn a competitive edge.</p>
  <h3 id="how-do-offerings-at-sap-help-support-strategic-workforce-planning-and-continuous-learning">How do offerings at SAP help support strategic workforce planning and continuous learning?</h3>
  <p>At SAP, we value ongoing learning as part of the foundation for success. In the fast-moving tech sector where skill demand changes faster than in other industries, we’re constantly evolving our learning offerings to support the hard and soft skills needed to help people stay competitive.</p>
  <p>Inside SAP, for example, we look at a long and successful track record in deploying skills management to effective resource management in our consulting business and are now evolving this to support dynamic and forward-looking workforce planning and development.</p>
  <p>Our customers can benefit from our experience as we are incorporating the best practices we learned in people and skills management into our SAP SuccessFactors solutions. When it comes to helping our customers and partners build and sustain SAP product skills, our digital learning offerings, <a href="https://open.sap.com/">openSAP</a> and <a href="https://learninghub.sap.com/">SAP Learning Hub</a>, work to provide easy-to-use, engaging content for learners to explore, build, and maintain relevant skills. Additionally, we help support career planning around the skills that learners are honing, working to provide the right learning journey targeted to each learner’s goals.</p>
  <p>Our mission is to create learning and development opportunity for all across the SAP ecosystem. We aim to empower everyone to successfully build SAP software skills using future-oriented content delivered in different formats to fit individual ways of learning. By better aligning strategic workforce planning and business strategy at the onset, as well as becoming laser-focused on a workplace culture that values agility and curiosity, businesses can get ahead of the skills curve.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Learning With SAP: What's New and What's to Come]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/learning-with-sap-new-to-come</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/learning-with-sap-new-to-come</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[What's new and next for learning with SAP? Chief Learning Officer Max Wessel discusses SAP's work to accelerate digital skills of the future.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Challenge for Leaders: Embracing Educational Diversity]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/embracing-educational-diversity</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/embracing-educational-diversity</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[People learn through different ways and experiences. Embracing educational diversity could mean finding your next top performer.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1db0ab4e5c57b8b4968862a58fe2bd6ba46346c13.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1db0ab4e5c57b8b4968862a58fe2bd6ba46346c13.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1db0ab4e5c57b8b4968862a58fe2bd6ba46346c13.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="A Challenge for Leaders: Embracing Educational Diversity" src="./media_1db0ab4e5c57b8b4968862a58fe2bd6ba46346c13.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="a-challenge-for-leaders-embracing-educational-diversity">A Challenge for Leaders: Embracing Educational Diversity</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learning-for-life-get-the-right-skills-to-thrive-with-meaningful-work-in-a-digital-world">Learning for Life: Get the right skills to thrive with meaningful work in a digital world</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability/education.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>I thought about how I’d write this article for a very long time, but I recently realized that it was time to stop over-analyzing and share my story, in the hopes that it would inspire others. The feedback I got when I shared my non-traditional educational background on LinkedIn was incredible. The support has motivated me to continue the dialogue and challenge my fellow leaders to reconsider how they view candidates with unique backgrounds.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>I don’t have a college degree.</strong> There, I said it. And you know what? That statement does not define me or limit me. It’s a fact, a part of my background, and is likely one of the reasons I’ve had the career I’ve had.</p>
  <p>Do I regret not finishing my degree? I do wish I had the life experience of college, the knowledge I would have gained, and the relationships I would have built. But I also know without a doubt that I would not be who I am today if I had gone down the path of a traditional education. Who knows, I may have accomplished “more.” But I have a husband and three daughters that I love, I have a job that I find tremendously fulfilling, and I’ve had the fortune to meet amazing people and travel to fantastic places.</p>
  <p>My career provided me the opportunity to stay home for seven years when my children were small. I now have the honor to lead and mentor others, and I hope to inspire and challenge them to achieve their own success. For me, that exceeds every expectation I had for my future when I entered — and re-entered — the workforce.</p>
  <p>The reality is, I’m in good company — many successful people did not finish college — but I’ve also been incredibly fortunate. Fortunate to have had people who took the time to look past my lack of a formal education, to get to know me and understand the skills, passion, and drive I bring to what I do. Those early leaders, mentors, and sponsors took a chance on me and supported my career growth. They saw my potential and opened doors that lead to a journey I would never have imagined. I’m beyond thankful for each of them and I am incredibly passionate about supporting and leading others as they grow and develop along their unique career paths.</p>
  <p>People learn through different ways and experiences. College is one way, but life and career experiences are tremendously valuable as well. For me, the lack of a formal education has made me more driven, more determined to create my own success, and very intentional when it comes to my personal development. In today’s world of rapid innovation and a tremendously competitive talent market, we all need to be lifelong learners, regardless of our educational background.</p>
  <p>If <a href="/covid-19">2020 taught us anything</a>, it’s that we need to be prepared to pivot, learn new skills, and adapt to ever changing circumstances. These and many other critical job skills, such as grit, empathy, and emotional intelligence, are not easily taught in a classroom, they are innate skills that are further developed through experience. These skills aren’t measured by a piece of paper or apparent on a resume or job application; they are evaluated through human-to-human interaction.</p>
  <p>Diversity comes in many forms, and educational diversity is one of those, one that isn’t often talked about or considered.</p>
  <p>With that, I challenge my fellow leaders to invest their time with someone from a non-traditional background. Get to know the person behind that resume or LinkedIn profile. You may find that they are a perfect for your team, you may not. Regardless, give them the gift of your time by providing feedback and, if appropriate, through mentorship. Help them network or find a role that is right for them. Take a chance, because you may find your next top performer hiding in places you never would have considered.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/katiemevis/">Katie Mevis</a> is head of North America High Growth at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-beyond-bias</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/leadership</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Expands People to Work Program by SAP to Equip More Job Seekers with Skills and Certification]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/people-to-work-program-expands-equip-job-seekers-skills-certification</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/people-to-work-program-expands-equip-job-seekers-skills-certification</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP will expand job skills-building program People to Work by SAP, which has already helped 400,000+ job seekers and professionals.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1683f83d4cdc4d21986f8c0907a389f2ba13be4cf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1683f83d4cdc4d21986f8c0907a389f2ba13be4cf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1683f83d4cdc4d21986f8c0907a389f2ba13be4cf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Expands People to Work Program by SAP to Equip More Job Seekers with Skills and Certification" src="./media_1683f83d4cdc4d21986f8c0907a389f2ba13be4cf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-expands-people-to-work-program-by-sap-to-equip-more-job-seekers-with-skills-and-certification">SAP Expands People to Work Program by SAP to Equip More Job Seekers with Skills and Certification</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-people-to-work-program">Learn more about the People to Work program</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/dmc/exp/2020-06-69309/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today said it would globally expand its job skills-building program, <a href="http://www.sap.com/people-to-work">People to Work by SAP</a>, which has helped more than 400,000 job seekers and professionals reskill or add skills.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Over 80% of those awarded SAP Global Certification digital badges as a result of participating in the program gained employment.</p>
  <p>The People to Work program by SAP brings together various country-specific training programs for job seekers, workers who need to reskill due to changing job requirements, people threatened by unemployment and the underemployed. Upon successful completion of the program and exam, SAP awards learners with SAP Global Certification digital badges to verify their competence, thereby facilitating their reentry into the job market.</p>
  <p>First established in Germany, the publicly funded program has already branched out into countries such as Denmark and South Korea. It uses high-quality learning content provided by SAP, social competence topics and soft skills to equip unemployed and those wanting to further their qualifications with the skills needed to solve the digital challenges of the future. Delivered by an extensive partner network, the program offers a wide range of training options that are hosted in traditional classroom and virtual learning environments.</p>
  <p>“While digital transformation has brought about a tremendous amount of progress and innovation, it has also changed jobs as we know them today and has put many people at risk of unemployment,” said Maxwell Wessel, Chief Learning Officer, SAP SE. “To help counteract the rising unemployment at an early stage, the People to Work program by SAP focuses on helping people who are looking to get back into employment, while enabling them to develop the digital skills that are necessary to thrive in the future workforce.”</p>
  <p>The rapid pace of the digital transformation has accelerated over the last year fueled by the global pandemic. According to the World Economic Forum, 42% of the core skills required for jobs will change by 2022.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_164011f4699f4fb691787ad2823f9959539fc10ca.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_164011f4699f4fb691787ad2823f9959539fc10ca.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_164011f4699f4fb691787ad2823f9959539fc10ca.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="BBC video coverage of People to Work program" src="./media_164011f4699f4fb691787ad2823f9959539fc10ca.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="500" height="350">
    </picture><br><a href="http://www.bbc.com/storyworks/digitally-enlightened/sap">http://www.bbc.com/storyworks/digitally-enlightened/sap</a>
  </p>
  <p><em>Click to watch a BBC video</em></p>
  <p>“My thirst for knowledge has been quenched and stimulated at the same time,” said Bettina Maas, a former program participant. Today she is a successful SAP software trainer and leader.</p>
  <p>To learn more about how the People to Work program has impacted the lives of many across Europe, watch this <a href="http://www.bbc.com/storyworks/digitally-enlightened/sap">video</a>. Learn more about the <a href="http://sap.com/people-to-work">program</a> in your country.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Martin Gwisdalla, +49 (6227) 7-67275, <a href="mailto:martin.gwisdalla@sap.com">martin.gwisdalla@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transforming Learning for a Digitally Native Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/digitally-native-future-transform-learning</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/digitally-native-future-transform-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To support readiness for a digitally native future, SAP is simplifying access to learning for all. Learn how the company is staying dynamic.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/moocs</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>