<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/intelligent-enterprise/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Grow with the Latest SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition 2402 Update]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-s4hana-cloud-public-edition-2402-update</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-s4hana-cloud-public-edition-2402-update</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition 2402 update, we are bringing a new round of exciting innovations. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-resource-planning</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-intelligent-rpa</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accelerate Innovation with a Clean Core Strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/accelerate-innovation-with-clean-core-strategy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/accelerate-innovation-with-clean-core-strategy</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With a clean core strategy for business tech, you can stay focused on what matters most to your business. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Technology Helps Sales Teams Win]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/technology-helps-sales-teams-win</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/technology-helps-sales-teams-win</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP IT applies tech-driven business transformation processes to improve business functions, like sales teams, throughout the company.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/machine-learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Unlocks Global Innovation Velocity with Next-Generation Cloud Delivery]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-successfactors-next-generation-cloud-delivery</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-successfactors-next-generation-cloud-delivery</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Next-Generation Cloud Delivery creates the foundation for our SAP SuccessFactors innovation road map. Read to learn more about the campaign.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/dynamic-teams</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Enable Now: The Digital Adoption Platform Powering Intelligent Enterprises]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-enable-now-digital-adoption-platform-powering-intelligent-enterprises</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-enable-now-digital-adoption-platform-powering-intelligent-enterprises</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[End users must be prepared for digital adoption, which is where a digital adoption platform like SAP Enable Now comes into play.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>product/sap-enable-now</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Set the Course of Business Innovation with Intelligent ERP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/set-course-of-business-innovation-with-intelligent-erp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/set-course-of-business-innovation-with-intelligent-erp</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A cloud-based ERP helps organizations prioritize business innovation to keep up with market dynamics and workplace and customer expectations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/premium-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In a Fragmented World, Technology Brings Us Together]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2023/01/fragmented-world-technology-unites</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2023/01/fragmented-world-technology-unites</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Technology is key to uniting a fragmented world; business, government, and society can tackle the challenges. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/wef-davos</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Increase Productivity with the Latest Innovations in SAP S/4HANA Cloud, Public Edition]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/sap-s4hana-cloud-2302-innovations-increase-productivity</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/sap-s4hana-cloud-2302-innovations-increase-productivity</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP S/4HANA Cloud 2302, users can improve organizational and employee productivity. Learn more about the latest release.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>product/sap-intelligent-rpa</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Solutions Come to Life at SAP Experience Center 2.0]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/sap-solutions-come-to-life-sap-experience-center-walldorf</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/sap-solutions-come-to-life-sap-experience-center-walldorf</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The updated SAP Experience Center Walldorf was designed to enable a personalized and up-close journey into the added value of SAP software.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-experience-center</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Upward Momentum Builds with Digitalization in the Chemicals Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/upward-momentum-digitalization-chemicals-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/upward-momentum-digitalization-chemicals-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the right approach to digitalization and the help of SAP Advisory Services, the chemicals industry can innovate across the value chain.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Upward Momentum Builds with Digitalization in the Chemicals Industry" src="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="upward-momentum-builds-with-digitalization-in-the-chemicals-industry">Upward Momentum Builds with Digitalization in the Chemicals Industry</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Chemical companies are on a nonstop roller coaster of market shocks and digital transformation. Sandwiched between feedstock and energy companies and downstream processing industries, they’re predestined to play a vital role in fulfilling business-to-business (B2B) and consumer expectations for sustainable, reliable, innovative, and trusted products and services.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But rising to the challenge of today’s marketplace – especially increasing raw material and energy prices, margin pressure, supply chain complexity, and regulatory requirements – requires much more than Industry 4.0 initiatives focused on efficiency and price reduction. From operational performance to customer experience, companies must integrate data from across the enterprise into a single source to form sound decisions that make sustainability profitable and profitability sustainable.</p>
  <p>Such a transformation is undoubtedly technology intensive, but the key enablers are also unassailably human. Understanding this reality, many chemical companies rely on the <a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/business-transformation.html">SAP Advisory Services</a> portfolio, provided by the Business Transformation Services group at SAP, to help transform their operations and gain a competitive edge amid fast global changes.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="transform-your-business-and-unlock-digital-innovation-with-help-from-sap-advisory-services">Transform your business and unlock digital innovation with help from SAP Advisory Services</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/business-transformation.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="turning-challenges-into-great-opportunities">Turning Challenges into Great Opportunities</h2>
  <p>Competitively addressing turbulence depends on the ability to view transformation through the lens of six fundamental challenges:</p>
  <p><strong>R&#x26;D Pressure across the Product Portfolio</strong> The imperative to resist margin shrinkage, mitigate risks, increase ROI, and boost growth calls for innovative products and services that offer business value and foster close partnerships with customers. By pushing forward the adoption of advanced technologies to drive global R&#x26;D, supplier, and customer collaborations and joint ventures, businesses can prevent commoditization.</p>
  <p><strong>The Need for Vertical Integration</strong> Evolving production facilities with a balance of high efficiency, global scale, flexibility, and intelligent responsiveness allows supply chains to weigh the synergistic benefits of integrated manufacturing plants or industrial parks against the flexibility of smaller plants. As a result, businesses can leverage new opportunities with disruptive business models, such as making raw materials instead of buying them and producing semi-finished or even finished goods.</p>
  <p><strong>Global Supply Chain Complexity</strong> Global supply chains must be secure enough to mitigate volatile market conditions, such as global health emergencies, rising prices for raw materials and energy, and other factors that impact economic conditions. Companies can gain this advantage by establishing commercial and logistical transparency to support optimization and global planning of demand, sales, and operations.</p>
  <p><strong>Hidden Advantages of Business Networks</strong> Business cannot stay competitive in a complex ecosystem alone. They must also scale and optimize their supply chain globally with business networks, such as the <a href="/2021/03/catena-x-automotive-alliance-picks-up-speed">Catena-X Automotive Network</a>. Doing so empowers suppliers, contract and toll manufacturers, joint ventures, and customers to collaborate openly and create new prospects for co-innovating better products and services, improving value chain efficiency, and fueling long-term growth.</p>
  <p><strong>Compliance and Sustainability Urgency</strong> A primary objective for any chemical business is ensuring compliance with industry regulations. Yet, B2B customers also favor suppliers that help meet their own environmental, social, and governance (ESG) mandates. Sustainable businesses and innovations provide balance between these two expectations, creating a highly sought-after competitive edge by gearing products and services towards a circular economy.</p>
  <p><strong>Business Agility</strong> The industry’s dynamic and fast-changing environment of mergers, acquisitions, and divestitures is creating tremendous complexity and pressure for permanent change and adaptation. Chemical companies need to balance industry-wide globalization and centralization while increasing business agility.</p>
  <p>Chemical companies with a digital strategy encompassing all these topics can address industry challenges and seize on market trends in a disruptive manner. Through <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2016/03/d2238cd0-627c-0010-82c7-eda71af511fa.html">digital innovation</a>, businesses can gain new opportunities and capabilities never previously considered possible – including increased speed and efficiency, process automation, and data transparency.</p>
  <h2 id="seizing-the-moment-with-advisory-expertise">Seizing the Moment with Advisory Expertise</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="at-sap-your-success-is-our-goal">At SAP, your success is our goal</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/support.html#services-support-offerings">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>From the perspective of SAP Advisory Services, digitalization is not just another IT term but also a critical business priority. The more intelligent and sustainable a company becomes, the more agile, flexible, and integrated its value chain becomes.</p>
  <p>Advisory experts from SAP can enable chemical companies to turn their fundamental challenges into opportunities with a well-structured, business-driven design. This approach elaborates on the steps of the digital transformation journey – leading to a road map for future architecture design. Each phase of the road map follows an ideal sequence of digital innovation, technology adoption, and industry best practices and leverages the highest value for the company in the short term.</p>
  <p>SAP Advisory Services help organizations evaluate and act on the sentiments of their customers, partners, and employees and improve their environmental impact. Chemical companies can then be well positioned to keep their workforce engaged, increase organizational agility, and deliver the products and services customers need and trust. Furthermore, they can control their varied sources and categories of spending with outstanding finance and operational efficiency and real-time enterprise insight.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13184d5b5d29ebbc4d371c407a9c86acc71402ad2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13184d5b5d29ebbc4d371c407a9c86acc71402ad2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_13184d5b5d29ebbc4d371c407a9c86acc71402ad2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_13184d5b5d29ebbc4d371c407a9c86acc71402ad2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="300" height="283">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Intelligent enterprise framework</em></p>
  <p>Essentially, chemical companies that work with SAP advisory experts can realize their potential as <a href="https://www.sap.com/intelligent-enterprise.html">intelligent enterprises</a>. They can make confident decisions and drive continuous innovation to adapt, innovate, and overcome challenges while making responsible choices that help reduce waste and emissions and drive long-term growth.</p>
  <p>This business model is accomplished with intelligent technologies, including business networks, a business technology platform, cloud-based infrastructures, and solutions for business process management, experience management, industry cloud, and sustainability management. Additionally, artificial intelligence (AI), blockchain, data platforms, the Internet of Things (IoT), machine learning, predictive analytics, and virtual as well as augmented realities (VR/AR) are embedded in the intelligent technologies to drive end-to-end business processes and decision-making across enterprise domains.</p>
  <h2 id="bringing-to-life-an-intelligent-and-sustainable-network">Bringing to Life an Intelligent and Sustainable Network</h2>
  <p>The pressures on the chemicals industry may be relentless, with shocks coming in from all directions. However, this doesn’t mean businesses cannot find great opportunities in this volatile environment. With the right approach to digitalization, they can transform, innovate, and collaborate across the value chain to build upward momentum and better serve customers as an intelligent and sustainable network.</p>
  <p>Learn more about the <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2022/09/29/business-and-digital-trends-in-the-chemical-industry/">market trends and business priorities shaping various lines of businesses in the chemical industry</a> and how SAP can help guide the innovation needed to overcome them. Read the series <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/tag/business-digital-trends-in-the-chemical-industry/">“Business and Digital Trends in the Chemical Industry</a>” on SAP Community.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Ornulf Rexin is chief business consultant of Chemicals and Life Sciences for Business Transformation Services at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advisory-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why Is CX Critical for Future-Proofing B2B Sales?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/future-proof-b2b-sales-cx-critical</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/future-proof-b2b-sales-cx-critical</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To future-proof your B2B sales, SAP Sales Cloud can connects experiences to outcomes that matter for your customer. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Disrupted ERP Systems Rise to Reckoning in the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/composable-business-for-disrupted-erp-systems</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/composable-business-for-disrupted-erp-systems</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Composable business is the future for cloud ERP software, promising faster innovation for stronger resilience against market disruptions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/new-ventures-and-technologies</category>
            <category>product/sap-erp</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Is Your Factory Intelligent Enough to Withstand the Next Business Crisis?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/is-your-factory-intelligent-enough-to-withstand-the-next-business-crisis</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/is-your-factory-intelligent-enough-to-withstand-the-next-business-crisis</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Manufacturers are embracing Industry 4.0 and intelligent factories to anticipate and respond faster to market demands. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-4-0</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/machine-learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Digital Strategy Behind Moen’s Customer Experience Magic]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/moen-customer-experience-digital-strategy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/moen-customer-experience-digital-strategy</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Moen, North America's leading faucet maker, is digitalizing on a cloud-based platform to get closer to customers and innovate business models.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-service-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Smart Meters Expand Sustainable Horizon of Smart Cities]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/american-water-smart-meters-sustainable-horizon</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/american-water-smart-meters-sustainable-horizon</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Utilities like American Water crunch intelligent data to meet sustainability objectives and build trusted relationships with customers.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Continuous Intelligence: Definition, Benefits, and Examples]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/continuous-intelligence-definition-benefits-examples</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/continuous-intelligence-definition-benefits-examples</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Continuous Intelligence, or continuously monitoring business data for anomalies, can help brands make smart, real-time business decisions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-innovation-center-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Signavio and LeanIX Bring Process Excellence and Enterprise Architecture Closer Together]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/sap-signavio-leanix-process-excellence-enterprise-architecture</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/sap-signavio-leanix-process-excellence-enterprise-architecture</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Signavio and LeanIX bring together process excellence and enterprise architecture management, connecting IT and business leaders.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-endorsed-apps</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Graham Construction Builds Intelligent Enterprise with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/graham-construction-builds-intelligent-enterprise-with-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/graham-construction-builds-intelligent-enterprise-with-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Graham Construction is applying ETM.next, an industry cloud solution from SAP and BearingPoint, to centralize equipment inventory management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[When Exceptions Become the Norm, Resilience Becomes the Objective]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2022/05/exceptions-norm-business-resilience-objective</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2022/05/exceptions-norm-business-resilience-objective</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In times of crisis, business resilience is critical. To support its customers, SAP is investing in five priorities for its engineering teams.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Closing the Gaps with SAP Enable Now]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/closing-the-gaps-with-sap-enable-now</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/closing-the-gaps-with-sap-enable-now</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's Kristina Kunad explains how SAP Enable Now helps drive adoption and upskill your workforce. Read the interview to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>product/sap-enable-now</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Signavio Leverages Experience Data to Expand the Value of Business Process Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/sap-signavio-experience-data-business-process-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/sap-signavio-experience-data-business-process-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Signavio correlates experience data with underlying IT systems so businesses can optimize their end-to-end business processes.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accelerating Digital Transformation through RISE with SAP and Integrated Business Networks]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/digital-transformation-rise-with-sap-integrated-business-networks</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/digital-transformation-rise-with-sap-integrated-business-networks</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Integrated business networks, like SAP Business Network, work to ensure greater supply chain visibility and resiliency. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Enterprise Adoption: Localization Services Power Global Sustainable Business]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/localization-services-power-global-sustainable-business</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/localization-services-power-global-sustainable-business</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In this exclusive Q&A, SAP’s Eva Zauke talks about the powerful localization revolution happening behind every digital-first business.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>product/sap-billing-and-revenue-innovation-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-adoption</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enterprise Content Management: A Pivotal Step to End-to-End Digitalization]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/enterprise-content-management-ecm-digitalization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/enterprise-content-management-ecm-digitalization</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[According to an IDC whitepaper, SAP ECM solutions by OpenText can help businesses go paperless, resulting in greater efficiency. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_184c064ceef0464e02871782164bc5c9529c8989b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_184c064ceef0464e02871782164bc5c9529c8989b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_184c064ceef0464e02871782164bc5c9529c8989b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Enterprise Content Management: A Pivotal Step to End-to-End Digitalization" src="./media_184c064ceef0464e02871782164bc5c9529c8989b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="enterprise-content-management-a-pivotal-step-to-end-to-end-digitalization">Enterprise Content Management: A Pivotal Step to End-to-End Digitalization</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Work patterns may have changed over the years, but surprisingly most workplaces have yet to make any meaningful progress toward becoming paperless. Is this resistance to content digitalization and integration holding businesses back from becoming resilient and sustainable enough to stay competitive?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While the concept of the paperless workplace is nothing new, the opportunity to achieve this vision is quickly approaching as businesses advance their transformation strategies. Over the past year, companies have invested in software-as-a-service (SaaS) and cloud-enabled systems, new methodologies such as process automation, and network-wide collaboration to keep employees productive, update suppliers, and deliver on customer expectations.</p>
  <p>Now, some organizations are looking to go even further in their business transformation journey by digitalizing and integrating content with a comprehensive enterprise platform.</p>
  <p>According to an IDC whitepaper sponsored by SAP and OpenText, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2022/01/629d79f0-127e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">The Business Value of SAP Enterprise Content Management Solutions by OpenText in the Digital-First World</a>,” implementing solutions ‒ such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/enterprise-content-management.html">SAP enterprise content management (ECM) solutions by OpenText</a> ‒ can quickly yield a 288% three-year ROI. And at the center of this effective transformation is fast and efficient document migration, intake, processing, and auditing with fewer errors and higher productivity.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="discover-enterprise-content-management-solutions-to-help-your-business-become-an-intelligent-enterprise">Discover enterprise content management solutions to help your business become an intelligent enterprise</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/oth/enterprise-content-management/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="capturing-us7-million-in-revenue-growth">Capturing US$7 Million in Revenue Growth</h2>
  <p>The benefits of content digitalization, integration, and automation with <a href="/2020/05/study-ecm-and-mdg-solution-extensions-opentext-utopia">enterprise content management can be combined to increase revenue</a> by more than $7 million per year. By increasing efficiency, reducing errors, and accelerating processes, organizations surveyed by IDC reported an average gain of 4,794 productive hours each ‒ a 21% increase in gross user productivity.</p>
  <p>This improvement allowed respondents to avoid the hiring of 2.6 full-time employees to accomplish equivalent workloads, resulting in approximately $178,000 in enhanced user productivity value per organization. Additionally, enhanced interdepartmental document sharing and the automation of manual processes boosted profitability even further by driving $3.82 million in savings per one million documents.</p>
  <h2 id="migrating-documents-with-more-efficiency">Migrating Documents with More Efficiency</h2>
  <p>Migrating millions of documents that have been created, managed, and stored on paper to digital is a daunting task during any change initiative, especially when moving to a modern enterprise resource planning (ERP) system, such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a>. However, document-related migration is not just a one-time effort; it’s a project that can happen as regularly as organizations continue to evolve throughout their digital transformation.</p>
  <p>Interviewed organizations that use solutions for enterprise content management cited considerable migration efficiencies and cost reductions. For example, some respondents required 24% fewer full-time employees to complete migration projects, from 128.6 to 97.3 on average. The duration of the migration was also shortened from 12.2 months to only seven months, a 43% improvement. As a result of these efficiencies gain, the cost of document-related migration became 24% more affordable.</p>
  <p>As one manufacturing executive noted, “Doing data migration is easier if you minimize the number of applications. SAP ECM solutions by OpenText helped us put building blocks in place. Our knowledge has increased, and the learning curve is less steep. We know more about what is required country to country.”</p>
  <h2 id="decreasing-invoice-errors">Decreasing Invoice Errors</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-a-snapshot-of-the-idc-whitepaper">Get a snapshot of the IDC whitepaper</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/10/3ede3947-027e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>When the volume of paper invoices increases, manual processes become too time-consuming and risk-prone to maintain. For one of the survey participants, the lack of history tracking, trend analysis, and currency distinction led to €300,000 lost on paying invoices because the organization missed out on receiving discounts upwards of two percent. And in some cases, IDC reported that many respondents also paid interest and penalties on late payments that they could have avoided.</p>
  <p>After automating invoicing tasks with enterprise content management, organizations realized a 35% drop in delayed payments and paid 36% less on penalties and interest. The system immediately validates and approves incoming invoices, improving overall invoice performance and decreasing errors by 43% on average.</p>
  <p>A participating executive from an industrial chemicals company remarked on the tremendous value of digitalizing invoice management: “From the moment the organization moved toward less touching, it saw a 70% improvement over paper.”</p>
  <h2 id="boosting-organizational-efficiency">Boosting Organizational Efficiency</h2>
  <p>As digital transformation becomes synonymous with business growth, executives must consistently consider new capabilities and enhancements to improve their operations, employees’ lives, desired outcomes, and customer experiences. In fact, this mindset is bringing forth a new focus on business efficiency and resiliency.</p>
  <p>From invoice intake and processing, accounts payable, and auditing teams to areas outside of finance, solutions for enterprise content management can have an impressive impact on organizational efficiency, ranging from 24% to 41%. This outcome is largely due to allowing multiple users to obtain documents with greater ease. Organizations can work independently of an office location and still have secure access to content from a single centralized environment.</p>
  <p>In return, users who work from remote locations can work more effectively, which is a tremendous benefit for businesses with most of their workforce still working from home and in the field. Companies can support employees from more geographic regions and across all process streams and operational areas ‒ all without shuttling physical documents back and forth in e-mail.</p>
  <p>In addition, since their content is archived and stored in a centralized process and database, organizations can stay compliant with regulatory and business requirements with minimal or no effort. A surveyed healthcare executive noted this advantage’s value: “We can see content now, whereas the older way we had to search. We can now look at transactional records, so compliance is handled on the schedule.”</p>
  <h2 id="gaining-the-full-potential-of-content-management">Gaining the Full Potential of Content Management</h2>
  <p>The deeper companies transform into digital-first enterprises, the closer they get to operate at a level of efficiency, intelligence, and speed that rivals their competitors. And the first place to gain that edge is best found in digitalization through enterprise content management that removes the complexity of siloed information, spreadsheets, data extractions, and manipulations.</p>
  <p>Explore the calculated cost savings and business benefits of SAP enterprise content management solutions by OpenText, which support enterprise content management. Read the IDC whitepaper, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2022/01/629d79f0-127e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">The Business Value of SAP Enterprise Content Management Solutions by OpenText in the Digital-First World</a>,” commissioned by SAP and Open Text.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/opentext</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Six Drivers of Innovation: How to Make Magic Happen for Your Organization]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/six-drivers-of-innovation-make-magic-happen-for-your-organization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/six-drivers-of-innovation-make-magic-happen-for-your-organization</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[What is innovation? What does it take to become a more innovative organization? Read to find out and gain tips and inspiration.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_104760a58e3da0a65f2ea001648e61664b1853868.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_104760a58e3da0a65f2ea001648e61664b1853868.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_104760a58e3da0a65f2ea001648e61664b1853868.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Six Drivers of Innovation: How to Make Magic Happen for Your Organization" src="./media_104760a58e3da0a65f2ea001648e61664b1853868.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="six-drivers-of-innovation-how-to-make-magic-happen-for-your-organization">Six Drivers of Innovation: How to Make Magic Happen for Your Organization</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>What is innovation? We could turn to the Oxford English Dictionary definition – “the introduction of new things, ideas, or ways of doing something” – or even quote former president Barack Obama – “Innovation is the creation of something that improves the way we live our lives.”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But my personal favorite is, in fact, an equation, which I believe is credited to Edward Roberts and is taught by the Massachusetts Institute of Technology: <strong>Innovation = invention x commercialization</strong>.</p>
  <p>The premise is that if either invention or commercialization is missing, there is no value and, consequently, no genuine innovation. So, what does it take to drive innovation in your organization? Here are six core enablers.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="simplify-digital-transformation-with-sap-services-and-support">Simplify digital transformation with SAP Services and Support</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/support.html#services-support-offerings">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="build-a-culture-of-innovation">Build a Culture of Innovation</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div><em>“For good ideas and true innovation, you need human interaction, conflict, argument, debate.”</em><br>– Margaret Heffernan, CEO and author</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Innovation can only blossom in a culture where <a href="/2021/11/four-essential-leadership-qualities-for-modern-times">its leadership encourages ideas from everyone</a>, from junior workers to the director. Financial incentives and gamification can help, but great cultures run deeper. People need the freedom – and confidence – to suggest ideas no matter how bold.</p>
  <p>Think of those outlandish fashions on the catwalks of Paris, London, and Milan. The outfits that ultimately roll off the production lines and into stores are simpler versions of those concepts. So, be open to the art of the possible – in the beginning, no idea is a bad idea!</p>
  <p>Organizations that make time for their people to learn are simultaneously making time for their people to be creative. Learning leads to imagination and cross-pollination, resulting in action and, eventually, innovation.</p>
  <p>Flat management structures can help companies to be more innovative, blended with cross-functional collaboration. If a flat structure and <a href="https://taskworld.com/blog/what-is-open-communication-and-why-is-it-important/">open communication</a> are not in reach right now, consider recruiting a team of innovation champions. Their role is to solicit ideas company-wide and facilitate workshops for brainstorming and debate. When people come together in a safe and empowering space, ideas grow wings and innovation will fly.</p>
  <h2 id="foster-diverse-teams">Foster Diverse Teams</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div><em>“Diverse and inclusive teams are the engines of innovation.”</em><br><em>–</em> Great Place to Work</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Research by the <em>Wall Street Journal</em> found that <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesinsights/2020/01/15/diversity-confirmed-to-boost-innovation-and-financial-results/?sh=5796025cc4a6">socially diverse teams</a> are more innovative than homogeneous teams. Innovation is born from an innate knowledge of your target audience’s needs. As most customer bases are varied, it takes a multifaceted group to understand their pains and desires.</p>
  <p>If you want your organization to be more innovative, start with your hiring practices. And in the era of remote working, the talent pool open to you needn’t be limited to your doorstep.</p>
  <h2 id="never-forget-the-humans">Never Forget the Humans</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div><em>“For innovation to be successful, the perspective of every human directly and indirectly impacted by the innovation needs to be top of mind.”</em><br><em>–</em> Ben Gilchriest, global VP, SAP</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In his <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2019/11/11/human-centered-innovation-find-your-way-out-of-the-proof-of-concept-trap/?sh=450a99495927">Forbes article</a>, Gilchriest says that human-centered innovation is the way out of the proof-of-concept trap. Keeping people at the heart of new solutions is crucial. Gilchriest argues that four factors are fundamental to successful innovation:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Desirability</strong>: defining the value to the consumer</li>
    <li><strong>Feasibility</strong>: the idea’s technical and regulatory workability</li>
    <li><strong>Viability</strong>: the commercial case for the idea</li>
    <li><strong>Scalability</strong>: how the concept can be scaled from a business and technology perspective</li>
  </ul>
  <p>In too many instances, the innovation process focuses on only one or two of these factors. Taking a human-centered approach ensures that those the technology touches remain central.</p>
  <p>Understand those who will interact with or benefit from the innovation – from internal users to end customers – and continuously look for ways to delight them.</p>
  <h2 id="view-failure-through-the-lens-of-opportunity">View Failure Through the Lens of Opportunity</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-innovation-challenge-how-to-make-the-extraordinary-happen">The Innovation Challenge: How to Make the Extraordinary Happen</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/12/innovation-challenge-make-extraordinary-happen">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div><em>“Don’t throw the baby out with the bathwater.”</em><br><em>–</em> 16th-century German proverb meaning don’t discard something valuable along with something undesirable</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>American entrepreneur Jeff Bezos left a trail of failed ideas in his wake. These included an online auction site, which evolved into zShops. Amid these failures lay the kernels of brilliance that would set the foundation for the e-commerce behemoth Amazon.</p>
  <p>Not all concepts will work the first time. Learning from past mistakes and evolving ideas are vital for innovation.</p>
  <h2 id="learn-from-your-critics-and-detractors">Learn from Your Critics and Detractors</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div><em>“You have so much to learn from your enemies.”</em><br>– Eckhart Tolle</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Now, I’m not suggesting that you should regard your critics and detractors as enemies. I merely quote Tolle to point out that those who speak negatively of your company can be your best teachers. It’s about having the humility to put aside the (entirely human) tendency to be defensive and honestly answer, ‘Are they right?’</p>
  <p>Detach yourself from any emotive narrative and look for ways to prove – not disprove – your critics’ views. In doing so, you might well pull opportunities to innovate out from the shadows and into the light.</p>
  <p>Where do you begin? Social media listening is one way to learn what people are saying about your products or solutions. And finding ways to capture feedback – both structured and unstructured – should pay dividends. Make it as easy as possible for customers to tell you what they think. And give those in account management and customer service roles the means to share feedback and anecdotal evidence in the ordinary course of their day.</p>
  <h2 id="know-your-competition">Know Your Competition</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div><em>“Whether it’s Google or Apple or free software, we’ve got some fantastic competitors and it keeps us on our toes.”</em><br>— Bill Gates</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Thriving organizations and entrepreneurs do not function in a vacuum. They are acutely aware of the strengths and weaknesses of their competitors and closely monitor what they are doing.</p>
  <p>If your company is not in the top spot, understanding why could help you identify what innovations are necessary to get you there. I’m not suggesting copying something already in the marketplace and making it better – that isn’t innovation. Instead, be inspired by what the competition is doing brilliantly and look for gaps your company could fill.</p>
  <h2 id="spark-alchemy-in-your-organization">Spark Alchemy in Your Organization</h2>
  <p>I hope these enablers of innovation spark alchemy in your organization. But change – especially change that endures – requires persistence, perspective, empathy, and no small degree of energy!</p>
  <p>My advice is to begin by tackling the ‘low-hanging fruit.’ What small changes can you make today, tomorrow, and next week? An incremental approach is more manageable, and as people begin to see the positive impact, they will be more open to supporting your initiatives. Feel free to <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/guidoschlief/">connect with me</a> and share your thoughts.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Guido Schlief is senior vice president and head of Services for Middle &#x26; Eastern Europe at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Next WoW for Hybrid Teamwork and Collaboration]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/the-next-wow-for-hybrid-teamwork-and-collaboration</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/the-next-wow-for-hybrid-teamwork-and-collaboration</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP AppHaus continues to innovate with customers by adapting to hybrid setups while shaping the next "WoW," way of working. Read more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_189d86016ff8b2dc31e06804628fcd3b892dbf7a8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_189d86016ff8b2dc31e06804628fcd3b892dbf7a8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_189d86016ff8b2dc31e06804628fcd3b892dbf7a8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Next WoW for Hybrid Teamwork and Collaboration" src="./media_189d86016ff8b2dc31e06804628fcd3b892dbf7a8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-next-wow-for-hybrid-teamwork-and-collaboration">The Next WoW for Hybrid Teamwork and Collaboration</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Innovation takes a diverse team of people with different expertise and skill sets working together in proximity to generate the “aha moment.” With the restrictions caused by the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, the SAP AppHaus team developed a way to best maintain collaboration remotely, on-site, and in a mixed or hybrid working model.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This journey of ups and downs from adapting to optimizing the setup has been published in “<a href="https://apphaus.sap.com/resource/next-wow">The Next WoW (Way of Working)”, a free and accessible whitepaper</a>. It describes how continuous co-innovation and collaboration with customers has been possible in changing work environments and how other companies and innovators across the globe can learn and benefit from the experience.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-btp-the-platform-for-the-intelligent-enterprise">SAP BTP: The platform for the Intelligent Enterprise</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="the-next-wow-keeping-up-business-in-changing-environments">The Next WoW: Keeping Up Business in Changing Environments</h2>
  <p>When the pandemic disrupted the way we collaborated at the beginning of 2020, it wasn’t an option for the SAP AppHaus team to stop innovating with customers and partners. Instead, they took the opportunity to grow and learn from the situation. <a href="https://apphaus.sap.com/approach">SAP’s human-centered approach to innovation</a>, which combines design thinking and architecture thinking, underlines the importance of collaboration among different stakeholders and end users. To enable efficient virtual meetings, SAP AppHaus launched the <a href="https://apphaus.sap.com/resource/innovation-toolkit-for-virtual-collaboration-bundle">Innovation Culture Toolkit for virtual collaboration</a> last year. But this was just the beginning.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a5add4bf5973b728b564781241e535bc99244442.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a5add4bf5973b728b564781241e535bc99244442.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1a5add4bf5973b728b564781241e535bc99244442.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1a5add4bf5973b728b564781241e535bc99244442.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="371">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>The SAP AppHaus Network, with its 21 locations spread across the globe, stands for sustainable co-innovation with customers. With a user-centered approach and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> as the solid foundation for custom-tailored innovation in the Intelligent Enterprise, the network brings innovation to life. Previously, the process of innovating has been reliant on physical meetings and workshops with all stakeholders attending, but things have changed during the pandemic. The requirements frequently switched from lockdown scenarios to office re-openings, back to social distancing regulations based on the current health situation – all of which needed spontaneous adaptation.</p>
  <p><a href="https://vimeo.com/656182286">The Next Way of Working | Experience a full day of hybrid work across the global SAP AppHaus team</a> from <a href="https://vimeo.com/apphaus">SAP AppHaus</a> on <a href="https://vimeo.com">Vimeo</a>.</p>
  <p>In response, a new hybrid setup had to replace on-site meetings, as reflected in “<a href="https://apphaus.sap.com/resource/next-wow">The Next WoW</a>.” The ongoing collaboration adjustments allowed for numerous successful innovation projects with several companies. Among them are: <a href="https://apphaus.sap.com/work/project/iren-innovates-invoice-processing-with-sap-business-technology-platform">Iren</a> in Italy, <a href="https://apphaus.sap.com/work/project/border-states-inc-order-management-cockpit-on-sap-business-technology-platform">Border States Electric</a> in the U.S., <a href="https://apphaus.sap.com/work/project/improved-market-share-forecast-accuracy-using-intuitive-analytics-tool">Ottogi</a> in South Korea, <a href="https://apphaus.sap.com/work/project/sunrice-grower-and-admin-portal-with-sap-btp">SunRice</a> in Australia, <a href="https://apphaus.sap.com/work/project/fostering-innovation-sustainability-with-sap-business-technology-platform">Royal Greenland A/S</a> in Greenland, <a href="https://apphaus.sap.com/work/project/border-states-inc-order-management-cockpit-on-sap-business-technology-platform">and many more</a>. Some of these were conducted by SAP AppHaus and some by SAP AppHaus Network partners like <a href="https://apphaus.sap.com/location/melbourne">Bourne Digital</a> and <a href="https://apphaus.sap.com/location/aarhus">Trifork</a>.</p>
  <p>No doubt, the successful completion of these projects was only possible because the new hybrid collaboration models were thoroughly planned. Applying these principles of collaboration enabled SAP AppHaus, its sister team SAP Platform Adoption and Advisory, and other SAP teams to seamlessly support key SAP initiatives such as SAP Discovery Center with its actionable use cases (58 use cases created so far), RISE with SAP, the Intelligent Enterprise, and SAP Business Technology Platform.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-discovery-center--a-self-service-for-customers">SAP Discovery Center – a Self-Service for Customers</h2>
  <p>Recently, SAP launched a new self-service for customers called <a href="https://discovery-center.cloud.sap/">SAP Discovery Center</a>. With this low-threshold portal, SAP can help customers quickly adopt SAP Business Technology Platform and turn data into real business value. Due to the disruption of many highly relevant business processes during the pandemic, there is an increased need for flexible solutions that can be integrated and scaled easily.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cc56d01abfc68c04c536b14b973acf8f60126ef2.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cc56d01abfc68c04c536b14b973acf8f60126ef2.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1cc56d01abfc68c04c536b14b973acf8f60126ef2.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot of SAP Discovery Center" src="./media_1cc56d01abfc68c04c536b14b973acf8f60126ef2.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="518">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Visit SAP Discovery Center and start your journey.</em></p>
  <p>To jump-start the innovation journey, visitors can browse for “missions” that represent different innovative business scenarios. Missions include free-of-charge best practices and step-by-step guidance for implementing business use cases, with well-established support provided by the community and mission experts. With their long-term relationships to customers across the globe, the SAP AppHaus team feeds appropriate innovation scenarios and use cases into this new channel. The knowledge gained, such as technical realization, is turned into a mission and made available for all SAP customers. Examples of these <a href="https://discovery-center.cloud.sap/search/UCF*">actionable use cases</a> include the invoice management process of Iren (<a href="https://discovery-center.cloud.sap/missiondetail/3392/3431/">Mission: “Gaining transparency into supplier invoice and purchase order processing”</a>) or the chatbot functionality of <a href="https://apphaus.sap.com/work/project/sap-conversational-ai-helps-fight-pandemic-at-parkland-hospital">Parkland</a> (<a href="https://discovery-center.cloud.sap/missiondetail/3327/3369/">Mission: “Improve online patient experience using a COVID-19 chatbot”</a>).</p>
  <p>Another step towards free accessible knowledge sharing and exchange is the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform/trial.html">free tier model for SAP BTP</a>, which allows a free-of-cost version for customers to try out before buying. <a href="https://discovery-center.cloud.sap/search/Free-tier">Many use cases are available</a> to try out and test.</p>
  <h2 id="rise-with-sap-the-flexibility-needed-in-changing-circumstances">RISE with SAP: The Flexibility Needed in Changing Circumstances</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-next-wow-whitepaper">Read "The Next WoW" whitepaper</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://apphaus.sap.com/resource/next-wow">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Another important SAP offering is <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/rise.html">RISE with SAP</a>, which offers holistic, on-your-terms, and on-your-timeline transformation support for customers’ journey to the Intelligent Enterprise. This concierge service can provide a tailored path for every customer without any high upfront investments. The offering can remove complexity through a simplified engagement and guided journey into the cloud.</p>
  <p>By focusing on SAP Business Technology Platform projects, SAP AppHaus, together with the technical experts of the SAP Platform Adoption &#x26; Advisory team, accompany customers’ business transformations. Past projects have shown that this journey can be mastered in a hybrid or remote collaboration setup. The <a href="https://discovery-center.cloud.sap/missionssearch/risewithsap/">missions of several RISE with SAP projects</a> can also be found in SAP Discovery Center.</p>
  <h2 id="learning-never-stops">Learning Never Stops</h2>
  <p>The approach of continuous knowledge sharing also includes the exchange of experiences with other innovation teams, regionally and globally. The event series “SAP AppHaus Meets SAP Labs Munich,” which took place this year, featured SAP AppHaus colleagues reporting about best practices for storyboarding, leading innovation teams, SAP’s human-centered approach to innovation, and the Innovation Culture Toolkit. Check out <a href="https://video.sap.com/channel/SAP%2BAppHaus%2Bmeets%2BSAP%2BLabs%2BMunich/230426393">recordings</a> from this event.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dc18a183a0cf9ba03445530da53921612b1f048d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dc18a183a0cf9ba03445530da53921612b1f048d.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1dc18a183a0cf9ba03445530da53921612b1f048d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1dc18a183a0cf9ba03445530da53921612b1f048d.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Regarding the <a href="https://apphaus.sap.com/toolkit">Innovation Culture Toolkit</a>, the free collection of methods and best practices got a revamp this year and now it’s even easier to apply and benefit from its resources. With that, a few new assets have been published, like the <a href="https://apphaus.sap.com/toolkit/methods#architecture-thinking">The Lean Architecture Toolkit</a>. The newest kid on the block is the updated material for <a href="https://apphaus.sap.com/resource/spectrum">Spectrum</a> to support the setup of innovation teams within an organization. It is free, downloadable, and printable to make it possible to run Spectrum workshops on your own.</p>
  <h2 id="straight-into-2022">Straight into 2022</h2>
  <p>“The Next WoW” whitepaper summarizes the ultimate learning and outcome of all co-innovation efforts the global SAP AppHaus team has run during the last year. For several months and together with SAP AppHaus Network and other SAP colleagues, the AppHaus 2.0 team – a team focused on the evolution and development of changed working circumstances – jointly conducted interviews, experiments, and tested new work settings. “The Next WoW” whitepaper is the first public share-out representing the starting point for innovative work scenarios in the future. It is supposed to inspire and support other innovators, companies, and organizations on their way to the next way of working. “The Next WoW” helps sustain the creative work with customers and partners. In brief, it helps customers be successful.</p>
  <p>By the looks of it, the SAP AppHaus Network teams are well prepared for a new year to come. They look forward to conducting many more interesting and, yes, challenging customer projects. The new work concept is a living one; it evolves and grows with many more co-innovation and collaboration experiences to come.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Svenja Mueller is communications associate at SAP AppHaus.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RISE with SAP and Shine with SAP Solution Extensions: What You Need to Know]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/rise-with-sap-shine-with-sap-solution-extensions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/rise-with-sap-shine-with-sap-solution-extensions</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Integrated with SAP offerings like RISE with SAP, solution extensions enable a more impactful digital transformation journey on your terms.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/s-sap-solution-extensions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[One Technical Revolution at a Time: 10 Years of SAP Innovation Center Potsdam]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/10-years-sap-innovation-center-potsdam</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/10-years-sap-innovation-center-potsdam</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Innovation Center Potsdam has given rise to many significant innovations since its founding in 2011. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19904870e2370d9e427b7fb6d43cce1bae7f8a673.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19904870e2370d9e427b7fb6d43cce1bae7f8a673.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19904870e2370d9e427b7fb6d43cce1bae7f8a673.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="One Technical Revolution at a Time: 10 Years of SAP Innovation Center Potsdam" src="./media_19904870e2370d9e427b7fb6d43cce1bae7f8a673.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="one-technical-revolution-at-a-time-10-years-of-sap-innovation-center-potsdam">One Technical Revolution at a Time: 10 Years of SAP Innovation Center Potsdam</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Small beginnings can lead to large impact. The first location of <a href="https://icn.sap.com/">SAP Innovation Center Network</a> was founded in October 2011 as a technology trend radar for the Walldorf-based company and has since given rise to a significant number of SAP’s most innovative products and solutions.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Invisible spheres making funny noises,” Marcus Krug says when asked about the first thing he remembers from the early days of SAP Innovation Center Potsdam. “We were located right underneath the Hasso Plattner Institute’s D-School and would always hear the HPI students playing funny ice-breaker games to get their creativity going on the lawn outside our windows.” Now the head of SAP Innovation Center Potsdam, Krug first joined when it was five months old and had just over 20 employees.</p>
  <p>SAP Innovation Center Potsdam was founded by the Executive Board of SAP SE and with the encouragement of Professor Hasso Plattner, chairman of the Supervisory Board of SAP SE. Today it serves as the nucleus of what has become SAP Innovation Center Network, which eventually gave rise to the New Ventures and Technologies department with close to 400 innovators within the SAP Technology and Innovation Board area.</p>
  <p>“The idea was to have a dedicated SAP unit looking into new technologies and what could be done with them,” Krug says. “We didn’t want to risk missing out on both technical and business opportunities.”</p>
  <p>Matthias Uflacker, the first SAP Innovation Center Potsdam employee at the time, explains why Potsdam was chosen as the first location: “The collaboration with the Hasso Plattner Institute helped us identify and try out new things outside of standard SAP product development. SAP Innovation Center Potsdam fostered research, providing a platform for the cooperation between SAP and scientists, with SAP not only funding but also bringing in relevant questions to solve. And, with its proximity to HPI and the academic hub that is Berlin, it was able to attract a lot of amazing, international talent over the years.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-sap-innovation-center-network">Learn more about SAP Innovation Center Network</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://icn.sap.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="technology-vanguard-for-sap">Technology Vanguard for SAP</h2>
  <p>“The original mission was to transform cutting-edge research into innovation, so obviously from the beginning we’ve had the ambition to explore and use the latest technology in order to find out how it could benefit our customers and SAP,” Krug says.</p>
  <p>Working closely with academia was an obvious way to get access to cutting-edge research. The birth of SAP HANA, for example, was the result of a strong relationship between SAP and HPI. Experts from both sides were eager to continue working together, with further projects revolving around the application side of SAP HANA.</p>
  <p>“Part of our mission was to explore novel SAP HANA use cases to see how far we could push what was possible with this new, paradigm-shifting in-memory technology,” Krug says. “To do so, we were looking at new applications leveraging data science and machine learning on Big Data sets in a broad range of industries, including healthcare, life sciences, and even gaming. Many of these projects were small and it was a lot of fun to work on them with highly talented colleagues coming from all over the world.”</p>
  <p>“HPI student projects had already been an important contribution to the development of SAP HANA,” Dr. Michael Perscheid, chair representative of Prof. Hasso Plattner at HPI, says. After founding SAP Innovation Center Potsdam, these types of projects were continued with a strong focus on the application side. “Gifted students from HPI got to work on a specialized business problem together with SAP and an industry partner,” he adds. Some of these projects were so successful that they were featured in Plattner’s SAPPHIRE NOW keynotes.</p>
  <h2 id="strategic-approach-to-innovation">Strategic Approach to Innovation</h2>
  <p>SAP Innovation Center Potsdam moved to a building of its own in September 2013, located in an idyllic spot north of Potsdam, near Lake Jungfernsee. Designed for transparency with its open spaces and large glass fronts, the new location in Potsdam is meant to foster communication, exchange of ideas, collaboration, and contemplation of new possibilities. Due to massive hiring, an additional building was opened in May 2016.</p>
  <p>In 2013, the leadership of SAP Innovation Center Potsdam changed to Juergen Mueller, formerly head of Plattner’s chair at HPI and today member of the Executive Board of SAP SE and chief technology officer, who was to give SAP an actual innovation strategy.</p>
  <p>“SAP Innovation Center Network, among other things rose from that strategy,” Krug says. “Juergen brought in the necessary structure and focus for the location to take on increasingly bigger responsibilities within the SAP family and to get ready to grow the team significantly over the next few years.”</p>
  <h2 id="startup-agility-combined-with-corporate-expertise">Startup Agility Combined with Corporate Expertise</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="intelligent-enterprises-are-changing-the-world-for-the-better">Intelligent enterprises are changing the world for the better</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/intelligent-enterprise.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Inspired by his work with startups and venture capitalists in the Berlin ecosystem, Krug developed the idea of creating an entrepreneurial space within SAP, allowing employees to develop new ventures following the same principles and governance as their non-SAP counterparts. The resulting blueprint for SAP’s intrapreneurship program made it into Mueller’s innovation strategy in 2014 and laid the foundation for yet another big step in the evolution of SAP’s innovation ambitions.</p>
  <p>After reaching more than 1,000 employees who submitted more than 400 venture ideas, it was clear that the program struck a chord. Venture capitalists who had been invited to help structure the program by providing outside-in perspective were impressed with the quality of the submissions and the proposal was met with a lot of interest by the executive board. In retrospect, Krug is certain: “Coming up with this idea, developing it, actually getting the mandate and the freedom to build the program the way we did – this could only have happened at SAP Innovation Center Potsdam.”</p>
  <p>Working closely with startups also spurred a certain SAP Innovation Center Potsdam-specific mindset about the development of new ideas. “Think big, start small. Fail often, fail early, as a startup would,” Krug sums up. “This isn’t typically possible when you’re part of a large corporation.”</p>
  <p>Using a lean startup approach, design thinking, and first-principles thinking, SAP Innovation Center Potsdam experts first focus on a business problem when working with SAP customers. While most big problems have already been addressed one way or another in the market, new technologies often allow for completely rethinking how to approach a problem. Machine learning and blockchain are two prominent examples of technologies that SAP has been able to adopt to build fundamentally new capabilities after exploring them in <a href="/topics/sap-innovation-center-network">SAP Innovation Center Network</a>.</p>
  <p>The setup for SAP Innovation Center Potsdam’s innovation projects with customers closely resembles the work of a startup. It starts with a small team and works to demonstrate in an agile way how it will benefit customers. Since SAP Innovation Center Potsdam typically works in close alignment with SAP’s lines of business, there is always a realistic chance that a successful solution might eventually become an SAP standard product.</p>
  <h2 id="outlook-into-the-future">Outlook into the Future</h2>
  <p>SAP Innovation Center Potsdam’s mission, however, still feels fresh and vibrant after 10 years. Now part of the bigger New Ventures and Technologies family, the team continues to tackle big customer problems using the latest technologies, including neurosymbolic artificial intelligence (AI), semantic technologies, and blockchain.</p>
  <p>Some of the team’s biggest bets are on decentralized technologies to build the business network of the future, enabling customers to seamlessly share scope-3 carbon emissions, embedding financial technology into business processes using smart contracts and decentralized finance, as well as new AI-powered simulation and decision-making tools to contextualize business events and augment SAP S4/HANA Finance users.</p>
  <p>“We don’t own a fail-proof crystal ball,” Krug says. “But I’m sure we will hear and see a lot more on the topics of AI-enabled contextualization, human augmentation, smart contracts, tokenization, and tokenomics. Our goal is to drive the change these new capabilities will enable to create a better world and help our customers address their biggest needs.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-innovation-center-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Becoming an Intelligent, Sustainable Enterprise: Why Adoption Matters]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-enterprise-adoption-intelligent-sustainable</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-enterprise-adoption-intelligent-sustainable</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Enterprise Adoption helps customers to realize value and business outcomes when it comes to resiliency, performance, and sustainability.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11add9f2e42b8b9d1eaf36cacfd0a404142b1e4e9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11add9f2e42b8b9d1eaf36cacfd0a404142b1e4e9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11add9f2e42b8b9d1eaf36cacfd0a404142b1e4e9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Becoming an Intelligent, Sustainable Enterprise: Why Adoption Matters" src="./media_11add9f2e42b8b9d1eaf36cacfd0a404142b1e4e9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="becoming-an-intelligent-sustainable-enterprise-why-adoption-matters">Becoming an Intelligent, Sustainable Enterprise: Why Adoption Matters</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Digitalization intensifies and further accelerates as businesses around the globe try to outpace the challenges of supply chain shortages and constantly evolving government regulations.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As we continue to further develop and explore the needs and opportunities of the new normal, digitalization keeps expanding while the need for businesses to upskill their workforce must be addressed at the same time. Indeed, according to a <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/content/dam/Deloitte/us/Documents/about-deloitte/us-fortune-deloitte-CEO-survey-january-2021-highlights.pdf">2021 Deloitte survey</a>, 85% of CEOs said that the pandemic significantly accelerated digital transformation plans for their business.</p>
  <p>This digital transformation can only become a working reality particularly for businesses operating globally and locally when the implications of operating in a country and across countries are considered and taken into account. Businesses must be able to plan and act holistically wherever they operate. While state-of-the-art enterprise software and solutions are needed to make this happen, adoption significantly supports businesses to generate the full value from these products. It is the key to realizing desired business outcomes.</p>
  <p>SAP Enterprise Adoption helps customers to realize value and business outcomes in three key aspects: resiliency, performance, and sustainability. Those aspects mean something quite specific for successful businesses. Here’s why adoption matters.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-localization-by-product-and-region">Learn more about localization by product and region</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/product/globalization.html#section_703941363">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="resiliency">Resiliency</h2>
  <p>In this context, resiliency means getting the full benefit of SAP software by adapting to new situations or conditions easily and without disruption. For example, many different countries have enacted different regulations, not only during the COVID-19 pandemic. We are providing those legal changes to our customers, so they can stay focused on their business and compliant with any existing or new regulations. On the other hand, a company opening a subsidiary — for example, in Brazil — would need to feel confident that it could implement its existing software solution while adhering to governmental policies. Operating locally and globally is one aspect, digitalization of business and meeting requirements for e-reporting and e-invoicing the other.</p>
  <p>Here, SAP Document and Reporting Compliance enables companies to comply with local regulations for e-invoicing and e-reporting in a huge number of countries. The solution is fully harmonized across countries and delivers approximately 350 statutory reports and electronic document processing scenarios out of the box and is kept up to date whenever a legal change happens.</p>
  <p>This harmonized and standardized approach enables customers to easily for example build up a shared service center and implement new obligations in almost no time. It provides the customer peace of mind doing business in multiple countries, especially when exchanging documents with governments.</p>
  <h2 id="performance">Performance</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-enable-now-reduce-learning-curves-with-contextually-relevant-timely-and-proactive-enablement-content">SAP Enable Now: Reduce learning curves with contextually relevant, timely, and proactive enablement content</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/enable-now.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP Enterprise Adoption helps customers to increase business innovation and productivity through the rapid adoption and automation of processes for SAP products and solutions. The most successful companies achieving greater efficiencies are those that balance automation and user performance.</p>
  <p>For example, SAP implemented localization capabilities for tax frameworks for an <a href="https://dam.sap.com/mac/app/p/pdf/asset/preview/TfNtmwE?ltr=a">international food and beverage company</a>, leading to a more than 60% efficiency gain in its fiscal department, which runs more than 16,000 tax obligations per year for its 20 million invoice items.</p>
  <h2 id="sustainability">Sustainability</h2>
  <p>SAP Enterprise Adoption helps customers to optimize the use of resources through transparency on respective regulations as well as through empowered users providing key abilities required for sustained adoption of SAP solutions.</p>
  <p>For example, a <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2020/01/e46fc525-7f7d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">large utility company</a> needed more than 1,000 users to become productive at the moment of go-live with SAP S/4HANA. To drive adoption readiness, the company began with the training and upskilling of its workforce four months before go-live, enabling users with embedded contextual help as they completed daily tasks. In addition, the company created e-learning materials, reference guides, and work instructions.</p>
  <p>This enablement and upskilling lead to empowerment of the workforce, an increase of motivation, and employee retention.</p>
  <p><strong>Resiliency, performance,</strong> and <strong>sustainability</strong> are the key levers of your desired business outcomes and make up what I like to call“the “whole enchilada” — the realization of intelligent, sustainable enterprises as a working reality.</p>
  <p>Adoption helps make the digital transformation a success, which is why, as enterprises continue their digital journey, it is essential to aid with adoption and enablement throughout the lifespan of SAP products, despite whatever future opportunities enterprises may face.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Eva Zauke is senior vice president and global head of SAP Enterprise Adoption.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-enable-now</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cirque du Soleil Entertainment Group Taps RISE with SAP to Drive Intelligent Enterprise Strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/cirque-du-soleil-entertainment-group-rise-with-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/cirque-du-soleil-entertainment-group-rise-with-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Cirque du Soleil Entertainment Group has expanded its relationship with SAP, investing in RISE with SAP to support global growth.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_156abd619041804682268f89108a7aaab035ebf4d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_156abd619041804682268f89108a7aaab035ebf4d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_156abd619041804682268f89108a7aaab035ebf4d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Cirque du Soleil Entertainment Group Taps RISE with SAP to Drive Intelligent Enterprise Strategy" src="./media_156abd619041804682268f89108a7aaab035ebf4d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="cirque-du-soleil-entertainment-group-taps-rise-with-sap-to-drive-intelligent-enterprise-strategy">Cirque du Soleil Entertainment Group Taps RISE with SAP to Drive Intelligent Enterprise Strategy</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="rise-with-sap-transform-your-business-in-the-way-that-works-best-for-you">RISE with SAP: Transform your business in the way that works best for you</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/rise.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that Cirque du Soleil Entertainment Group has expanded its relationship with SAP by investing in SAP’s business-transformation-as-a-service offering, RISE with SAP, to further the entertainment company’s intelligent enterprise journey.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Cirque du Soleil Entertainment Group will upgrade its existing SAP ECC 6.0 environment to SAP S/4HANA Cloud on Microsoft Azure and integrate other modular cloud solutions including SAP Ariba, SAP SuccessFactors and SAP Concur software. Where highly unique processes are required, SAP Business Technology Platform will be used to innovate.</p>
  <p>“Embracing an intelligent enterprise strategy will simplify our business and support the organization’s global growth strategy,” said Philippe Lalumière, vice president, Information Technology, Cirque du Soleil Entertainment Group. “Having the ability to quickly pivot, scale and create new, engaging fan experiences has never been more important given the impact the global pandemic has had on the entertainment industry. RISE with SAP and SAP S/4HANA will help power our ability to deliver on these goals.”</p>
  <p>“People around the world love Cirque du Soleil for the performers’ incredible agility, flexibility, coordination and talent,” said SAP North America President DJ Paoni. “This partnership is all about helping Cirque du Soleil embrace and incorporate these same values in its day-to-day operations as a company.”</p>
  <p>This project is the latest step in SAP and Cirque du Soleil Entertainment Group’s ongoing, innovation-driven partnership aimed at delivering new and exciting experiences to audiences around the world using the power of technology. Cirque du Soleil Entertainment Group became an SAP customer in 2001 to help transform its business to be the leading entertainment company in the world — a two-decade milestone both organizations are excited to celebrate in the months to come.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Justin Wolz, +1 (919) 306-7084, <a href="mailto:j.wolz@sap.com">j.wolz@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>industry/media: industry/sports-entertainment</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>