<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/moments-of-service/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transform Your Career and the World Around You Through Volunteering]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/transform-career-world-through-volunteer-pro-bono-work</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/transform-career-world-through-volunteer-pro-bono-work</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP employees are transforming the world through their volunteer and pro bono consulting work. Learn more about their efforts.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_151aa28cc4c3b93ece1704e100b04d40a6cf71ac9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_151aa28cc4c3b93ece1704e100b04d40a6cf71ac9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_151aa28cc4c3b93ece1704e100b04d40a6cf71ac9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Transform Your Career and the World Around You Through Volunteering" src="./media_151aa28cc4c3b93ece1704e100b04d40a6cf71ac9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="transform-your-career-and-the-world-around-you-through-volunteering">Transform Your Career and the World Around You Through Volunteering</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-csr-at-sap">Learn more about CSR at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>If you were given the opportunity to help others, build your professional skills, gain confidence, and feel more energized in your life and career, would you take it? SAP has dedicated over <a href="https://www.sap.com/dmc/exp/2017_03_46558/enUS/impact/">a decade to exactly that</a>: creating volunteer and pro bono consulting programs that not only help the world run better and improve people’s lives, but also benefit employees, their teams, and the company as well.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Karen Vergara, from the Global Learning Services Enablement Program Management for SAP Concur, is an alumni participant from several SAP-driven pro bono consulting programs, as well as a mentor, trainer, and SAP Corporate Social Responsibility (SAP CSR) fellow.</p>
  <p>Vergara always knew she wanted to help other people become successful and has taken that passion, along with the development of her own professional skills, to a new level. She began her career in education, but found that while she was making a difference, she wanted to do more. She leveraged her educational foundation to move into various roles at Microsoft, Accenture, and most recently SAP, earning a higher salary that allowed her to donate more to the causes she was passionate about but offered her less time for traditional, hands-on volunteering. Vergara decided to seek out opportunities within her professional role to make an impact in new ways.</p>
  <p>What started as a way to get involved soon turned into so much more. With each experience, Vergara gained more than she expected.</p>
  <p>“I’ve found that I’ve taken away as much as I’ve given, maybe sometimes even more,” she says. Volunteering, particularly skills-based volunteer experiences, provided her with the ability to do good and to keep learning and growing both personally and professionally at the same time.</p>
  <p>From helping students find success to changing her career and making an impact through volunteerism and pro bono consulting as a part of the SAP community, Vergara’s journey is showing no signs of slowing down. Over the past six months, she has been working on a fellowship with the SAP CSR team to position every type of volunteering offered at SAP, particularly pro bono engagements, as an opportunity for learning, career, and leadership development.</p>
  <p>“If you are already volunteering, it is a just a bonus and a way to think more intentionally about your professional development,” Vergara shares. “You can do good and learn, taking skills away from it and gaining experience that will help you in your own career.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-stories-and-coverage-about-csr-efforts-at-sap">Read more stories and coverage about CSR efforts at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sap-csr">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In fact, Vergara has taken this one step further, becoming a leader and champion for employee volunteering. She shared one anecdote from an SAP employee who was looking to gain specific experience to advance to a new role. Vergara pointed them to skills-based volunteering, and when it came time for the interview for the new role, the employee was able to share examples of the experience they gained through participation in these kinds of activities – experience that they otherwise would not have had – putting them in a better position to obtain the new role.</p>
  <p>Thanks to Vergara’s work during her fellowship, as well as her own lived experiences as a corporate volunteer and pro bono consultant, she has demonstrated that utilizing skills and concepts through volunteering and pro bono consulting <em>is</em> career development.</p>
  <p>Through volunteering in any capacity, there is always an opportunity to explore career interests and find a path forward utilizing the right opportunities. CSR activities represent an alternative form of experiential learning; it benefits every professional, whether employee or manager, to consider how they can be incorporated into our professional development plans and goal setting. Vergara’s work has highlighted that intentional and well thought-out engagement in these types of offerings can lead to the acquisition of new skills and chances to practice skills someone may have learned in an academic setting. It also provides an opportunity to learn from others, share one’s own skills, and build a network.</p>
  <p>Everyone who participates in CSR activities stands to gain from the work that Vergara has done in defining how volunteering contributes to career growth beyond social impact. When thinking about volunteerism, often what comes to mind is doing good, serving others, giving back to our communities, and making a positive social and environmental impact. Beyond these more obvious benefits, there are powerful takeaways for the volunteer as well. Traditional activities are a fantastic way to build community with others who are like-minded and share common interests. Skills-based volunteering and pro bono consulting offers an opportunity to build a professional network, while practicing skills such as collaboration, creative problem-solving, and inclusive leadership behaviors. Like Vergara, many employees seek fulfillment beyond their day-to-day roles. Her story is one example of taking the initiative to make a societal impact and gaining so much more. She has found community in her career, opportunities to lead, and a renewed commitment to continue helping the world run better and improving people’s lives.</p>
  <p><strong>Join Us</strong></p>
  <p>With a <a href="https://www.sap.com/dmc/exp/2017_03_46558/enUS/impact/">decade of success</a> engaging employees like Karen Vergara, SAP, together with EY, MovingWorlds, TRANSFORM, and Unilever, continue to partner on the TRANSFORM Support Hub, connecting employees everywhere to social entrepreneurs anywhere through pro bono consulting, coaching, and more. If you feel inspired to build your skills as well as a more sustainable world, we invite you to <a href="https://movingworlds.org/transform/corporates">join us</a>!</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/moments-of-service</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Forward Together for an Equitable Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/forward-together-equitable-future</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/forward-together-equitable-future</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Moving "forward together," the SAP Corporate Social Responsibility team is embarking on a refreshed strategy. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/moments-of-service</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acceleration Collective: Small Contribution, Big Impact]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/acceleration-collective-small-contribution-big-impact</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/acceleration-collective-small-contribution-big-impact</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Through the Acceleration Collective, SAP colleagues apply their skills to organizations that lead through sustainable business practices.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_110aa5b25939256a2229893d1150931d9f8a01a23.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_110aa5b25939256a2229893d1150931d9f8a01a23.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_110aa5b25939256a2229893d1150931d9f8a01a23.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Acceleration Collective: Small Contribution, Big Impact" src="./media_110aa5b25939256a2229893d1150931d9f8a01a23.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="acceleration-collective-small-contribution-big-impact">Acceleration Collective: Small Contribution, Big Impact</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-how-sap-is-powering-opportunity-for-all-people-through-digital-inclusion">Learn how SAP is powering opportunity for all people through digital inclusion</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/csr.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Sometimes the things you consider to be a small contribution can amount to big impact. In 2021, I had the honor of being asked to coach a young entrepreneur as part of the <strong>Acceleration Collective</strong>, a <a href="https://movingworlds.org/partner/sap/acceleration-collective-employees">virtual pro bono consulting experience from SAP</a>, powered by MovingWorlds.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the corporate world, you hear a lot about supporting the future of business. This program flips that concept on its head, and instead focuses on the opportunity for SAP employees to connect with and support the “business of future,” a phrase referring to next-generation leaders and organizations that operate as social enterprises.</p>
  <p>Acceleration Collective matches the skills and expertise of SAP employees everywhere with social entrepreneurs anywhere. The <a href="/2021/07/possibilists-study-youth-lead-post-pandemic-world">young social innovators</a> — or <a href="https://thepossibilists.org/">Possibilists</a> as they are also called — need support to solve critical business challenges. SAP employees offer that support to them in two ways: as certified coaches and as pro bono consultants also known as “experteers,” each volunteer position playing a critical role in support of the enterprises.</p>
  <p>In my case, I worked as a coach with <a href="/topics/we-are-family-foundation">We Are Family Foundation</a> Global Teen Leader <a href="https://www.wearefamilyfoundation.org/gtl-2021/angela-busheska">Angela Busheska</a><u>,</u> the founder of <a href="https://www.enroute-app.com/">En Route</a>. Angela has personally experienced the impact of climate change, recently losing her aunt as a result of extreme air pollution. “I wasn’t committed until I saw the negative impact of pollution firsthand. I knew I had to do something.” The death of Angela’s aunt is not an isolated event in her home country of <a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/gallery/2021/4/21/in-pictures-air-pollution-in-north-macedonia">North Macedonia</a>, and she wants that to change.</p>
  <p>Her answer to a better future is En Route, a tech startup that educates children about their carbon footprints through an interactive, gamified app that makes being environmentally responsible fun. Their aim is simple: build a community that will save the planet.</p>
  <p>“COVID has turned the world into a global village. I use technology to not only connect to organizations that can help me [We Are Family Foundation, SAP], but also to connect to others. I want to transform the people who don’t care,” Angela offered.</p>
  <p>Angela knew she wanted to grow her organization, reach more children, and make a bigger impact. But where to start? Through a couple of coaching exercises that help the client identify and rank priorities, Angela quickly realized that funding for growth was the essential next step. Backing out of the funding goal she identified all the necessary steps to find donors. She did the work and it paid off. I was delighted to learn that Angela had this to say about our coaching experience together: “I was working with Allison on what’s next for me and En Route. Her support ultimately helped me create the strategic connections I needed for my business.”</p>
  <p>Through coaching, Angela tapped into all the answers that were already within her. In early January she shared the following: “I am so happy to inform you that our sessions were a success and we ended up being funded by <a href="https://storymaps.arcgis.com/stories/085f4052608944abb6bff76c307b86d8">National Geographic</a>!” I am over the moon excited for this young entrepreneur, and frankly for all of the young leaders who are inspiring global change. Angela told me that she got started because she was tired of everyone blaming others for what was wrong. She wanted to do something. Her engagement with me and this program is another example that she does not just talk about making the change, she gets to work.</p>
  <p>I started coaching in 2017, and it has become one of the most rewarding experiences of my life. Helping clients discover the answers within themselves and seeing them grow, accomplish goals, and thrive is truly an amazing experience. When clients successfully realize their potential through coaching, there is nothing.</p>
  <p>This experience in particular was an opportunity to push the envelope of what is possible through coaching. I’m proud to know that my efforts helped someone who is truly making a difference in the world. En Route teaches children the importance of their carbon footprint, and helps them form sustainable habits at an early age. The potential impact of such an effort is exciting.</p>
  <p>Sustainability topics have long been of interest to me, and this opportunity allowed me to combine my love of coaching with a meaningful cause — a win-win for me. My small contribution to the Acceleration Collective has resulted in a positive impact on Angela, her organization, and hopefully the world.</p>
  <p>You can learn more about the Acceleration Collective and other SAP Corporate Social Responsibility programs by visiting <a href="http://www.sap.com/csr">sap.com/csr</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Allison Gapter is vice president of Global Strategic Ecosystem Marketing at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/moments-of-service</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
            <category>news-tag/we-are-family-foundation</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Volunteering Now for Our Common Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/international-volunteer-day-common-future</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/international-volunteer-day-common-future</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In the wake of International Volunteer Day, get the highlights on how SAP employees support their communities worldwide.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b93f175ced05c33ccf0725f22369911d25972fc8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b93f175ced05c33ccf0725f22369911d25972fc8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b93f175ced05c33ccf0725f22369911d25972fc8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Volunteering Now for Our Common Future" src="./media_1b93f175ced05c33ccf0725f22369911d25972fc8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="volunteering-now-for-our-common-future">Volunteering Now for Our Common Future</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Each year on December 5, the United Nations (UN) Volunteers organization hosts International Volunteer Day with the goal of <a href="https://www.un.org/en/observances/volunteer-day">recognizing and promoting the dedication of volunteers</a> around the world.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Most of the world’s volunteering happens informally and cannot be tracked, but the <a href="https://swvr2022.unv.org/">documented economic contribution</a> of time and support that volunteers deliver globally is estimated to represent the work of approximately 61 million full-time workers monthly.</p>
  <p>In a world struggling to combat seemingly insurmountable issues like climate change, a global health crisis, and growing inequality, even millions of volunteers are not enough. While it is easy to focus on the problems, International Volunteer Day represents an important opportunity to appreciate and reflect on the efforts of the incredible commitment and passion of <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/csr.html#connect">those at SAP who dedicate their time and talents as volunteers</a> to help the world run better and improve people’s lives.</p>
  <p>As non-profit partners in residence working with the SAP Corporate Social Responsibility (CSR) team, we offer a unique perspective on days like this. While we live and breathe the value of volunteering, we know that our experience is not shared by everyone. Volunteering helps others while also promoting learning, personal growth, and community. Together we bring our non-profit organizations’ — <a href="https://www.realizedworth.com/">Realized Worth</a> and <a href="https://www.handsonbayarea.org/">HandsOn Bay Area</a> — extensive experience in social impact and volunteer management alongside our own, collaborating for sustainability with employees directly.</p>
  <p>As the newest members of the SAP CSR team, we have learned so much in a short time about what it means when companies like SAP provide skills-based volunteering services to non-profits and social enterprises, and just how valuable it is to the underserved communities that SAP volunteers support across <a href="https://joom.ag/rUVC/p6">113 countries</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="how-sap-csr-empowers-employees-to-take-action-on-causes-they-care-about">How SAP CSR empowers employees to take action on causes they care about</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/csr.html#connect">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="why-volunteering-matters">Why Volunteering Matters</h2>
  <p>A common misconception about volunteering, especially skills-based volunteering, is that the engagement only delivers value to the organization and its respective clients being served.</p>
  <p>One of the most significant reasons why corporate volunteering matters is that it is an experiential leadership opportunity. It offers employees a chance to build new skills and put current expertise into action while also satisfying a non-profit or community need. Ultimately, this helps employees explore and fulfill career goals, and gain exposure to different perspectives as well as business-relevant experiences to grow personally and professionally.</p>
  <p>Beyond personal growth, corporate volunteering is good business. Companies benefit from employee participation in many ways. For example, when employees volunteer through work, they can become more engaged and connected and experience greater personal fulfillment.</p>
  <p>The various skills-based volunteer opportunities available at SAP all offer meaningful ways to strengthen inclusive and empathetic leadership, communication, and teamwork among so many other important career- and company-building skills.</p>
  <p>Chris Jarvis, co-founder and chief strategy officer of Realized Worth, confirms this: “The contribution of time and other resources to charities and their communities is profoundly valuable. Without these contributions, our world would have a grave deficit of social, human, and physical capital. But the power of volunteering lies in more than its utilitarian application. As passionate volunteers will profess, it is not the transaction that motivates them; rather, it is the transformation that occurs in their own lives.”</p>
  <p>This year, after more than 15 years of focused volunteer engagement each October, SAP evolved its signature volunteer campaign to <a href="/2021/08/moments-of-service-impactful-employee-engagement">Moments of Service</a>. With the shift, SAP is enabling its more than 105,000 employees with varied and valuable skills to connect to causes that matter to them personally. Through skills-based volunteering opportunities, they can create sustainable, long-lasting change in their communities and across the SAP ecosystem.</p>
  <h2 id="volunteering-now-at-sap">Volunteering Now at SAP</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="moments-of-service-a-re-energized-approach-to-impactful-employee-engagement">Moments of Service: A Re-Energized Approach to Impactful Employee Engagement</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/08/moments-of-service-impactful-employee-engagement">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Building on more than a decade of success in our pro bono volunteering portfolio, we are honored to work alongside the SAP CSR team to diligently transform programs like SAP Social Sabbatical and grow new ones including Pro Bono for Economic Equity, a response to SAP’s social justice commitments, and the virtual pro bono Acceleration Collective initiative.</p>
  <p>“Working alongside <a href="https://movingworlds.org/">MovingWorlds</a> to serve young social entrepreneurs from the <a href="https://changemakerxchange.org/">ChangemakerXChange</a>, <a href="https://socialshifters.co/">Social Shifters</a>, and <a href="https://www.wearefamilyfoundation.org/">We Are Family Foundation</a> communities, we are hopeful that we can improve the experience and most importantly the social impact of virtual pro bono volunteering,” shares Jennifer Beason, global program director of SAP CSR. “We are honored that more than 60 expert volunteers and certified coaches are working with us to accelerate the success of 25 outstanding social businesses like <a href="http://www.durian.org.ng/">Durian</a>, a Nigeria-based social enterprise that is building communities of the future – circular, creative, and empowered by rural women.”</p>
  <p>The company’s longest running pro bono portfolio, <strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/dmc/exp/2017_03_46558/enUS/index.html">SAP Social Sabbatical</a></strong>, which is executed in partnership with <a href="https://www.pyxeraglobal.org/">PYXERA Global</a>, has embraced local roles for employees to help tackle global goals right in their own backyard. By keeping employees and programs closer to home, SAP volunteers were able to continue delivering impact despite the pandemic. Working with diverse teams and matched with nonprofits and social enterprises, employees like Esteban Samartin dedicated an estimated $450,000 (estimated USAID value) in pro bono consulting services to solve strategic business assignments in 2021.</p>
  <p><strong><a href="https://sap.sharepoint.com/sites/124545">Pro Bono for Economic Equity</a></strong>, also in partnership with PYXERA Global, follows a similar structure to SAP Social Sabbatical. Small teams of SAP employees are paired with Black-owned businesses to provide their professional skills as pro bono volunteer consultants. At a recent closing event for the U.S. arm of the program, a key theme was that SAP groups offered frameworks and scalable solutions that the businesses can use again and again. A favorite example was a team that developed marketing strategies and templates for baking mix company <a href="https://sugarlessketo.com/">Sugarless Keto</a>. Initially launched in the U.S., the program expanded to Brazil, South Africa, and the UK in the second half of 2021.</p>
  <p>Joining the SAP CSR team with nonprofit backgrounds, our view of corporate volunteerism was very different than the reality of what we now experience and observe every day. The global scale at which SAP’s portfolio of programs and partnerships operate is greater than we imagined.</p>
  <p>It might be difficult to comprehend the difference that SAP employees are making to the more than 1,500 organizations they are serving, but the connections being made are providing the building blocks for more resilient communities. We have seen firsthand that impactful and meaningful work through volunteerism does not just benefit the recipient non-profit organizations – one employee’s contributions to one project can affect thousands of people.</p>
  <p>‘Tis the season for good news and it brings us great joy knowing the work that we are a part of is changing lives for the better. To share how you are making difference, tag us on social media using #SAP4good and share how you are helping your community run better.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Heidi Pio and Atalanta Kyriazi are non-profit partners in residence with the SAP CSR team.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/moments-of-service</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Moments of Service: A Re-Energized Approach to Impactful Employee Engagement]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/moments-of-service-impactful-employee-engagement</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/moments-of-service-impactful-employee-engagement</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is evolving its Month of Service employee volunteer campaign into Moments of Service for year-round impact around the world. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b70b35dab15b1bef363099c4681f970ed46e2f20.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b70b35dab15b1bef363099c4681f970ed46e2f20.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b70b35dab15b1bef363099c4681f970ed46e2f20.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Moments of Service: A Re-Energized Approach to Impactful Employee Engagement" src="./media_1b70b35dab15b1bef363099c4681f970ed46e2f20.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="moments-of-service-a-re-energized-approach-to-impactful-employee-engagement">Moments of Service: A Re-Energized Approach to Impactful Employee Engagement</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Greek philosopher Heraclitus was said to have coined the phrase, “The only constant in life is change.” In any organization this rings true, but especially at SAP, where we are committed to constant evolution and innovation in support of our mission to help the world run better and improve people’s lives.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>On the SAP Corporate Social Responsibility (CSR) team, we believe that this mission extends beyond our customers, which is why <a href="https://view.joomag.com/powering-opportunity-sap-corporate-social-responsibility-2020-in-review/0967587001608130031?short&#x26;">our work</a> supports under-resourced people, communities, and nations around the world with partnerships and programs and is bolstered by employee volunteering. Our focus is on those most deeply impacted by the intersections of the far-reaching social and environmental issues that our world faces.</p>
  <p>More than 15 years ago, SAP’s <a href="/topics/month-of-service">Month of Service</a> campaign was created to provide employees with a dedicated time each October to connect with social causes they care about. The campaign grew year-over-year, with more individuals, leaders, and teams taking the opportunity to bring our company purpose to life and give back to the communities where SAP operates. Volunteering became part of the company DNA involving many of our employees.</p>
  <p>SAP employees have allocated more than 1.9 million hours of volunteer time to worthy non-profits and social enterprises across the globe since 2012, demonstrating a growing commitment to purpose. With few exceptions, there has been steady growth as volunteering opportunities for employees have expanded and our focus on skills-based and pro bono activities has sharpened.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-impact-of-month-of-service-in-2020">Learn more about the impact of Month of Service in 2020</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2020/12/sap-month-of-service-in-2020">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="volunteering-opportunities-available-through-the-year-and-across-the-globe">Volunteering Opportunities Available through the Year and Across the Globe</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-sap4good-stories">Read more SAP4Good stories</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sap4good">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>When 2020 challenged us all to pivot to virtual, the SAP CSR team knew it could spin this long-standing annual campaign on its axis and focus Month of Service on cross-border virtual volunteering and a series of inspiring speaker sessions. Last year, the goal was to keep momentum going at a time when in-person gatherings were not possible, as well as to deepen employees’ connection to the social and environmental topics outlined in SAP’s broader sustainability framework.</p>
  <p>As a result, more than 10,000 employees engaged and took advantage of 207,000 hours of employee learning. Combine this with the 136,000 hours of volunteer time that SAP employees dedicated across the whole of 2020 and the depth of the commitment to bettering our world becomes clear.</p>
  <p>This year, SAP CSR will further evolve the campaign as Month of Service becomes <strong>Moments of Service</strong>.</p>
  <p>Moments of Service will no longer be limited to activities that are available in October, but will focus on the entire spectrum of volunteer experiences that are available through the year and across the globe. This will make it even easier to offer non-profits the support they need when they need it and for employees to engage when the time is right for them.</p>
  <p>The last 18 months have shown that purpose is as relevant and urgent as it has ever been. In making it easier for employees to learn about SAP’s various social and environmental investments and take action as volunteers, the new Moments of Service campaign will become a more effective lever for change and create more space for empathy and inclusive leadership.</p>
  <p>In the words of SAP CEO Christian Klein, “I’m excited about how this new campaign will make it even easier for all of us to find new ways to live SAP’s purpose and make a positive and lasting impact on the communities in which we live and work!”</p>
  <p>Upon announcing the change to employees, SAP is already seeing excitement about the Moments of Service evolution and engagement with the campaign. We look forward to continuing year-round moments of impact that benefit our employees, our company, and our world.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/moments-of-service</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>