<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/enterprise-asset-management/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Roche Connects Asset Data to Contextualize and Improve Every Decision]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/roche-asset-data-contextualize-improve-decisions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/roche-asset-data-contextualize-improve-decisions</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical company Roche has been improving its asset management and maintenance processes with the help of SAP solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f4368188f69034eaee3b53188d1e3cd047f4908b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f4368188f69034eaee3b53188d1e3cd047f4908b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f4368188f69034eaee3b53188d1e3cd047f4908b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Roche Connects Asset Data to Contextualize and Improve Every Decision" src="./media_1f4368188f69034eaee3b53188d1e3cd047f4908b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="roche-connects-asset-data-to-contextualize-and-improve-every-decision">Roche Connects Asset Data to Contextualize and Improve Every Decision</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In a recent webinar, Iago Accioli, project manager of Assets at Roche, discussed how the pharmaceutical company has been improving its asset management and maintenance processes from a broader supply chain perspective.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="https://www.roche.com/about/">Roche</a> is one of the world’s largest biotech companies, a leading provider of in-vitro diagnostics and a global supplier of transformative, innovative solutions across major disease areas.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="find-a-balance-between-performance-cost-and-risk-with-sap-asset-performance-management">Find a balance between performance, cost, and risk with SAP Asset Performance Management</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/apm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="cost-as-a-main-driver-for-asset-intensive-organizations">Cost as a Main Driver for Asset-Intensive Organizations</h2>
  <p>“As a pharmaceutical company, Roche was founded more than 100 years ago in Basel, Switzerland, with both pharma and diagnostics divisions. We are in the middle of an <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA</a> journey with the goal to harmonize business processes on all sites and divisions around the world,” said Accioli.</p>
  <p>To <a href="/topics/asset-management">manage assets</a> under volatile conditions effectively, just like other asset-intensive organizations, Roche focuses on <strong>reducing maintenance cost</strong> and <strong>increasing asset reliability</strong>, which are key to its customers and patients.</p>
  <p>The challenge is “the handover from original manufacturer to engineering to maintenance and how to interact with each other,” explained Accioli. “We resolve this with these business process harmonization initiatives.”</p>
  <h2 id="risk-resilience-as-an-investment-for-the-future">Risk Resilience as an Investment for the Future</h2>
  <p>SAP suggests three strategies to help companies manage their business holistically, including cost, speed, profit, customer service, and risk:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Connecting supply chains</strong> to the entire business so that information insight flows go quickly from operations to manufacturing, design, and into the business to respond to disruptions</li>
    <li><strong>Contextualizing information</strong> during the work process to equip users with technology to get real-time insights and make decisions during the business process to increase impact</li>
    <li><strong>Collaborating externally</strong> with suppliers, asset operators, OEMs, and logistics providers to ensure that information is flowing beyond the internal network to set up a risk-resilient business while mitigating risk</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="closing-the-loop-between-strategy-and-execution">Closing the Loop Between Strategy and Execution</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-a-video-to-learn-more-about-enterprise-asset-management">Watch a video to learn more about enterprise asset management</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2020/10/9870e39a-b97d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Managing costs and increasing equipment reliability is a major factor and closing the loop between asset strategy and maintenance execution, such as to make assets more reliable and connected to maintenance execution considering different asset type, is a big opportunity.</p>
  <p>“Five to 10 years ago, reliability engineering became a shining topic at Roche, and we discussed where to start, how much we spend on maintenance, what our most important assets were, and where we should spend more energy and money. We standardized processes to classify our equipment into different asset criticalities – high, medium, and low – and, based on each category, we established a maintenance strategy,” explained Accioli.</p>
  <p>“Afterwards, we looked for a tool that would best suit Roche given the amount of data. Now we have an asset and maintenance strategy in place that is reflected in our system. In 2019, we started harmonizing our processes and were pleased that SAP solutions could support us,” he continued.</p>
  <p>In particular, Roche looked to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/asset-strategy-performance.html">SAP Asset Strategy and Performance Management</a>, which helps with performing criticality evaluations directly in the SAP system instead of spreadsheets. With criticality results reflected in the system, the maintenance strategy can result in preventive maintenance plans. “Roche is in the middle of the journey. No sites are live yet,” said Accioli. Roche is also enabling access to its service providers to get design insights and improve collaboration.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/asset-manager.html">SAP Service and Asset Manager</a>, which enables maintenance plans and work orders to be accessible to maintenance technicians so that they can make instant material reservations and get access to maintenance manuals on mobile devices.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>“I expect a significant <strong>decrease of maintenance execution</strong> as we can plan our work better thanks to a mobile-supported solution,” said Accioli. “The experience with the solution is quite good.”</p>
  <p>Roche was already using SAP at different sites with its own work order types and data model, but it was not automated and connected.</p>
  <p>“We also intend to migrate to <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/apm.html">SAP Asset Performance Management</a>, a successor cloud-based application, where Roche’s enhancement ideas have been incorporated,” explained the manager.</p>
  <h2 id="connected-asset-data-helps-contextualize-business-decisions">Connected Asset Data Helps Contextualize Business Decisions</h2>
  <p>For contextualizing every business process through the eyes of maintenance, it is necessary to converge enterprise IT data with equipment and sensor data to run analyses based on algorithms and machine learning technology. Accioli explained: “Being able to schedule maintenance activities is a substantial improvement for maintenance organizations. To monitor both targets and results, we are using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics/features.html">SAP Analytics Cloud</a>, which has many good capabilities. We are developing maintenance KPIs with the insights we get from artificial intelligence (AI) and rolling these back into the asset strategy and reliability process. These are particularly good tools.”</p>
  <h2 id="effective-collaboration-across-the-ecosystem-to-build-a-collaborative-supply-chain">Effective Collaboration Across the Ecosystem to Build a Collaborative Supply Chain</h2>
  <p>“For Roche, sharing information and effective collaboration with asset providers and across our ecosystem is particularly important. Vendors and different equipment suppliers must exchange and collaborate on asset data. Operators and service providers should be able to use the network but also manage the work order process,” said Accioli.</p>
  <p>To summarize, the key benefits of SAP Asset Strategy and Performance Management and SAP Service and Asset Manager Accioli sees are:</p>
  <p><strong>SAP Asset Strategy and Performance Management:</strong></p>
  <ul>
    <li>Defining which maintenance strategy applies to which classification of equipment</li>
    <li>Maintaining assessments in the system</li>
    <li>Generating criticality based on assessments</li>
    <li>Reflecting reliability-centered maintenance in the system, including decision trees and supportive templates</li>
  </ul>
  <p><strong>SAP Service and Asset Manager:</strong></p>
  <ul>
    <li>Being a digitized, automated, paperless solution</li>
    <li>Being able to work offline</li>
    <li>Having all maintenance data at hand in one place</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Listen to the webinar recording <a href="https://event.on24.com/eventRegistration/console/apollox/mainEvent?&#x26;eventid=4174635&#x26;sessionid=1&#x26;username=&#x26;partnerref=&#x26;format=fhvideo1&#x26;mobile=&#x26;flashsupportedmobiledevice=&#x26;helpcenter=&#x26;key=56D188F6DDC0731803732D04D9287E5F&#x26;newConsole=true&#x26;nxChe=true&#x26;newTabCon=true&#x26;consoleEarEventConsole=false&#x26;text_language_id=en&#x26;playerwidth=748&#x26;playerheight=526&#x26;eventuserid=616413864&#x26;contenttype=A&#x26;mediametricsessionid=533671932&#x26;mediametricid=5886174&#x26;usercd=616413864&#x26;mode=launch">here</a>. In addition, watch this <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/asset-management-eam.html?video=9870e39a-b97d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff">overview video</a> to learn how to maximize asset health and performance with SAP Intelligent Asset Management solutions and read what <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2022/09/77fdedf5-7bbb-4ed6-bc18-1d3febe209ca.html">benefits other enterprises achieved</a>. To know more about the role of service and asset management in your industry, <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/idc-info-brief-on-service-excellence/index.html">download this complimentary paper from IDC</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Karin Fent is senior director of Global Customer Success Digital Supply Chain at SAP.</em><br><em>Top photo credit: Roche</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/asset-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-asset-management</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How a European Utilities Company Makes Maintenance More Efficient, Transparent, and Cost-Effective]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/european-utilities-company-retipiu-makes-maintenance-efficient-transparent-cost-effective</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/european-utilities-company-retipiu-makes-maintenance-efficient-transparent-cost-effective</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read to learn how Retipiù is increasing productivity and improving customer service with smart asset maintenance using SAP solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16f49651583a397641725139ac5d57886a78fc80f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16f49651583a397641725139ac5d57886a78fc80f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16f49651583a397641725139ac5d57886a78fc80f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How a European Utilities Company Makes Maintenance More Efficient, Transparent, and Cost-Effective" src="./media_16f49651583a397641725139ac5d57886a78fc80f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-a-european-utilities-company-makes-maintenance-more-efficient-transparent-and-cost-effective">How a European Utilities Company Makes Maintenance More Efficient, Transparent, and Cost-Effective</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The Italian natural gas and electricity provider RetiPiù S.r.l. is in charge of 2,900 kilometers of gas and electricity networks that serve homes, businesses, and public spaces in 25 towns across the northern Italian province of Monza and Brianza.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="maximize-asset-health-and-performance-with-sap-intelligent-asset-management-software">Maximize asset health and performance with SAP Intelligent Asset Management software</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/supply-chain-management/asset-management-eam.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="managing-ever-complex-asset-networks-at-minimum-cost">Managing Ever Complex Asset Networks at Minimum Cost</h2>
  <p>As these networks grow and become more complex, RetiPiù must ensure safety and reliability through daily maintenance performed by its field workers. It is also crucial for them to quickly identify critical network events and efficiently prioritize, schedule, and track field-service assignments and maintenance activities.</p>
  <p>But disparate asset management systems made it hard to prioritize and schedule maintenance calls. In addition, they were not integrated with the company’s core enterprise resource planning (ERP) system.</p>
  <h2 id="moving-from-reactive-to-predictive-maintenance">Moving from Reactive to Predictive Maintenance</h2>
  <p>To increase efficiency and optimize resources, RetiPiù looked to move from a reactive to a predictive maintenance model. The goal was to understand critical events as early as possible, track and trace issues from alert to resolution, get better visibility into maintenance schedules and work-order status, and use that information to better manage maintenance across the network.</p>
  <p>To meet these goals, RetiPiù required a <strong>unified <a href="/topics/intelligent-asset-management">intelligent asset maintenance</a> system</strong> that workers could access from the field and that was integrated with its intelligent ERP software.</p>
  <h2 id="one-central-asset-intelligence-system-to-speed-up-maintenance-cycles-and-lower-costs">One Central Asset Intelligence System to Speed up Maintenance Cycles and Lower Costs</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-industry-40-intelligent-assets-report">Read the Industry 4.0 Intelligent Assets Report</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/intelligent-assets/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As its utilities networks continue to grow, RetiPiù S.r.l. deployed <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a> to help improve data quality and access for engineers and back-office teams. Building on that digital transformation, it then added the SAP Enterprise Asset Management solution to help configure digital twins for equipment and activate predictive models respectively. These algorithms help assess and prioritize maintenance requirements and optimize resources. The company leverages the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/iot-data-services.html">SAP Internet of Things (SAP IoT)</a> solution to gather detailed sensor data from across the network assets to share information via mobile applications with field technicians, who get information and update the status of work orders in real time.</p>
  <h2 id="increasing-productivity-and-improving-customer-service-with-smarter-asset-maintenance">Increasing Productivity and Improving Customer Service with Smarter Asset Maintenance</h2>
  <p>The system currently supports thousands of pieces of equipment. In addition to making maintenance simpler and more efficient, asset and maintenance data – including cost data – are immediately available for analysis in <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a>. As a public utility, the real beneficiaries are RetiPiù customers that now have faster activation service. And in addition, RetiPiù benefits by being rewarded by the Italian government for its continually reliable service.</p>
  <p>The most <strong>striking benefits</strong> the utilities company gained are:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>100% increase in assets that can be managed on the network – from 12,000 to 24,000 pieces of equipment</li>
    <li>50% reduction in maintenance cost</li>
    <li>15%-20% less time needed to activate new gas customers</li>
    <li>Increased efficiency and resource optimization</li>
    <li>Improved prioritization of field-service assignments and maintenance tasks</li>
    <li>Improved field operations effectiveness through mobile system access to maintenance staff</li>
    <li>One single platform to manage data and analytics for all assets – creating a fully integrated and transparent maintenance process from order to the field and back</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="real-time-data-transfer-from-technician-mobile-apps-to-back-end-erp-systems">Real-Time Data Transfer from Technician Mobile Apps to Back-End ERP Systems</h2>
  <p>“In choosing an intelligent, predictive maintenance solution, integration with our core ERP systems was key. With <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/supply-chain-management/asset-management-eam.html">SAP Intelligent Asset Management</a>, we have <strong>one unified system</strong> that provides everyone the visibility they need to work efficiently and effectively,” says Massimo De Filippi, director of Technical and Information Services and Design at RetiPiù S.r.l.</p>
  <p>He continues: “This project has allowed RetiPiù to ensure service continuity and avoid shutdowns. We can provide quality service while also reducing costs. We are a public company, so the ultimate benefit is for the citizens.”</p>
  <p>“By being able to access data and reports in real time, field engineers can intervene promptly whenever issues arise, improving the customer experience and strengthening our reputation as a trusted energy provider,” says Mario Carlo Borgotti, managing director of RetiPiù.</p>
  <p>In regard to future plans and after being live with the gas network, RetiPiù now has a template for rolling out intelligent asset management and predictive maintenance to its electricity and public lighting networks. As the next step, it will enable simulation of maintenance requirements for new assets that have yet to be added and include geolocation services for route optimization.</p>
  <p>To learn more about how to enable intelligent asset management processes, <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/intelligent-assets/index.html">download the report</a>, “The Building Blocks of Industry 4.0 with Intelligent Assets.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Karin Fent is senior director of Global Customer Success Digital Supply Chain at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/asset-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-asset-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>