<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/ibm/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IBM and SAP Plan to Expand Collaboration to Help Clients Become Next-Generation Enterprises with Generative AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/ibm-and-sap-generative-ai-new-value-generation-partnership</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/ibm-and-sap-generative-ai-new-value-generation-partnership</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New Value Generation partnership from SAP and IBM includes new generative AI capabilities and industry-specific cloud solutions. Read the news]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aeeb46bbfcb4f664eb2a3c5eaebfbd24570cce9b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aeeb46bbfcb4f664eb2a3c5eaebfbd24570cce9b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1aeeb46bbfcb4f664eb2a3c5eaebfbd24570cce9b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="IBM and SAP Plan to Expand Collaboration to Help Clients Become Next-Generation Enterprises with Generative AI" src="./media_1aeeb46bbfcb4f664eb2a3c5eaebfbd24570cce9b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="ibm-and-sap-plan-to-expand-collaboration-to-help-clients-become-next-generation-enterprises-with-generative-ai">IBM and SAP Plan to Expand Collaboration to Help Clients Become Next-Generation Enterprises with Generative AI</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>New Value Generation partnership initiative focused on delivering greater client productivity and innovation with new generative AI capabilities and industry-specific cloud solutions</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <p><strong><em>WALLDORF and ARMONK</em></strong></p>
                <hr>
                <p>IBM (NYSE: <a href="http://www.ibm.com/investor">IBM</a>) and <a href="http://sap.com">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced their vision for the next era of their collaboration, which includes new <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/generative-ai.html">generative AI</a> capabilities and industry-specific cloud solutions that can help clients unlock business value.</p>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="unlock-new-capabilities-with-generative-ai">Unlock new capabilities with generative AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/generative-ai.html">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“IBM and SAP’s shared approach to generative AI, built on an open ecosystem, trust and purpose-built models, will help empower clients to optimize business outcomes,” said John Granger, Senior Vice President, IBM Consulting. “Our new Value Generation partnership initiative will enable clients to accelerate the path to innovation, competitive advantage and become a next generation enterprise through generative AI.”</p>
  <p>“It makes perfect sense to expand our partnership with IBM to help more customers accelerate their cloud journey leveraging RISE with SAP and realize the transformative benefits of generative AI for business in the cloud,” said Scott Russell, Chief Revenue Officer &#x26; Executive Board Member, Customer Success of SAP SE. “This expanded partnership will help more of our joint customers reach new heights by innovating through the cloud, data and business AI to grow and transform their businesses.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.ibm.com/consulting">IBM Consulting</a> and SAP aim to accelerate transformation enabled by RISE with SAP by supporting clients in the following key areas:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Next-Generation AI Business Processes</strong>: Together, the companies are exploring opportunities to build new generative AI capabilities for RISE with SAP and infuse AI into SAP business processes across industry-specific cloud solutions and line of business applications. Initially, IBM plans to extend AI capabilities across SAP’s portfolio of cloud solutions and applications, all of which are underpinned by SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP). This includes RISE with SAP, the GROW with SAP solution, financial solutions for the office of the CFO, supply chain management solutions, solutions for human capital management, SAP Customer Experience solutions and intelligent spend management solutions. IBM also plans to leverage SAP Signavio and SAP Business AI solutions to help define next-generation business processes through a proof-of-concept adoption program.</li>
    <li><strong>Next-Generation Industry Innovation</strong>: IBM and SAP plan to build intelligent industry use cases, enabled by data-driven insights, into end-to-end business processes to fuel next-generation industry innovation. These use cases will initially focus on the industrial manufacturing, consumer packaged goods (CPG), retail, defense, automotive and utilities industries. This includes IBM’s recent work with SAP to develop new AI solutions for the CPG and retail industries. As part of this initiative, IBM has begun the development of an extensive portfolio of over 100 AI solutions across industry, line-of-business and product delivery. In addition, IBM plans to develop prescriptive industry value maps that define next-generation business processes and opportunities for impact with AI. Clients will be able to access all of these new AI solutions through the global <a href="https://www.ibm.com/about/innovation-studio">IBM Innovation Studios</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation.html">SAP Experience Center</a> sites.</li>
    <li><strong>Next-Generation Platform Architecture and Customer Adoption Approach</strong>: Next-generation enterprises require next-generation platform architectures and a modernized approach to customer adoption. Through the Value Generation partnership initiative, IBM intends to provide next-generation reference architectures that enable a clean core approach. To do this, IBM plans to leverage SAP BTP, SAP Signavio and LeanIX solutions. These new reference architectures will help define standards across data, process, systems and device integration, process orchestration and automation. IBM consultants supporting clients on SAP projects can also leverage IBM Consulting Advantage, IBM’s AI services platform, and its portfolio of proprietary methods, assets and Assistants to bring more repeatability and consistency to client delivery. With IBM Consulting Advantage, IBM consultants can transform the way they deliver SAP solutions to boost productivity and mitigate risk by leveraging generative AI to help complete tasks like generation of user stories, test scripts, training and change management content and code creation.</li>
    <li><strong>Next-Generation Ecosystem Expansion</strong>: IBM and SAP plan to partner around their respective employee network groups and “next-gen” communities, such as the business women’s networks at IBM and SAP, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/next-gen-innovation-platform/university-alliances.html">SAP University Alliances</a> program and the <a href="https://jobs.sap.com/content/Military-Veterans/?locale=en_US">Veterans to Work</a> program of SAP and Veterans at IBM to increase the SAP solutions experience in the consulting workforce and develop the next generation of talent. The companies also plan to explore new ways to collaborate on social impact programs, such as training at- risk youth in the IT sector and accelerating the integration of social businesses into global supply chains.</li>
    <li><strong>watsonx Planned Availability on the Generative AI Hub</strong>: IBM Granite Model Series are expected to be accessible for use across SAP’s portfolio of cloud solutions and applications – which is underpinned by the generative AI hub in SAP AI Core. The generative AI hub facilitates relevant, reliable and responsible business AI and provides instant access to a broad range of large language models (LLMs). This expands on IBM and SAP’s collaboration around <a href="https://newsroom.ibm.com/2023-05-02-SAP-to-Embed-IBM-Watson-Artificial-Intelligence-into-SAP-R-Solutions">embedding IBM Watson AI technology into SAP solutions</a>. To further highlight watsonx.ai Granite capabilities, IBM Consulting plans to build extensions using the model on the generative AI hub for select customers.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>This initiative will build on the companies’ over 50-year collaboration based on deep technology, industry and domain expertise and demonstrates the two organizations’ joint commitment to continue to evolve to put clients first and meet market demand.</p>
  <p>IBM Consulting accelerates business transformation for our clients through hybrid cloud and AI technologies, leveraging our open ecosystem of partners. With deep industry and business expertise spanning strategy, experience design, technology, and operations, we have become the trusted partner to the world’s most innovative and valuable companies, helping modernize and secure their most complex systems. Our 160,000 consultants embrace an open way of working and apply our proven, collaborative engagement model, IBM Garage, to scale ideas into outcomes. As the only major global systems integrator inside a technology company, we don’t just advise – we invent and build what’s next together with our clients. Find out more at <a href="http://ibm.com/consulting">IBM.com/consulting</a>.</p>
  <p>To learn more about the Value Generation partnership initiative, visit <a href="https://www.ibm.com/info/sap-value-generation">ibm.com/info/sap-value-generation</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About IBM</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>IBM is a leading provider of global hybrid cloud and AI, and consulting expertise. We help clients in more than 175 countries capitalize on insights from their data, streamline business processes, reduce costs and gain the competitive edge in their industries. More than 4,000 government and corporate entities in critical infrastructure areas such as financial services, telecommunications and healthcare rely on IBM’s hybrid cloud platform and Red Hat OpenShift to effect their digital transformations quickly, efficiently and securely. IBM’s breakthrough innovations in AI, quantum computing, industry-specific cloud solutions and consulting deliver open and flexible options to our clients. All of this is backed by IBM’s commitment to trust, transparency, responsibility, inclusivity and service.</p>
  <p>Visit <a href="http://www.ibm.com/">www.ibm.com</a> for more information.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE:SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Scott Malinowski, SAP, +1 (781) 852-3822, <a href="mailto:scott.malinowski@sap.com">scott.malinowski@sap.com</a><br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a><br>Jamee Nelson, IBM, <a href="mailto:jamee.nelson@ibm.com">jamee.nelson@ibm.com</a></p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-power-of-sap-partners-who-drive-customer-success-delivering-trusted-advice-and-deep-product-knowledge">Learn more about the power of SAP partners, who drive customer success, delivering trusted advice and deep product knowledge</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/partners.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/ibm</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Starts Pilot with Accenture and IBM to Co-Validate SAP Expertise for Advanced Professionals]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/accenture-ibm-pilot-co-validate-sap-expertise</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/accenture-ibm-pilot-co-validate-sap-expertise</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A new pilot to co-validate SAP expertise, with first partners Accenture and IBM, is paving the way for career growth and business success.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>news-tag/ibm</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-partner-connect</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP to Embed IBM Watson Artificial Intelligence into SAP Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/ibm-watson-artificial-intelligence-in-sap-solutions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/ibm-watson-artificial-intelligence-in-sap-solutions</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[IBM Watson will be embedded into SAP solutions to provide new AI-driven insights and automation to help accelerate innovation. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c4f9b2f04042262bfb08bc930ea7f153a5ce1e32.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c4f9b2f04042262bfb08bc930ea7f153a5ce1e32.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c4f9b2f04042262bfb08bc930ea7f153a5ce1e32.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP to Embed IBM Watson Artificial Intelligence into SAP Solutions" src="./media_1c4f9b2f04042262bfb08bc930ea7f153a5ce1e32.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-to-embed-ibm-watson-artificial-intelligence-into-sap-solutions">SAP to Embed IBM Watson Artificial Intelligence into SAP Solutions</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="realize-your-potential-with-business-ai">Realize your potential with business AI</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF and ARMONK</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) and IBM (NYSE: IBM) today announced that IBM Watson technology will be embedded into SAP solutions to provide new AI-driven insights and automation to help accelerate innovation and create more efficient and effective user experiences across the SAP application portfolio.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP will use IBM Watson capabilities to power its digital assistant in SAP Start, which provides a unified entry point for cloud solutions from SAP. With SAP Start, users can search for, launch and interactively engage with apps provided in cloud solutions from SAP and SAP S/4HANA Cloud. New AI capabilities in SAP Start will be designed to help users boost productivity with both natural language capabilities and predictive insights using IBM Watson AI solutions built on IBM’s trust and transparency and data privacy principles.</p>
  <p>“This milestone collaboration with IBM aims to provide SAP customers a better user experience, faster decision-making and greater insights to help transform their business processes,” said Christian Klein, CEO and Member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “Working together to incorporate additional AI, machine learning and other intelligent technologies into SAP solutions can lead to better business outcomes for our joint customers. Today’s news, along with the recent news of our expanded use of Red Hat Enterprise Linux, is a prime example of how the rich, 50-year partnership between our companies continues to grow stronger and move the industry forward.”</p>
  <p>New digital assistant capabilities in SAP Start will be extended across SAP solutions to help answer diverse questions for managers and employees. By automating and speeding up common tasks, the capabilities are designed to help unlock employee productivity to focus on more strategic work. SAP Start will allow customers to benefit from intelligence at the point of decision-making with the ability to use AI and machine learning to extract information from a variety of data sources and answer user questions across lines of business. Today, <a href="https://www.ibm.com/products/environmental-intelligence-suite">IBM technology</a> currently available in the TripIt mobile app from SAP Concur is helping nearly 13 million users easily access AI-derived weather insights to make more sustainable travel choices before and during their trips.</p>
  <p>IBM delivers market-leading AI capabilities with Watson products deployed by more than 100 million users across 20 industries. In addition, SAP and IBM Consulting are currently supporting customers with 25 joint intelligent industry solutions that use IBM Watson capabilities underpinned by <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP). These industry solutions help customers across industries such as retail, manufacturing and utilities accelerate their business transformation and use data to make more informed decisions.</p>
  <p>“IBM and SAP are joining forces to give businesses new and exciting ways to harness the transformative power of AI and use it as a source of competitive advantage,” said Arvind Krishna, IBM Chairman and Chief Executive Officer. “With this announcement, we are infusing IBM Watson’s powerful, enterprise-grade AI capabilities into SAP’s leading ERP platform to help businesses reimagine customer experiences, boost productivity and fuel growth.”</p>
  <p>In addition to natively embedding IBM Watson AI capabilities into SAP solutions, SAP and IBM are collaborating on generative AI and large language models aimed to deliver consistent continuous learning and automation based on SAP’s mission-critical application suite.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>About IBM</strong></p>
  <p>IBM is a leading global hybrid cloud and AI, and business services provider, helping clients in more than 175 countries capitalize on insights from their data, streamline business processes, reduce costs and gain the competitive edge in their industries. Nearly 3,800 government and corporate entities in critical infrastructure areas such as financial services, telecommunications and healthcare rely on IBM’s hybrid cloud platform and Red Hat OpenShift to affect their digital transformations quickly, efficiently, and securely. IBM’s breakthrough innovations in AI, quantum computing, industry-specific cloud solutions and business services deliver open and flexible options to our clients. All of this is backed by IBM’s legendary commitment to trust, transparency, responsibility, inclusivity, and service. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.ibm.com">www.ibm.com</a>. Statements regarding IBM’s future direction and intent are subject to change or withdrawal without notice and represent goals and objectives only.</p>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong></p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent, sustainable enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Alex Vaught, +1 (425) 590-0844, <a href="mailto:alex.vaught@sap.com">alex.vaught@sap.com</a>, PT<br>Holli Haswell, +1 (720) 396 5485, <a href="mailto:hhaswell@us.ibm.com">hhaswell@us.ibm.com</a>, CT<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2021 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2023 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/ibm</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How ERP Is Breaking Down Silos and Driving Sustainable Change]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sustainability-and-erp-breaking-down-silos-driving-change</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sustainability-and-erp-breaking-down-silos-driving-change</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Sustainability and ERP go hand in hand, and IBM and SAP bring together technologies, services, and platforms to help break down silos.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/ibm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insights from SAP and IBM: Building an Efficient, Resilient Organization]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/sap-and-ibm-insights-efficient-resilient-organization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/sap-and-ibm-insights-efficient-resilient-organization</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and IBM shared insights building efficient, resilient organizations at the Forbes event, Strategies for a Resilient Future. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/ibm</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IBM Transforms Business Operations with the RISE with SAP Solution in Expanded Partnership with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/expanded-ibm-partnership-rise-with-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/expanded-ibm-partnership-rise-with-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With an expanded IBM partnership, SAP technology is helping fuel the company’s growth and better support clients. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/ibm</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Superpower Summit: Tech Giants Join Forces in Manufacturing Industry Rescue]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/ibm-sap-join-forces-manufacturing-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/ibm-sap-join-forces-manufacturing-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[IBM utilized a variety of SAP products to create its Connected Plant solution, which makes manufacturing processes more efficient.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a2eb52edcb5cb4575ac4d41bcd0e183eaafc56fc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a2eb52edcb5cb4575ac4d41bcd0e183eaafc56fc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a2eb52edcb5cb4575ac4d41bcd0e183eaafc56fc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Superpower Summit: Tech Giants Join Forces in Manufacturing Industry Rescue" src="./media_1a2eb52edcb5cb4575ac4d41bcd0e183eaafc56fc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="superpower-summit-tech-giants-join-forces-in-manufacturing-industry-rescue">Superpower Summit: Tech Giants Join Forces in Manufacturing Industry Rescue</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Even before <a href="/topics/covid-19">COVID-19</a> and the supply chain crisis hit, two global tech pioneers were surveying the state of manufacturing, aware that there were problems that had to be addressed quickly.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Manufacturing operations were woefully lacking in real-time visibility. During manufacturing execution, process data could not be automatically captured. Tracking worker safety remained an elusive goal. The absence of an end-to-end perspective meant that it was difficult to understand process effectiveness and make quick, crucial decisions, compromising future planning.</p>
  <p>Under these circumstances, continuously and effectively running a manufacturing operation was a challenge – as was providing added value to customers. And during COVID-19, the absence of available shop floor operators only made the situation worse.</p>
  <p>Desperately needed was a smart and intuitive solution to execute, monitor, and analyze the end-to-end manufacturing process, starting with planning and extending all the way to inventory. Updates on labor planning and worker safety would have to be provided in real time.</p>
  <p>This would particularly benefit servitized industries, in which outcome is now directly related to the revenue situation.</p>
  <p>Additionally, the solution would need to be intelligent enough to evaluate data, consider a variety of business scenarios, and propose the best future actions.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-ibms-sap-innovation-awards-pitch-deck">Explore IBM's SAP Innovation Awards pitch deck</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2414">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="a-leading-edge-alliance">A Leading-Edge Alliance</h2>
  <p>Since 1911, technology and innovation trailblazer IBM had been creating responsive, resilient, next-generation solutions to the challenges of the day. One hundred years and a decade later, that movement still continues.</p>
  <p>Now, the company merged forces with the market leader in enterprise application software: SAP.</p>
  <p>The two established their first Global Alliance Partnership in 1989. But their relationship dated back to the founding of SAP in 1972 – by five former IBM employees.</p>
  <p>In recent years, as customer needs shifted to the cloud, SAP and IBM had been working together to accelerate the digital revolution, using such technologies as machine learning, artificial intelligence (AI), digital twin – virtual representations of physical objects or processes – and Internet of Things (IoT) sensors.</p>
  <p>With global lockdowns and associated disruptions impacting the world in the summer of 2020, the two corporations announced the next stage of their alliance, branding it the Evolution Partnership initiative.</p>
  <p>The manufacturing effort topped their list.</p>
  <h2 id="informed-real-time-decisions">Informed, Real-Time Decisions</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="digital-manufacturing-solutions-are-the-future-of-productivity">Digital manufacturing solutions are the future of productivity</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/supply-chain-management/manufacturing.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Indeed, the Connected Plant solution created by the two companies would enable real-time manufacturing execution planning and tracking and provide automated reporting of machine and process data.</p>
  <p>The innovation could be used to ensure that the proper equipment was being provided and certify both quality inspection and cognitive worker guidance. When defects were detected, a repair order would be automatically generated.</p>
  <p>From this point forward, guesswork was no longer required to make informed business decisions. Instead, conclusions were based on managers’ instant accessibility to end-to-end analytics and up-to-date key performance indicators (KPIs).</p>
  <h2 id="seamless-and-integrated">Seamless and Integrated</h2>
  <p>With the seamlessly integrated manufacturing tool, new possibilities abounded. The Connected Plant solution allowed managers to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>View manufacturing and production orders for every shift</li>
    <li>Ensure that all needed components were available</li>
    <li>Execute tasks with a few simple words via chatbot</li>
    <li>Detect deficiencies during quality inspections</li>
    <li>Confirm assembly and sub-assembly completion</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Today, with the world struggling to compensate for supply chain gaps, the Connected Plant platform is being utilized to provide supplies and drive continuous planning across resource networks.</p>
  <p>And both SAP and IBM are prepared to revise the solution as business models evolve and processes are reconfigured in areas like energy, natural resource consumption, and emissions management.</p>
  <p>“To compete in a highly disruptive and rapidly evolving world, companies require the ability to rewire their organizations to create efficient, automated business processes – applying advanced technologies to transform static, siloed processes into agile, intelligent workflows,” said Mark Foster, IBM Services senior vice president.</p>
  <p>As the Connected Plant solution continued to expand the number of tasks it could perform, IBM was honored as a finalist in the 2021 SAP Innovation Awards, a yearly ceremony commemorating organizations using SAP products to transform business and society.</p>
  <p>To learn more about IBM’s smart and intuitive solution, be sure to check out its SAP Innovation Awards <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2414">pitch deck</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Keith E. Greenberg is an SAP global marketing contributor.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/ibm</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IBM and SAP Strengthen Partnership to Help Clients Move Workloads from SAP Solutions to the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/ibm-and-sap-strengthen-partnership-move-workloads-to-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/ibm-and-sap-strengthen-partnership-move-workloads-to-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[IBM and SAP will make it easier for clients to embrace a hybrid cloud approach and move mission-critical workloads to the cloud.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e788976dfc0194582bcc3b8555b608645549ef68.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e788976dfc0194582bcc3b8555b608645549ef68.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e788976dfc0194582bcc3b8555b608645549ef68.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="IBM and SAP Strengthen Partnership to Help Clients Move Workloads from SAP Solutions to the Cloud" src="./media_1e788976dfc0194582bcc3b8555b608645549ef68.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="ibm-and-sap-strengthen-partnership-to-help-clients-move-workloads-from-sap-solutions-to-the-cloud">IBM and SAP Strengthen Partnership to Help Clients Move Workloads from SAP Solutions to the Cloud</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong><em>ARMONK, N.Y. and WALLDORF</em></strong> — IBM (NYSE: <a href="https://www.ibm.com/investor">IBM</a>) today announced it is teaming with <a href="http://www.sap.com">SAP</a> (NYSE: SAP) to provide technology and consulting expertise to make it easier for clients to embrace a hybrid cloud approach and move mission-critical workloads from SAP solutions to the cloud for regulated and non-regulated industries.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="rise-with-sap-transform-your-business-in-the-way-that-works-best-for-you">RISE with SAP: Transform your business in the way that works best for you</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/rise.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="ibm-is-the-first-partner-to-offercloud-infrastructure-and-technical-managedservices-as-part-of-the-rise-with-sap-offering">IBM is the first partner to offercloud infrastructure and technical managedservices as part of the RISE with SAP offering</h2>
  <p>As clients look to adopt hybrid cloud strategies, moving the workloads and applications that are the backbone of their enterprise operation requires a highly secured and reliable cloud environment. With today’s launch of the <a href="https://mediacenter.ibm.com/media/1_vac06lox">premium supplier option with IBM for RISE with SAP</a>, clients will have the tools to help accelerate the migration of their on-premise SAP software workloads to IBM Cloud, backed by industry-leading security capabilities.*</p>
  <p>IBM is also unveiling a new program, BREAKTHROUGH with IBM for RISE with SAP, a portfolio of solutions and consulting services that help accelerate and amplify the journey to SAP S/4HANA Cloud. Built on a flexible and scalable platform, the solutions and services use intelligent workflows to streamline operations. They provide an engagement model that helps plan, execute and support holistic business transformation. Clients are also offered the flexibility and choice to migrate SAP solution workloads to the public cloud with the support of deep industry expertise.</p>
  <p>Today’s announcement of IBM becoming a premium supplier makes IBM the first cloud provider to offer infrastructure, business transformation and application management services as part of RISE with SAP. IBM’s premium supplier designation is a continuation of SAP’s long-standing efforts to provide choice and optionality to customers and further support IBM customers that have a preference for their RISE with SAP package to run on IBM Cloud.</p>
  <p>Additionally, migration to SAP S/4HANA on IBM Cloud from on-premise data centers can potentially deliver the following benefits, according to a study by IDC, sponsored by IBM.**</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Return on investment: Migrating to SAP S/4HANA on IBM Cloud delivered <strong>revenue increases for up to 90%</strong> of organizations making the transition according to users surveyed.</li>
    <li>Reduced costs: More than <strong>80% of the organizations</strong> in the study said they experienced a reduction in operational costs.</li>
    <li>Greater productivity: <strong>9 out of 10 businesses</strong> in the study said they improved their productivity after migrating to SAP S/4HANA on IBM Cloud.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>“We are thrilled to advance our long-standing partnership through RISE with SAP,” said John Granger, Senior Vice President, IBM Consulting. “Our shared commitment is to meet our clients, especially those in highly regulated industries, where they are in their digital journey, while giving them choices for migrating or modernizing their mission-critical workloads with a hybrid cloud approach.”</p>
  <p>“BREAKTHROUGH with IBM is an outstanding complement to RISE with SAP as it lays the foundation for our customers to embark on or advance their business transformation journeys. Further, it reaffirms the value customers recognize from RISE with SAP and the impact and innovation opportunity RISE with SAP offers to organizations that move to the cloud. I have every confidence that the combined expertise and experience SAP and IBM offer will accelerate cloud adoption and business growth for customers across the globe,” said Brian Duffy, President of Cloud, SAP.</p>
  <p>IBM and SAP have worked with hundreds of clients globally on thousands of individual projects to modernize their systems and business processes based on an open, hybrid cloud approach. Recent examples include <a href="https://newsroom.ibm.com/2020-08-11-Coca-Cola-European-Partners-Signs-a-Multiyear-Agreement-with-IBM-to-Accelerate-its-Strategic-Transformation-Journey-with-Hybrid-Cloud">Coca-Cola European Partners</a>, <a href="https://newsroom.ibm.com/2021-04-22-Parle-Products-Worlds-Largest-Selling-Biscuit-Brand-Teams-with-IBM-to-Drive-Growth-Through-Hybrid-Cloud">Parle Products</a>, <a href="https://newsroom.ibm.com/2021-06-03-Harmont-Blaine-Chooses-IBM-Cloud-to-Support-the-Companys-Growth-in-the-Global-Markets">Harmont &#x26; Blaine</a>, <a href="https://in.newsroom.ibm.com/2021-10-07-Puravankara-IBM-collaboration">Puravankara Ltd</a> and <a href="https://newsroom.ibm.com/2021-10-13-Virgin-Megastore-in-Saudi-Arabia-to-Accelerate-Digital-Transformation-with-IBM-and-SAP">Virgin Megastore KSA</a>.</p>
  <p>Underscoring its commitment to SAP S/4HANA both as an SAP customer and a business partner for 50 years, IBM has also made a significant investment in RISE with SAP to help transform its own infrastructure. IBM is a new premium supplier for the RISE with SAP offering and is using the IBM Hybrid Cloud, including IBM Power–enabled Infrastructure as a Service, to enhance the performance, availability and security of deployments of private editions of SAP S/4HANA Cloud.</p>
  <p>To learn more about the BREAKTHROUGH with IBM program for the RISE with SAP offering, please visit: <a href="https://www.ibm.com/services/sap/rise-with-sap">ibm.com/services/sap/rise-with-sap</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>About IBM</strong></p>
  <p>IBM is a leading global hybrid cloud and AI, and business services provider. We help clients in more than 175 countries capitalize on insights from their data, streamline business processes, reduce costs and gain the competitive edge in their industries. Nearly 3,000 government and corporate entities in critical infrastructure areas such as financial services, telecommunications and healthcare rely on IBM’s hybrid cloud platform and Red Hat OpenShift to affect their digital transformations quickly, efficiently and securely. IBM’s breakthrough innovations in AI, quantum computing, industry-specific cloud solutions and business services deliver open and flexible options to our clients. All of this is backed by IBM’s legendary commitment to trust, transparency, responsibility, inclusivity and service. Visit <a href="http://www.ibm.com/">www.ibm.com</a> for more information.</p>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong></p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong> Stacy Ries, SAP, +1 (484) 619 0411, <a href="mailto:stacy.ries@sap.com">stacy.ries@sap.com</a><br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a><br>Lauren Nowicki, IBM, <a href="mailto:lauren.nowicki@ibm.com">lauren.nowicki@ibm.com</a></p>
  <p>*Based on IBM Hyper Protect Crypto Service, the only service in the industry built on FIPS 140-2 Level 4–certified hardware. FIPS 140-2 Level 4 provides the highest level of security defined in this standard. At this security level, the physical security mechanisms provide a comprehensive envelope of protection around the cryptographic module with the intent of detecting and responding to all unauthorized attempts at physical access.<br>**IDC White Paper, sponsored by IBM, Business Benefits Possible by Choosing the Right Cloud Provider to Run SAP Workloads. Doc #US47166220, December 2020.</p>
  <p><em>Statements regarding IBM’s future direction and intent are subject to change or withdrawal without notice and represent goals and objectives only.</em></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2020 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2022 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/ibm</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Power and Scale of a Global Sustainability Ecosystem]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/global-sustainability-ecosystem-power-scale</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/global-sustainability-ecosystem-power-scale</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hear from the SAP sustainability ecosystem about tackling challenges and delivering a path to innovation no individual competitor can match.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d6145a5beac2544e30db5fc832b0b98396b71881.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d6145a5beac2544e30db5fc832b0b98396b71881.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d6145a5beac2544e30db5fc832b0b98396b71881.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Power and Scale of a Global Sustainability Ecosystem" src="./media_1d6145a5beac2544e30db5fc832b0b98396b71881.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-power-and-scale-of-a-global-sustainability-ecosystem">The Power and Scale of a Global Sustainability Ecosystem</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>According to a recent <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/10/92351eae-017e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">SAP and Alpha Sense survey</a>, most businesses have not embedded sustainability into their core strategies. In some cases, corporations see sustainability management as a regulatory and compliance challenge rather than a strategic opportunity for economic and social growth.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Therefore, businesses run different technologies and end up operating in silos, which prevent them from connecting financial outcomes with non-financial metrics. Additionally, companies can view sustainability as an after-the-fact reporting activity without any influence in its executive decisions.</p>
  <p>Today, more than ever, businesses need to holistically manage their business models across their supply chains, operations, and people agenda.</p>
  <p>At the recent COP26 climate conference, <a href="/2021/11/cop26-reflections-enabling-business-action-and-planetary-ambition">business and government leaders agreed on the urgency</a> to reinvent their business models to accelerate sustainable business performance. Business leaders want to meet regulatory requirements, improve efficiency in their processes, and create responsible products and services.</p>
  <p>As the leading enterprise resource management company, SAP has committed to help customers in their digital transformation to make sustainability profitable and profitability sustainable.</p>
  <p>In this digital transformation, SAP’s approach is based on providing visibility and transparency to make sustainable decisions from the CEO’s office to the end user, connecting business processes to embed sustainability into all business functions — from carbon accounting to gender equality — and providing a global ecosystem of partners than can help SAP to scale impact through businesses of all sizes and across all industries around the world.</p>
  <p>Providing a global ecosystem to help businesses is core to SAP’s DNA.</p>
  <p>Julia White, chief marketing and solutions officer and member of the Executive Board at SAP SE, points out: “<a href="/">Sustainability is a team sport</a>. No company or organization can do it alone. We work with many of the world’s best companies who support our vision and work together with us every day to deliver sustainable outcomes for our customers.”</p>
  <p>Working with SAP, <a href="https://www.sap.com/partner.html">partners</a> advance market development for sustainable solutions. They turn ideas and imperatives into compelling paths to action that leverage SAP solutions. Together, we advocate with thought leadership and galvanize collective efforts and methodologies in industry forums like the World Economic Forum, World Business Council on Sustainable Development, and United Nations Organizations.</p>
  <p>SAP and its ecosystem accelerate sustainable innovation as a central element of the intelligent enterprise. Through co-innovation as well as solution and content partnerships, SAP brings more complete solutions to market faster, benefiting our customers and the planet. More broadly, SAP serves as a key player in a thriving ecosystem of sustainability innovation — helping customers more easily capitalize on emerging solutions that tie closely to their digital core. With its robust network, SAP can deliver a path to sustainability innovation that no other individual competitor can match.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th colspan="2">Promo</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <h3 id="choose-both-profitability-and-sustainability-with-sap">Choose both profitability and sustainability with SAP</h3>
              </td>
              <td><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability/economics.html">Learn more</a></strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <h2 id="accenture">Accenture</h2>
        <p>“With fewer than 2,000 working days left to 2030, the time to rewire business top to bottom to meet the UN Sustainable Development Goals is now. We are proud to expand our work with SAP, which includes launching SDG Ambition with UN Global Compact that over 700 companies have joined. By committing to put sustainability at the center of all we do and everyone we work with, together we can show companies how to tackle climate change, build circular economy practices, businesses, human rights and supply chains, and focus on data-driven measurement as well as accurately report ESG performance when delivering their commitments.”</p>
        <p><em>– Peter Lacy, Global Sustainability Services Lead, Chief Responsibility Officer and</em><br><em>Member of the Global Management Committee, Accenture</em></p>
        <h2 id="bearingpoint">BearingPoint</h2>
        <p>“Helping our clients meet their decarbonization targets has been one of our proven market offerings for more than 10 years. At BearingPoint, we not only calculate the product and corporate footprint of our clients, we also enable them to optimize the climate impact of every product across the entire life cycle. Providing end-to-end CO2 as a service is our core enabler for our clients. We at BearingPoint, as co-development partner for SAP Product Footprint Management, believe that together with SAP we can bring our vision to life: managing the ‘green line’ as equally as the financial bottom line. As partners, we go beyond business, making a positive impact on the climate.”</p>
        <p><em>– Donald Wachs, Head of IP-Assets and</em><br><em>Member of Management Committee, BearingPoint</em></p>
        <h2 id="capgemini">Capgemini</h2>
        <p>“Our ambitions are to act on climate change by being carbon neutral across our own operations by 2025 and across our supply chain by 2030, becoming a net-zero business well ahead of 2050, and to lead to low-carbon economic transition by helping our clients achieve their environmental commitments and save 10m tons of CO2eq globally by 2030. We cannot do this without our partner ecosystem. We are a strategic partner of SAP; by combining our deep industry knowledge, our human energy, and SAP’s world-class portfolio of enterprise and sustainability solutions, we commit to delivering on our promise to co-create a greener tomorrow with our clients.”</p>
        <p><em>– Aiman Ezzat, CEO, Capgemini</em></p>
        <h2 id="deloitte">Deloitte</h2>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th colspan="2">Promo</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <h3 id="sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises-taking-action-together">SAP Cloud for Sustainable Enterprises: Taking Action Together</h3>
              </td>
              <td><strong><a href="/">Learn more</a></strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>“The climate change emergency is unfolding in front of our eyes, touching all corners of the globe. The future of our people, planet, and profession depends on the business community taking measurable, decisive action on the climate crisis. Through our WorldClimate strategy, Deloitte will embed climate-smart considerations into our own operations, encourage our professionals to act on climate change at work and at home, and engage our broader ecosystem – including SAP – to create solutions that facilitate the transition to a low-carbon economy.”</p>
        <p><em>– Punit Renjen, Global CEO, Deloitte</em></p>
        <h2 id="ey">EY</h2>
        <p>“Sustainability is one of the defining issues of our time, and today there is an unprecedented opportunity to create value for all. Together with SAP and stakeholders around the globe, the EY organization is committed to making business work for sustainability and making sustainability work for business. Enterprises and people are inspired now more than ever to do the right thing — to collaborate, innovate, be inclusive, and accelerate to a more sustainable and equitable future.”</p>
        <p><em>– Steve Varley, Global Vice Chair – Sustainability, EY</em></p>
        <h2 id="ibm">IBM</h2>
        <p>“With five generations in the workplace, we are witnessing the birth of an era where technological innovation is being used to create social, economic, environmental, and business opportunities for all. Businesses of all sizes need to move from ambition to action and embrace radical thinking, like IBM’s commitment to achieve net-zero greenhouse gas emissions by 2030. We are partnering with SAP to operationalize sustainability for our customers and society using ethical innovation to build a world that is responsible, equitable, and leaves no one behind in net-zero transition. We are committed to furthering our decades-long work to address the global climate crisis.”</p>
        <p><em>– Sheri R. Hinish, Global Executive Partner, Enterprise Sustainability and</em><br><em>Sustainable Supply Chain Practice Leader, IBM</em></p>
        <h2 id="pwc">PwC</h2>
        <p>“PwC’s global sustainability network in over 60 countries is supporting organizations to deliver ESG-related outcomes across the globe. PwC works with clients to help them create their strategy, set targets, measure impact, and report on key performance indicators relevant to internal and external ESG drivers. Together with SAP, PwC is leveraging its ESG expertise to integrate and build strategic ESG solutions leveraging SAP technology. Organizations will benefit from these integrated solutions to help set and manage net-zero targets, define ESG strategies, and mitigate climate and ESG risks to deliver transparent investor-grade ESG reporting.”</p>
        <p><em>– Michael Rasch, Global SAP Alliance Leader, PwC Germany</em></p>
        <p><em>Bernd Schmalzridt is senior director of Global Business Development for Sustainability at SAP.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>news-tag/capgemini</category>
            <category>news-tag/deloitte</category>
            <category>news-tag/ey</category>
            <category>news-tag/ibm</category>
            <category>news-tag/pwc</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IBM and SAP to Help Financial Institutions Accelerate Cloud Adoption to Modernize Operations in a Secured Environment]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/ibm-sap-financial-institutions-cloud-adoption</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/ibm-sap-financial-institutions-cloud-adoption</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To better support business transformation and innovation for financial institutions, SAP and IBM are collaborating. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1361f061c8e72d25da24000daaab745a457966f8a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1361f061c8e72d25da24000daaab745a457966f8a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1361f061c8e72d25da24000daaab745a457966f8a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="IBM and SAP to Help Financial Institutions Accelerate Cloud Adoption to Modernize Operations in a Secured Environment" src="./media_1361f061c8e72d25da24000daaab745a457966f8a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="ibm-and-sap-to-help-financial-institutions-accelerate-cloud-adoption-to-modernize-operations-in-a-secured-environment">IBM and SAP to Help Financial Institutions Accelerate Cloud Adoption to Modernize Operations in a Secured Environment</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-financial-services-software-from-sap">Learn more about financial services software from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/financial-services.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong><em>ARMONK, N.Y., and WALLDORF</em></strong> — IBM (NYSE: <a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&#x26;l=en&#x26;o=3120992-1&#x26;h=446680453&#x26;u=https%3A%2F%2Fc212.net%2Fc%2Flink%2F%3Ft%3D0%26l%3Den%26o%3D3081386-1%26h%3D3322217637%26u%3Dhttp%253A%252F%252Fwww.ibm.com%252Finvestor%26a%3DIBM&#x26;a=IBM">IBM</a>) and <a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that SAP intends to onboard two of SAP’s finance and data management solutions to IBM Cloud for Financial Services to help accelerate IBM cloud adoption within the financial services industry.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The collaboration will be designed to help the companies address the industry’s stringent compliance, security and resiliency requirements, while supporting business transformation and innovation for financial services institutions.</p>
  <p>As banks and insurers balance the need to deliver innovative services and meeting the industry’s strict security and compliance requirements, <a href="https://www.ibm.com/thought-leadership/institute-business-value/report/banking-hybrid-multicloud">hybrid cloud environments have become increasingly important</a>. To fuel industry-wide innovation, IBM introduced the IBM Cloud for Financial Services with built-in security and compliance controls that help reduce risk and regulatory barriers impeding IT landscape modernization, transformation and innovation.</p>
  <p>IBM Cloud for Financial Services offers a highly secured, purpose-built environment for financial services institutions to transact with their technology partners and FinTechs. By onboarding to the IBM Cloud for Financial Services, clients can adopt migrated SAP offerings, while addressing their regulatory and compliance standards. Supported by a growing ecosystem of more than 100 partners and FinTechs, the cloud platform is designed to speed customers’ business transformations by both addressing risk in the supply chain for financial institutions and unlocking new revenue opportunities.</p>
  <p>In the context of their ongoing global strategic partnership, IBM and SAP have helped hundreds of companies digitalize their operations using an open, hybrid cloud approach. SAP intends to join IBM’s ecosystem to deliver finance risk, operations and total spend management offerings on the IBM Cloud for Financial Services. The companies intend to help financial institutions benefit from faster business transformation through industry-specific data value offerings and enhanced customer and employee experiences.</p>
  <p>“The rapid transition of regulated industries, such as financial services, toward the cloud makes it necessary to address new operational and technology challenges,” said Bob Cummings, head of SAP Financial Services Sector. “The combination of IBM Cloud and SAP’s capabilities can help banks and insurers around the world to accelerate their digitalization journey and scale their business globally.”</p>
  <p>“As we continue to add partners, such as SAP, to our growing ecosystem, we’re one step closer to driving a true change in cloud adoption for the industry to ultimately help reduce risk throughout the supply chain,” said Joel Spieth, General Manager, IBM Cloud for Industries. “We’re helping financial institutions modernize with SAP solutions on IBM Cloud for Financial Services, driving innovation, and creating operational efficiencies.”</p>
  <p>When onboarded, SAP’s offerings that can now be delivered on the IBM Cloud for Financial Services will provide financial services institutions, their partners and FinTechs with the following:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>SAP’s intelligent suite, including SAP S/4HANA solutions: With its intelligent enterprise framework, SAP provides integrated applications, intelligent technologies and a digital platform designed to enable banks to better serve current customers.</li>
    <li>SAP’s solutions for strategic data management, including SAP Adaptive Server Enterprise, and SAP IQ software: Combining the strength of in-memory technology with these solutions, SAP offers a robust data platform to achieve business agility.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP and IBM together have hundreds of clients and more than 5,500 individual products. SAP and IBM are focused on helping enterprises modernize their businesses and making the most of cutting-edge technologies.</p>
  <p>For more information on IBM Cloud for Financial Services, visit <a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&#x26;l=en&#x26;o=3120992-1&#x26;h=2552284147&#x26;u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.ibm.com%2Fcloud%2Ffinancial-services&#x26;a=www.ibm.com%2Fcloud%2Ffinancial-services">www.ibm.com/cloud/financial-services</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong></p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: 77% of the world’s transaction revenue touches an SAP system. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/">www.sap.com.</a></p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong> Stacy Ries, SAP, +1 (484) 619-0411, <a href="mailto:stacy.ries@sap.com">stacy.ries@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a><br>Suzanne Cross, IBM Communications, <a href="mailto:Suzanne.cross@us.ibm.com">suzanne.cross@us.ibm.com</a>, ET</p>
  <p>Statements regarding IBM’s future direction and intent are subject to change or withdraw without notice and represent goals and objectives only.</p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/financial-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/ibm</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IBM and SAP Partnering to Help Industrial Manufacturers Thrive in the New Service-Based Economy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/industrial-manufacturers-service-based-economy-ibm-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/industrial-manufacturers-service-based-economy-ibm-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In a service-based economy, IBM and SAP provide the intelligent workflows to help industrial manufacturers thrive. Read about the partnership.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dee27b3b14075492b8e43739a32a35fc2bd351cf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dee27b3b14075492b8e43739a32a35fc2bd351cf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1dee27b3b14075492b8e43739a32a35fc2bd351cf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="IBM and SAP Partnering to Help Industrial Manufacturers Thrive in the New Service-Based Economy" src="./media_1dee27b3b14075492b8e43739a32a35fc2bd351cf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="ibm-and-sap-partnering-to-help-industrial-manufacturers-thrive-in-the-new-service-based-economy">IBM and SAP Partnering to Help Industrial Manufacturers Thrive in the New Service-Based Economy</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Industrial manufacturing companies are dealing with significant economic challenges, changing customer demands, increased digitalization, new competitors, and complex global supply chains. These challenges have been amplified during the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, forcing industrial manufacturing companies to focus on building resilient operations and optimize and automate their existing business processes.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>However, to sustain and grow their business, industrial manufacturing companies must develop new business models that address an economy that is moving to outcome-based and sustainable solutions.</p>
  <p>The IBM Institute for Business Value and Oxford Economics recently published the results of a survey, based on interviews with 500 executives. According to this <a href="https://www.ibm.com/downloads/cas/0VQ6LXK1">survey</a>:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Sixty-six percent of industrial manufacturing companies are already focusing on new service business models and increasing revenue share from services</li>
    <li>Five to 10% yearly growth is forecasted in services revenue against two percent in selling new equipment</li>
    <li>EBIT margin generated by service-based models is three to seven times higher compared to new equipment sales</li>
    <li>Twenty-two percent growth is expected in outcome-based services</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-solution-sheet-harness-the-power-of-intelligent-manufacturing-workflows-with-sap-and-ibm">Read the solution sheet: Harness the Power of Intelligent Manufacturing Workflows with SAP and IBM</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/05/9eb062fe-e07d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="ibm-cognitive-enterprise-solutions-enable-intelligent-workflows-for-industrial-manufacturers">IBM Cognitive Enterprise Solutions Enable Intelligent Workflows for Industrial Manufacturers</h2>
  <p>In this time of constant and accelerated change, industrial manufacturing companies must adapt quickly to optimize their existing business and develop new service models for growth. They have to manage complex processes across their entire enterprise and systems. So they are looking for out-of-the-box integrated business applications, which support modular processes that solve specific industry problems, be flexibly consumed, and have intelligence embedded in the processes.</p>
  <p>The IBM Cognitive Enterprise solution, jointly developed by IBM and SAP, provides the intelligent workflows that support these data-driven processes: Intelligent as they are embedded with artificial intelligence to predict outcomes; workflow as they follow the natural flow of work, from one employee to the next, tapping into application data along the way and making appropriate decisions — whether it means capturing customer feedback to further personalize the next client interaction or leveraging machine data to increase the productivity of the production line.</p>
  <p>We are grateful for the feedback that the SAP Global Industry Advisory Council for Industrial Machinery &#x26; Components shared with our joint teams. This input was leveraged as the blueprint of the now available end-to-end intelligent workflows.</p>
  <p>The teams, under the umbrella of the SAP/IBM Evolution Partnership, have delivered four differentiating intelligent workflows — lead-to-order, plan-to-manufacture, order-to-cash, and maintain-to-resolve (aftermarket) — that include new capabilities focused on improving specific business metrics. Key capabilities include intelligent Ssles, cognitive pricing, outcome-based business model, connected manufacturing, and connected asset, which help clients improve win-rates, reduce lead-to-order cycle time, improve customer experience, improve worker safety, and improve overall equipment effectiveness, as well as other key performance indicators (KPIs).</p>
  <h2 id="scale-your-transformation">Scale Your Transformation</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="video-harness-the-power-of-intelligent-manufacturing-workflows-with-sap-and-ibm">Video: Harness the Power of Intelligent Manufacturing Workflows with SAP and IBM</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/04/00e0d5b0-de7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>These intelligent workflows are built on IBM’s Essentials® platform. This platform helps with technology adoption and modernization by individualizing the orchestration of these industry-specific intelligent workflows into our client environments. It enables seamless deployment into heterogeneous landscapes that globally distributed organizations are characterized with, along with a modern architecture that allows for integration with existing applications. It provides possibilities to modernize applications, without disturbing the end-to-end process orchestration, while providing process visibility and control through embedded intelligence and automation.</p>
  <p>This helps our clients to deploy and scale innovations, and supports them on their journey to become intelligent enterprises by:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Accelerating implementations and reducing time to value</li>
    <li>Lowering the cost of implementation through reduced need for customization</li>
    <li>Providing the ability to rapidly adapt the preconfigured workflows to each clients’ specific needs</li>
    <li>Allowing different solutions to be incorporated flexibly via a consumption model</li>
  </ul>
  <p>We are pleased to report early successes in various life-cycle stages of clients in this industry. These include</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Lead-to-order at an European engineered appliances manufacturer</li>
    <li>Outcome-based business model at a leading European packaging machinery manufacturer</li>
    <li>Connected manufacturing at a leading defense equipment manufacturer in the Middle East</li>
    <li>End-to-end industry capability model at a leading Japanese machine tools, automation, and textile machinery manufacturer</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="ready-for-the-next-transition">Ready for the Next Transition</h2>
  <p>We continue to listen to our customers, and our current focus areas include incorporating sustainable and carbon metrics through the design-to-operate process as well as a control tower, which will provide additional data-driven insights to co-ordinate agile and responsive supply chains.</p>
  <p>To read more about the solutions see the Industrial <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/05/9eb062fe-e07d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Manufacturing</a> Solution Sheet: <a href="https://www.ibm.com/downloads/cas/ZRBEEBZ1">https://www.ibm.com/downloads/cas/ZRBEEBZ1</a></p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>To get more information on IBM’s partnership with SAP and additional solutions visit <a href="http://www.ibm-sap.com/digitaltransformation">www.ibm-sap.com/digitaltransformation</a></div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Georg Kube is global vice president of Industrial Machinery and Components at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><em>Manish Chawla is general manager of Global Chemicals, Petroleum &#x26; Industrial Products Industries at IBM.</em></p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="industrial-machinery-and-components-deliver-personalized-smart-products-and-solutions-at-scale-and-as-a-service">Industrial Machinery and Components: Deliver personalized, smart products and solutions at scale and as a service</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/industrial-manufacturing.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/ibm</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/service-industries</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>