<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/industry/healthcare/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Celebrates Healthcare and Life Sciences Industry Heroes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-celebrates-innovation-life-sciences-healthcare</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-celebrates-innovation-life-sciences-healthcare</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At the SAP Innovation Days for Life Sciences & Healthcare, healthcare and life sciences heroes are being celebrated for their innovation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a28e0140b4548307544da21ffb5966dc472b880.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a28e0140b4548307544da21ffb5966dc472b880.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11a28e0140b4548307544da21ffb5966dc472b880.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Celebrates Healthcare and Life Sciences Industry Heroes" src="./media_11a28e0140b4548307544da21ffb5966dc472b880.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-celebrates-healthcare-and-life-sciences-industry-heroes">SAP Celebrates Healthcare and Life Sciences Industry Heroes</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In the rapidly evolving landscape of life sciences and healthcare, a new breed of heroes has emerged – visionaries that are revolutionizing the industries through innovative SAP technology. From the adoption of artificial intelligence (AI) for drug discovery to building an intuitive mobile app to help Parkinson’s disease patients track symptoms, technology plays a pivotal role in creating a healthier world.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="bring-life-saving-medications-to-market-faster-and-improve-patient-outcomes-with-sap-technology">Bring life-saving medications to market faster and improve patient outcomes with SAP technology</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/life-sciences-healthcare.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With the integration of cutting-edge technologies, organizations can leverage data-driven insights to make informed decisions, accelerate time-to-market for new treatments, and ultimately improve patient care. Life sciences and healthcare companies are at the forefront of innovation and competitive advantage by embracing changing industry trends and harnessing technology’s power.</p>
  <p>The SAP Industry Heroes program was launched in 2023 to celebrate companies that leverage technology to transform their business in innovative ways. Healthcare and life sciences heroes have harnessed the power of technology to transform the traditional patient paradigm into an adaptive, customer-centric frontier.</p>
  <h2 id="astellas">Astellas</h2>
  <p>Astellas Pharma Inc. is a leading pharmaceutical company dedicated to advancing healthcare through innovative therapies and cutting-edge research. Focusing on addressing unmet medical needs, Astellas develops and markets a wide range of healthcare solutions across various therapeutic areas, striving to improve the health and well-being of patients globally. With RISE with SAP and SAP SuccessFactors solutions, Astellas is building an internal environment that will leverage globally integrated data to unlock the organization’s full potential.</p>
  <h2 id="dxc-technology">DXC Technology</h2>
  <p>DXC Technology is a global IT services and solutions company known for its expertise in digital transformation, enterprise applications, cloud computing, and cybersecurity. With a focus on enabling clients to thrive in the digital era, DXC offers a wide range of technology and advisory services tailored to meet the diverse needs of businesses across industries. A mobile app built on the SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP) and SAP Business AI is enabling individuals with Parkinson’s disease to keep clinicians informed about their symptoms, accompanied by a clinician dashboard – and generative AI query extensions are also in development. The innovative solution aims to improve the quality of life for these patients and their caregivers and marks a huge step forward in using AI to support clinical decisions.</p>
  <h2 id="gilead-sciences">Gilead Sciences</h2>
  <p>Gilead Sciences, Inc. is a biopharmaceutical company that has pursued and achieved breakthroughs in medicine for more than three decades, with the goal of creating a healthier world for all people. The company is committed to advancing innovative medicines to prevent and treat life-threatening diseases, including HIV, viral hepatitis, COVID-19, and cancer. Gilead operates in more than 35 countries worldwide, with headquarters in Foster City, California.</p>
  <p>Gilead’s digital transformation journey includes a bold migration to SAP S/4HANA with segmentation and SAP Ariba and continues to expand its reach with <a href="/topics/business-technology-platform">SAP BTP</a> and cutting-edge solutions such as SAP Intelligent Clinical Supply Management, SAP Cell and Gene Therapy Orchestration, and SAP Batch Release Hub for Life Sciences.</p>
  <p>Most notably, Gilead and SAP are co-innovating on SAP Batch Release Hub for Life Sciences. This groundbreaking add-on will support continued compliance with regulatory standards across regions and jurisdictions with emphasis on highest quality and safety standards for Gilead’s products, further safeguarding patient wellbeing across the globe. Integrating SAP Ariba solutions, including SAP Business Network, Gilead aims to create a globally interconnected platform, enhancing collaboration between suppliers and buyers while optimizing its global procurement operations.</p>
  <p>Additionally, SAP and Gilead are collaborating on co-innovating jurisdiction control checks using SAP Batch Release Hub for Life Sciences. The add-on will perform control checks on manufactured batches of pharmaceutical products, helping life science organizations to maintain compliance with regulatory standards across multiple regions and jurisdictions. This safeguard checklist will further support the quality and safety of products.</p>
  <p>SAP celebrates these organizations’ outstanding efforts, collaboration, and dedication to driving successful business outcomes with technology. The innovations streamline research processes, enhance efficiency, and improve patient care, ultimately revolutionizing how healthcare and life sciences companies operate.</p>
  <p>SAP Innovation Days for Life Sciences &#x26; Healthcare are taking place in Palo Alto, California, from April 24- 25, 2024, and Newton Square, Pennsylvania, from April 29-30, 2024, celebrating industry heroes and bringing attendees together to discuss leveraging technology to drive business outcomes. Get more information on the events <a href="https://events.sap.com/noam/life-sciences-and-healthcare-innovation-and-discovery-days-us-24/en/home">here</a>.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HomeMade: Self-Service Home Care Because There Is No Place Like Home]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/homemade-self-service-home-care-sap-btp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/homemade-self-service-home-care-sap-btp</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[HomeMade, an Australian startup working to empower its customers in the home care sector, used SAP BTP to help scale, grow, and innovate.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_132610f4998fda9f546e77509f74312e342bbea68.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_132610f4998fda9f546e77509f74312e342bbea68.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_132610f4998fda9f546e77509f74312e342bbea68.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="HomeMade: Self-Service Home Care Because There Is No Place Like Home" src="./media_132610f4998fda9f546e77509f74312e342bbea68.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="homemade-self-service-home-care-because-there-is-no-place-like-home">HomeMade: Self-Service Home Care Because There Is No Place Like Home</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>People over age 65 made up 16% of the Australian population in 2020, and they’re on track to represent more than 22% by 2026. This growing cohort is increasingly forgoing traditional facility care models to remain at home. The Australian government offers financial support to qualifying citizens, who can use those funds to support in-home care.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>These government funds are typically managed by a traditional provider who establishes a plan within the customer’s budget and assigns caregivers. They offer limited to no choice regarding providers and little transparency on how the funds are being spent. This inefficient and costly approach reduces available funds for actual care with limited and often unfamiliar providers.</p>
  <p>Enter HomeMade, a startup looking to disrupt the home care sector with a transformative solution that would empower customers to not only stay in their own homes but also to oversee their spending and self-select their providers. With an initial staff of only six, HomeMade set out to create a <a href="/topics/business-technology-platform">technology platform</a> that would deliver efficiency, flexibility, transparency, and ease of use for customers and a scalable model that would grow and evolve with the company.</p>
  <h2 id="a-rock-solid-technology-foundation-for-a-digitally-native-startup">A Rock-Solid Technology Foundation for a Digitally Native Startup</h2>
  <p>Technology is at the heart of HomeMade’s business model, so choosing the right technology partner and the right digital platform was essential. “We wanted a solution that would give us that ability to scale rapidly and with confidence knowing that the rails weren’t going to fall off, because to be digitally enabled is what makes us different,” <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/laura-westhorpe/?originalSubdomain=au">Laura Westhorpe</a>, HomeMade general manager, said.</p>
  <p>HomeMade found the perfect partner in Bourne Digital, part of Accenture, which steered the startup to <a href="http://sap.com/btp">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP). In choosing the platform, HomeMade benefits from a locally hosted, high-performance cloud architecture that can scale across its network. As a React Native open-source Cloud Foundry runtime service, the HomeMade application is intuitive, user-friendly, and easy for the company to maintain and support long term. Add SAP Integration Suite and SAP HANA data storage into the mix and HomeMade emerged with a secure, integrated, and scalable technology foundation to offer efficient care and support to Australia’s at-home care population.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="bring-out-your-best-with-data-and-ai-from-sap-btp">Bring out your best with data and AI from SAP BTP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="young-company-makes-an-outsize-impact">Young Company Makes an Outsize Impact</h2>
  <p>In just two years, HomeMade has grown its business to 2,500 customers and reduced new user onboarding time from 14 days to 48 hours. The company has empowered qualifying citizens to manage their budgets and choose their care while saving 14 million Australian dollars and counting.</p>
  <p>Customers and families rave about the solution’s functionality and ease of use. HomeMade’s team members, who have grown to over 100, can happily focus on the customer instead of the endless paperwork they might find in traditional care management. Service providers appreciate timely payment, and another critical stakeholder – the Australian government – conducted a regulatory compliance audit and found that HomeMade scored 100% across 42 requirements for the Age Care Quality Safety Standards.</p>
  <p>And this is only the beginning for a new company already making an appreciable impact. “As the needs of HomeMade grow and evolve, the platform will grow and evolve with HomeMade,” <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/selimahmed/?originalSubdomain=au">Selim Ahmed</a>, managing director of Bourne Digital, part of Accenture, explained. For example, Ahmed continued, “We leverage AI business services to read documents…and we’re feeling really confident that those AI services will continue to play a part in the future evolution of HomeMade as the company moves more and more towards automation and self-service.”</p>
  <h2 id="adding-value-through-innovation">Adding Value Through Innovation</h2>
  <p>An SAP Innovation Award winner in 2023, HomeMade continues to grow and think creatively about how its foundational SAP BTP-based technology can enable it to continue to innovate and add value for customers. “There are endless opportunities,” Westhorpe said, from increasing efficiency to leveraging data to identify falls or other incidents to using large language models to recognize clinical deterioration in users and launch preventative interventions.</p>
  <p>For other startups looking to build technology solutions that will make a dramatic impact, Westhorpe offered to consider, “You want to build everything and you’ve got all these grand ideas, but what are the biggest things that will add value for customers?” Ahmed adds that resilience, a strong partnership, and hard work are critical: “Adapt, learn, grow together, and accept feedback…To build something innovative, you must be prepared to roll up your sleeves.”</p>
  <h2 id="the-full-episode">The Full Episode</h2>
  <p>Special thanks to <a href="https://apphaus.sap.com/">SAP AppHaus</a>, a hub for fostering human-centered innovation, for collaborating on this <a href="https://www.sap.com/programs/btp-better-together-customer-series.html">Better Together: Customer Conversations</a> on SAP Business Technology Platform episode. Learn more about how HomeMade built a better solution for qualifying citizens:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Thought leadership podcast:</strong> Thulium’s CEO <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/tamaramccleary/">Tamara McCleary</a> sat down with Westhorpe and Ahmed to discuss the change in caring for older adults, home-based care, and how technology can deliver on a promise dedicated to purpose.</li>
    <li><strong>Practitioners’ video</strong>: Westhorpe, Ahmed, and I discussed the challenges and opportunities in creating a world-class digital solution for a small but rapidly scaling startup.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Explore more success stories of customers leveraging SAP BTP to help optimize processes for the sake of people and purpose:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/04/ac38cbd6-6d7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Colsubsidio</a></strong>: This nonprofit provider of wide-ranging social services chose SAP BTP and SAP HANA Cloud to enable extensive solution integrations, helping deliver better data connectivity and operational efficiency.</li>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/07/b457bfbe-837e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Heartland Dental</a></strong>: Administratively supporting over 1,700 dental practices, Heartland Dental leverages SAP BTP to help improve the business assistant’s user experience, increase productivity, and reduce turnover.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>For the full episode and the on-demand Better Together: Customer Conversations series, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/programs/btp-better-together-customer-series.html">sap.com/btp</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Timo Elliott is vice president and a global innovation advocate for SAP BTP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/startups</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Success Stories: Underway in the Amazon with the Hospital Boat]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-success-stories-underway-in-the-amazon-with-the-hospital-boat</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-success-stories-underway-in-the-amazon-with-the-hospital-boat</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors employee Ana Khouri helped deliver medical and dental services to isolated communities in the Amazon. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bc4eb9cb5d2c9b1ad1db6f2dadf797f0752a1d44.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bc4eb9cb5d2c9b1ad1db6f2dadf797f0752a1d44.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1bc4eb9cb5d2c9b1ad1db6f2dadf797f0752a1d44.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Success Stories: Underway in the Amazon with the Hospital Boat" src="./media_1bc4eb9cb5d2c9b1ad1db6f2dadf797f0752a1d44.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-success-stories-underway-in-the-amazon-with-the-hospital-boat">SAP Success Stories: Underway in the Amazon with the Hospital Boat</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In the quiet darkness of the Amazon night, a broad boat deftly navigates a tributary of the Madeira River, making its way towards a tiny village of wooden houses and thatched shelters nestled on the shoreline. But the boat’s approach does not take the village by surprise. As it nears the riverbank, the cheers of children excitedly herald its arrival: “The doctors are here! The doctors are here!”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>And so begins a new day of service for Ana Khouri, manager for Partner Delivery Management of <a href="/topics/human-resources">SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a>. Khouri was a member of the 2023 expedition of <a href="https://www.doutoresdasaguas.org.br/">Doutores das Águas</a> (Doctors of the Waters), a non-governmental organization (NGO) in Brazil that provides medical and dental care, alongside essential socioenvironmental education, to the isolated communities of the Amazon River Basin. “We had such a welcome,” Khouri says, reflecting on her experiences in the villages the expedition visited along the Acari and Canumã rivers from July 31 to August 12. “We arrived there at night. The boat had not yet docked and everything was dark, and then all these kids were already at the edge waiting for the boat. They were screaming and cheering. It made me kind of emotional.”</p>
  <h2 id="healthcare-for-isolated-communities">Healthcare for Isolated Communities</h2>
  <p>For these communities, the annual visit of Doutores das Águas, now in its twelfth year, is often the only occasion people are able to see a doctor. Their villages are so remote that they would otherwise need to travel many days by boat just to reach the nearest health center. Many have been looking forward to the NGO’s visit. Beforehand, families receive a password to access the services onboard the boat, which include health checks, vaccinations, vital medicines, dental care, and new dentures.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-success-stories-building-strong-communities-of-compassion-and-connection">SAP Success Stories: Building Strong Communities of Compassion and Connection</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/2023/06/strong-compassionate-communities-marissa-baum">Read the feature</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Doutores das Águas sends one expedition per year into the Amazon, divided into two successive stages with each taking either a northern or southern route. Khouri’s expedition traveled south, navigating the Acari and Canumã rivers for 12 days to deliver services to six villages. The boat, 21 meters long and seven meters wide, has sleeping berths for 32 team members plus 12 crew members. It travels at an average speed of 15 kilometer per hour, powered by a 300 HP propulsion engine and has capacity to carry 13,000 liters of fuel, enough to last an entire month. Two generators are also onboard. Built specially for Doutores das Águas, it is equipped with modern medical equipment, including an ultrasound machine, four dental chairs and a dental lab, and a portable wash basin for lessons on teeth brushing. It carries enough stockpiles of vaccines and medicines to support communities for one year, until the boat’s next visit.</p>
  <p>In 2023, the expedition provided services to 36 communities in 23 days to deliver 2,081 medical treatments or vaccines and perform 1,890 dental treatments and 62 micro-surgeries. And the onboard dental lab produced 265 dental prostheses or dentures, giving many people their smiles back.</p>
  <h2 id="hidden-skill-set-reveals-passion-for-healthcare">Hidden Skill Set Reveals Passion for Healthcare</h2>
  <p>In the Amazon, even winters are intense, as daily temperatures reach 37 degrees Celsius with high humidity and frequent rain. The shrill buzz of mosquitos is ever present. Creatures of the rainforest move about invisibly, eager for a free pantleg or untucked shirt to crawl into.</p>
  <p>For Khouri, who joined SAP in 1999, life on the hospital boat is a long distance from her workspace at SAP Brazil in Rio de Janeiro, where she ensures that partners have the enablement tools and support that they need to deliver successfully to customers. Her energetic, affable interpersonal skills and tenacity for problem-solving – the same qualities that help her succeed in her work at SAP – enable her to thrive in dynamic environments.</p>
  <p>But there is another side to Khouri that few colleagues know about. She has a background in nutrition with a master’s degree from Michigan State University. This hidden skill set, which is an integral part of Khouri’s whole self, qualified her to join the expedition as a socioenvironmental and nutritional health expert. “I always liked the healthcare field,” she says. “So, to be there and to be able to provide this benefit to these people and to be part of the team, that’s my motivation. We are giving the people healthcare.”</p>
  <h2 id="learning-by-doing-for-health-and-hygiene">Learning by Doing for Health and Hygiene</h2>
  <p>In the early morning, villagers gather to listen to the doctor, dentist, and the socioenvironmental and nutrition team, who discuss the importance of nutrition and hygiene for long-term health. Afterwards, the adults go to the line to be called in for treatment. “We stay with the kids and teenagers. We play games about food, nutrition, garbage disposal, and recycling,” Khouri says. This year, 750 children received instruction in socioenvironmental and nutritional activities.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="put-your-people-at-the-center-of-everything-with-sap-successfactors">Put your people at the center of everything with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>One game is a competition to see which team can collect the most garbage in a big bag. “The kids are all running, and we run after them, in this intensive heat,” Khouri says. A prize is awarded for the most garbage collected. There are lots of batteries and plastic drink bottles. “This is one exercise we do to tell them they shouldn’t just throw things on the ground because it’s going to be washed away to the river.”</p>
  <p>Twice a day, the children receive instruction on how to brush their teeth. They each receive a dental examination aboard the hospital boat. “We teach them with games and music how to brush their teeth,” Khouri says. “In the boat, we bring a huge sink with eight places so we can have eight kids at once and we give them a small toothbrush and toothpaste.”</p>
  <p>Children who have no cavities at their annual dental checkup receive a badge. In communities where the boat has visited previously, the number of children with no cavities is increasing – evidence of the NGO’s impact on healthcare in the region. “We have lots of little kids, 5 years old or 6 to 7. They have the badge ‘Zero Cavities,’” Khouri says. “We also teach them how to wash their hands and to always wash their hands before they eat.”</p>
  <p>“The kids somehow get attached to you,” Khouri says. “They don’t know you, but then at the end of the day, sometimes you sit quietly somewhere to have a break and they come and hug you. They stay with you. This is something that touched me.”</p>
  <h2 id="tapping-natural-resources-to-satisfy-global-markets">Tapping Natural Resources to Satisfy Global Markets</h2>
  <p>People in the communities along the river live simply from the land and the water. They sometimes sell the fruits, cashew nuts, and mandioca (basis of tapioca) that they cultivate. Many have begun to earn money by selling copaiba oil, used in traditional medicines. The oil is extracted using traditional, sustainable methods to tap tree resin. The oil is popular in high-end cosmetics and pharmaceuticals, including sunscreen, because of its anti-inflammatory properties. “Some of the communities extract the oil,” Khouri says. “Unfortunately, they sell it very cheap to the middleman, who sells it to cosmetics companies for a lot of money.”</p>
  <p>The NGOs that work in the region, including Doutores das Águas, are encouraging the communities to create a cooperative so they can sell copaiba oil directly and receive more money, because the oil “is really cheap and it is very ‘in’ at the moment,” Khouri explains.</p>
  <h2 id="one-boat-is-not-enough">One Boat Is Not Enough</h2>
  <p>Khouri wants to participate in the next expedition of Doutores das Águas, scheduled for April 2024. Also, the communities change over time, as she notes, “Some of the communities disappear. They are so small that they migrate.” One community has become more developed since becoming connected to the region’s main road, making healthcare more accessible to community members.</p>
  <p>“What I expect for the future of these communities is that they get more access to healthcare, improve hygiene, and take care of the river by adopting the garbage collection practice that we teach them,” says Khouri. “I would like people to know that this issue exists and that the need in the Amazon is huge. One boat is not enough.”</p>
  <p>Watch <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/successconnect/virtual.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SuccessConnect Virtual</a> on demand.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Top photo courtesy of Ana Khouri</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-us-on-linkedin">Connect with us on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Follow SAP News</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-employee-profile</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RISE with SAP Accelerates Biotech Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/rise-with-sap-accelerates-innovation-stemcell</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/rise-with-sap-accelerates-innovation-stemcell</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[STEMCELL Technologies is digitally transforming to speed up advanced healthcare discoveries, bringing hope to patients and their families.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/research-development</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patterson Dental Improves Customer Experience with Streamlined Field Service Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/patterson-dental-field-service-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/patterson-dental-field-service-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Patterson Dental was able to cut costs and boost customer service by digitalizing field service operations. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/field-service-management</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP S/4HANA Cloud Is Digital Foundation for Lifesaving Medicines of the Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-s4hana-cloud-digital-foundation-zymeworks</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-s4hana-cloud-digital-foundation-zymeworks</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Biotech innovator Zymeworks builds a foundation for fast growth with SAP solutions, gaining industry best practices with less customization.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In Life Sciences and Healthcare, SAP’s Industry Cloud Is Key to Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/life-sciences-healthcare-sap-industry-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/life-sciences-healthcare-sap-industry-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP’s industry cloud is helping life sciences and healthcare customers preserve and improve human health one innovation at a time.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wellstar Health Improves the Employee Experience through Innovative LMS Governance]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/wellstar-health-employee-experience-lms-governance</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/wellstar-health-employee-experience-lms-governance</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Improved governance helped Wellstar Health make the most out of its SAP SuccessFactors Learning solution. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_133c1cc6858830182923838b672bf97c1f0d1448f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_133c1cc6858830182923838b672bf97c1f0d1448f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_133c1cc6858830182923838b672bf97c1f0d1448f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Wellstar Health Improves the Employee Experience through Innovative LMS Governance" src="./media_133c1cc6858830182923838b672bf97c1f0d1448f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="wellstar-health-improves-the-employee-experience-through-innovative-lms-governance">Wellstar Health Improves the Employee Experience through Innovative LMS Governance</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="building-a-lifelong-learning-culture-is-more-important-than-ever">Building a Lifelong Learning Culture Is More Important Than Ever</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2022/10/building-a-lifelong-learning-culture">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Imagine that you’ve just been hired into a new job, but due to training you can’t really start your actual duties for a week and a half. Now add to this the fact that you’re a healthcare worker whose expertise is very much in need. This was the scenario at Wellstar Health System prior to the start of its learning management system (LMS) governance initiative.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a customer of multiple <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/hxm-suite.html">SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a>, Wellstar is familiar with the power of SAP and knew it could be getting more out of its SAP SuccessFactors Learning solution. Danielle Mecum, manager of Learning Technology at Wellstar, believed that improved governance of the system was part of the road to getting there. “When governance is lacking, the employee experience suffers,” Mecum explained.</p>
  <p>With a nursing background, she knew firsthand the need to get new hires trained properly and quickly, and that reducing the time from hire to actual work was key. She added, “In addition to our non-clinical employees, our medical employees were taking longer to get to the patient floors to start providing care because of how the required onboarding training was organized and set up. There were inaccurate training assignments, courses not marked as required, and, in some cases, no required-by dates.”</p>
  <p>In addition, users said that their learning assignments were too cluttered and disorganized, Mecum explained. And there were instances where new employees would get to a patient floor and realize that they were not able to enter a patient’s chart, for example, because a course hadn’t been assigned to them in the correct sequence.</p>
  <p>The need to get employees onboarded faster could have been enough to justify the governance project, but to add to the complex nature of the project – and completely out of Wellstar’s control – the organization faced the impending deprecation of Flash content and the impacts of the <a href="/topics/covid-19">COVID-19</a> pandemic. To help tackle this challenge, Wellstar decided to work with its customer engagement executive to start a solution adoption engagement. This type of engagement is intended to provide recommendations to a customer to help them create an action plan to optimize their use of their system – in this case <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">SAP SuccessFactors Learning</a>. A recommendation came out of this engagement that confirmed the needed for the governance initiative.</p>
  <p>Mecum’s nursing background helped her understand the urgency of the situation. She and her team looked at the issues already discussed and began to build a governance model. For example, they instituted a content life cycle management process that incorporated a formal method for requesting the creation of new items, curricula, and assignment profiles. In addition, they implemented an ongoing review procedure that included automated notifications to course owners to review material that had reached expiration. Additionally, Wellstar leveraged and configured custom fields within SAP SuccessFactors Learning to track key data and report on it from within the system to ensure compliance with the new governance process.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="foster-continuous-learning-and-reduce-compliance-risk-with-sap-successfactors-learning">Foster continuous learning and reduce compliance risk with SAP SuccessFactors Learning</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Other governance steps included reviewing and consolidating LMS admin roles to ensure the right administrators had the right permissions to perform administrative tasks as appropriate in the system – without giving them freedom to add to the problem at large. A formal process for vetting new LMS administrators was created to ensure they weren’t simply giving just anyone these permissions. “We knew we needed to define what goes into the system, so we could control what comes out. This helps when we need to get rid of old, outdated courses,” Mecum explained.</p>
  <p>These changes, among others, were implemented as part of the governance initiative. The result is that Wellstar is now reaping greater benefits from <a href="/topics/sap-successfactors-learning">SAP SuccessFactors Learning</a> and, most importantly, employees now have an improved experience with the system. Frustration levels are down and new hires are able to start their actual jobs much sooner than before – in three days rather than a week and a half!</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">Learn how an LMS can help your organization.</a></div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Mark Tarallo is a solution marketing fellow for SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-management-system</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Digital Innovations Behind the Booming Life Sciences Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/digital-innovations-life-sciences-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/digital-innovations-life-sciences-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The pandemic has irrevocably disrupted the life sciences industry, revealing a new vision for innovation from cloud-based collaboration.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[California’s Low-Cost Insulin Is Symptom of Lifesaving Innovations to Come]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/life-sciences-innovations-to-come</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/life-sciences-innovations-to-come</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Life sciences leaders are connecting data and people to find for more cost-effective disease prevention innovations and lifesaving cures.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Sartorius Are Reinventing Collaboration and Manual Processes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sap-and-sartorius-reinventing-collaboration</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sap-and-sartorius-reinventing-collaboration</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Sartorius developed a prototype that aims to replace manual practices with automated cross-company orchestrations. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>news-tag/blockchain</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-innovation-center-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Innovation Helps the German National Bone Marrow Donor Registry Save Lives]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/german-national-bone-marrow-donor-registry-zkrd-innovation-save-lives</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/german-national-bone-marrow-donor-registry-zkrd-innovation-save-lives</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The German National Bone Marrow Donor Registry (ZKRD) uses SAP Signavio solutions to help patients receive lifesaving treatment on time.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Take: Digital Twins and the Future of Healthcare]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/the-take-personal-digital-twins-and-healthcare</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/the-take-personal-digital-twins-and-healthcare</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Are personal digital twins — digital doppelgangers of individual humans — on the horizon? Get SAP's take on the future of healthcare.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/perspective</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/the-take</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improve Employee Well-Being through Smarter Healthcare Spend]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/improve-employee-well-being-through-smarter-healthcare-spend</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/improve-employee-well-being-through-smarter-healthcare-spend</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Make the most of your benefits budget by proactively managing your healthcare spend with advanced analytics and modeling tools. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Morocco’s Ministry of Health Saved Thousands of Lives Overnight]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/morocco-ministry-of-health-saved-thousands-overnight</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/morocco-ministry-of-health-saved-thousands-overnight</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To protect its citizens, Morocco’s Ministry of Health developed a COVID-19 Real-Time Monitoring system with SAP Analytics Cloud. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Payroll Company Prioritizes the Patient Journey over Paperwork]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/payroll-company-epi-use-prioritizes-patient-journey-over-paperwork</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/payroll-company-epi-use-prioritizes-patient-journey-over-paperwork</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[EPI-USE utilized SAP Extension Suite to build LogBox, an app aiming to ease stress at the doctor’s office by facilitating patient journeys.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_120aa07f344722d96c00cfab6c0f2dc89c59745c4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_120aa07f344722d96c00cfab6c0f2dc89c59745c4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_120aa07f344722d96c00cfab6c0f2dc89c59745c4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Payroll Company Prioritizes the Patient Journey over Paperwork" src="./media_120aa07f344722d96c00cfab6c0f2dc89c59745c4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="payroll-company-prioritizes-the-patient-journey-over-paperwork">Payroll Company Prioritizes the Patient Journey over Paperwork</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>A visit to the doctor’s office can be as taxing as the reason for the infirmity itself. Patients complain about long wait times not only to see the physician, but also for records and results.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Oftentimes, no matter how competent the administrative staff is and how many hours they work, there is also inaccurate information. And paper. Lots of paper.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-epi-uses-sap-innovation-awards-pitch-deck">Explore EPI-USE's SAP Innovation Awards pitch deck</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2306">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="fragmented-care-and-the-burden-of-extra-paperwork">Fragmented Care and the Burden of Extra Paperwork</h2>
  <p>Head-scratching as it may be, the reality is that <strong>paperwork</strong> is still part of the norm in many modern medical offices – contributing to lengthy wait times and a lackluster patient experience. Many of us, if not all, have experienced this.</p>
  <p>So, what’s the reason for all of this? It’s something called <strong>fragmentation of care</strong>, where the doctor’s office, medical facility, the lab tests, the lab equipment even, and each specialty is managed independently. There are associated administrative functions that are mismatched between each point, and, as such, each point adds an <strong>additional cost</strong>.</p>
  <p>In the 34 countries where it operates, <strong>EPI-USE</strong> – one of the world’s largest and most experienced independent HR and payroll SAP specialists – saw that the dominant medical record companies were focused more on the billing and not so much on the patient.</p>
  <h2 id="an-app-to-integrate-fragmented-care">An App to Integrate Fragmented Care</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-btp-the-platform-for-the-intelligent-enterprise">SAP BTP: The platform for the Intelligent Enterprise</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To combat these costs and improve patient experience, EPI-USE developed <strong>LogBox</strong> – an app that <strong>connects healthcare professionals to their patients</strong> and allows patients to securely share their information with their healthcare professionals electronically.</p>
  <p>This <strong>patient-centric digital solution</strong>, built on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/extension-suite.html">SAP Extension Suite</a>, facilitates the patient journey by making the check-in process easier. Patients enter their information once into the system where it is stored securely, allowing the patient to control where and to whom that information is shared among various different care-provider specialty offices.</p>
  <p>Further enhancements of the system include seamless pre-admissions, a clinical case collaboration tool for multidisciplinary teams, a form editor tool to allow for customizable clinical databases, theater and waiting list modules, multidisciplinary team meetings, and discharge summaries.</p>
  <p>Interoperability with other systems facilitates the exchange of data between various systems – from billing to radiology systems and hospital systems – reducing check-in time and more. All of this may be invisible to the patient, but it will certainly contribute to a more <strong>positive patient journey</strong>.</p>
  <h2 id="making-a-difference-by-ending-the-paper-chase">Making a Difference by Ending the Paper Chase</h2>
  <p>After deploying LogBox, EPI-USE saw the following improvements across the board:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>A more than 30% increase in self check-ins</li>
    <li>Over 280,000 healthcare and patient user accounts created</li>
    <li>A 66% reduction in referral wait times – down from 15 minutes to under five minutes</li>
  </ul>
  <p>“The <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> pandemic forced us to change the way we deliver care to patients, and the LogBox team’s rapid response in adapting the technology to meet our evolving requirements has been remarkable,” said Dr. Sue Trager, CEO, Wits Donald Gordon Medical Center.</p>
  <p>Now, it’s just a matter of time until paper-heavy doctor’s offices will also invest in digital services. It will help them reduce overhead costs and manage more patients, which, in turn, will help them increase their revenue and, just as importantly, generate stress-free patient experiences.</p>
  <p>To learn more about EPI-USE’s solution, check out its SAP Innovation Awards <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2306">pitch deck</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Rajshree Chauhan and Michael Kure are SAP Global Marketing contributors.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wholesale Distribution: Operating with a Purpose Along the Value Chain]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/wholesale-distribution-value-chain-purpose</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/wholesale-distribution-value-chain-purpose</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In a session on operating with a purpose in the value chain, SAP and AmerisourceBergen discussed the vital role of healthcare distributors.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_180c94b9d4110b32aa61155d3fa696189e925f94f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_180c94b9d4110b32aa61155d3fa696189e925f94f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_180c94b9d4110b32aa61155d3fa696189e925f94f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Wholesale Distribution: Operating with a Purpose Along the Value Chain" src="./media_180c94b9d4110b32aa61155d3fa696189e925f94f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="wholesale-distribution-operating-with-a-purpose-along-the-value-chain">Wholesale Distribution: Operating with a Purpose Along the Value Chain</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>While every industry has been affected in some form in recent months, wholesale distribution has been at the center of the global supply chain revolution. Extraordinary measures have been implemented across a variety of industries to handle the unique challenges presented by the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Those in supply chain and logistics have made significant adjustments to help ensure that every segment — including healthcare — has continued to move forward as efficiently and effectively as possible.</p>
  <p>AmerisourceBergen, a wholesale distributor of pharmaceutical products to nearly 100% of hospitals in the U.S., recently joined Cloud Wars Host and Creator Bob Evans and Magnus Meier, global head and vice president of Wholesale Distribution at SAP, for a <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/video/live/urn:li:ugcPost:6798252598970327040/">LinkedIn Live interview</a> to discuss these fundamental changes.</p>
  <p>During the session, Jeff Denton, vice president of Global Secure Supply Chain at AmerisourceBergen, discussed the vital role healthcare distributors play to get life-saving drugs to those who need them most and how the company has managed to ethically balance supplier and customer needs.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="meet-international-and-regional-directives-for-drug-serialization-with-sap-advanced-track-and-trace-for-pharmaceuticals">Meet international and regional directives for drug serialization with SAP Advanced Track and Trace for Pharmaceuticals</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/track-trace-pharmaceuticals.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="new-normal-customer-centric-patient-focused-business">New Normal: Customer-Centric, Patient-Focused Business</h2>
  <p>Wholesale distributors across all sub-segments have managed to keep the supply chain moving forward despite numerous hurdles on a global scale. However, distributors of today can no longer simply focus on moving products through the supply chain. The entire industry has shifted to take on new responsibilities that address the latest regulatory requirements and heightened customer expectations.</p>
  <p>To address these growing concerns, wholesale distributors — especially those in the healthcare distribution segment — are now focused on “doing business with a purpose,” as Meier perfectly described it. By operating with a purpose, this helps ensure the supply chain is safe and secure. It also protects the integrity of the products and provides peace of mind to hospitals, pharmacies, and patients.</p>
  <p>In the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/video/live/urn:li:ugcPost:6798252598970327040/">interview</a>, Denton describes how creating healthier futures starts with protecting the health of people and our planet. As a purpose-driven industry leader with a global footprint, AmerisourceBergen has an obligation to champion global sustainability and corporate responsibility. This includes processing more than $2.5 billion in saleable product returns annually, allowing products that would otherwise have been removed and destroyed to be reintroduced into the supply chain. This is good for AmerisourceBergen along with its customers, patients, and manufacturers across the entire supply chain.</p>
  <h2 id="to-thrive-distributors-require-collaboration-and-innovation">To Thrive, Distributors Require Collaboration and Innovation</h2>
  <p>To address the new concerns and increased responsibility of the distribution industry, AmerisourceBergen approached SAP to co-innovate and create a cross-industry solution centered around meeting the latest regulatory requirements. The result was a new and innovative solution that allows products to be tracked and traced across the entire supply chain: <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/track-trace-pharmaceuticals.html">SAP Advanced Track and Trace for Pharmaceuticals.</a></p>
  <p>The collaboration also allowed AmerisourceBergen and other industry leaders to streamline communication across the entire supply chain, from suppliers through to the pharmacies and hospitals. This supports business continuity through not only an individual enterprise but the entire business network. With this technology, the AmerisourceBergen team can “<a href="/2021/04/amerisourcebergen-best-in-class-industry-innovation">seamlessly match digital data to physical data</a>,” which aids in counterfeit prevention and sustainability efforts.</p>
  <h2 id="data-and-purpose-will-drive-the-industry-forward">Data and Purpose Will Drive the Industry Forward</h2>
  <p>AmerisourceBergen is focused on what the future holds, shifting focus beyond simply reacting to regulatory requirements to understanding the use cases for all of the new data obtained through track and trace technology.</p>
  <p>Without the consortium brought about by AmerisourceBergen and SAP, these industry-specific outcomes and supply chain alignment may not have been possible. Moving forward, collaboration and innovation will be key aspects of the industry and areas in which distributors can add immense value to the supply chain.</p>
  <p>New advancements, technology, and cross-industry collaborations must continue to drive solutions that keep up with the latest regulatory requirements and consumer needs.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>If you missed the LinkedIn Live interview, “Wholesale Distribution: Operating with a Purpose Along the Value Chain” <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/video/live/urn:li:ugcPost:6798252598970327040/">watch the replay here</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-supply-chain</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advanced-track-and-trace-for-pharmaceuticals</category>
            <category>industry/wholesale-distribution</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Innovative Medical Apps: Partners and Ecosystem, Engine of the OP 4.1 Prototype]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/op-41-integration-platform-partner-ecosystem</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/op-41-integration-platform-partner-ecosystem</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read more about what partners and their application developers need to bring their innovations to patients. Here's how SAP supports,]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[OP 4.1: UX Design Puts Patients Front and Center]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/user-experience-design-op-41-dashboard</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/user-experience-design-op-41-dashboard</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn more about OP 4.1 dashboard and how UX design contributes to the optimal user experience in the operating room in this post.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15b84f3a98a771ba3edcfa838caa75978b107a697.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15b84f3a98a771ba3edcfa838caa75978b107a697.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_15b84f3a98a771ba3edcfa838caa75978b107a697.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="OP 4.1: UX Design Puts Patients Front and Center" src="./media_15b84f3a98a771ba3edcfa838caa75978b107a697.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="op-41-ux-design-puts-patients-front-and-center">OP 4.1: UX Design Puts Patients Front and Center</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>One of the key applications on the OP 4.1 platform prototype is the <strong>OP 4.1 dashboard</strong>. Designed to help provide surgical teams with relevant information at the right time, it leaves them free to focus on what matters most: their patients.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At each phase of a surgical operation, the OP 4.1 dashboard displays data pulled from various sources according to need, providing surgical teams with vital information in a way that makes it easy for them to consume it. The data they need for an operation appears on a 47-inch touchscreen monitor placed between three and five meters from the operating table, where anesthetists, surgeons, and other medical and nursing staff can see it clearly.</p>
  <p>The monitor’s main function is to display all the information about a patient and the operation he or she is undergoing at the precise stage in the process when the medical team needs it – before, during, and after surgery.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div><strong>This article is part of the <a href="/topics/op-4-1">series</a>OP 4.1: The Operating Room of the Future</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="end-user-focus-a-principle-of-ux-design">End-User Focus a Principle of UX Design</h2>
  <p>User experience (UX) design provides the foundation. UX designers start with the software user’s story and work backwards to create a design that will deliver maximum benefit. Thus the design and development process for the OP 4.1 dashboard began with a detailed assessment of how modern surgical teams work today.</p>
  <p>When a patient has surgery, the information the medical staff need about that patient comes from different sources and in different formats/ Medical records are usually paper-based; patients often supply visual material, such as CT and x-ray images and the like, on a USB flash drive or similar; lab results are displayed on a PC, like in Cerner i.s.h. med from SAP; and patient consent forms are submitted on paper.</p>
  <p>As a result, the medical staff have to draw together the information they need from multiple sources themselves. They can then plan the operation. Once at the operating table, the surgical team has to cognitively link existing patient data with the information that is generated during the operation as they work. This is where the OP 4.1 dashboard comes in – its aim being to bundle information and display it precisely as and when the operating team needs it. For that to happen, it is vital that the dashboard’s design is as user-centric as possible.</p>
  <h2 id="how-the-dashboard-was-developed">How the Dashboard Was Developed</h2>
  <p>The first task for the dashboard’s designers was to identify all the different sources of information and to find out – by holding user research sessions – what data was required at which point during surgery. Thanks to these sessions, the designers not only learned a lot of detail about surgical processes, they also discovered a great deal about the needs and wishes of the operating teams. On top of that, Heidelberg University Clinic arranged for the UX designers to sit in on operations and observe surgeons as they worked.</p>
  <p>Equipped with the input they had gathered, the designers were able to build a basic grid layout, which then passed through several iterations before achieving its current look. Using this design approach means that end users are involved in development processes and can provide validation along the way.</p>
  <h2 id="op-41-dashboard-close-up">OP 4.1 Dashboard Close Up</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="ux-design-five-principles-for-creating-unique-flexible-user-experiences">UX Design: Five Principles for Creating Unique, Flexible User Experiences</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2020/06/ux-design-principles">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ffcf4af52384fe550becde7c32338001b6d6eac0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ffcf4af52384fe550becde7c32338001b6d6eac0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ffcf4af52384fe550becde7c32338001b6d6eac0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1ffcf4af52384fe550becde7c32338001b6d6eac0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2956" height="1443">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <ol>
    <li>On the left-hand side of the dashboard is an accordion drop-down menu listing the various phases of surgery.</li>
    <li>The shell bar at the very top of the screen shows the operating room logged on as a user. Here, the operating surgeon can also make the appropriate settings for the operation. The shell bar also contains the voice interaction icon.</li>
    <li>Directly below the shell bar is the header. This permanently displays key basic information – such as the total duration of the operation and a stopwatch – that is relevant for all the defined user personas.</li>
    <li>On the far right of the screen is the app drawer, a slide-out side panel displaying third-party apps that medical staff have defined in advance as relevant for the operation.</li>
    <li>The content area in the center of the screen contains various tiles that change dynamically at each stage of the operation. They summarize all the relevant information and make it visible at a glance. Some of the tiles can also be opened to display more detailed information. The content area is also scrollable so that content can be accessed quickly if the operating surgeon has activated more tiles in the settings than can be displayed simultaneously on the screen.</li>
  </ol>
  <p>Further user research sessions were held to validate this layout with the medical teams. In this way, the dashboard was optimized in several iterations to meet the needs of the two main personas: anesthetists and surgeons.</p>
  <p>Once this process was complete, the design was discussed with the SAP UX team to help ensure that it aligned as closely as possible with SAP’s current design language and guidelines, in this case, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/fiori.html">SAP Fiori 3</a> Quartz dark theme.</p>
  <h2 id="app-guidelines-for-third-party-providers">App Guidelines for Third-Party Providers</h2>
  <p>In addition, special design specifications were developed for applications from third-party providers. These were implemented in the first apps built for the dashboard by the German Cancer Research Center (DKFZ) and mbits imaging GmbH and validated with end users.</p>
  <p>The third-party apps deviate from the SAP Fiori 3 Quartz dark theme guidelines used in the dashboard because, unlike the dashboard, they require certification as medical products. Nevertheless, the app designs are closely aligned to the look and feel of the dashboard that end users do not perceive any difference.</p>
  <h2 id="focus-on-the-patient">Focus on the Patient</h2>
  <p>The aim in designing this clearly structured dashboard was to make it as easy as possible for users to work with, and to put patients front and center. The dashboard helps surgical teams focus their skills and energy on their core tasks and, as such, supports gentle, successful, and efficient surgery. And by leveraging digital technology and connectivity in the operating room in this way, it provides a compelling insight into future possibilities that could benefit everyone.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fda750bfe1b384c3be37399e7cef23e63f03a3b9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fda750bfe1b384c3be37399e7cef23e63f03a3b9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1fda750bfe1b384c3be37399e7cef23e63f03a3b9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="OP 4.1 – The Operating Room of the Future" src="./media_1fda750bfe1b384c3be37399e7cef23e63f03a3b9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/_kiKR5Z_u0I">OP 4.1 – The Operating Room of the Future</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <picture>
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a380fdbc7d6330cd15d798556723a53f6e40c046.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a380fdbc7d6330cd15d798556723a53f6e40c046.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
          <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a380fdbc7d6330cd15d798556723a53f6e40c046.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1a380fdbc7d6330cd15d798556723a53f6e40c046.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="709" height="585">
        </picture>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><em><a href="/germany/2021/04/ux-user-experience-design-op41">This story originally appeared on the SAP Germany News Center</a>.</em><br><em>Top image via video screenshot.</em></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Operating Room of the Future: Insight into OP 4.1 Technology]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/op-41-prototype-operating-room-future-technology</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/op-41-prototype-operating-room-future-technology</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn more about OP 4.1 prototype technology and how the "operating room of the future" can add value for all stakeholders here. Read more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d9cb9a5a5b9202ad8f143234b8c2ea3a84b9c7d4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d9cb9a5a5b9202ad8f143234b8c2ea3a84b9c7d4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d9cb9a5a5b9202ad8f143234b8c2ea3a84b9c7d4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Operating Room of the Future: Insight into OP 4.1 Technology" src="./media_1d9cb9a5a5b9202ad8f143234b8c2ea3a84b9c7d4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="operating-room-of-the-future-insight-into-op-41-technology">Operating Room of the Future: Insight into OP 4.1 Technology</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The OP 4.1 prototype provides a look at the “operating room of the future.” Get insight into OP 4.1 technology, which enables a sustainable business model that can offer added value to all stakeholders.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Many operating rooms of the present are equipped with the latest medical technology. The various devices and data sources provide large amounts of information needed for a surgery. However, these are often isolated solutions that make manufacturer-independent networking difficult. The surgeon still has to cognitively combine all information during the operation.</p>
  <p>The OP 4.1 project aimed to showcase how to connect hospitals with their doctors and nurses, device manufacturers, and independent software vendors by providing the right data at the right time while introducing a solid business platform model for the exchange of information.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div><strong>This article is part of the <a href="/topics/op-4-1">series</a>OP 4.1: The Operating Room of the Future</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="what-makes-op-41-an-integration-platform">What Makes OP 4.1 an Integration Platform?</h2>
  <p>The most important goal is patient health. Through intelligent networking of data, operations can be performed more precisely, and patients can be treated more quickly and gently. A technical operating environment that supports an intervention with different functionalities can make this possible.</p>
  <p>To accomplish that requires information — information from the patient file, availability of blood products, results from the laboratory, sensor data from medical devices or even medical imaging from an endoscope. The latter can be combined with CT or MRT images to create a 3D augmentation of the (inward) structures in the surgical area. To get all that information, integration is necessary; for example, medical devices in the operating room.</p>
  <p>But what benefits would the OP 4.1 platform prototype offer to healthcare providers such as hospitals, medical device manufacturers, app developers, or startups? What could be the motivation behind the fact that the parties involved are willing to share their data and make integration possible?</p>
  <ul>
    <li>For hospitals, it is the support of surgeries to enable better and safer procedures as well as improve commercial aspects.</li>
    <li>Medical device manufacturers become enabled to infer new business models as well as get detailed insights of the usage of their products in the surgical environment.</li>
    <li>For startups and healthcare app developers, the operating room moves literally to their fingertips when using the OP 4.1 platform as a development environment.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The following example shows the OP 4.1 billing and invoicing feature and provides some technological insights how OP 4.1 integrates different information, leveraging aspects of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP).</p>
  <h2 id="op-41-technology-insight-invoicing">OP 4.1 Technology Insight: Invoicing</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-the-video-see-how-the-op-41-prototype-provides-a-look-at-the-operating-room-of-the-future">Watch the video: See how the OP 4.1 prototype provides a look at the "operating room of the future"</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_kiKR5Z_u0I">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The OP 4.1 prototype’s core component is based on SAP Business Technology Platform. Alongside that OP 4.1 cloud integration platform, an on-premise OP 4.1 gateway as interface to medical devices in the operating room exists, which processes the devices’ sensor data and sends it to cloud. The communication between on-premise and cloud is realized using Internet of Things (IoT) components like SAP Edge Services and the corresponding SAP IoT solution.</p>
  <p>As central billing component, SAP Subscription Billing is part of OP 4.1. communication throughout the OP 4.1 system and components, especially in terms of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP BTP</a>. External requests are done with APIs structured, secured, and made accessible with SAP API Management. Orchestration is done by SAP BTP and various OP 4.1-specific components, such as event handlers, business logic, and an invoice engine that generates PDF invoices based on usage and billing data of SAP Subscription Billing.</p>
  <p>The following diagram shows and describes the component ensemble and its interactions from using a medical device in the operating room (purple) to invoice creation:</p>
  <h2 id="partner-onboarding">Partner Onboarding</h2>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_156a60aabb37b130e92787ae5e545f81cdac2e2ac.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_156a60aabb37b130e92787ae5e545f81cdac2e2ac.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_156a60aabb37b130e92787ae5e545f81cdac2e2ac.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_156a60aabb37b130e92787ae5e545f81cdac2e2ac.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1867" height="857">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Onboarding new contributors to the platform is key to create a multi-sided market. But how smoothly and quickly is that possible?</p>
  <p>Toward the end of the project, another equipment manufacturer was to be onboarded – truly a proof of concept for the platform. Step one was to connect a new equipment on-premise to the OP 4.1 Gateway via its interfaces like <em>IEEE 11073 Service-Oriented Device Connectivity (SDC)</em> or <em>Patient Care Device Interface (PCD-01)</em>. Step two was to configure its digital representation on the OP 4.1 platform and finally uploading device data to SAP IoT in step three before it could be processed by the business logic to result in a new entry on the invoice document.</p>
  <p>The conclusion of the project is positive; based on the overall approach of using standardized interfaces and generic data processing, the onboarding concepts of the OP 4.1 platform proved working on both business and technological criteria.</p>
  <h2 id="discharge">Discharge</h2>
  <p>In addition to the billing and invoicing feature for medical devices and platform apps shown in the example, the OP 4.1 prototype offers a variety of other functionalities. The platform enables voice command supported tracking of surgery timestamps via the OP 4.1 surgery dashboard and recording of voice notes during surgery. The surgery team, nursing staff, and coordinators can be informed by the platform about the current surgical progress and status for example via mobile notification.</p>
  <p>Based on SAP Consent Repository, the OP 4.1 platform presents a digital alternative to the mainly paper based patient consent process. A consent app provides the patient details about the planned surgery, its risks, and consequences. Furthermore, the patient can give, refuse, or withdraw consent for the surgery while all consent records get centrally managed in the consent repository of the platform.</p>
  <p>The OP 4.1 prototype gives a taste of an exciting future and the potential that digital platforms offer.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fda750bfe1b384c3be37399e7cef23e63f03a3b9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fda750bfe1b384c3be37399e7cef23e63f03a3b9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1fda750bfe1b384c3be37399e7cef23e63f03a3b9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="OP 4.1 – The Operating Room of the Future" src="./media_1fda750bfe1b384c3be37399e7cef23e63f03a3b9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/_kiKR5Z_u0I">OP 4.1 – The Operating Room of the Future</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a380fdbc7d6330cd15d798556723a53f6e40c046.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a380fdbc7d6330cd15d798556723a53f6e40c046.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a380fdbc7d6330cd15d798556723a53f6e40c046.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1a380fdbc7d6330cd15d798556723a53f6e40c046.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="709" height="585">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em><a href="/germany/2020/02/operationssaal-zukunft-platform">This story was originally published on the SAP Germany News Center</a>.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Not-So-Obvious Lessons Learned Managing a Global Vaccine Distribution Cold-Chain]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/vaccine-supply-chain-lessons-distribution-cold-chain</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/vaccine-supply-chain-lessons-distribution-cold-chain</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Vaccine supply chain lessons learned this year are setting companies up for future excellence. Discover how quick pivots have imparted wisdom.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Is Telehealth the Solution? Reimagining Community Health Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/telehealth-reimagine-community-health-systems</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/telehealth-reimagine-community-health-systems</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Telehealth can advance health equity, as shown in the recent Reimagining Community Health Systems Challenge. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_199fe41cb02cf0f5251a5876004ab9635b4525795.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_199fe41cb02cf0f5251a5876004ab9635b4525795.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_199fe41cb02cf0f5251a5876004ab9635b4525795.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Is Telehealth the Solution? Reimagining Community Health Systems" src="./media_199fe41cb02cf0f5251a5876004ab9635b4525795.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="is-telehealth-the-solution-reimagining-community-health-systems">Is Telehealth the Solution? Reimagining Community Health Systems</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As <a href="https://econofact.org/essential-and-frontline-workers-in-the-covid-19-crisis">frontline workers</a> during the COVID-19 pandemic, the care teams of Iowa’s community health centers — who are also members of the <a href="https://iowapca.org/">Iowa Primary Care Association</a> (Iowa PCA) — have been in a pitched battle to provide testing and, most recently, vaccines to the 226,000 Iowans who rely on the network’s community health centers for care.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Health equity for all” is the mission of the Iowa PCA, which provides care and services to underserved populations through a statewide network of 14 community health centers.</p>
  <p>This spring, thanks to valuable insights from the cross-corporate teams that volunteered their skills for the <a href="https://www.pyxeraglobal.org/reimagining-community-health-systems/">Reimagining Community Health Systems Challenge</a>, administrators at the Iowa PCA will be heading into their statewide strategic growth planning sessions with an innovative, comprehensive vision for integrating telehealth services into its plans for an electronic health records system. By optimizing telehealth services, the Iowa PCA aims to improve access and clinical outcomes for patients and connect them to an evolving model of care that maintains quality, enhances health equity, and lowers costs.</p>
  <p>“We benefited a ton from having plans, ideas, innovation, and things we could try from a perspective that is much broader than the pandemic,” says Sarah Dixon, senior director of Partnerships and Development at Iowa PCA. “The teams did in one month something that would take us a year to do. In terms of the rapidness of the response, thoroughness, and comprehensiveness, it was really an amazing experience for advancing our work.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.nachc.org/research-and-data/research-fact-sheets-and-infographics/americas-health-centers-2020-snapshot/">Community Health Centers in the United States</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="cross-corporate-teams-innovate-for-social-impact">Cross-Corporate Teams Innovate for Social Impact</h2>
  <p>As a cross-corporate volunteer competition, the Reimagining Community Health Systems Challenge brought together diversified teams of skilled professionals to apply their expertise to formulating bold solutions to complex challenges on behalf of public sector organizations that have potential to make an impact on social, economic, or environmental problems. Organized by <a href="https://www.pyxeraglobal.org/">PYXERA Global</a>, an organization that brings together the public, private, and social sector to address global challenges, the challenge ran from May through September 2020 as part of a larger <a href="https://youtu.be/PA2l1IUYcHU">Reimagine Series</a> of social impact challenges designed to find innovative solutions to longstanding societal concerns that have been made worse by the COVID-19 pandemic.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16d84e2df8dbb967b16f14ea672e4f03dc1e5754f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16d84e2df8dbb967b16f14ea672e4f03dc1e5754f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16d84e2df8dbb967b16f14ea672e4f03dc1e5754f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Reimagine Series | The Multiple Perspectives of the Reimagining Community Health Systems" src="./media_16d84e2df8dbb967b16f14ea672e4f03dc1e5754f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/hiBKrw4tHXc">Reimagine Series | The Multiple Perspectives of the Reimagining Community Health Systems</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP took an active role as a lead corporate sponsor, along with <a href="https://www.medtronic.com/us-en/index.html">Medtronic Foundation</a>, a charitable organization funded solely by global medical technology company Medtronic. Medical device maker <a href="https://www.bd.com/en-us">BD</a> and <a href="https://www.celanese.com/en/About-Us">Celanese</a>, the chemicals and specialty materials company, also joined the challenge to advance health equity through telehealth. Altogether, these industry partners selected 40 employee volunteers distributed across three continents to participate in the challenge, which was held virtually. The volunteers were organized into eight cross-corporate teams in a collaborative competition to see which team could develop the most innovative solution to the challenges proposed by two public sector organizations, called Anchor Partners.</p>
  <p>The key advantage of cross-corporate teams is the outside-in approach that they bring to problem solving. This diversity of thought leads to creative, comprehensive, and cost-effective solutions for growth-oriented, not-for-profit organizations, which often lack internal resources for strategic business planning.</p>
  <p>“Multi-company teams add a unique dimension of diversity to a global pro bono program, as participants bring their personal experiences, tools, methodologies, and corporate culture to the table,” says Hemang Desai, global program director for Corporate Social Responsibility at SAP. “These elements result in innovative and impactful solutions to the business challenge presented to the teams, while creating a rich, multi-faceted learning experience for the participants as they build strong people connections in the business world.”</p>
  <p>The two Anchor Partners in the challenge were the Iowa PCA and the National Association of Community Health Centers (NACHC). In its challenge statement, the Iowa PCA sought input for a framework to roll-out and integrate telehealth across its network of community health centers. The challenge from NACHC differed in that it sought broader guidance on how to create a clear role and business plan to position itself in the telehealth landscape as a leader for community health centers on a national level. With the pandemic accelerating, both organizations were motivated by the pressing need to realistically assess the potential for telehealth to expand access to care.</p>
  <p>Jason Patnosh, associate vice president of NACHC, recalled the urgency NACHC faced during the lockdowns in early March. “For the first time, outside of natural disasters, health centers had to close their doors to patients for the safety of their staff. This meant they had to find alternatives to reaching out to some of their most vulnerable patients,” Patnosh said during <a href="https://youtu.be/KrjOANrsJLI">a Reimagine Series webinar</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Telehealth Expands Care Access</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="addressing-long-journey-times-and-broadband-access">Addressing Long Journey Times and Broadband Access</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="make-your-organization-more-resilient-and-agile-in-todays-challenging-environment-get-back-to-best-with-sap">Make your organization more resilient and agile in today’s challenging environment: Get back to best with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/covid-19/back-to-best.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The eight teams prepared for the challenge by talking to stakeholders and studying policy information. In August, they got down to business tackling the four project phases: Discover, Ideate, Create, and Deliver.</p>
  <p>Fouad Sadik, an SAP development architect, worked on the challenge for the Iowa PCA as the lead for the Tele-Transformers team. Sadik is an SAP volunteer ambassador who has worked on cross-corporate teams in the past and sees many advantages to this problem-solving approach. “The community health centers benefit from tapping into the diversity of the skill sets coming from multi-company knowledge,” Sadik says. “Being a member of a team of five allowed us to divide and conquer the deliverables according to each member’s skill set to get the best outcome.”</p>
  <p>Sadik’s team analyzed stakeholders’ perspectives from healthcare professions and view-of-the-customer interviews to gain a comprehensive understanding of the issues surrounding telehealth adoption for the Iowa PCA. They also spoke with insurers and the presidents of Iowa’s two Medicaid Managed Care Organizations to ensure alignment on the reimbursement models for telehealth services. To better understand issues affecting different patient populations, the team developed detailed personas and undertook geo-mapping to analyze patient journey times to care centers. Strikingly, they discovered that some patients were traveling more than three-and-a-half hours to access care. This led the team to make recommendations for co-hosted telehealth sites with other organizations, like libraries or schools, that could serve as access points for telehealth services.</p>
  <p>Dixon says it is a recommendation that the Iowa PCA will investigate further. “Telehealth may allow us to go into some communities where a full clinic site isn’t viable, but telehealth in partnership with another community provider could be a really viable way to increase services. We’ll be looking at that as part of our statewide strategic growth planning this spring.”</p>
  <p>Digital broadband connectivity remains a hurdle across much of the state of Iowa. To address this imperative need, the Iowa PCA is part of a coalition of schools, libraries, and rural economic development agencies that are working on securing broadband infrastructure across the state. The teams developed innovative ideas for extending phone signals, expanding digital footprints to include parking lots for mobile telehealth vehicles, telehealth ATM machines in hotspot locations, and broadband sharing with other community and civic centers.</p>
  <h2 id="empowering-patient-access-and-satisfaction">Empowering Patient Access and Satisfaction</h2>
  <p>At the end of the challenge, judges chose two winning proposals based on six criteria: innovation, social impact, sustainability, desirability, feasibility, and viability. The Tele-Transformers team, led by Sadik, won the challenge for the Iowa PCA, presenting a comprehensive telehealth program based on three pillars: strategy and process improvement, marketing and training for both patients and care providers, and technology systems and software. The team provided a detailed software comparison list of 14 telehealth software providers and six learning management systems, allowing them to make a recommendation for a strategy and unified approach that uses a common platform. Sustainability, social impact, and empathy for end users played a large role in the team’s proposal, which also included recommendations for expanding telehealth services for mental health, behavioral, and chronic care.</p>
  <p>As a participant, Sadik says he benefited professionally from exposure to the healthcare domain, design thinking sessions, and project management methodology, while attaining personal development by helping the Iowa PCA expand care access for patients. “This challenge made an impact toward the refinement of existing processes, building a road map for telehealth business programs and providing a digital footprint for telehealth on a grassroots level close to affected communities,” Sadik says, adding, “that’s actually the challenge by itself that allowed us to improve telehealth systems and empower patients’ access and satisfaction.”</p>
  <p>The winning team for the NACHC Challenge was R/Evolution, which emphasized establishing best practices and using strategic partnerships and data analytics to elevate NACHC’s leadership on telehealth.</p>
  <p>For Suzie Moskal, senior IT manager at Medtronic, participating in the challenge on behalf of NACHC was a rewarding experience that she would recommend for future participants considering the estimated four hours per-week time commitment. “I would say definitely do it, make the time to make it happen. When I looked at the pitch session and saw all the amazing ideas and concepts that NACHC was going to receive, I was excited for them. Whether my team won or not, they got a very amazing set of products out of this experience.”</p>
  <p>To see all of the concepts that were presented, view the <a href="https://www.pyxeraglobal.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Reimagine-Series-Challenge-Report-Reimagining-Community-Health-Systems-PYXERA-Global-2.pdf">Reimagining Community Health Systems Challenge Report</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="care-access-enhanced-by-technology">Care Access Enhanced by Technology</h2>
  <p>NACHC is moving ahead with due diligence to operationalize not only the winning concept but also integrate positive aspects of the other solutions. Its staff is engaging in further ideation sessions with PYXERA Global to refine the solutions and create a version to put into action.</p>
  <p>Patnosh sees clear value in having participated in the Reimagine Series: “To get the amount of input that we had from the teams and to have that level of engagement, and then also the quality of the presentations that come in, we estimate that those would have probably been 50 to 75 thousand-dollar engagements just with each team, if we were to contract that out.”</p>
  <p>Following the challenge, the Iowa PCA has shifted its plans away from implementing a standalone e-health platform. Feedback from the teams and voice-of-the-customer interviews convinced the Iowa PCA of the need for a simplified, integrated e-health solution that is easy for everyone to use. The organization is currently evaluating new electronic health records systems with a strategic focus on integrated telehealth functions.</p>
  <p>Dixon says, “The insight from the challenge was so important because it brought in a different voice – a voice that wants the same things we do: simple tools, the ability to access information at our fingertips, and have a workflow that is enhanced by technology, not negatively impacted by technology.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/pyxera-global</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Telehealth: Temporary Fix or the Future of Health Care?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/telehealth-temporary-fix-or-future-of-health-care</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/telehealth-temporary-fix-or-future-of-health-care</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Telehealth is changing the way patient care takes place. Read to learn how telehealth is more than a hasty response to COVID-19.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14f7998a06d5632d3e89912a37ba4b3ca9d4147ae.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14f7998a06d5632d3e89912a37ba4b3ca9d4147ae.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_14f7998a06d5632d3e89912a37ba4b3ca9d4147ae.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Woman at home talking with her doctor on tablet; telehealth appointment" src="./media_14f7998a06d5632d3e89912a37ba4b3ca9d4147ae.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="telehealth-a-temporary-fix-or-the-future-of-health-care">Telehealth: A Temporary Fix or the Future of Health Care?</h1>
        <p>After a slow start, the pandemic forced an embrace of telehealth. Now it’s changing the way patient care takes place.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Most telehealth visits with patients are for routine care, not potentially life-changing diagnoses. Yet Dr. Albert Chan, the chief of digital patient experience at Sutter Health, describes a time when a cardiology colleague met virtually with a patient who had recently undergone open heart surgery and quickly noticed one of the patient’s incisions had become infected. Surgical site infections can be uncomfortable for patients, costly for healthcare providers, and if left untreated, potentially fatal.</p>
  <p>“Because of the ability to communicate virtually, we were able to catch that infection early,” says Chan. “That’s a tremendous opportunity.”</p>
  <p>In fact, telehealth is quickly redefining how people access, view, and receive healthcare services. Real-time virtual visits with physicians, mobile apps that let patients book appointments and pay bills, and wearable devices that remotely monitor an individual’s vital signs are enabling healthcare providers to engage with patients in a more proactive way, make services more readily available, free up precious hospital resources, and in some cases, save lives.</p>
  <p>That wasn’t always the case. Criticized for being a costly and complicated delivery modality, less than 1% of all physician visits in the U.S. were conducted using telehealth before early 2020. But COVID-19 changed all that as stringent social distancing measures, pandemic-related telehealth policies, and an overburdened hospital infrastructure forced physicians and consumers alike to embrace telehealth as a viable patient care modality.</p>
  <p>Today, more than half of all consumers expect to rely more heavily on telehealth than they did before the pandemic, and a whopping 92% of providers plan to continue offering video consultations, even after it’s safe for in-person visits, according to an <a href="https://static.americanwell.com/app/uploads/2020/09/Amwell-2020-Physician-and-Consumer-Survey.pdf">Amwell</a> report. Moreover, three years from now, 70% of providers anticipate using telehealth sometimes or frequently.</p>
  <p>But the telehealth movement is more than just a response to changes in government guidelines, healthcare policies, and public sentiment. Rather, it heralds a unique opportunity to redefine the patient-physician relationship, glean greater value from patient data, and even reimagine the physical footprint of healthcare facilities. That is, provided the sector can overcome obstacles ranging from digital disparities to data security.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13e744108c09bf644388f276b0ccadca818087035.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13e744108c09bf644388f276b0ccadca818087035.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_13e744108c09bf644388f276b0ccadca818087035.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Doctor is on the phone for telehealth appointment" src="./media_13e744108c09bf644388f276b0ccadca818087035.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="drivers-of-change">Drivers of change</h2>
  <p>Several factors explain telehealth’s transformation from seldom-used modality to major trend. Chief among these are the sweeping regulatory changes introduced by the U.S. government in March 2020, including these temporary measures:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>The Centers for Medicare &#x26; Medicaid Services (CMS) decided to pay healthcare providers for telehealth services given to Medicare beneficiaries so that they can receive a wider range of healthcare services without having to travel to a healthcare facility.</li>
    <li>The Office for Civil Rights (OCR) at HHS announced it would waive potential penalties for HIPAA violations associated with providing care via noncompliant platforms such as FaceTime and Skype.</li>
    <li>Congress passed the Coronavirus Aid, Relief, and Economic Security (CARES) Act, which eliminates the requirement that providers must have an established relationship with a Medicare patient to provide telehealth services.</li>
    <li>The government eliminated geographic restrictions, allowing patients to receive telehealth services in their homes.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>By removing geographic restrictions and relaxing regulations, the number of telehealth visits during the last week of March 2020 increased by <a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/69/wr/mm6943a3.htm">154%</a>, compared with the same period in 2019, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.</p>
  <p>“The pandemic has taken telehealth in its broadest sense and made it much more accessible to both patients and providers,” says Ann Mond Johnson, CEO of the American Telemedicine Association (ATA), which represents more than 400 organizations, academic medical centers, payers, and solution providers. “The uptick in utilization has skyrocketed.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dfbe8ca59852b8e3c6ef04da435300c642b44c8b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dfbe8ca59852b8e3c6ef04da435300c642b44c8b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1dfbe8ca59852b8e3c6ef04da435300c642b44c8b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="A stethescope and an iPad on a table" src="./media_1dfbe8ca59852b8e3c6ef04da435300c642b44c8b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="842" height="560">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="catering-to-the-patient-experience">Catering to the patient experience</h2>
  <p>Another variable drives rapid telehealth adoption: the consumerization of healthcare. Just as same-day delivery and highly personalized interactions have come to define customer engagement, so too are consumers increasingly looking for greater ease and speed from their healthcare providers.</p>
  <p>“Technology has entered so many other facets of our life that many patients now say the most important thing they look for in a provider is convenience,” says David Hinkle, executive director of business operations at Mercy Virtual. “They don’t want to drive a couple of hours from their community to the big city for a follow-up. That’s really pushed doctors to adapt to meet this demand from consumers.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="cloud-based-platform-news">Cloud-Based Platform News</h3>
        <p>SAP boosts industry-wide innovation with startup partnerships.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://news.sap.com/2020/09/industry-wide-innovation-startup-partnerships-iristrace/">Read the news</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Mercy Virtual is a perfect example. Completely dedicated to virtual care, this four-story facility houses a large medical team of practitioners who rely on highly sensitive two-way cameras and online instruments to meet virtually with patients, whether they’re in a traditional hospital, a doctor’s office, or at home.</p>
  <p>Doctors can monitor patients’ vital signs and provide backup for bedside caregivers in 30 ICUs across five states. The facility’s TeleStroke program ensures patients who arrive at any community emergency department, many of which don’t have a neurologist on-site, can be seen immediately by the care center’s neurologist using a two-way audio and video connection. And Mercy Virtual provides continuous remote monitoring for more than 3,800 patients, intervening quickly when needed, thereby reducing patients’ need for hospitalization.</p>
  <p>By delivering quality care with on-demand convenience, telehealth initiatives such as Mercy Virtual transform the role of patient into that of healthcare consumer.</p>
  <p>“We know that if patients are going to rely on remote monitoring, we have to make it as easy as possible for people,” says Mond Johnson. “We need to take our cues from companies like Amazon where consumers go online, order something, it shows up at your house the next day, you turn it on, and it works perfectly.”</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">We know that if patients are going to rely on remote monitoring, we have to make it as easy as possible for people.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Ann Mond Johnson, CEO, American Telemedicine Association</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Efforts to ensure patients have easy access to detailed information about their care are also underway. For example, the 21st Century Cures Act of 2016 requires healthcare providers to grant patients access to all the health information in their medical records. But recent regulations from the Office of the National Coordinator for Health Information Technology upped the ante by expanding the type of information that must be easily accessible, including consultation notes, procedure notes, and pathology reports.</p>
  <p>“Our patients can see all of their notes as soon as the doctor is done writing them,” says Chan of Sutter Health. “They can see doctors’ notes, laboratory tests, X-ray results – almost immediately.”</p>
  <p>The result, says Chan, is not only documentation that can “help guide care,” but also a prime opportunity for patients to become partners in the management of their own health care. In fact, according to a JAMA <a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2763607">survey</a>, clinicians agree that it is a good idea to share notes with patients, and 74% viewed sharing notes as useful for engaging patients in their care.</p>
  <h2 id="innovative-applications">Innovative applications</h2>
  <p>As adoption of telehealth grows, healthcare organizations are discovering more innovative use cases, from compassionate care to clinical trial participation.</p>
  <p>“We’ve had some sad circumstances where COVID-19 patients had to spend their last hours without visitors,” says Hinkle. “Our chaplains have been able to loop in family from home using telehealth technology so that these patients could spend those hours with their loved ones.”</p>
  <p>Virtual sitting is another increasingly popular application of telehealth in which patient sitters – nonclinical staff members – provide in-room monitoring of patients who are at high risk for falls or self-harm. In fact, the Agency for Healthcare Research and Quality <a href="https://www.ahrq.gov/patient-safety/settings/hospital/fall-prevention/toolkit/index.html">estimates</a> that 700,000 to 1 million hospitalized patients fall each year. More than <a href="https://psnet.ahrq.gov/issue/preventing-falls-and-fall-related-injuries-health-care-facilities">one-third</a> of these result in serious injury. Depending on the severity of the injury, unreimbursed costs for treating a single hospital-related fall injury can reach nearly US$30,000.</p>
  <p>Providing a physical sitter in each room can be challenging for resource-strapped healthcare organizations. Fortunately, virtual sitters are a cost-effective alternative, allowing for real-time, continuous monitoring of at-risk patients using a combination of in-room cameras, remote monitoring tools, and two-way video and audio feeds.</p>
  <p>In fact, in some cases, “virtual can be even better than face-to-face, particularly in telebehavioral health,” says Mond Johnson of the ATA, noting today’s shortage of qualified mental health professionals. “We have an opportunity to do better for more people using technology, and that’s something you cannot do face-to-face without using up all your resources.”</p>
  <p>Telehealth is even enabling patients to participate in clinical trials that would otherwise remain unavailable to them. For example, one rural patient with Stage 4 lung cancer was able to participate in two clinical trials and undergo chemoradiation treatment and surgery at a tertiary care center through the successful coordination of telehealth services, including videoconferencing. The patient remained disease free for 18 months, according to a <a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S2468294216300338">report</a> published by Cancer Treatment and Research Communications. Better yet, telehealth promises to improve the speed and efficacy of clinical trials by broadening researchers’ pool of potential candidates.</p>
  <p>Telehealth is enabling patients to participate in clinical trials that would otherwise remain unavailable to them.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c86814f1c95210ae5cdd4403c889c77ab5c40f0a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c86814f1c95210ae5cdd4403c889c77ab5c40f0a.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1c86814f1c95210ae5cdd4403c889c77ab5c40f0a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Digital identity scanner" src="./media_1c86814f1c95210ae5cdd4403c889c77ab5c40f0a.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3198" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="from-security-breaches-to-the-digital-divide">From security breaches to the digital divide</h2>
  <p>Despite its advantages, many are questioning the role telehealth will play in a post-pandemic world. Will patients return to in-person interactions when it’s safe to do so? Or will telehealth continue to serve as a cost-effective and convenient alternative to traditional care?</p>
  <p>The answers to many of these questions hinge on how successfully healthcare providers are able to overcome certain obstacles.</p>
  <p>Chief among these challenges is data security. “As we shift towards telemedicine, we’re sending patients home with devices that allow them to communicate bidirectionally, whether it be checking blood glucose or various vital signs,” says Scott Harrison, chief data officer for Parkland Health. “But with all new IT endeavors, you always have to think about security first – what kind of risk am I imposing by allowing these systems of engagement to now interact and connect to my systems that are on premises.”</p>
  <p>After all, healthcare organizations are prime targets for ill-intentioned hackers and other bad actors. According to <em><a href="https://www.hipaajournal.com/">HIPAA Journal</a></em>, hacking and IT incidents comprised 59.4% of healthcare breaches in 2019, while accounting for 87.6% of breached records. And more than a quarter (28.82%) of data breaches consisted of unauthorized access and disclosure incidents, involving 11.27% of all records breached in 2019.</p>
  <p>In fact, hackers can easily hack videoconferencing and messaging apps used for telehealth, providing them with a pathway to more sensitive data and critical systems. For this reason, Harrison says it’s critical healthcare organizations “make sure that there’s endpoint encryption so that the data residing with the patient is safeguarded and that it’s capable of entering a network in a safe manner.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="biometrics-sensing-a-healthy-society">Biometrics: Sensing a Healthy Society</h3>
        <p>We need technology that can evolve with us to ensure our health and safety.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/blogs/biometrics-sensing-healthy-society">Learn more about biometrics</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Chan at Sutter Health agrees, citing restricted access, password-protected network entry points, and continuous monitoring of remote devices as critical measures all healthcare providers must take to ensure “data is kept sacrosanct for patients.” That’s especially true as healthcare providers continue to adjust to record numbers of participants. Case in point: Sutter Health’s MyHealthOnline initiative received 7,000 video visits in 2019 – a number that skyrocketed to over 1 million in 2020.</p>
  <p>But while concerns over secure and reliable access to corporate networks keep IT leaders up at night, many Americans don’t have any connection. The Federal Communications Commission <a href="https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/fact-sheets/2019/07/21-million-americans-still-lack-broadband-connectivity">estimates</a> that 21 million people in the United States lack broadband connectivity – 30% of which live in rural areas. And a staggering 60% of healthcare facilities outside metropolitan areas lack the speed of connectivity needed to properly store and manage electronic health records.</p>
  <p>Says Mond Johnson, “The pandemic has really laid bare the problems that we’ve had as a society in terms of [broadband] inequities.”</p>
  <p>Fortunately, change is underway: the FCC recently earmarked $9.2 billion in funding for the development of high-speed broadband networks for more than 10 million rural Americans across the country. It’s one of a growing number of initiatives that “have been formed to acknowledge that while we did not cause disparities, we’re uniquely positioned to address them as telehealth organizations,” says Mond Johnson.</p>
  <p>Harrison also sees an opportunity for telehealth providers to help bridge today’s digital divide: “One of the disparities that we have is access to care. By increasing our capabilities in that area, we can close the gap on some of those disparities. So I’m very bullish on the increased influence of virtual care and telemedicine – that’s the way of the future.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fe70478dd92fbe87debdc6d7659336e84c956896.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fe70478dd92fbe87debdc6d7659336e84c956896.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1fe70478dd92fbe87debdc6d7659336e84c956896.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Doctor and patient using digital tablet in office" src="./media_1fe70478dd92fbe87debdc6d7659336e84c956896.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="the-human-factor">The human factor</h2>
  <p>Silver linings aside, there is a learning curve that comes with properly implementing a telehealth strategy and raising awareness of its benefits.</p>
  <p>“Educating both providers and patients is a huge challenge,” says Dr. Tearsanee Carlisle Davis, director of clinical and advanced practice operations at the University of Mississippi Medical Center’s Center for Telehealth. “With so many tools out there, it is very important to have a clear plan for educating providers on workflows and troubleshooting. Patients also need to be made aware of what telehealth does for them and how to access it. This is a very heavy lift for groups who have not been doing telehealth prior to COVID-19.”</p>
  <p>Then there are the inherent limitations of telehealth. “There are definitely situations for which telemedicine is not appropriate,” says Lori Uscher-Pines, a senior policy researcher at the RAND Corporation. “For example, when a clinician needs to do a physical exam or a procedure, in-person care is necessary.” Uscher-Pines also offers the example of physicians treating patients with opioid use disorder: “Although telehealth has a lot of promise for patients with opioid use disorder, it can be difficult to establish rapport with patients over telemedicine. Many providers tell us that they really rely on in-person interactions to fully access a patient.” What’s more, she adds, in-person therapy sessions offer ingredients such as “accountability and ritual that enable treatment to be more successful.”</p>
  <p>Technology-fueled interactions can also feel antiseptic compared to face-to-face consultations.</p>
  <p>“We’ve been very conscious of the healing power of touch,” says Hinkle of Mercy Virtual. “You want to make sure that you aren’t losing that personal provider-to-patient relationship and that it doesn’t begin to feel transactional. We have to be careful that even in cases where we’re using telemedicine, the patient still feels like there is a special relationship with the doctor.”</p>
  <p>Yet one of the biggest hurdles facing telehealth is cost. Policymakers will need to expand telehealth benefits permanently for Medicare beneficiaries and continue to advance access to care in rural areas if telehealth is to maintain mainstream traction. “Policies such as receiving reimbursement only if you go to the clinician’s office for a telehealth service are absurd,” says Mond Johnson. “During the public health emergency, regulations finally caught up with technology. But the temporary waivers put in place during the public health emergency, which led to gains in telehealth, need to remain permanent.”</p>
  <p>Overutilization is another cost consideration. Granting patients greater access to care can lead to unnecessary visits – and escalating healthcare costs. “One of telehealth’s greatest strengths is one of its greatest weaknesses – it’s extremely convenient,” says Uscher-Pines. “It’s great that it’s convenient for patients but that convenience can lead to extra-utilization. It’s really hard to thread this needle. You want to increase access to provide high-quality services to patients but you also want to make sure that you’re not doing it in a way that causes healthcare costs to go out of control.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ebc973b75da7fc9689c52c33842564e6a53c9670.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ebc973b75da7fc9689c52c33842564e6a53c9670.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1ebc973b75da7fc9689c52c33842564e6a53c9670.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Woman doctor looking at screen" src="./media_1ebc973b75da7fc9689c52c33842564e6a53c9670.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1958" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="checking-the-future-for-vital-signs">Checking the future for vital signs</h2>
  <p>Provided healthcare organizations successfully overcome these obstacles, Chan believes the “possibilities for telehealth are quite endless.” For instance, as healthcare providers increasingly adopt a hybrid approach to patient care, Hinkle envisions a time when full-service hospitals might “transition away from trying to provide care for whatever patient might walk in the door.” Instead, he says, a more efficient and cost-effective approach will be for hospitals to serve as “centers of excellence” that cater to “various specialties.”</p>
  <p>Predictive health care is another area poised for significant innovation. Wearable monitoring devices, patient portals, and home monitoring apps all produce vast volumes of data. “Being able to ingest all of those various mechanisms of data and blending them with the data we have curated in our own systems – that can tell a big story,” says Harrison of Parkland Health. “And that’s where it’s getting very exciting.”</p>
  <p>For instance, Harrison says by monitoring a patient’s blood glucose levels, combining this data with information gleaned from personal fitness apps and online food trackers, and applying sophisticated <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-artificial-intelligence.html">artificial intelligence (AI)</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-machine-learning.html">machine learning</a> algorithms, healthcare practitioners can begin to identify patterns, such as the likelihood certain cohorts of patients will develop life-threatening complications from diabetes.</p>
  <p>“By integrating the right sets of data and learning from these patterns over time, there’s absolutely no reason not to think that we could start predicting various disease patterns before they happen,” says Harrison. Better yet, he adds, “When we get in front of these patterns before they become a problem, it becomes much easier to treat them.”</p>
  <p>But newly designed hospital facilities and predictive health care are only the beginning of telehealth’s transformational impact on an age-old sector. Business processes and workflows must also evolve to support greater cross-functional collaboration. As technology embeds itself in every aspect of patient care delivery, Hinkle says “a sense of camaraderie between clinicians and IT support teams” will prove “critical to moving forward as we attempt to leverage technology in patient care.”</p>
  <p>Davis agrees. She advises healthcare providers to “form teams with individuals from IT, education, and clinical areas to develop plans [that will address the challenges of telehealth]. Having a very strong project management team is key. And there has to be a standardized process for communication and implementation.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15c53b10537cebadb0372ca58083993aa82192426.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15c53b10537cebadb0372ca58083993aa82192426.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15c53b10537cebadb0372ca58083993aa82192426.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Doctor in scrubs with digital tablet and clipboard" src="./media_15c53b10537cebadb0372ca58083993aa82192426.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2600" height="1733">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="a-new-landscape">A new landscape</h2>
  <p>No one can dispute the invaluable contributions telehealth has made to providing patients with quality care and compassion in the midst of a global pandemic. “There’s been enormous innovation on the part of the healthcare industry in terms of getting people care and keeping them safe, while at the same time allowing people with chronic illnesses to be monitored at home as opposed to getting in their car and going to the hospital or a physician’s office,” says Mond Johnson.</p>
  <p>And for many, there’s no turning back. “There have been so many successes in the world of telehealth since the pandemic that I don’t see it going back to the prepandemic world,” says Hinkle. “It’s going to continue to evolve.”</p>
  <p>What shape telehealth takes remains to be seen. But one thing is certain: telehealth is more than a hasty response to COVID-19. Rather, it marks a tipping point in how healthcare providers grant access to medical services and the ways in which patients are willing to receive care.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Baby Boomers: Consumer and Workplace Preferences]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/boomers-want-value-integrity-substance</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/boomers-want-value-integrity-substance</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[As both consumers and prospective employees, mature Boomers are looking for authentic leaders who demonstrate ethical behavior. Learn more!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1072bd9ac01236b5619d4e00d6f18e1d607bc8946.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1072bd9ac01236b5619d4e00d6f18e1d607bc8946.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1072bd9ac01236b5619d4e00d6f18e1d607bc8946.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Older woman taking notes from laptop" src="./media_1072bd9ac01236b5619d4e00d6f18e1d607bc8946.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="research-findings-boomers-want-integrity-in-work-and-life">Research Findings: Boomers Want Integrity in Work and Life</h1>
        <p>As consumers and prospective employees, members of this demographic are looking for quality healthcare and ethical leaders.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Grizzled Baby Boomers (born between 1946 and 1964) are less passionate about global issues than younger generations and more pragmatic when it comes to buying decisions. They are, however, also more demanding that business leaders behave responsibly.</p>
  <p>By far, healthcare is the most important issue for people in their mid-50s and up, as cited by 63% of the nearly 4,000 Boomers who answered SAP’s January 2020 online survey of 10,000 U.S. and Canadian consumers. Climate change was the second biggest issue for Boomers, followed by poverty and hunger.</p>
  <p>Those are some of the top-line results of the survey, which sought to understand how different generational groups view the significance of global issues; how individuals respond emotionally to leadership decisions; and how business characteristics affect individuals’ decisions to buy from, work for, and respect companies.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-5-new-truths-about-leadership">The 5 new truths about leadership:</h3>
        <p>Why leaders need to think, and act, more broadly if they want to be successful.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/research/social-responsibility-of-business">Read the report</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The research provides a window into the sentiments of four generations – Boomers, <a href="/resources/generation-x-search-for-hope">Gen Xers</a>, <a href="/resources/millennials-passions-influence-decisions">Millennials</a>, and <a href="/resources/generation-z-behavior-explained">Gen Zers</a> – at a time when people are evaluating the behaviors of companies and their leaders. To discern respondents’ levels of emotional intensity, individuals were presented with 17 global issues, such as climate change, education, and work-life balance, and were asked to attach an emotional rating to each one, choosing from 12 different emotions, such as admiration, disgust, and enthusiasm. (Response choices were equally balanced between positive and negative emotions). Using their responses, we generated a standardized Emotional Index to capture the strength of participants’ emotions across all areas.</p>
  <p>The results clarify that for companies looking to tap into the immense buying power of the 71 million U.S. Boomers, a one-size-fits-all strategy that also appeals to Gen Xers, Millennials, and Gen Zers won’t work. Boomers are different and require an approach tailored to their unique requirements.</p>
  <h2 id="top-of-mind-for-boomers-healthcare-and-the-planets-future">Top-of-mind for Boomers: Healthcare and the planet’s future</h2>
  <p>It’s no surprise that aging Boomers have more concerns about healthcare than the other groups. But Boomers also worry about what kind of planet they’re handing down to their grandchildren.</p>
  <p>Boomers care significantly more about a cluster of environmental issues than the other groups. For example, Boomers listed <a href="/blogs/by-land-sea-and-air-emerging-technologies-to-tackle-climate-change">climate change</a> as their number two issue at 46.9%, compared with 37.8% for Millennials and 36.3% for Gen Xers. Boomers also said they were more concerned about recycling (31.4% vs. 18.2% for Gen Zers), clean water (25.6% Boomers vs. 18.7% Millennials), and <a href="/blogs/technology-for-biology-preserving-biodiversity">biodiversity</a> (15.2% vs. 13.1% for Gen Xers).</p>
  <p>On the flip side, Boomers care less about mental health issues, work-life balance, education, income inequality, and sexual harassment (see Figure 1).</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_135f044b4dbc560c1d63054b787ee891205961b07.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_135f044b4dbc560c1d63054b787ee891205961b07.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_135f044b4dbc560c1d63054b787ee891205961b07.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Figure 1: Healthy Bodies and a Healthy Planet Matter Most to Baby Boomers" src="./media_135f044b4dbc560c1d63054b787ee891205961b07.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="1080">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Figure 1: Healthy Bodies and a Healthy Planet Matter Most to Baby Boomers</em></p>
  <p><strong>The takeaway:</strong> To resonate with Boomers in general, digital business leaders should seek opportunities to focus on issues tied to wellness – of the body and the planet.</p>
  <p>Boomers primarily focus on the state of healthcare access. We see the same pattern of Boomers standing apart from the other generations when it comes to a slew of environmental issues.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11e30f890bd82ed9d9a607026ffb3573fa786541a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11e30f890bd82ed9d9a607026ffb3573fa786541a.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_11e30f890bd82ed9d9a607026ffb3573fa786541a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Baby boomer doctor looking at x-ray of spinal cord" src="./media_11e30f890bd82ed9d9a607026ffb3573fa786541a.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1856">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="boomers-as-buyers-focused-on-the-here-and-now">Boomers as buyers: Focused on the here and now</h2>
  <p>For Boomers, the top three <a href="https://news.sap.com/2021/01/sap-study-shopping-habits-recovery-roll-out/">buying criteria</a> are old-school – product quality, features, and price. Compared with the other generations, Boomers are also more likely to do business with a company where leaders demonstrate ethical behavior and engender personal trust.</p>
  <p>Baby Boomers don’t expect companies to solve all the world’s problems – a company’s ability to make a difference in the world has less influence on their buying behavior than it does with the other groups. But they do expect business leaders to demonstrate personal integrity. Boomers also demand ethical behavior from business leaders (74% vs. 68% for the other groups).</p>
  <p>The top three buying criteria for Boomers are traditional metrics like quality of the product or service (94% vs. 77% for Gen Zers), features and performance (93% vs. 74% for Gen Zers), and price (92% vs. 77% for Gen Zers).</p>
  <p>Boomers are far less interested in buying considerations that might seem frivolous to them, like celebrity endorsements, online reviews, aesthetics, and the quality of the company’s partner ecosystem (see Figure 2).</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1573e2c777886fe6d85ec3c40463f4532344ff919.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1573e2c777886fe6d85ec3c40463f4532344ff919.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1573e2c777886fe6d85ec3c40463f4532344ff919.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Figure 2: How Baby Boomers Differ from Other Generations in Buying Decisions" src="./media_1573e2c777886fe6d85ec3c40463f4532344ff919.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="1080">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Figure 2: How Baby Boomers Differ from Other Generations in Buying Decisions</em></p>
  <p><strong>The takeaway:</strong> Unlike the other groups, Boomers demonstrate that traditional buying factors (price, quality, features, buying experience) still reign supreme in their minds. To win their business, companies must focus on these bedrock issues. But that’s not all – Boomers expect companies to behave ethically, so business leaders need to show integrity in their decisions and actions.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10b6ce99aed836099637f7361834ea244172f665b.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10b6ce99aed836099637f7361834ea244172f665b.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_10b6ce99aed836099637f7361834ea244172f665b.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Someone carving wood" src="./media_10b6ce99aed836099637f7361834ea244172f665b.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="boomers-and-the-workplace-show-us-substance">Boomers and the workplace: Show us substance</h2>
  <p>The Boomer age group is 56 to 74. Many are retired and many others are approaching retirement. But, generally speaking, when asked how important it is to work for a company that makes a difference in the world and improves people’s lives, their responses were in sync with those of the other groups.</p>
  <p>Baby Boomers care little about celebrity endorsements and online reviews, but they place an elevated importance on positive work experience (90%), product quality (89%), pay (88%), product features and performance (86%), and personal trust in leaders (85%).</p>
  <p>They also care more than the younger age groups about things like business leaders’ authenticity, their ability to effect change, and their ethical behavior, as well as organizational transparency and openness to new ideas. But those criteria fall into a second tier, behind the more practical aspects of a job – how you’re treated, how well you’re paid, and how much you respect the product and the leadership team.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_141d57c2c05ab42e8b396d67b31d9e76fdeeab479.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_141d57c2c05ab42e8b396d67b31d9e76fdeeab479.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_141d57c2c05ab42e8b396d67b31d9e76fdeeab479.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Close-up of finances spreadsheet, pen, and credit card" src="./media_141d57c2c05ab42e8b396d67b31d9e76fdeeab479.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="7952" height="5304">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_137bb017ea9072ed64b40e2a03dee3e7af3184507.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_137bb017ea9072ed64b40e2a03dee3e7af3184507.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_137bb017ea9072ed64b40e2a03dee3e7af3184507.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Figure 3. How Baby Boomers Differ from Other Generations in the Workplace" src="./media_137bb017ea9072ed64b40e2a03dee3e7af3184507.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="1080">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Figure 3. How Baby Boomers Differ from Other Generations in the Workplace</em></p>
  <p><strong>The takeaway:</strong> For Boomers deciding where to work, it’s about more than the pay or whether you can work from home. Boomers are the polar opposite of gig economy workers who view a job as something to tide them over for a while. Leaders should recognize that Boomers are different from the other groups. They’re looking for a company they can be proud to work for, that produces quality products, and has leaders they can personally trust. They also want to work for a company that offers great healthcare.</p>
  <p>When asked to define the qualities that engender respect, Boomer responses mirrored their views on buying and workplace decisions. They place the greatest importance on product quality, features, performance, and price. And they differ from the other generations in placing greater importance on business leaders’ ethical behavior, organizational actions that benefit the community, and ability to effect change, as well as their level of personal trust in leaders.</p>
  <h2 id="less-passion-yes-but-boomers-care-deeply-about-the-big-picture">Less passion? Yes. But Boomers care deeply about the big picture</h2>
  <p>Along with identifying the issues Boomers and other generational groups care about, we also measured their level of passion about these issues. We identified a group we call “Passionates.” This subgroup is most likely to have intense feelings about global issues and to link those feelings to buying and employment decisions based on the company’s commitment to these issues. Emotional ratings included terms like admiration and disgust and contained 12 choices balanced equally between positive and negative sentiments.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>While Boomers may not be as passionate as younger generations, they still care deeply about society and the environment.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Overall, the Passionates make up 20% of total respondents, though the respondents who fit this profile tend to skew younger than the Boomers. Only 14.2% of Boomers were Passionates. (In contrast, 31.6% of Gen Zers were Passionates). At the other end of the sentiment spectrum, Boomers showed more dispassion than other groups – 23% vs. 18.2%.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="ok-boomer-we-still-want-you">OK Boomer! We Still Want You!</h3>
        <p>Hiring managers should look to this valuable talent pool for their expertise.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/ok-boomer-we-still-want-you">Read the story</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While Boomers may not be as passionate as younger generations, they still care deeply about a wide range of societal and environmental issues. And they differ from the younger generations in their view of government. To a greater extent, Boomers believe that governments should be a leading force in effecting global change.</p>
  <p>For organizations in fields like healthcare, insurance, retail, financial planning, personal services, and travel and entertainment, Boomers want you to stick to your knitting. They’re not looking for slick marketing campaigns featuring celebrities, fancy packaging, or hyped-up online reviews.</p>
  <p>They want solid value, a great buying experience, and top-notch customer service from a company that demonstrates ethical behavior and whose leaders are trustworthy.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Generation X: In Search of Reasons for Hope]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/generation-x-search-for-hope</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/generation-x-search-for-hope</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To attract Generation X as consumers or employees, companies need to find areas of Gen X passion. Learn more about the priorities of Gen X.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18c528588df6c94cf53b190dc048eb127d280f124.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18c528588df6c94cf53b190dc048eb127d280f124.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_18c528588df6c94cf53b190dc048eb127d280f124.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Two hikers walking along mountain range" src="./media_18c528588df6c94cf53b190dc048eb127d280f124.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="generation-x-in-search-of-reasons-for-hope">Generation X: In Search of Reasons for Hope</h1>
        <p>Members of this group, now in their 40s and 50s, are focused on work-life balance – and looking for uplifting signs both as consumers and in their jobs.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Members of Generation X who grew up during the 1970s carry an overriding sense of detachment. Compared with other generations – both those younger and those older – individuals born between 1965 and 1980 are generally less optimistic about their future, are slightly less concerned about global issues, and demonstrate less passion than other generations in a survey.</p>
  <p>Generation X may care less about critical issues of the day than other generations, but businesses shouldn’t take this relative aloofness to mean that Gen X doesn’t put thought into its purchasing or employment decisions. Rather, to attract Gen Xers as consumers or employees, companies need to find areas of Gen X passion.</p>
  <p>Organizations that tap into this group’s areas of emotional intensity – including the appearance, performance, and quality of products or services – can win their respect and their buying power. And leaders who offer optimistic views of the future and provide evidence that they care about peoples’ well-being can appeal to this group.</p>
  <p>These findings about Gen X emerged from a January 2020 online survey of 10,000 Canadians and Americans by SAP Insights research group. While the research into different generations’ emotional responses to leadership decisions took place before the pandemic and related economic woes, the results demonstrate that emotions evoke and influence decisions regardless of topics of the day.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Leaders who offer optimistic views of the future and provide evidence that they care about peoples’ well-being can appeal to this group.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>That’s because prospective customers and employees in all generations are gauging their buying and employment decisions on issues that sometimes go beyond traditional metrics like prices and pay rates to include larger-picture issues, such as organizational transparency and the ethical behavior of business leaders.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-changing-mission-of-leadership">The Changing Mission of Leadership</h3>
        <p>A groundswell of voices are driving business leaders to act on global issues.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/research/social-responsibility-of-business">Read the research</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To discern respondents’ levels of emotional intensity, individuals were presented with 17 global issues, such as climate change, education, and work-life balance, and were asked to attach an emotional rating to each one, choosing from 12 different emotions, such as admiration, disgust, and enthusiasm. (Response choices were equally balanced between positive and negative emotions). Using their responses, we generated a standardized Emotional Index to capture the strength of participants’ emotions across all areas.</p>
  <p>We then identified areas of intensity and specific displays of passion around different issues. A group we defined as the <a href="/research/passionates-how-they-are-changing-your-strategy">Passionates</a> compromise 20% of our respondent base across all generations, with 18% of Generation X respondents falling into this group. The Passionates’ strong feelings clearly influence their purchasing and employment decisions. For example, 73% of Passionates have said a business leader’s position on societal issues affects their buying behavior, compared with 64% of Gen X respondents.</p>
  <h2 id="generation-x-focuses-on-well-being">Generation X focuses on well-being</h2>
  <p>At ages 40 to 55, members of Generation X are thinking very close to home when they identify issues they care most about. For example, about one-third (33.8%) of Gen Xers rated mental health as an important issue, compared with 31.6% of others in the survey. And 27.6% of Gen X say work-life balance is a critical concern, compared to 20.9% of everybody else.</p>
  <p>As Figure 1 shows, Gen X cares a great deal about healthcare access and is less passionate about environmental issues than those in other generations.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e014ad98f34b0a4c67964800e99e44f9bd6c1f31.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e014ad98f34b0a4c67964800e99e44f9bd6c1f31.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1e014ad98f34b0a4c67964800e99e44f9bd6c1f31.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Figure 1: Healthcare Matters Most to Generation X" src="./media_1e014ad98f34b0a4c67964800e99e44f9bd6c1f31.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="850">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Figure 1: Healthcare Matters Most to Generation X</em></p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1646dbfc3e9b926110dcf12805f8af11bda545df4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1646dbfc3e9b926110dcf12805f8af11bda545df4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1646dbfc3e9b926110dcf12805f8af11bda545df4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Generation X nurse spending socially-distanced time with child" src="./media_1646dbfc3e9b926110dcf12805f8af11bda545df4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1680" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="buying-considerations-finding-the-right-signals-for-gen-x">Buying considerations: Finding the right signals for Gen X</h2>
  <p>Because Gen X is less optimistic about the future – about 3% less so than other groups in the survey – businesses will have to work harder for their dollars. Leaders seeking to appeal to those individuals now in their 40s and early 50s have to strike a balance: persuade Gen X that their products and services are reliable, trustworthy, and visually appealing.</p>
  <p>A key trigger for this group of <a href="/news/2021/01/sap-study-shopping-habits-recovery-roll-out">buyers</a> is aesthetics, including the look and feel of products and services and the appearance and design of company branding, packaging, and Web sites. Gen Xers are more likely to pay attention to aesthetics, with 66% ranking it as an important consideration, compared to 63% of all other respondents. Whether it’s packaging or a visually enticing Web site, businesses would do well to make it look good.</p>
  <p>Otherwise, Gen Xers more closely align with <a href="/resources/millennials-passions-influence-decisions">Millennials</a> in their purchasing decisions. Traditional characteristics, such as price, product and service performance, and quality, matter more to Gen Xers than <a href="/resources/generation-z-behavior-explained">Gen Zers</a>, who are in their early 20s and younger, as Figure 2 shows.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14dd514e22a1af76a9263264934afc96a99f9dda1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14dd514e22a1af76a9263264934afc96a99f9dda1.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_14dd514e22a1af76a9263264934afc96a99f9dda1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Figure 2: Generation X Aligns with Millennials on Purchasing Factors" src="./media_14dd514e22a1af76a9263264934afc96a99f9dda1.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="800">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Figure 2: Generation X Aligns with Millennials on Purchasing Factors</em></p>
  <p>There are cases where Generation X aligns with Generation Z, such as with placing stock in the opinions of others: 64% of Gen Xers and 67% of Gen Zers say online reviews are an important factor in their purchasing decisions, compared with 53% of <a href="/resources/boomers-want-value-integrity-substance">Boomers</a> and 74% of Millennials.</p>
  <p>However, Gen X is less likely than all other generations to base purchasing decisions on the ability of business leaders to affect change or the authenticity of these leaders.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a12f046cbad2fb404d430997cb576aa3fdd8e4f2.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a12f046cbad2fb404d430997cb576aa3fdd8e4f2.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1a12f046cbad2fb404d430997cb576aa3fdd8e4f2.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Poland, Warsaw, lounge at hotel" src="./media_1a12f046cbad2fb404d430997cb576aa3fdd8e4f2.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="in-the-workplace-gen-x-says-pay-me-be-real-lets-make-quality-products">In the workplace, Gen X says: Pay me. Be real. Let’s make quality products.</h2>
  <p>To attract and retain Gen X employees, organizations must emphasize compensation while remembering that pride of place, authenticity, and strong business leadership are important characteristics.</p>
  <p>Gen Xers, likely near the peak of their earning potential, care a lot about their wages. Asked which employment considerations are most important to them, 86% chose occupational compensation. That’s more in line with Boomers (88%) and Millennials (82%) and much higher than Gen Zers (73%).</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16795747613b94dc0c02bfd9d4bfc4ee8f764453d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16795747613b94dc0c02bfd9d4bfc4ee8f764453d.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_16795747613b94dc0c02bfd9d4bfc4ee8f764453d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Figure 3: Generation X Is Relatively Passionate About the Products and Services Its Employers Offer" src="./media_16795747613b94dc0c02bfd9d4bfc4ee8f764453d.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="800">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Figure 3: Generation X Is Relatively Passionate About the Products and Services Its Employers Offer</em></p>
  <p>In addition, Gen Xers are most likely to desire authenticity in their employers, with 79% giving this characteristic importance compared with 63% of Baby Boomers. Millennials and Gen Zers have a similar desire, at 78% and 76%, respectively.</p>
  <p>They also want to be proud of their work. Gen Xers, like Boomers, refer to product/service performance and quality as important factors in their employment decisions – more so than Millennials and Gen Zers.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1131aad07b2b038ffa6d8123325ce90494a1b10d5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1131aad07b2b038ffa6d8123325ce90494a1b10d5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1131aad07b2b038ffa6d8123325ce90494a1b10d5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Generation Xer explaining something to two younger adults" src="./media_1131aad07b2b038ffa6d8123325ce90494a1b10d5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1493" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Similarities between Gen X and other generations are evident in such workplace issues as their business leaders’ ability to effect change while demonstrating transparency, empathy, and openness. Generation X demonstrates the same levels of emotional intensity in these areas as other groups in the survey.</p>
  <h2 id="positive-outcomes-can-result-from-an-optimistic-slant">Positive outcomes can result from an optimistic slant</h2>
  <p>In some respects, Generation X may care less about critical issues of the day than those in other generations. Yet that doesn’t mean that they don’t care about anything.</p>
  <p>Organizations would do well to highlight factors like price, compensation, appearance, and quality. Like everybody else, Gen Xers will compare, buy, and work for organizations that demonstrate they’ve paid attention to these matters. And leaders need to give Gen Xers reasons to care about their work: showing they can effect change and care about the quality of the work. With those efforts, businesses will tap into Gen X’s passions.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coming to Our Senses: The Future of Sensors]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/coming-to-our-senses-the-future-of-sensors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/coming-to-our-senses-the-future-of-sensors</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With tinier, increasingly capable sensors assessing almost anything, we’ll gain new insights and abilities to transform our minds, bodies, and the planet.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10b2d6417db0967ee9bc47aa44865ee53a7b8713a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10b2d6417db0967ee9bc47aa44865ee53a7b8713a.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_10b2d6417db0967ee9bc47aa44865ee53a7b8713a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Jellyfish on purple background" src="./media_10b2d6417db0967ee9bc47aa44865ee53a7b8713a.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="coming-to-our-senses-the-future-of-sensors">Coming to Our Senses: The Future of Sensors</h1>
        <p>Smaller, smarter sensors will give us new insights into the world around us – from inside a cancerous cell to the ocean floor.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_169fa3c23de0f53521dbe868a6291881e34a0d160.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_169fa3c23de0f53521dbe868a6291881e34a0d160.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_169fa3c23de0f53521dbe868a6291881e34a0d160.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_169fa3c23de0f53521dbe868a6291881e34a0d160.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="320" height="179">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/m/hzRXLe3/hls.m3u8">SAP Digital Futures: Coming to Our Senses - The Future of Sensors</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="want-a-quick-overview">Want a quick overview?</h3>
        <p>Learn how sensors will become a powerful force in the future.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2022/10/5e78b8ff-477e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Read the brief</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="human-progress-depends-on-the-ability-to-measure">Human progress depends on the ability to measure.</h2>
  <p>For millennia, our five senses were all we had to interpret and respond to the world around us. The story of civilization is the story of developing and using technology to extend the limits of our natural capabilities. We created ways to measure time – first sundials, then sophisticated devices like the <a href="https://www.britannica.com/science/astronomy/History-of-astronomy#ref1211262">sky disc of Nebra</a> and the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Antikythera_mechanism">Antikythera mechanism</a> – so we could better control our use of it. We mapped the night sky on the walls of the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lascaux">Lascaux</a> caves and drew the <a href="https://www.britannica.com/biography/Anaximander">first map of the world</a> to determine where we were and where we wanted to go. And from the early telescopes and microscopes of the 16th and 17th centuries to the <a href="https://hubblesite.org/">Hubble Space Telescope</a> and the <a href="https://home.cern/topics/large-hadron-collider">CERN particle collider</a>, we’ve created increasingly sophisticated tools that let us interpret our world far beyond what our five senses permit on their own.</p>
  <p>These tools now include digital sensors that will soon be ubiquitous. They’re so small that they’ll be completely integrated into the world around, on, and inside of us. These tiny sensors are already allowing us to understand the world we know more easily and precisely. But more intriguingly, they also enable us to measure things that were never measurable before.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16c9bbff4a2c733d229a603fcce0bd53079e17215.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16c9bbff4a2c733d229a603fcce0bd53079e17215.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16c9bbff4a2c733d229a603fcce0bd53079e17215.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Person looking at small sensor with flashlight" src="./media_16c9bbff4a2c733d229a603fcce0bd53079e17215.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="5760" height="3840">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="tiny-and-mighty">Tiny and mighty</h2>
  <p>Early sensors were essentially just highly sophisticated monitors. They could be installed in places too small or dangerous for humans in order to measure common metrics like motion and acceleration, pressure, light, heat, and levels of chemicals and radioactivity. Still, their relatively large size and hunger for power limited their usefulness.</p>
  <p>Today’s sensors require far less space and energy. As sensors get ever smaller, we’re likely to see microscopic “<a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2019/06/18/wild-tech-ideas-with-big-chance-of-becoming-breakthroughs-in-a-decade.html">smart dust</a>” that will alert farmers when their fields are dry, monitor engine performance from inside the fuel line, or determine whether someone’s neurons are firing properly after a stroke. Scientists have created <a href="https://news.mit.edu/2019/ingestible-expanding-pill-monitors-stomach-0130">sensor-laden pills</a> that can transmit data about ulcers, cancer, and other gastrointestinal conditions for up to a month and then pass safely out of the body.</p>
  <p>The use of sensors will extend long past quantifying and monitoring aspects of our physical health. In fact, they will augment the human body. We’ll have implantable sensors that measure and transmit muscle signals for more precise control of <a href="https://robotics.sciencemag.org/content/4/32/eaaw6306">robotic prostheses</a>; stretchy, transparent sensors that can feel and respond to complex sensations like skin does; and wearable sensors that can monitor <a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2020-01/uos-slm011320.php">medication levels</a> and electrolyte levels in a person’s sweat in real time. And this technology will do more than just let us restore or enhance human abilities. It could let us give human abilities to technology, such as by letting soft robots safely handle fragile objects like glass or food by gauging how delicate their grip should be.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bb1061aaa6db704f1d06e85ca28b35b545bccef8.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bb1061aaa6db704f1d06e85ca28b35b545bccef8.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1bb1061aaa6db704f1d06e85ca28b35b545bccef8.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Man sitting under The Milky Way Galaxy" src="./media_1bb1061aaa6db704f1d06e85ca28b35b545bccef8.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="exploring-where-no-human-has-gone-before">Exploring where no human has gone before</h2>
  <p>Smaller, more durable sensors will grant us access to previously unexplored realms, like the bottom of the sea. Scientists at Princeton University are trying to understand and predict seismic activity with a network of <a href="https://geoweb.princeton.edu/people/simons/earthscopeoceans">floating sensors</a> that measure the buoyancy, viscosity, temperature, and density of the <a href="https://phys.org/news/2019-12-jules-verne-scientists-deploy-ocean.html">ocean floor</a> and the kilometers of molten rock beneath it.</p>
  <p>Similarly, MIT researchers are developing a network of battery-free, interconnected sensors that can drift through the ocean, transmitting data through acoustic waves, while a research team at a Saudi university is actually attaching flexible, non-toxic, silicon-based <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ariellasimke/2020/03/05/fish-wearing-marine-skin-sensors-collect-information-6500-feet-below-the-sea/#38474a83254a">sensors</a> directly to fish. These systems will track marine life and measure ocean dynamics like currents, water temperature, and pH levels in ecosystems humans have yet to explore, supporting long-term studies that might help us monitor and mitigate climate change.</p>
  <p>Further afield, researchers at the National Institute of Standards and Technology have built a <a href="https://phys.org/news/2019-11-light-sensing-camera-extraterrestrial-life-dark.html">camera</a> out of sensors capable of counting individual particles of light. Although the camera itself can’t go into deep space, it can spot and measure the absorption spectra of a star’s light as it passes through the atmosphere of one of its exoplanets. Scientists can then use that data to determine what elements are in the planet’s atmosphere and whether it might be able to support life.</p>
  <h2 id="taking-new-measurements-of-the-world">Taking new measurements of the world</h2>
  <p>In addition to measuring things we previously couldn’t quantify, tomorrow’s sensors will let us measure things we previously didn’t consider quantifying or that we couldn’t conceive of as quantifiable. We might choose to hear at a spectrum as low as an elephant’s or as high as a dolphin’s, or adjust our vision to see ultraviolet, infrared, and other spectra whenever we want.</p>
  <p>With sensors so <a href="https://techxplore.com/news/2020-04-tiny-sensors-penny-transmit-tissue.html">minuscule</a> that 30,000 of them fit on a penny and so powerful that they can record individual nerve signals, we could refine our other senses as well. You may never have considered the possibilities of measuring and quantifying taste, at least not beyond the famous Scoville unit that measures the heat of a hot pepper. But researchers have. Hypertaste is an <a href="https://www.ibm.com/blogs/research/2019/07/hypertaste-ai-assisted-etongue/">AI-assisted digital tongue</a> that can identify complex liquids quickly by using sensors that respond to different combinations of molecules to develop “fingerprints” (or would that be “tongueprints”?) of specific liquids and comparing them to a database of known liquids.</p>
  <p>Electronic noses aren’t as far along in development, maybe because scent can be as emotional as it is objective. But researchers are also exploring how to <a href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acsami.9b16561">engineer sensor arrays</a> that can be tuned to distinguish specific odors, from the fruity breath characteristic of <a href="https://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.1088/1752-7163/aafc77">diabetics</a> to the chemical compounds suggesting a <a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s11633-019-1212-9">sewage</a> leak.</p>
  <p>Consider the <a href="https://phys.org/news/2020-01-zeroing-electronic-nose-air-quality.html">potential use cases</a> for sensor-driven senses. They could deliver early warnings for <a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-india-50313344">environmental disasters</a>, detect <a href="https://phys.org/news/2020-03-submersible-sensors-rapidly-bacterial-pollution.html">contaminated water</a>, and track <a href="https://news.mit.edu/2020/ethylene-sensor-food-waste-0318">food freshness</a> throughout the supply chain. A shopping AI might even draw on data from warehouse sensors to evaluate a particular product against quality checks and a customer’s known preferences: Has this <a href="https://phys.org/news/2019-05-sensor.html">milk</a> gone bad? Is this sweater too <a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2019-05/lu-ans051419.php">warm</a> or itchy? Is this air freshener pleasantly fragrant, or will it instantly trigger the customer’s allergies?</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cd10b2c583cad4e5ead5f37e87e754cc69a41c7d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cd10b2c583cad4e5ead5f37e87e754cc69a41c7d.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1cd10b2c583cad4e5ead5f37e87e754cc69a41c7d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="A futuristic electronic eye depicting the advances in medical technology embedded in the human form" src="./media_1cd10b2c583cad4e5ead5f37e87e754cc69a41c7d.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1958" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="well-see-you-in-our-dream">We’ll see you in our dream</h2>
  <p>Some scientists are even working on sensors that will let us improve our lives <a href="https://futurism.com/mit-scientists-devices-hack-dreams">while we sleep</a>. <a href="https://www.umass.edu/newsoffice/article/research-team-introduces-%E2%80%98phyjama%E2%80%99">Pajamas</a> that can sense the wearer’s heartbeat, breathing, and sleep posture will be a boon for everyone, from people with sleep apnea to elderly residents of long-term care facilities, alerting them and their caretakers when they need to wake up, roll over, or call for emergency care.</p>
  <p>And while the movie <em>Inception</em> remains a masterpiece of science fiction, sensors will bring us a bit closer to its world of altered dreams. MIT’s Dream Lab is working on open-source wearables that can detect what <a href="https://onezero.medium.com/an-mit-lab-is-building-devices-to-hack-your-dreams-d1a10ff932e3">stage of sleep</a> you’re in based on your muscle tone, heart rate, and skin conductance, and then change what you’re dreaming about by playing a prerecorded audio cue or emitting a scent at the moment you’re most receptive to it. You could enhance a new habit by hearing the word exercise, break yourself out of a nightmare with a whiff of a favorite food, or use the scent of a loved one’s perfume to help yourself heal from trauma and PTSD.</p>
  <p>If you can measure something – capture it, record it, and quantify it – you can act on it. And with ever-tinier, increasingly capable sensors that assess almost anything, we’ll gain new insights and abilities to transform our minds, bodies, and the planet.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>content-type/trends-predictions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Connecting the Disconnected Using SMS to Reduce Sexual Violence Against Nigerian Women and Girls]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/connecting-the-disconnected-using-sms-to-reduce-sexual-violence-against-nigerian-women-and-girls</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/connecting-the-disconnected-using-sms-to-reduce-sexual-violence-against-nigerian-women-and-girls</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Women At Risk International Foundation (WARIF) founder, Dr. Kemi DaSilva, is doubling down on her passion to help vulnerable populations in rural Nigeria. One year...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>