<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/content-type/use-case/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Who Really Runs Your Organization]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/who-really-runs-your-organization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/who-really-runs-your-organization</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Organizational network analysis provides a data-based view into the informal interactions that make companies work.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bee56882580d353aa873b9348fc4133202e579b5.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bee56882580d353aa873b9348fc4133202e579b5.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1bee56882580d353aa873b9348fc4133202e579b5.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Magnifying glass on woman’s headshot among others in a yearbook-style layout." src="./media_1bee56882580d353aa873b9348fc4133202e579b5.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="who-really-runs-your-organization">Who Really Runs Your Organization</h1>
        <p>Organizational network analysis provides a data-based view into the informal interactions that make companies work.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Large companies with geographically dispersed workforces, an ongoing need for the best talent, and the desire to have an adaptive collaborative organization are finding a decades-old academic instrument – organizational network analysis (ONA) – has fresh relevance. ONA, a technique originated by sociologists, maps the informal networks that play just as crucial a role as formal organizational charts in shaping employee experiences, delivering business benefits, and improving operational efficiencies.</p>
  <p>Analyzing how people work together, the networks they form to get work done, make decisions, and act on them, reveals how organizations really operate. And it’s typically not the command-and-control structures that leaders have drawn up.</p>
  <p>For decades, companies have relied on static organizational charts to clarify roles, improve communication, and streamline decision-making. “Julius Caesar organized his army into commanders and lieutenants – a hierarchy that is basically how employees work today,” says Maya Bodan, leader of the organization strategy and design talent group for Deloitte LLP in San Francisco, California.</p>
  <p>ONA is a tool for creating visual representations of how communications, information, and decisions flow through an organization using data from employee surveys, enterprise systems, and other sources. Unlike an organizational chart’s breakdown structure, ONA provides “an x-ray” into how a company actually works by “mapping patterns of connectivity and collaboration inside the organization,” says Rob Cross, an expert on ONA and SVP of research at the Institute for Corporate Productivity.</p>
  <p>By making strategically important individuals visible, the analysis sheds light on informal relationships and invisible patterns, providing deep insight into how information flows, the identity of key influencers, and the existence of silos that can lead to bottlenecks. This has never been more important – or more possible – than in today’s geographically dispersed employees working together using virtual collaboration tools.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">A very small set of people have a disproportionate impact on how work gets done.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Rob Cross, SVP of research, Institute for Corporate Productivity</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Experts describe how the results of an organizational analysis highlight different types of individual contributors. Cross says ONA can reveal, for example, who in the company is a <strong>central connector</strong>, someone whom other members of the network consult frequently for information and hold the network together; <strong>knowledge brokers</strong>, people who connect different groups or teams within a network, and <strong>peripheral</strong>, those who have limited connections with the rest of the network.</p>
  <p>These characterizations can reveal who the major influencers and actors are in an organization, as well as those who could benefit from more engagement. (As you will learn in this article, there are additional employee archetypes.)</p>
  <p>Consider this hypothetical. Mark serves as a central connector in a large pharmaceutical company. As an entry-level data administrator, Mark is low on the corporate hierarchy, but he is critical in that he connects human resources, sales, and marketing colleagues by serving as a conduit for the exchange of ideas and information. Mia, on the other hand, is an expert coder who is great at developing apps, but she is peripheral – disconnected from others in the employee network who could assist and collaborate with her. On paper, Mia’s programmer title may be higher in the organizational hierarchy. However, she is unable to make the connections she needs to progress and be selected for high-value projects.</p>
  <p>These are the kinds of situations and relationships that exist in organizations of any substantial size. Understanding them in depth can help leaders foster more collaboration, enhance employee engagement, and promote talent development.</p>
  <p>But these benefits rely on good data. Organizations need to allay fears about data privacy, communicate the advantages of ONA to employees, and remain clear-eyed about the technology’s limitations.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_157d0358d0a6015b3e3aae97be8899e42f73f7091.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_157d0358d0a6015b3e3aae97be8899e42f73f7091.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_157d0358d0a6015b3e3aae97be8899e42f73f7091.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Man and woman coworkers having a discussion and looking at post-it notes on a clear whiteboard." src="./media_157d0358d0a6015b3e3aae97be8899e42f73f7091.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="visibility-into-far-flung-workforces">Visibility into far-flung workforces</h2>
  <p>Organizational network analysis emerged in the 1930s as a framework for sociologists to study the social interactions of prison inmates and reform school girls. Then, the work was done through observation and paper diagrams. In recent years, ONA has found a foothold in the corporate world for two reasons: the changing nature of work and the ability to analyze communications and other data.</p>
  <p>Over the past few years, organizations of all kinds have gone to great lengths to set up distributed, geographically dispersed, flexible teams. The workplace changes that occurred during the COVID-19 pandemic only reinforce the idea that employees need to be able to respond quickly to change and have the necessary space to pivot and experiment.</p>
  <p>However, companies’ work to make this shift has led to a new challenge: gaps of knowledge and awareness that prevent leaders from knowing who’s working effectively with whom on a wide range of projects.</p>
  <p>This is where the data comes in. Never before have organizations had access to vast volumes of passive data – information that exists within the company, such as e-mail, chat, calendar, and collaboration-software data. Unlike active data, gathered from time-consuming surveys typically administered by human resources teams, passive data provides a more objective, less biased view of workplace dynamics without requiring direct input from employees.</p>
  <p>ONA applications are also becoming easier to use, notes Bodan of Deloitte. “In the past, you needed a data science degree [to understand ONA],” says Bodan. “But there are many user-friendly platforms now that allow non-technical users like HR professionals to easily interpret the data and drive insights.”</p>
  <p>Together, the rise of remote work, passive data, and easier-to-use ONA tools are encouraging organizations to make ONA a key component of their talent strategy, experts say.</p>
  <h2 id="revealing-the-most-valuable-network-players">Revealing the most valuable (network) players</h2>
  <p>As its name suggests, ONA is about analyzing the networks among people who work together. Its value lies in helping companies identify important connections and potential obstacles to information flow and collaboration. ONA can serve like a tide that washes away the sand to reveal what’s hidden underneath. The results of an analysis can pinpoint different employee archetypes that don’t always show up in organizational charts. For example:</p>
  <h3 id="hidden-value-creators">Hidden-value creators</h3>
  <p>One important node in an organizational network is hidden-value creators – employees who contribute significantly to an organization yet are easily overlooked due to factors, such as geographic location, communication style, or corporate rank.</p>
  <p>“A very small set of people have a disproportionate impact on how work gets done,” says Cross of i4cp. He notes that, based on his work with more than 300 organizations, he has found that, on average, 2% to 3% of employees account for 20% to 35% of an organization’s key collaborative work. The problem, he says, is “if these workers are overlooked, they’re far more likely to leave the organization and take their networks with them.”</p>
  <p>ONA can cast a light on these unsung heroes, giving leaders the opportunity to offer incentives for them to stay and keep valuable networks intact.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-only-path-forward-is-together">The only path forward is together</h3>
        <p>Discover how business networks find new avenues for growth and innovation.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/blogs/ext-business-networks-the-only-path-forward">Read more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="energizers">Energizers</h3>
  <p>Energizers are positive thinkers who are quick to support coworkers’ ideas and “leave people feeling better after an interaction,” says Peter Gray, an ONA expert and professor of commerce at the University of Virginia’s McIntire School of Commerce in Charlottesville, Virginia.</p>
  <p>Gray’s research highlights the role human behavior can play in building a network. The most effective networks include energizers, says Gray. A single energizer in a network can greatly reduce the risk of attrition among team members while leading high performance.</p>
  <p>Organizational network analysis can help identify these such contributors, Gray says, by asking employees in a survey to identify the people in the company who make them feel good about themselves.</p>
  <h3 id="fast-movers">Fast movers</h3>
  <p>Employees who make a concerted effort to discover coworkers’ needs are also more likely to establish mutually beneficial and meaningful connections with coworkers. For example, while researching employee relationships, Cross discovered that 10% to 15% of employees are “fast movers” who become well-connected in less than a year after hiring (most workers require three to five years to become well-connected.) These fast movers, Cross says, share an interesting trait: When asked to disclose information about themselves, “fast movers are much more likely to pivot in that moment and say, ‘I can, but can you first give me a sense of what your priorities are? What are you excited about? What keeps you up at night?’”</p>
  <p>By investing in coworkers’ needs, Cross says fast movers are not only able to infiltrate powerful networks at rapid speed, but they are also more likely to be tapped for high-value projects.</p>
  <h3 id="weak-nodes">Weak nodes</h3>
  <p>As one might expect, the analysis can also highlight employees who are not well-connected to their networks. These weak nodes represent a situation that can “undercut an organization’s ability to deliver enterprise value,” Cross says. Underutilized and at higher risk of departure, he says these siloed workers can create “breakdowns in connectivity that are likely to hurt a company in terms of revenue potential, innovation, scale, or efficiencies – quantifiable points of impact.”</p>
  <p>In this scenario, knowledge is power. By identifying disconnected employees, organizations can stage team-building exercises and launch cross-functional projects that connect these peripheral players to central connectors and knowledge brokers for a more solid network.</p>
  <p>The good news is organizations are finding ways to bridge the gaps of knowledge created by issues related to scalability, engagement, and context. These best practices are not only helping organizations identify key influencers and isolated figures within a network, but also gaining a better understanding of how people work in today’s modern world and why some succeed – and others don’t.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1357353a61bace47c09b540d83a232c12e79cf37f.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1357353a61bace47c09b540d83a232c12e79cf37f.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1357353a61bace47c09b540d83a232c12e79cf37f.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Man working at a creative office using his computer with blurred coworkers moving in the background." src="./media_1357353a61bace47c09b540d83a232c12e79cf37f.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="when-insight-leads-to-new-organizational-structures">When insight leads to new organizational structures</h2>
  <p>Retaining hidden talent and connecting valuable outliers aren’t the only business benefits of using ONA. Organizations can also realize substantial operational gains by visualizing the informal relationships that exist within an organization.</p>
  <p>Deloitte’s Bodan describes one client who had 14 different functions, including legal, finance, and accounts payable, all working within a single business unit. Desperate to break down these functional silos, Bodan says the company turned to ONA. Upon analyzing the company’s passive and active data, “we discovered that the natural communities that existed, based on how people operate on a day-to-day basis, was actually four,” she says. Moreover, although the company’s organizational chart dictated that employees collaborate according to function, networks had formed naturally around customer segments.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">The modern workplace “is moving away from functional fiefdoms to a much more collaborative environment.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Maya Bodan, leader of the organization strategy and design talent group, Deloitte LLP</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In response, Bodan says the company whittled down its 14 functional silos into six key collaborative groups, each one dedicated to a particular customer segment. Creating these more meaningful and connected groups not only provided employees “with much more of an end-to-end view of how they’re working,” says Bodan, but also helped to increase speed to market, improve customer experience, and streamline decision-making.</p>
  <p>That’s a case when the analysis leads to organizational change. However, realizing such a result requires overcoming a set of challenges.</p>
  <h2 id="addressing-challenges-to-implementing-ona">Addressing challenges to implementing ONA</h2>
  <p>To achieve the benefits of ONA, companies will need to address technological, cultural, and organizational challenges to effectively apply it.</p>
  <h3 id="confronting-privacy-concerns">Confronting privacy concerns</h3>
  <p>As with any data-crunching tool, privacy concerns can limit the value organizations derive from ONA. Although employees can opt out of participating in a survey, passive data is generated from e-mail, texting, calendars, and collaboration applications without any employee involvement – or expressed consent.</p>
  <p>“Privacy has to be handled incredibly carefully in terms of how and what you're disclosing and to whom,” says Cross.</p>
  <p>But while establishing privacy practices related to disclosure can help protect employees, most ONA tools are already limited in terms of the data they’re able to gather, according to Gray, the University of Virginia professor.</p>
  <p>For example, Gray says, “Passive network data collection software programs that mine e-mail and meeting data are excellent at stripping out any information that could get a company in trouble.” That’s not to suggest, however, that passive data isn’t worth parsing. Rather, by examining the nature of e-mail exchanges, not the communication itself, organizations can discover patterns of collaboration, including which employees are most likely to respond to messages after work hours, and from whom – telltale signs of important relationships.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="hr-and-the-use-of-ai">HR and the Use of AI</h3>
        <p>Learn how HR can lead the way for AI adoption in your organization.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/how-hr-can-direct-use-of-ai">Read more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="managing-scalability-limitations">Managing scalability limitations</h3>
  <p>Another obstacle to effective ONA is the nature of work itself – especially when the organization itself is very large. Multinational corporations have hundreds of thousands of employees, making it impractical to chart every single worker and their respective networks. Many employees simply don’t have the time to respond to lengthy surveys, which can prevent companies from achieving the response rates needed for accuracy. Passive data in isolation can fail to provide the necessary context for truly understanding the ties that bind employees.</p>
  <p>For example, is a particularly intense rally of text messages about a business-critical project or Sunday brunch plans? And what exactly constitutes a positive link between two employees? There are simply no standards for what a good network should look like.</p>
  <p>Leaders need to account for these potential weaknesses – just as they adjust their sights when evaluating outputs from business analytics systems with the knowledge that the results reflect incomplete data.</p>
  <h3 id="securing-employee-acceptance">Securing employee acceptance</h3>
  <p>Even the most clearly marked targets can be missed if employees aren’t on board with ONA. “There is sometimes a concern that ONA will be used in regressive ways – that it will be used to fire people,” says Gray. For this reason, he recommends that managers earn employee trust by assuring them that the insights generated by ONA will be used in ways that will benefit them directly, such as improving performance, pinpointing places to build strong connections, and uncovering hidden factors for success.</p>
  <p>Leaders must also take steps to present the discoveries made by ONA as compelling information rather than intractable truths. Consider, for example, the damage that could be done if a veteran manager learns that his energizer score is a fraction of the department’s latest hire. To avoid conflict and bruised egos, Gray says employees should be offered training on how to become more of an energizer, because “there are actual behaviors they can adopt to change their energizing score. You have to help them see that this is a function of behaviors that are malleable and change over time. No one is doomed.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1135fcc02c642fb46d5450b14b8a4a9b76968a37e.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1135fcc02c642fb46d5450b14b8a4a9b76968a37e.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1135fcc02c642fb46d5450b14b8a4a9b76968a37e.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Diverse group of businesspeople around a desk smiling cheerfully during an office meeting." src="./media_1135fcc02c642fb46d5450b14b8a4a9b76968a37e.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="adopting-a-data-first-method-to-organizational-thinking">Adopting a data-first method to organizational thinking</h2>
  <p>Adopting ONA will require leaders to use a data-first method to measure and illustrate the collaboration patterns among employees, says Bodan. Moreover, she adds, an “adaptable mindset” is crucial, because ONA’s analysis of the strength, frequency, and nature of employee interactions may reveal some counterintuitive truths about which employees really wield influence in the organization and which ones are simply coasting on their titles.</p>
  <p>Either way, says Bodan, the modern workplace “is moving away from functional fiefdoms to a much more collaborative environment”– one in which ONA can serve as a valuable tool and the hierarchy of Caeser’s legions really is history.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adapting Agile for the Enterprise]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/adapting-agile-for-the-enterprise</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/adapting-agile-for-the-enterprise</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Can other corporate functions adopt the software world’s Agile methodology? We explore what works best and where.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[8 Examples of Artificial Intelligence in Action]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/eight-examples-of-artificial-intelligence-in-action</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/eight-examples-of-artificial-intelligence-in-action</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Enterprise use of AI is growing fast. Here are eight examples with lessons for businesses of all kinds.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Four Steps for Hunting for Advanced Manufacturing Talent]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/hunting-for-advanced-manufacturing-talent-four-moves</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/hunting-for-advanced-manufacturing-talent-four-moves</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To source advanced manufacturing talent, companies can start by updating training and job listings.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ERP Security in a Cybercrime World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/erp-security</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/erp-security</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn why ERP security is crucial to overall software security for your entire business. Cloud ERP solutions are designed for more secure data and better cybersecurity.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ERP for manufacturing: Now more than ever]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/erp-for-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/erp-for-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how cloud-based ERP for manufacturing can integrate cloud manufacturing processes with supply chain and the rest of your manufacturing operations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>industry/industrial-manufacturing</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Green Logistics: What It Is and Why It Matters]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/green-logistics</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/green-logistics</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how green logistics and sustainable distribution networks are helping businesses reduce carbon footprint and meet consumer demands.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d833e4ccd4df8048b6491d5f4b13015956b5a6a1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d833e4ccd4df8048b6491d5f4b13015956b5a6a1.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1d833e4ccd4df8048b6491d5f4b13015956b5a6a1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Electric vehicles are an essential component of a greener future for logistics networks" src="./media_1d833e4ccd4df8048b6491d5f4b13015956b5a6a1.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="green-logistics-what-it-is-and-why-it-matters">Green Logistics: What It Is and Why It Matters</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Green logistics includes any business practice that minimizes the environmental impact of the logistics network and delivery. Sustainable logistics or green logistics secure a strong bottom line without sacrificing customer satisfaction, or the well-being of the planet. Intelligent businesses are rushing to understand and embrace sustainable logistics management, supported by powerful technologies such as artificial intelligence, machine learning, and advanced analytics.</p>
  <p>As enterprises make the shift toward greener logistics, they realize benefits across the business, including improved profitability and good corporate citizenship. But a primary driver is customer demand. As customers (both businesses and consumers) see the real-world results of climate change on newsfeeds and streaming channels daily, they are quickly shifting loyalties to companies that demonstrate significant, permanent steps toward a sustainable future. Customers (and shareholders) advocate for a circular supply chain that incorporates reverse logistics, and are not content with or influenced by “greenwashing.”</p>
  <h2 id="reverse-logistics-and-circular-supply-chains">Reverse logistics and circular supply chains</h2>
  <p>Traditionally, supply chains have been linear and unidirectional: raw materials are processed into products and shipped to customers, who then dispose of them. Today, this flow is being disrupted with two practices – reverse logistics and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability/what-is-circular-economy.html">circular supply chains</a> – that add bottom-line value to supply chains <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/what-is-a-sustainable-supply-chain.html">while reducing environmental impact</a>.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Reverse logistics:</strong> As the name implies, reverse logistics refers to processes related to the return of items and goods traveling backward through the supply chain. This can include repairs and maintenance, returns of defective items, reuse of packaging, or recycling and reclamation of end-of-life products. For businesses, today’s reverse logistics challenges most often come <a href="/resources/business-of-returning-things">in the form of customer returns</a>. Online purchases contribute to a much higher rate of customer returns than in-store purchases. This issue is further exacerbated by the business model of “subscription box” brands (typically fashion), which are based entirely on the concept of customers selecting from a wide assortment of delivered goods and returning whatever they decide not to keep. In fact, as this trend progresses, estimates are for the global amount of e-commerce returns to exceed <a href="https://www.the-future-of-commerce.com/2021/05/11/ecommerce-returns-marketing-metrics/">one trillion dollars</a> over the coming decade. Furthermore, transporting returned inventory creates more than <a href="https://www.optoro.com/2018-impact-report/">15 million metric tons</a> of CO2 in the U.S. alone each year.</li>
    <li><strong>Circular supply chains</strong>: A <a href="/resources/circular-economy-sustainable-profitability">circular supply chain</a> is a loop in which organizations reclaim as much as possible, from raw materials to finished products. In its simplest form, this means realizing value from end-of-life products, often by recycling their primary components. For example, plastics can be shredded and repurposed – even into the very shipping pallets that are used to move goods. And as the world’s metal supplies diminish, there is meaningful value to be had in extracting gold, copper, and other recyclable commodities from otherwise discarded items.</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="circularity-is-going-mainstream">Circularity is Going Mainstream</h3>
        <p>Learn how companies are using circular models to improve their performance.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/the-circular-economy-goes-mainstream">Read the guide</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="green-transport-and-the-growing-use-of-commercial-evs">Green transport and the growing use of commercial EVs</h2>
  <p>At the height of the COVID pandemic, online shopping rose to an all-time high with parcel volume in the US alone, growing 37% from 2019 to 2020, reaching <a href="https://www.pitneybowes.com/content/dam/pitneybowes/us/en/shipping-index/parcel-shipping-index-ebook.pdf">55 million deliveries each day</a>. The Amazon Effect put further strain on logistics operations with consumers expecting deliveries within a day – and sometimes even within a few hours. This means goods can no longer be warehoused in a single location and distributed nationally. To achieve such aggressive delivery speeds, items must be stored in local distribution centers and then rushed to consumers in smaller batches. This calls for larger fleets of smaller vehicles.</p>
  <p>And as the pandemic shifts and restrictions lift, these trends show no sign of slowing. According to the <a href="https://www.weforum.org/press/2020/01/urban-deliveries-expected-to-add-11-minutes-to-daily-commute-and-increase-carbon-emissions-by-30-until-2030-without-effective-intervention-e3141b32fa/">World Economic Forum</a>, we should expect demand for urban <a href="/resources/last-mile-logistics">last-mile delivery</a> to grow as much as 78% by 2030, and add up to 36% more delivery vehicles in the world’s largest 100 cities.</p>
  <p>To meet these changing delivery demands, businesses are rapidly shifting to EV fleets. At less than half the cost per mile for electricity as for gas or diesel, and without any need for tune-ups or oil changes, EV fleets have lower operating costs and <a href="https://www.thedetroitbureau.com/2022/02/commercial-ev-market-will-grow-faster-than-retail-side-forecasts-ram-boss/">less downtime</a>. For businesses, another advantage of EVs is the ease with which they can be integrated into a greater cloud-connected supply chain network. This means that businesses can use AI-powered technologies to analyze both past and real-time operational data – delivering powerful (and actionable) insights into ways to save money, lower fuel consumption, and streamline their operations overall.</p>
  <p>The capacity and size of modern EVs is also becoming increasingly diverse. Today, we are seeing a rise in not only light commercial vehicles (LCVs) like cargo vans but also a growing range of electric semi-trucks and long-haul transport vehicles.</p>
  <p>And when it comes to greener transport, let’s not forget that some 80-90% of the world’s goods are transported by sea. Each year, container ships spew about 1 billion metric tons of carbon dioxide into the air — about <a href="https://www.npr.org/2021/12/01/1060382176/shipping-industry-is-pressured-to-cut-pollution-caused-by-merchant-fleet">three percent of all greenhouse gas emissions</a> — and tons of toxic waste left in the oceans. Recognizing this, in September 2021, the International Maritime Organization (IMO), representing 150 industry leaders, set a <a href="https://www.imo.org/en/MediaCentre/HotTopics/Pages/Reducing-greenhouse-gas-emissions-from-ships.aspx">decarbonization goal</a> to reduce emissions by 50% by 2050, compared to 2008 levels.</p>
  <p>Danish company Maersk (whose ships emitted 33 million tons of CO<sub>2</sub> in 2020) ordered eight new vessels that run on <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/sustainable-business/maersk-orders-eight-vessels-able-run-carbon-neutral-methanol-2021-08-24/">carbon-neutral methanol</a> to help meet that ambitious goal. Shipping companies in Japan and Norway are also bringing significant innovation to the marine cargo sector, unveiling fully electric tanker ships and even the world’s first autonomous electric cargo carrier which (using radar, infrared, and automotive integrated solutions cameras) can be operated and moored entirely via remote control.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18fda86a6db710bcbb0bfbe3d47d56def23a6b95d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18fda86a6db710bcbb0bfbe3d47d56def23a6b95d.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_18fda86a6db710bcbb0bfbe3d47d56def23a6b95d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Delivery driver using connected logistics software" src="./media_18fda86a6db710bcbb0bfbe3d47d56def23a6b95d.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>A connected logistics system helps improve profitability and brand perceptions while reducing environmental impact.</em></p>
  <h2 id="alternative-distribution-networks-and-green-logistics-solutions">Alternative distribution networks and green logistics solutions</h2>
  <p>Of course, making the switch to EVs and alternative fuels is probably the most significant change when it comes to greener logistics. However, as <a href="https://www.weforum.org/press/2020/01/urban-deliveries-expected-to-add-11-minutes-to-daily-commute-and-increase-carbon-emissions-by-30-until-2030-without-effective-intervention-e3141b32fa/">McKinsey’s Bernd Heid</a> points out “<em>in an 'ecosystem scenario' in which both public and private players work together effectively, delivery emissions and congestion could be reduced by 30%...when compared to a 'do nothing' scenario</em>”. To achieve maximum cost efficiency, faster delivery speeds, and meaningful reductions in emissions and waste, businesses will need to consider more collaborative logistics methods, and a more sophisticated array of optimizations.</p>
  <p>A few additional optimization strategies include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Load pooling:</strong> A growing trend in optimized <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/what-is-supply-chain-management.html">supply chain management</a> sees similar (even competitive) companies working together to pool their warehouse and logistics resources. At first glance, this can seem like a challenging concept but fortunately, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/supply-chain-logistics.html">cloud-connected logistics management technologies</a> are helping businesses to collaborate and cooperate with maximum visibility and control.</li>
    <li><strong>Unbranded parcel lockers</strong>: Amazon pioneered the idea of neighborhood parcel lockers to shorten routes and speed up delivery. This is highly effective but has tended to shut out the competition. Unbranded community parcel lockers function similarly to the existing Amazon locker networks, but are accessible to a much broader range of delivery providers. By making this resource more widely available, the major logistics providers can work together to save time and money – and improve consumer choice.</li>
    <li><strong>Automated load optimization</strong>: This refers to coordinating items (held in warehouses and distribution centers) with similar delivery ETAs and destinations. With today’s volumes, it’s essentially impossible to achieve this via manual efforts but smart supply chain solutions can identify and automate vehicle loading, to help eliminate the costly practice of sending delivery vans out with only half a load.</li>
    <li><strong>Night-time delivery</strong>: The more time vehicles spend on the road, the greater the amount of fuel and energy used. Especially in urban areas, making deliveries at night can reduce road-time and congestion by <a href="https://www.weforum.org/press/2020/01/urban-deliveries-expected-to-add-11-minutes-to-daily-commute-and-increase-carbon-emissions-by-30-until-2030-without-effective-intervention-e3141b32fa/">up to 15%</a>. Furthermore, with EVs being quieter, there is less risk of adding to night-time noise pollution.</li>
    <li><strong>On-demand micro-mobility networks</strong>: Micro-mobility refers to small – often two-wheeled – vehicles like electric scooters and e-bikes. Modern logistics technologies now give drivers easy access to cloud-connected apps. This means connectivity with the home base (dispatch) and the customer (delivery ETAs) in real time. By leveraging an on-demand network of independent drivers (not exclusively employed by any one business), companies are reaping significant savings in both fuel usage, and the cost of maintaining standing fleets.</li>
    <li><strong>Dynamic route allocation</strong>: In urban settings, cloud-connected route allocation tools can assess traffic, parking, even construction or other delays. In rural areas, other factors may be more relevant such as road and weather conditions, or distance from EV charging stations. By incorporating this kind of intel into real-time route planning, companies can increase delivery speed and minimize fuel consumption.</li>
    <li><strong>Drones and automated vehicles</strong>: It’s visually compelling to think of drones crossing the skies and dropping packages like mechanized storks, or unmanned robots rolling down city sidewalks, laden with parcels. In reality though, we are still a few years away from fully automated logistics networks. But innovation is fast in this sector and digital automation is at the fore of many green solutions – so watch this space…</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sustainable-logistics-on-the-move">Sustainable Logistics on the Move</h3>
        <p>How technology is paving the way to greener, more sustainable logistics.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/sustainable-logistics-on-the-move">Explore the story</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="advantages-of-green-logistics">Advantages of green logistics</h2>
  <p>The advantages of green logistics accrue to the company, its suppliers and partners, its customers, and every member of society. Here are just a few:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Improved long-term profitability</strong>: From first to last-mile delivery, green logistics cut waste, cost, and carbon emissions. Although realizing the advantages of green logistics requires an upfront investment, the downstream benefit outweighs the cost. A recent <a href="https://www.hbs.edu/ris/Publication%20Files/SSRN-id1964011_6791edac-7daa-4603-a220-4a0c6c7a3f7a.pdf">study</a> found “evidence that High Sustainability companies significantly outperform their counterparts over the long-term, both in terms of stock market as well as accounting performance.” The bottom line? Green business equals good business.</li>
    <li><strong>New or enhanced partnerships</strong>: When businesses use <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/what-is-a-sustainable-supply-chain.html">sustainable supply chains</a> and green logistics, they’re not only more attractive to customers but to corporate partners as well. A recent study from <a href="https://hbr.org/2020/03/a-more-sustainable-supply-chain">HBR</a> found that the largest global multinationals are using the United Nations Global Compact or the Carbon Disclosure Project’s (CDP’s) Supply Chain Program to assess their suppliers’ levels of sustainability and environmental impact. Suppliers, in turn, are eager to partner with the largest brands and are making investments to try to reduce their carbon footprints.</li>
    <li><strong>Happier, loyal customers</strong>: Customers – both retail and business – demand fast delivery and the flexibility to make easy returns. They want to know where their products came from, whether they’re sustainably sourced and transported, and where they are in their journey – in real time. Companies that offer these insights and transparency gain new customers and earn long-term loyalty among existing ones.</li>
    <li><strong>Better corporate responsibility reputation:</strong> Large companies are increasingly called to the mat to answer for their contribution to global warming, which is considered a social justice issue. Publicly leveraging the advantages of green logistics will help companies win in the court of public opinion. Smart companies are scrutinizing their environmental footprint locally, as well as globally. Those that aren’t willing to change, especially in moving away from fossil fuels, risk their reputation and are at a competitive disadvantage.</li>
    <li><strong>Easier recruitment:</strong> In the tightest job market in decades, every company advantage matters. An organization focused on green logistics is more attractive to young professionals who desire to work for a company that embodies their values.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="green-logistics-strategies">Green logistics strategies</h2>
  <p>Organizations that combine a cloud-based smart supply chain with mobile technologies get a birds-eye view of their entire logistics process, from manufacturing to delivery to returns. But green logistics isn’t achieved in isolation. Successful implementation requires planning and the inclusion of all the various stakeholders. Below are a few suggested steps:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Collaborate with suppliers, vendors, third- and fourth-party logistics (3PL and 4PL) partners, and experienced advisors to develop environmentally-friendly procurement protocols and eco-friendly shipping options.</li>
    <li>Use AI-powered technologies like <a href="/resources/supply-chain-control-tower">supply chain control towers</a> to integrate carbon footprint analysis into all stages of the business.</li>
    <li>Engage with corporate networks to share logistics resources and data-driven insights. Even brands that are typically competitive can become partners for a shared purpose.</li>
    <li>Strategize and right-size your fleet. Build in the ability to handle fluctuating demand with elastic logistic networks so that trucks aren’t sitting idle. For last-mile delivery, consider adding micro-mobility vehicles, such as e-bikes or drones.</li>
    <li>Educate customers on the impact of fast delivery speeds versus more sustainable choices. Amazon, for example, encourages customers to pick an “Amazon Day” that groups packages into fewer shipments, which saves money on packaging and transportation.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="green-logistics-and-the-future-of-distribution-networks">Green logistics and the future of distribution networks</h2>
  <p>Robust, AI-powered, cloud-based logistics solutions are at the core of the supply chains of the future – helping businesses to consolidate loads, automate dispatch and tracking, optimize routes, determine when and where to charge batteries, calculate ETAs, monitor vehicle maintenance, and more. Data modeling and simulations can test routes and fleet capacities, and integrated technologies can help incorporate and analyze supply chain and delivery data across the entire value chain. Every step toward the smoother and faster movement and delivery of goods, is a win/win, making customers happier and more engaged, and helping businesses to improve both their sustainability profiles and their bottom lines.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-green-logistics-solutions">Explore green logistics solutions</h3>
        <p>Achieve your sustainability goals with SAP Supply Chain Logistics software.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/supply-chain-logistics.html">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-supply-chain</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[XaaS and Subscription Business Models: Get Started with Business Model Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/business-model-innovation-xaas</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/business-model-innovation-xaas</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Explore business model innovation and the rise of XaaS and subscription business models – learn about the benefits, examples, and more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e9a0241203aed0aecae5c03a5aff8ff85d77abd9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e9a0241203aed0aecae5c03a5aff8ff85d77abd9.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1e9a0241203aed0aecae5c03a5aff8ff85d77abd9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Connected nodes" src="./media_1e9a0241203aed0aecae5c03a5aff8ff85d77abd9.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="xaas-and-subscription-business-models-how-business-model-innovation-is-driving-growth-strategies">XaaS and subscription business models: How business model innovation is driving growth strategies</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Today we live in a digital world with an estimated 2.5 quintillion bytes of data generated <a href="https://seedscientific.com/how-much-data-is-created-every-day/">every day</a>, transforming how we live, work, and do business. For organizations, this influx of data – coupled with a global shift to cloud-based technology – is fueling business model innovation that’s resulting in greater resiliency, competitiveness, and growth for companies.</p>
  <p>In the past 50 years, the average <a href="https://www.bcg.com/capabilities/innovation-strategy-delivery/business-model-innovation">business model life span</a> has fallen from about 15 years to less than five. And to survive in such a fast-paced environment, organizations must be agile, quickly adapting to changes in technology, market trends, and customer expectations.</p>
  <p>Implementing new business models in response to these changes is critical to the success of the organization. Business model innovation can open up additional lines of revenue, expand market share, and increase profitability. There are also some surprising, and unexpected, benefits emerging as well.</p>
  <h2 id="what-is-a-business-model-what-is-business-model-innovation">What is a business model? What is business model innovation?</h2>
  <p>A business model defines how a company creates, delivers, and captures value. Business models vary based on numerous dimensions – such as key offerings, target market, company resources, and business value chain – and are a critical component in driving a company’s business growth strategy.</p>
  <p>Business model innovation occurs when existing models are modified, or new models are constructed. Often triggered by advances in technology and digitization, new business models such as “everything-as-a-service” or “anything-as-a-service” (XaaS) and subscription-based and are undergoing rapid adoption to help support the business’ strategic vision and ultimate success.</p>
  <p>A classic example of business model innovation is Amazon. Shortly after launching as an online bookseller in 1995, the company began to offer new services beyond books such as Free Super Savers Shipping. Over 10 years (2005-2015), the company’s expansion included cloud computing (Amazon AWS), eBooks, and streaming services (Amazon Music, Amazon Video). By 2015, its market capitalization <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/amazon-bigger-than-walmart-2015-7">surpassed that of Walmart</a>.</p>
  <p>Each time Amazon expanded to incorporate new products or services, it adjusted or created new business models to support its strategy.</p>
  <h2 id="business-model-innovation-today-xaas-and-the-rise-of-subscription-based-business-models">Business model innovation today: XaaS and the rise of subscription-based business models</h2>
  <p>Business models and the kind of innovation that’s happening vary greatly based on industry and business strategy. From consumer products to high tech, businesses are constantly innovating to find new ways to serve customers and grow revenues. Examples include new parents who subscribe to reusable diaper services instead of buying disposables, <a href="https://www.rolls-royce.com/media/press-releases-archive/yr-2012/121030-the-hour.aspx">Rolls-Royce</a> provides engine maintenance and replacement services for their business jets, and automotive companies are providing car subscriptions and even parcel as a service.</p>
  <p>The examples above reflect the growing trend towards implementing “everything-as-a-service” – or XaaS – and subscription business models, a popular type or form of XaaS. These types of digital business models are the result of product/service digitization and the global shift to cloud-based technologies.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10f0b593293a6a924192706e765cb94de984029de.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10f0b593293a6a924192706e765cb94de984029de.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_10f0b593293a6a924192706e765cb94de984029de.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Diagram showing the evolution of business models" src="./media_10f0b593293a6a924192706e765cb94de984029de.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="851">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>The evolution of business models from distinct products and services towards XaaS.</em></p>
  <p>Here are some basic definitions of these important terms:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>What is everything as a service?</strong> XaaS is a broad category of business models in which users access products, tools, technologies, and/or services “as a service.” More traditionally and commonly, in the software industry, XaaS examples include software as a service (SaaS), platform as a service (Paas), and infrastructure as a service (IaaS), but XaaS is not limited to the tech space. Today almost everything is available “as a service.”</li>
    <li><strong>What is a subscription business model?</strong> Subscription-based models are a type of XaaS, where a customer subscribes to services or products – similar to renting – on an ongoing basis. This approach generates monthly or annual recurring subscription revenue for the business. The focus of this model is on retention of a customer versus acquisition to increase the lifetime value (LTV) of each customer. Learn more about <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/financial-management/billing-revenue-innovation-management/what-is-subscription-management.html">subscription management</a>.<br><br>Other forms of XaaS include monetization based on volume of usage – or the outcome – as well as fixed price or variable price approaches.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="why-are-subscription-business-models-so-popular-today">Why are subscription business models so popular today?</h2>
  <p>Aside from cloud and digital technology advances, there are several important reasons why subscription-based models are increasing in popularity. First, selling as a service is more profitable. For example, <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/apple-s-5-most-profitable-lines-of-business-4684130">Apple</a> entered the market in the 1970s as a hardware vendor. In 2008, the company offered its first service, the App Store, selling third-party applications for its iPhone and iPod Touch. By 2019, its services business posted gross margins of 63.7%, almost doubling that of its product division, which posted a 32.2% gross margin.</p>
  <p>Second, a subscription-based model is also a predictable and stable source of revenue for companies, which is especially critical during times of uncertainty – like a pandemic.</p>
  <p>And third, from the customer perspective, it’s beneficial for anyone sensitive or reluctant to invest in large capital expenditures. A service-based model removes the need for companies to make significant investments in turbulent times while opening the door to new products and services at a reasonable cost that were previously out of reach. For smaller and mid-sized businesses this can make a world of difference – giving them access to new tools to compete and grow.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>A subscription-based business model allows companies to deliver meaningful services quickly to customers, bring new offerings to market in less time, accelerate cash collection, and define and modify pricing models.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="what-is-subscription-management">What is subscription management?</h3>
        <p>Learn how subscription managment software helps monetize business models.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/financial-management/billing-revenue-innovation-management/what-is-subscription-management.html">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="examples-of-business-model-innovation-and-xaas">Examples of business model innovation and XaaS</h2>
  <p>A good example of the shift to XaaS (more broadly referred to as “servitization”) is within the manufacturing industry. Manufacturers can now provide access to their products versus selling them (XaaS), bundled with associated services such as maintenance and repair (subscription-based).</p>
  <p>Today, manufacturing companies around the world are adopting XaaS business models. Examples include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2020/06/da2b87c0-9d7d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Hewlett Packard Enterprise</a> (HPE) transformed its traditional product offerings into high-value solutions to generate lifetime customer loyalty and recurring revenue streams.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/09/e0a1c926-fb7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">MOSCA</a>, manufacturer of some of the world’s most advanced strapping machines and materials, is laying the foundation for new business models with a central ERP system and IoT technology.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="the-benefits-of-xaas">The benefits of XaaS</h2>
  <p>The importance of diversifying and adjusting business models to adapt in current market conditions is critical. There are many obvious benefits to businesses, but also some surprising advantages of XaaS that could have a broader impact on how business make things, how consumers use products and services, and the product/service life cycle.</p>
  <p>Here are the key benefits of XaaS and subscription models from a business’ point of view:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Growth through new revenue streams and markets</li>
    <li>Greater predictability and profitability</li>
    <li>Improved resiliency and competitiveness</li>
  </ul>
  <p>From a customer perspective, the benefits include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Greater range and improved quality of products and services</li>
    <li>Lower costs for customer and consumers</li>
    <li>Lower risk as shared with service provider</li>
    <li>More predictability in operations and guaranteed performance</li>
  </ul>
  <p>From a broader perspective, the move to XaaS and the servitization of products can promote a <a href="/resources/circular-economy-sustainable-profitability">circular economy</a> – especially in the manufacturing industry. In this sector, there is a shifting focus from creating a product at a specific point in time to the continued use of that product over an extended period. With this change comes a greater emphasis on the quality, use, longevity, maintenance, and disposal or recycling of the product.</p>
  <p>With greater ownership of the assets across their entire life, ensuring compliance and minimizing waste, energy usage, or carbon emissions makes sense for manufacturers; it also encourages product, material, and waste reuse of recycling. This may even generate new opportunities. In the electric vehicle industry, used or <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/industries/automotive-and-assembly/our-insights/second-life-ev-batteries-the-newest-value-pool-in-energy-storage">“second-life” batteries</a>, for example, are having an effect on the power and energy storage sector – a great example of how sustainability makes business sense.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-future-of-the-as-a-service-model">The future of the as-a-service model</h3>
        <p>Explore the trend towards servitization and its impact.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://podcast.opensap.info/the-future-of-supply-chain/2023/01/25/episode-2-servitization-make-services-a-vital-part-of-your-business-with-patrick-crampton-thomas/?url_id=banner-glo-insights-reg-fundamentals">Listen to the podcast</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="choosing-a-suitable-business-model-strategy">Choosing a suitable business model strategy</h2>
  <p>Since business models vary based on industry and business strategy, there’s no “one-size-fits-all.” Instead, you should consider the unique needs of your company and the specific growth strategies you intend to implement.</p>
  <p>Common factors for consideration include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Technology:</strong> Is your existing infrastructure able to support the strategic vision of the company? Business model innovation will require connected products that are networkable, digital, and even sensor-equipped – and the ability to use the data from the connected products and equipment within new processes.</li>
    <li><strong>Data:</strong> Is your data centralized or siloed? Business model innovation relies on advanced data modelling and predictive capabilities to support analytics and forecasting.</li>
    <li><strong>IT infrastructure:</strong> Is your IT core robust and flexible enough to share data across the value chain to support a range of models such as information technology/operational technology (IT/OT) collaboration?</li>
    <li><strong>Pricing and packaging:</strong> How sophisticated is your pricing and packaging models? Will these need to be adjusted to support a new business model?</li>
  </ul>
  <p>You must also consider organizational support. Business model innovation often requires that the company and individual stakeholders shift what may be long-held business perspectives. How easily will the company adjust to a customer-centric versus product-centric business model?</p>
  <p>The business will also have to shift from one-time (usually capex sales) to a recurring (usually opex) financial model. This impacts compensation, margins, and reporting – a big change, especially for sales. Will these changes be supported across all teams or will additional effort be required to bring everyone onboard? And, do you have a strong business network of partners that are open to collaboration?</p>
  <h2 id="technology-and-business-model-innovation--where-to-start">Technology and business model innovation – where to start</h2>
  <p>Understanding where to start on the path to business model innovation is challenging, especially when you have an established business with various customer bases, revenue streams, and stakeholders.</p>
  <p>Starting with a strong foundation using an intelligent <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp.html">cloud-based ERP system</a> with embedded artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning is essential. Look for a system that can:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Seamlessly manage a variety of contracts that include different types of products, services, and pricing</li>
    <li>Build and execute subscription and/or recurring billing models easily</li>
    <li>Manage revenue recognition and partner settlement</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The system must be flexible and adaptable, supporting contract changes, such as price, contract duration, and other details. A good ERP system will include these <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/financial-management/billing-revenue-innovation-management.html">billing capabilities</a> or can be purchased as an add-on to your existing ERP system and licensed separately.</p>
  <p>As your business model strategy matures and you gain access to usage and other data intelligence, such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-iot.html">Internet of Things (IoT) data</a> from equipment and products, you can develop additional revenue models such as bill-based metering. This requires smart, connected products that support the flow and sharing of data. It also requires a collaborative asset network where data and processes are shared.</p>
  <h2 id="digital-business-model-faqs">Digital business model FAQs</h2>
  <div class="accordion">
    <div>
      <div>What is servitization?</div>
      <div>
        <p>Servitization refers to the trend away from a single sale, towards using products to sell additional services. These can be service and maintenance contracts, everything as a service (XaaS), or “outcome as a service.”</p>
        <p>This is a common trend in the manufacturing industry, where manufacturers move from simply building and selling a product. They start adding additional services and products and may sell direct to consumers. In this approach manufacturers get closer to customers, provide more value to them, and retain them by providing different levels of service differentiation.</p>
        <p>There are four levels of servitization within manufacturing:</p>
        <ul>
          <li><strong>Distinct products and services:</strong> This is the basics of manufacturing businesses in which products and equipment are built and then sold to customers. There is very limited customer involvement once products are sold, and also limited revenue.</li>
          <li><strong>Bundles of products:</strong> Similar to the above, but the products are more personalized.</li>
          <li><strong>Aftersales and subscription servicing, repairs, and condition monitoring:</strong> In this level, the maintenance of a product provides an ongoing source of revenue for manufacturers.</li>
          <li><strong>Advanced services:</strong> Taking aftersales to the next level, advanced services are more relationship focused and customer-centric than just selling and maintaining a product. In many cases, advanced services are delivered on a subscription model in which the consumer pays for the outcome.</li>
        </ul>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>What is an outcome-based business model?</div>
      <div>An outcome-based business model is a type of XaaS in which customers are charged for services based on the amount or volume of usage of a service. This model requires that you collect and monitor, and bill, against the amount the service is used.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distributed Energy Resources (DER) and the Rise of the Prosumer]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/distributed-energy-resources-der-and-the-rise-of-the-prosumer</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/distributed-energy-resources-der-and-the-rise-of-the-prosumer</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Discover how distributed energy resources (DER), prosumers, and microgrid users are paving the way to a shift to renewable energy sources.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1420fa9c0cd21e919a3c0163f4f060ae6edabaf63.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1420fa9c0cd21e919a3c0163f4f060ae6edabaf63.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1420fa9c0cd21e919a3c0163f4f060ae6edabaf63.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="solar power panels" src="./media_1420fa9c0cd21e919a3c0163f4f060ae6edabaf63.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="distributed-energy-resources-der-and-the-rise-of-the-prosumer">Distributed energy resources (DER) and the rise of the prosumer</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For over a century, utilities companies have accomplished marvels of engineering that have brought power to billions of people around the world. Without their enormous and complex undertakings, we could never be where we are today. However, modern utilities companies are under growing pressure to reduce carbon emissions and transition to renewable energy sources. So, for the first time in their long history, utilities are not the sole energy providers, as distributed energy resources (DERs) owned by third parties and prosumers are also producing power for the grid. Lower costs for photovoltaic (PV) solar equipment and other renewable energy assets, along with government incentives, are driving the growth of DERs in the energy sector.</p>
  <p>Leading the charge toward these new operational models are prosumers, also known as “active consumers.” As a whole, prosumers demand more from their utility service providers, including more control over on-demand services, improved self-sufficiency, and transparency on their own terms. While DER asset owners may at first seem like a competitor on the energy market, the most innovative and fearless utilities industry leaders not only accept that these changes are coming but are already seizing new opportunities for growth and industrial diversification.</p>
  <h2 id="what-is-der-and-how-is-it-changing-trends-in-the-utilities-industry">What is DER and how is it changing trends in the utilities industry?</h2>
  <p>Distributed energy resources include any assets used for generating, storing, or distributing power that exist outside the central utilities-run power grid. These can include assets like photovoltaic cells for solar energy, wind turbines, and local battery systems such as those on electric vehicles (EVs). Typically DER assets have a capacity less than 10 MW, are located at or near the consumer, and exist “behind-the-meter,” meaning they are on the consumer-side of power grid metering systems.</p>
  <p>These resources are in contrast to the traditional utilities-owned assets, including the remotely-located central power plants and high-voltage transmission lines necessary for large-scale electrical distribution. However, the ability for the owners of DER assets to bring additional resilience and flexibility to the electrical grid through the use of modern technologies makes them a valuable component in the market. For example, energy storage DERs like battery banks and connected EVs can be used to assist utilities companies in the event of a blackout by helping to kick-start the larger generators of the utilities companies so that they can more easily restore power to the whole network. Between the social and political pressures for a more energy-efficient future and the expectations for a more stable energy grid, DERs have the potential to optimize and bring better value to existing grid networks.</p>
  <h2 id="what-are-prosumers-and-how-do-they-work-with-utilities">What are prosumers and how do they work with utilities?</h2>
  <p>“Prosumer” is a <em>portmanteau</em> word combining “producer” and “consumer.” Energy prosumers typically remain connected to the central grid. However, they are also capable of producing and even storing energy – typically with photovoltaic solar panels and EV batteries. Depending on the amount of power generated, this energy can either be used to offset monthly bills or be sold back as surplus to utilities companies, or other energy distribution services. This model may be applied to both residential and commercial prosumers, with a growing number of businesses plugging their solar panels and EV fleets into the grid.</p>
  <p>Prosumers typically fall into three categories:</p>
  <ol>
    <li>Those who optimize self-consumption rates without a direct connection to the electrical grid</li>
    <li>Those who optimize self-consumption while remaining connected to the grid</li>
    <li>Those who provide flexibility services at the systems level (virtual power plants)</li>
  </ol>
  <p>Based upon current growth rates, DER assets that are connected to the main electrical grid (categories two and three above) are major stakeholders, while isolated prosumers are growing in numbers but are currently less significant to the overall energy model.</p>
  <p>DERs in the U.S. are expected to generate <a href="https://www.greentechmedia.com/articles/read/5-takeaways-on-the-future-of-the-u.s-distributed-energy-resources-market">387 GW of power</a> by 2050. Of these DERs, small-scale solar is one of the most common forms for prosumers, who are currently responsible for <a href="https://www.eia.gov/electricity/data/browser/#/topic/0?agg=2,0,1&#x26;fuel=vtvv&#x26;geo=g&#x26;sec=g&#x26;linechart=ELEC.GEN.DPV-US-99.A~ELEC.GEN.SUN-US-99.A~~~~~ELEC.GEN.TSN-US-99.A&#x26;columnchart=ELEC.GEN.ALL-US-99.A~ELEC.GEN.COW-US-99.A~ELEC.GEN.NG-US-99.A~ELEC.GEN.NUC-US-99.A~ELEC.GEN.HYC-US-99.A~ELEC.GEN.WND-US-99.A&#x26;">nearly one-third</a> of all solar energy produced in the U.S. For prosumers, most modern PV systems are generally established as a two-way connection up and down the existing grid, allowing them both consumer power from the grid when necessary and the ability to supply it to the grid when possible.</p>
  <p>Another model for prosumers includes microgrid and energy-storing prosumers who can fit into different categories depending on their specific setup. A university campus, for example, could establish a microgrid where it supplies and provides all of its power needs independent of the rest of the main power grid. Furthermore, microgrids can generally connect or disconnect from the main power grid as needed, offering the flexibility to consume from the main grid or to function as a virtual power plant, depending on capacities and needs.</p>
  <h2 id="how-do-behind-the-meter-microgrid-and-der-energy-models-work">How do behind-the-meter, microgrid, and DER energy models work?</h2>
  <p>DER encompasses more than just renewable energy production or prosumers; it refers to any kind of behind-the-meter or off-grid power generation and storage. A familiar model is that of a diesel backup generator or a series of backup battery cells for energy storage. These are traditional examples of DER, but with more advanced technology, new systems are constantly evolving.</p>
  <p>With the growth of the electric vehicle market, for example, it is projected that EV car companies will soon turn into virtual power stations and energy storage systems. The growth of artificial intelligence (AI) has made this more feasible, as smart charging/discharging can be used to charge at off-peak times. This gives the grid more flexibility and stability in terms of energy storage – and this kind of AI also facilitates lower charging costs for EV owners when coupled with variable rates on their electricity bill when they charge at off-peak hours.</p>
  <p>This increased adoption of AI systems also makes room for new energy startups looking to capture a share of the market. Competitive new startups and utilities giants alike are leveraging AI technologies to better address customer needs. AI is being used to forecast load requirements and generation capabilities, as well as for grid optimization and network planning, all of which can prevent outages, save money, and improve operational efficiency.</p>
  <h2 id="the-age-of-the-prosumer-challenges-and-benefits">The age of the prosumer: Challenges and benefits</h2>
  <p>Prosumerism and “smart,” data-driven business models are driving change that better meets consumer demands to economize, show more corporate transparency, and minimize environmental footprints. While these new models definitely present some challenges, they also provide an opportunity for existing utilities companies to integrate with this new breed of customers to provide win/win benefits across a more diverse range of product and service provisions.</p>
  <ul>
    <li>DER hardware, installation, and maintenance are all growing cheaper and more efficient over time, especially for PV systems. The price of PV systems has dropped by <a href="https://www.seia.org/solar-industry-research-data">more than 70% over the past decade</a>, which helps explain the exponential growth in these types of systems. In fact, with an average annual growth rate for installations in the <a href="https://www.seia.org/solar-industry-research-data">U.S. of 42% each year</a> over the past decade, it’s no surprise that solar represents the largest share of new electrical generating capacity for 2021. And of course, the improved performance and dropping costs of PV technologies benefit both the small prosumer and the utility-grade hardware buyer alike.</li>
    <li>Utilities companies can also support prosumers more directly by addressing their extensive equipment and technology needs by vertically integrating services like tech support and educational services for customers. This can be realized in the form of volume-discounted maintenance and installation of things like PV equipment, solar panels, and batteries.</li>
    <li>Finally, switching to alternative energy sources and DER assets also has the potential to reduce political and financial dependency and risk associated with the use of finite, geo-specific resources like coal and oil. This is particularly evident in light of the reduction in the <a href="https://www.irena.org/newsroom/pressreleases/2021/Jun/Majority-of-New-Renewables-Undercut-Cheapest-Fossil-Fuel-on-Cost">cost to produce renewable energy</a>.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>In other words, it may appear that prosumers and DERs represent a threat by taking a share of the energy market from major utilities providers. But in reality, the world’s energy consumption is only going to continue to grow, along with customer demands for transparency and sustainability. By seizing upon these trends and applying their formidable customer networks, extensive resources, and decades of experience, utilities providers can leverage and monetize DERs in order to improve their operational efficiency – and better serve their customers.</p>
  <h2 id="smart-data-driven-utilities-solutions-benefit-prosumers-and-utilities-alike">Smart, data-driven utilities solutions benefit prosumers and utilities alike</h2>
  <p>To handle the growing number of DERs being integrated into the power grid without becoming overwhelmed, utilities companies need to rely more heavily on smart utility infrastructures. These AI-powered solutions can improve data collection and management in order to inform operators of risk, inefficiency, and opportunities to optimize systems and grids. These can then be targeted predictively to augment the overall benefit that prosumers bring to the power grid, as well as the value they receive as contributors.</p>
  <p>And while there are emerging opportunities for energy sector businesses to engage with their consumer networks, low customer satisfaction with electrical utility companies in both Europe and North America continues to present an issue. With more players and energy distribution startups in the game, the expectations of consumers and prosumers alike are on the rise. The providers best positioned to succeed will be those that find ways to add meaningful support and value to this competitive and increasingly complex market.</p>
  <p>Through the use of smart, AI-powered utilities solutions, providers can manage, analyze, and leverage data across their consumer networks. This can allow utilities companies of the future to personalize customer experiences and energy savings plans, as well as develop <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/apm/what-is-predictive-maintenance.html">predictive insights</a> as to when and where customers will want to upgrade or augment their DER and prosumer assets and hardware.</p>
  <h2 id="alternative-energy-sources-and-utilities-sector-business-models">Alternative energy sources and utilities sector business models</h2>
  <p><a href="/research/passionates-how-they-are-changing-your-strategy">Growing social pressure</a>, political complexity, and disastrous climate events are fueling the drive to decarbonization. And, the desire for more efficient and cost-effective energy sources is motivating a new generation of more engaged consumers.</p>
  <p>For innovators and thought leaders in the energy generation and distribution sector, the future of their industry is highly dependent upon the provision of superior customer satisfaction. This means reshaping infrastructure and services around the customers of the future – specifically, the prosumers. If managed strategically, this can lead to a win/win for both the utilities sector <em>and</em> prosumers. To bring prosumer-pleasing solutions to life requires the ability to gather and understand a wide variety of disparate and complex data sets. And not just to collect this data and look at it in isolation, but to bring it to life with intelligent systems, <a href="/blogs/what-generative-ai-can-do-for-utilities">using AI</a> and machine learning tools to make it tell actionable stories, make insightful recommendations, and help inform fast, smart decisions in real time.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-utilities-and-energy-management">Explore utilities and energy management</h3>
        <p>Learn how smart solutions and resources can help you diversify your business.</p>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/utilities.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Smart Metering: Helping Customers Reduce Consumption]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/smart-metering-helping-customers-reduce-consumption</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/smart-metering-helping-customers-reduce-consumption</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Discover how smart meters, advanced metering infrastructure (AMI), and smart grids, give customers the data and support needed to reduce energy consumption.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_195e10339a1fc417336b3ee0b272a5b97956b1f70.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_195e10339a1fc417336b3ee0b272a5b97956b1f70.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_195e10339a1fc417336b3ee0b272a5b97956b1f70.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="smart meters gauging energy usage" src="./media_195e10339a1fc417336b3ee0b272a5b97956b1f70.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="smart-metering-helping-customers-reduce-consumption">Smart metering: Helping customers reduce consumption</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Global energy demand is on the rise – forecasted to increase almost 50% over the next three decades, according to the <a href="https://www.eia.gov/outlooks/ieo/">U.S. Energy Information Administration</a>. At the same time, extreme weather events are expected to continue, taxing the capabilities of an aging utilities infrastructure and unreliable energy grids. Consumer awareness about how and when to use energy is critical in order to optimize energy resources. Smart meters are at the heart of giving customers the information they need to reduce consumption, lower their bills, and support the environment.</p>
  <h2 id="what-is-a-smart-meter">What is a smart meter?</h2>
  <p>Smart meters are <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-iot.html">Internet of Things</a> (IoT) devices that attach to homes and businesses to track energy, water, and natural gas consumption. Whereas traditional meters only measure overall consumption, smart meters track exactly when and how much electricity – or water or gas – is used and transmit that information to utilities in near real time.</p>
  <p>Using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-artificial-intelligence.html">artificial intelligence</a> (AI) and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-machine-learning.html">machine learning</a>, the data generated by smart meters can be parsed to determine how to lower operating costs, increase efficiency, and forecast demand. That ability to track usage, analyze it, and plan ahead could result in smart meters saving utility companies up to <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/smart-meters-utilities-iot-energy-water?international=true&#x26;r=US&#x26;IR=T">US$157 billion by 2035</a>. Smart meters are also a gateway for consumers to become prosumers, allowing them to produce, store, and consume energy.</p>
  <p>Knowledge is power, and smart meter data benefits consumers by helping them:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Reduce energy consumption with detailed energy usage information that pinpoints energy-guzzling activities and appliances.</li>
    <li>Optimize energy usage by taking advantage of time-of-use tariffs and replacing outdated, power-hogging appliances with more energy-efficient ones.</li>
    <li>Manage their costs with notifications that alert them when their account hits a certain threshold or is higher than usual – to avoid an unexpectedly high bill at month end.</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>With the ability to adapt and react to usage patterns and energy prices, [smart meters] could represent massive energy savings if applied to the broader population. Widespread implementation could contribute to a greener, more stable electric grid for everyone.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/arielcohen/2020/08/31/get-smart-ai-and-the-energy-sector-revolution/?sh=5b70fe6b6044">Forbes</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="what-is-a-prosumer">What is a prosumer?</h2>
  <p>“Prosumer” is a <em>portmanteau</em> word combining “producer” and “consumer.” Energy prosumers typically remain connected to the central grid. However, they are also capable of producing and even storing energy – typically with photovoltaic solar panels and EV batteries. Depending on the amount of power generated, this energy can either be used to offset monthly bills or be sold back as surplus to utilities companies or other energy distribution services. This model may be applied to both residential and commercial prosumers, with a growing number of businesses plugging their solar panels and EV fleets into the grid.</p>
  <h2 id="smart-utilities-billing-supports-smart-engaged-customers">Smart utilities billing supports smart, engaged customers</h2>
  <p>With smart meters, power companies gain significant opportunities to improve the customer experience. Rather than relying on transactional communications around billing and payment, companies can use the data gathered from smart meters to drive communications that increase customer satisfaction, trust, and engagement.</p>
  <p>Companies can analyze this data and use it to send personalized recommendations to customers via text, e-mail, or as part of the billing process. For example, they can offer pool owners more efficient pool pumps, or encourage those with EVs to charge their vehicles when energy demands – and costs – are lower. This ability to personalize communications while helping customers save money and energy moves utilities from being seen as mere service providers to being valued energy partners. And at a time when there is rising competition in the energy sector, this opportunity to strengthen relationships with customers is paramount.</p>
  <p>Despite these benefits, smart meters haven’t quite come into their own yet. In the U.S., <a href="https://www.smart-energy.com/regional-news/north-america/75-of-us-households-have-smart-meters-report/">75% of homes</a> have smart meters, whereas about <a href="https://www.businessgreen.com/feature/4025086/getting-smart-meters-track-reach-half-britain-homes-businesses-2021">40% of UK</a> and <a href="https://www.smart-energy.com/industry-sectors/smart-meters/australia-new-directions-proposed-to-optimise-smart-meter-rollout/">fewer than 25%</a> of Australian households use them. As smart meter technology evolves, consumers will soon be able to set budgets and receive alerts via an app on their phone to let them know that they’ve left their stove on or have a water leak. They’ll also be able to integrate IoT devices such as smart thermostats or smart lighting into their home networks to better understand and manage their energy consumption. And with <a href="https://www.eia.gov/todayinenergy/detail.php?id=48396">renewable energy use growing</a>, consumers will be able to connect solar panels and batteries to the <a href="/resources/smart-grid-ai-in-energy-technologies">smart grid</a>, becoming prosumers. This will allow them to both store energy and sell excess power back to the grid – making them more active and engaged in the overall conversation around energy and the environment.</p>
  <h2 id="the-benefits-of-advanced-metering-infrastructure-ami">The benefits of advanced metering infrastructure (AMI)</h2>
  <p>AMI integrates smart meters, communication networks, and data management systems to provide two-way communications between utility providers and customers.</p>
  <p>The benefits of AMI include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Increasing reliability and better managing outages by being able to pinpoint outage locations quickly and automatically alert utilities when the power comes back on</li>
    <li>Evaluating and managing energy consumption by providing accurate information about power usage and patterns that can be used to improve customer engagement</li>
    <li>Improving data quality and billing by providing accurate readings and alerting customers to usage anomalies as they happen rather than after the fact</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="smart-meters-and-ami-support-smart-grids">Smart meters and AMI support smart grids</h2>
  <p>Increasingly severe weather events have highlighted the weaknesses of existing power grids. And the global impact from flooding, forest fires, hurricanes, and heat is expected to continue to rise. As just one example, a recent McKinsey report on <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/business-functions/sustainability/our-insights/climate-risk-and-response-physical-hazards-and-socioeconomic-impacts">climate risk and response</a> noted that in “Ho Chi Minh City, direct infrastructure asset damage from a 100-year flood could rise from about $200 to $300 million today, to $500 million to $1 billion in 2050.” That, coupled with <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/16/europes-energy-crisis-is-making-the-market-nervous-ahead-of-winter.html">rising energy prices</a>, calls for better overall energy management, which is where smart grids come into the picture.</p>
  <p>Smart grids, which integrate smart meters, renewable technologies, sensors, communications networks, and monitoring systems, allow utilities and their customers to exchange information and energy. This improves the grid’s reliability, quality, and efficiency, optimizing energy usage and catching and adjusting for small problems before they balloon into big issues.</p>
  <p>Smart grids also have self-healing, predictive capabilities. They can identify faults, isolate them, and react to them, reconfiguring energy flow around affected areas to protect the broader grid. They also can access weather and energy usage forecasts to adjust for upcoming situations. Using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics/what-is-predictive-analytics.html">predictive analytics</a>, they can also anticipate future maintenance and system management needs.</p>
  <h2 id="can-smart-metering-and-smart-grids-help-eliminate-overloads">Can smart metering and smart grids help eliminate overloads?</h2>
  <p>The short answer is “yes.” The connected, communicative nature of smart meters and smart grids allows for a much more nuanced response to everyday energy use, as well as to overloads and emergencies. Smart grids use edge computing, 5G, IoT, cloud, advanced streaming analytics, and AI to assess grid conditions in real time and rapidly adapt and respond to ever-changing demands. Customers can support overload management by reducing their consumption in response to current conditions.</p>
  <p>For example, they can respond to alerts and notifications via phone apps that advise them to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Reduce their energy use or turn off non-essential appliances and devices in the face of impending brownouts or outages.</li>
    <li>Turn heating systems down in cold snaps and reduce AC usage in heat waves to decrease the surge in demand and lessen the risk of blackouts.</li>
    <li>Save money by charging EVs and running washing machines, dryers, dishwashers, or other appliances when their power company’s time-of-use tariffs are lower.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="smart-meter-technologies-drive-greener-cleaner-smarter-energy-solutions">Smart meter technologies drive greener, cleaner, smarter, energy solutions</h2>
  <p>Energy solutions like smart metering and smart grids have many eco-friendly benefits including the reduction in diesel and gas consumption, as utilities would no longer need to dispatch meter readers in trucks.</p>
  <p>Smart meters can support:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>The integration of renewables into smart grids, reducing dependency on gas, nuclear, and coal-fired power</li>
    <li>Smart technology that can turn on and off heat pumps and other appliances to align usage with supply and demand without negatively impacting homeowners</li>
    <li>Encouraging consumers to use renewable energy when the supply is robust so that excess demand doesn’t need to be met by carbon-based energy sources</li>
    <li>Supporting local energy, which is cleaner energy – a decentralized smart grid will be able to connect microgrids where prosumers sell excess solar or wind energy back to utilities or even trade it with their neighbors</li>
    <li>Evolving smart cities. While cities only cover 2% of the Earth’s surface, <a href="https://unhabitat.org/topic/climate-change">UN research shows</a> that they account for more than 60% of greenhouse gas emissions and use 78% of the Earths’ energy</li>
  </ul>
  <p>But greener energy isn’t just about the power that gets used; it’s also about the energy that’s wasted – about two-thirds <a href="https://cleantechnica.com/2020/01/16/how-much-energy-does-the-us-consume-where-does-it-come-from-pew-research/">of all energy</a> in the U.S. annually. Smart meters can pinpoint energy wasted by not turning off lights or leaving devices on standby to help eliminate wastage. Because the cleanest energy is energy that isn’t used at all.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-smart-metering-solutions">Explore Smart Metering solutions</h3>
        <p>Monitor, manage, and forecast energy consumption with analytics in real time.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/utilities.html#smart-metering">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Telehealth: Temporary Fix or the Future of Health Care?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/telehealth-temporary-fix-or-future-of-health-care</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/telehealth-temporary-fix-or-future-of-health-care</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Telehealth is changing the way patient care takes place. Read to learn how telehealth is more than a hasty response to COVID-19.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14f7998a06d5632d3e89912a37ba4b3ca9d4147ae.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14f7998a06d5632d3e89912a37ba4b3ca9d4147ae.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_14f7998a06d5632d3e89912a37ba4b3ca9d4147ae.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Woman at home talking with her doctor on tablet; telehealth appointment" src="./media_14f7998a06d5632d3e89912a37ba4b3ca9d4147ae.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="telehealth-a-temporary-fix-or-the-future-of-health-care">Telehealth: A Temporary Fix or the Future of Health Care?</h1>
        <p>After a slow start, the pandemic forced an embrace of telehealth. Now it’s changing the way patient care takes place.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Most telehealth visits with patients are for routine care, not potentially life-changing diagnoses. Yet Dr. Albert Chan, the chief of digital patient experience at Sutter Health, describes a time when a cardiology colleague met virtually with a patient who had recently undergone open heart surgery and quickly noticed one of the patient’s incisions had become infected. Surgical site infections can be uncomfortable for patients, costly for healthcare providers, and if left untreated, potentially fatal.</p>
  <p>“Because of the ability to communicate virtually, we were able to catch that infection early,” says Chan. “That’s a tremendous opportunity.”</p>
  <p>In fact, telehealth is quickly redefining how people access, view, and receive healthcare services. Real-time virtual visits with physicians, mobile apps that let patients book appointments and pay bills, and wearable devices that remotely monitor an individual’s vital signs are enabling healthcare providers to engage with patients in a more proactive way, make services more readily available, free up precious hospital resources, and in some cases, save lives.</p>
  <p>That wasn’t always the case. Criticized for being a costly and complicated delivery modality, less than 1% of all physician visits in the U.S. were conducted using telehealth before early 2020. But COVID-19 changed all that as stringent social distancing measures, pandemic-related telehealth policies, and an overburdened hospital infrastructure forced physicians and consumers alike to embrace telehealth as a viable patient care modality.</p>
  <p>Today, more than half of all consumers expect to rely more heavily on telehealth than they did before the pandemic, and a whopping 92% of providers plan to continue offering video consultations, even after it’s safe for in-person visits, according to an <a href="https://static.americanwell.com/app/uploads/2020/09/Amwell-2020-Physician-and-Consumer-Survey.pdf">Amwell</a> report. Moreover, three years from now, 70% of providers anticipate using telehealth sometimes or frequently.</p>
  <p>But the telehealth movement is more than just a response to changes in government guidelines, healthcare policies, and public sentiment. Rather, it heralds a unique opportunity to redefine the patient-physician relationship, glean greater value from patient data, and even reimagine the physical footprint of healthcare facilities. That is, provided the sector can overcome obstacles ranging from digital disparities to data security.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13e744108c09bf644388f276b0ccadca818087035.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13e744108c09bf644388f276b0ccadca818087035.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_13e744108c09bf644388f276b0ccadca818087035.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Doctor is on the phone for telehealth appointment" src="./media_13e744108c09bf644388f276b0ccadca818087035.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="drivers-of-change">Drivers of change</h2>
  <p>Several factors explain telehealth’s transformation from seldom-used modality to major trend. Chief among these are the sweeping regulatory changes introduced by the U.S. government in March 2020, including these temporary measures:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>The Centers for Medicare &#x26; Medicaid Services (CMS) decided to pay healthcare providers for telehealth services given to Medicare beneficiaries so that they can receive a wider range of healthcare services without having to travel to a healthcare facility.</li>
    <li>The Office for Civil Rights (OCR) at HHS announced it would waive potential penalties for HIPAA violations associated with providing care via noncompliant platforms such as FaceTime and Skype.</li>
    <li>Congress passed the Coronavirus Aid, Relief, and Economic Security (CARES) Act, which eliminates the requirement that providers must have an established relationship with a Medicare patient to provide telehealth services.</li>
    <li>The government eliminated geographic restrictions, allowing patients to receive telehealth services in their homes.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>By removing geographic restrictions and relaxing regulations, the number of telehealth visits during the last week of March 2020 increased by <a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/69/wr/mm6943a3.htm">154%</a>, compared with the same period in 2019, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.</p>
  <p>“The pandemic has taken telehealth in its broadest sense and made it much more accessible to both patients and providers,” says Ann Mond Johnson, CEO of the American Telemedicine Association (ATA), which represents more than 400 organizations, academic medical centers, payers, and solution providers. “The uptick in utilization has skyrocketed.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dfbe8ca59852b8e3c6ef04da435300c642b44c8b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dfbe8ca59852b8e3c6ef04da435300c642b44c8b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1dfbe8ca59852b8e3c6ef04da435300c642b44c8b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="A stethescope and an iPad on a table" src="./media_1dfbe8ca59852b8e3c6ef04da435300c642b44c8b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="842" height="560">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="catering-to-the-patient-experience">Catering to the patient experience</h2>
  <p>Another variable drives rapid telehealth adoption: the consumerization of healthcare. Just as same-day delivery and highly personalized interactions have come to define customer engagement, so too are consumers increasingly looking for greater ease and speed from their healthcare providers.</p>
  <p>“Technology has entered so many other facets of our life that many patients now say the most important thing they look for in a provider is convenience,” says David Hinkle, executive director of business operations at Mercy Virtual. “They don’t want to drive a couple of hours from their community to the big city for a follow-up. That’s really pushed doctors to adapt to meet this demand from consumers.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="cloud-based-platform-news">Cloud-Based Platform News</h3>
        <p>SAP boosts industry-wide innovation with startup partnerships.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://news.sap.com/2020/09/industry-wide-innovation-startup-partnerships-iristrace/">Read the news</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Mercy Virtual is a perfect example. Completely dedicated to virtual care, this four-story facility houses a large medical team of practitioners who rely on highly sensitive two-way cameras and online instruments to meet virtually with patients, whether they’re in a traditional hospital, a doctor’s office, or at home.</p>
  <p>Doctors can monitor patients’ vital signs and provide backup for bedside caregivers in 30 ICUs across five states. The facility’s TeleStroke program ensures patients who arrive at any community emergency department, many of which don’t have a neurologist on-site, can be seen immediately by the care center’s neurologist using a two-way audio and video connection. And Mercy Virtual provides continuous remote monitoring for more than 3,800 patients, intervening quickly when needed, thereby reducing patients’ need for hospitalization.</p>
  <p>By delivering quality care with on-demand convenience, telehealth initiatives such as Mercy Virtual transform the role of patient into that of healthcare consumer.</p>
  <p>“We know that if patients are going to rely on remote monitoring, we have to make it as easy as possible for people,” says Mond Johnson. “We need to take our cues from companies like Amazon where consumers go online, order something, it shows up at your house the next day, you turn it on, and it works perfectly.”</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">We know that if patients are going to rely on remote monitoring, we have to make it as easy as possible for people.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Ann Mond Johnson, CEO, American Telemedicine Association</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Efforts to ensure patients have easy access to detailed information about their care are also underway. For example, the 21st Century Cures Act of 2016 requires healthcare providers to grant patients access to all the health information in their medical records. But recent regulations from the Office of the National Coordinator for Health Information Technology upped the ante by expanding the type of information that must be easily accessible, including consultation notes, procedure notes, and pathology reports.</p>
  <p>“Our patients can see all of their notes as soon as the doctor is done writing them,” says Chan of Sutter Health. “They can see doctors’ notes, laboratory tests, X-ray results – almost immediately.”</p>
  <p>The result, says Chan, is not only documentation that can “help guide care,” but also a prime opportunity for patients to become partners in the management of their own health care. In fact, according to a JAMA <a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2763607">survey</a>, clinicians agree that it is a good idea to share notes with patients, and 74% viewed sharing notes as useful for engaging patients in their care.</p>
  <h2 id="innovative-applications">Innovative applications</h2>
  <p>As adoption of telehealth grows, healthcare organizations are discovering more innovative use cases, from compassionate care to clinical trial participation.</p>
  <p>“We’ve had some sad circumstances where COVID-19 patients had to spend their last hours without visitors,” says Hinkle. “Our chaplains have been able to loop in family from home using telehealth technology so that these patients could spend those hours with their loved ones.”</p>
  <p>Virtual sitting is another increasingly popular application of telehealth in which patient sitters – nonclinical staff members – provide in-room monitoring of patients who are at high risk for falls or self-harm. In fact, the Agency for Healthcare Research and Quality <a href="https://www.ahrq.gov/patient-safety/settings/hospital/fall-prevention/toolkit/index.html">estimates</a> that 700,000 to 1 million hospitalized patients fall each year. More than <a href="https://psnet.ahrq.gov/issue/preventing-falls-and-fall-related-injuries-health-care-facilities">one-third</a> of these result in serious injury. Depending on the severity of the injury, unreimbursed costs for treating a single hospital-related fall injury can reach nearly US$30,000.</p>
  <p>Providing a physical sitter in each room can be challenging for resource-strapped healthcare organizations. Fortunately, virtual sitters are a cost-effective alternative, allowing for real-time, continuous monitoring of at-risk patients using a combination of in-room cameras, remote monitoring tools, and two-way video and audio feeds.</p>
  <p>In fact, in some cases, “virtual can be even better than face-to-face, particularly in telebehavioral health,” says Mond Johnson of the ATA, noting today’s shortage of qualified mental health professionals. “We have an opportunity to do better for more people using technology, and that’s something you cannot do face-to-face without using up all your resources.”</p>
  <p>Telehealth is even enabling patients to participate in clinical trials that would otherwise remain unavailable to them. For example, one rural patient with Stage 4 lung cancer was able to participate in two clinical trials and undergo chemoradiation treatment and surgery at a tertiary care center through the successful coordination of telehealth services, including videoconferencing. The patient remained disease free for 18 months, according to a <a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S2468294216300338">report</a> published by Cancer Treatment and Research Communications. Better yet, telehealth promises to improve the speed and efficacy of clinical trials by broadening researchers’ pool of potential candidates.</p>
  <p>Telehealth is enabling patients to participate in clinical trials that would otherwise remain unavailable to them.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c86814f1c95210ae5cdd4403c889c77ab5c40f0a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c86814f1c95210ae5cdd4403c889c77ab5c40f0a.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1c86814f1c95210ae5cdd4403c889c77ab5c40f0a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Digital identity scanner" src="./media_1c86814f1c95210ae5cdd4403c889c77ab5c40f0a.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3198" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="from-security-breaches-to-the-digital-divide">From security breaches to the digital divide</h2>
  <p>Despite its advantages, many are questioning the role telehealth will play in a post-pandemic world. Will patients return to in-person interactions when it’s safe to do so? Or will telehealth continue to serve as a cost-effective and convenient alternative to traditional care?</p>
  <p>The answers to many of these questions hinge on how successfully healthcare providers are able to overcome certain obstacles.</p>
  <p>Chief among these challenges is data security. “As we shift towards telemedicine, we’re sending patients home with devices that allow them to communicate bidirectionally, whether it be checking blood glucose or various vital signs,” says Scott Harrison, chief data officer for Parkland Health. “But with all new IT endeavors, you always have to think about security first – what kind of risk am I imposing by allowing these systems of engagement to now interact and connect to my systems that are on premises.”</p>
  <p>After all, healthcare organizations are prime targets for ill-intentioned hackers and other bad actors. According to <em><a href="https://www.hipaajournal.com/">HIPAA Journal</a></em>, hacking and IT incidents comprised 59.4% of healthcare breaches in 2019, while accounting for 87.6% of breached records. And more than a quarter (28.82%) of data breaches consisted of unauthorized access and disclosure incidents, involving 11.27% of all records breached in 2019.</p>
  <p>In fact, hackers can easily hack videoconferencing and messaging apps used for telehealth, providing them with a pathway to more sensitive data and critical systems. For this reason, Harrison says it’s critical healthcare organizations “make sure that there’s endpoint encryption so that the data residing with the patient is safeguarded and that it’s capable of entering a network in a safe manner.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="biometrics-sensing-a-healthy-society">Biometrics: Sensing a Healthy Society</h3>
        <p>We need technology that can evolve with us to ensure our health and safety.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/blogs/biometrics-sensing-healthy-society">Learn more about biometrics</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Chan at Sutter Health agrees, citing restricted access, password-protected network entry points, and continuous monitoring of remote devices as critical measures all healthcare providers must take to ensure “data is kept sacrosanct for patients.” That’s especially true as healthcare providers continue to adjust to record numbers of participants. Case in point: Sutter Health’s MyHealthOnline initiative received 7,000 video visits in 2019 – a number that skyrocketed to over 1 million in 2020.</p>
  <p>But while concerns over secure and reliable access to corporate networks keep IT leaders up at night, many Americans don’t have any connection. The Federal Communications Commission <a href="https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/fact-sheets/2019/07/21-million-americans-still-lack-broadband-connectivity">estimates</a> that 21 million people in the United States lack broadband connectivity – 30% of which live in rural areas. And a staggering 60% of healthcare facilities outside metropolitan areas lack the speed of connectivity needed to properly store and manage electronic health records.</p>
  <p>Says Mond Johnson, “The pandemic has really laid bare the problems that we’ve had as a society in terms of [broadband] inequities.”</p>
  <p>Fortunately, change is underway: the FCC recently earmarked $9.2 billion in funding for the development of high-speed broadband networks for more than 10 million rural Americans across the country. It’s one of a growing number of initiatives that “have been formed to acknowledge that while we did not cause disparities, we’re uniquely positioned to address them as telehealth organizations,” says Mond Johnson.</p>
  <p>Harrison also sees an opportunity for telehealth providers to help bridge today’s digital divide: “One of the disparities that we have is access to care. By increasing our capabilities in that area, we can close the gap on some of those disparities. So I’m very bullish on the increased influence of virtual care and telemedicine – that’s the way of the future.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fe70478dd92fbe87debdc6d7659336e84c956896.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fe70478dd92fbe87debdc6d7659336e84c956896.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1fe70478dd92fbe87debdc6d7659336e84c956896.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Doctor and patient using digital tablet in office" src="./media_1fe70478dd92fbe87debdc6d7659336e84c956896.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="the-human-factor">The human factor</h2>
  <p>Silver linings aside, there is a learning curve that comes with properly implementing a telehealth strategy and raising awareness of its benefits.</p>
  <p>“Educating both providers and patients is a huge challenge,” says Dr. Tearsanee Carlisle Davis, director of clinical and advanced practice operations at the University of Mississippi Medical Center’s Center for Telehealth. “With so many tools out there, it is very important to have a clear plan for educating providers on workflows and troubleshooting. Patients also need to be made aware of what telehealth does for them and how to access it. This is a very heavy lift for groups who have not been doing telehealth prior to COVID-19.”</p>
  <p>Then there are the inherent limitations of telehealth. “There are definitely situations for which telemedicine is not appropriate,” says Lori Uscher-Pines, a senior policy researcher at the RAND Corporation. “For example, when a clinician needs to do a physical exam or a procedure, in-person care is necessary.” Uscher-Pines also offers the example of physicians treating patients with opioid use disorder: “Although telehealth has a lot of promise for patients with opioid use disorder, it can be difficult to establish rapport with patients over telemedicine. Many providers tell us that they really rely on in-person interactions to fully access a patient.” What’s more, she adds, in-person therapy sessions offer ingredients such as “accountability and ritual that enable treatment to be more successful.”</p>
  <p>Technology-fueled interactions can also feel antiseptic compared to face-to-face consultations.</p>
  <p>“We’ve been very conscious of the healing power of touch,” says Hinkle of Mercy Virtual. “You want to make sure that you aren’t losing that personal provider-to-patient relationship and that it doesn’t begin to feel transactional. We have to be careful that even in cases where we’re using telemedicine, the patient still feels like there is a special relationship with the doctor.”</p>
  <p>Yet one of the biggest hurdles facing telehealth is cost. Policymakers will need to expand telehealth benefits permanently for Medicare beneficiaries and continue to advance access to care in rural areas if telehealth is to maintain mainstream traction. “Policies such as receiving reimbursement only if you go to the clinician’s office for a telehealth service are absurd,” says Mond Johnson. “During the public health emergency, regulations finally caught up with technology. But the temporary waivers put in place during the public health emergency, which led to gains in telehealth, need to remain permanent.”</p>
  <p>Overutilization is another cost consideration. Granting patients greater access to care can lead to unnecessary visits – and escalating healthcare costs. “One of telehealth’s greatest strengths is one of its greatest weaknesses – it’s extremely convenient,” says Uscher-Pines. “It’s great that it’s convenient for patients but that convenience can lead to extra-utilization. It’s really hard to thread this needle. You want to increase access to provide high-quality services to patients but you also want to make sure that you’re not doing it in a way that causes healthcare costs to go out of control.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ebc973b75da7fc9689c52c33842564e6a53c9670.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ebc973b75da7fc9689c52c33842564e6a53c9670.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1ebc973b75da7fc9689c52c33842564e6a53c9670.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Woman doctor looking at screen" src="./media_1ebc973b75da7fc9689c52c33842564e6a53c9670.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1958" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="checking-the-future-for-vital-signs">Checking the future for vital signs</h2>
  <p>Provided healthcare organizations successfully overcome these obstacles, Chan believes the “possibilities for telehealth are quite endless.” For instance, as healthcare providers increasingly adopt a hybrid approach to patient care, Hinkle envisions a time when full-service hospitals might “transition away from trying to provide care for whatever patient might walk in the door.” Instead, he says, a more efficient and cost-effective approach will be for hospitals to serve as “centers of excellence” that cater to “various specialties.”</p>
  <p>Predictive health care is another area poised for significant innovation. Wearable monitoring devices, patient portals, and home monitoring apps all produce vast volumes of data. “Being able to ingest all of those various mechanisms of data and blending them with the data we have curated in our own systems – that can tell a big story,” says Harrison of Parkland Health. “And that’s where it’s getting very exciting.”</p>
  <p>For instance, Harrison says by monitoring a patient’s blood glucose levels, combining this data with information gleaned from personal fitness apps and online food trackers, and applying sophisticated <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-artificial-intelligence.html">artificial intelligence (AI)</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-machine-learning.html">machine learning</a> algorithms, healthcare practitioners can begin to identify patterns, such as the likelihood certain cohorts of patients will develop life-threatening complications from diabetes.</p>
  <p>“By integrating the right sets of data and learning from these patterns over time, there’s absolutely no reason not to think that we could start predicting various disease patterns before they happen,” says Harrison. Better yet, he adds, “When we get in front of these patterns before they become a problem, it becomes much easier to treat them.”</p>
  <p>But newly designed hospital facilities and predictive health care are only the beginning of telehealth’s transformational impact on an age-old sector. Business processes and workflows must also evolve to support greater cross-functional collaboration. As technology embeds itself in every aspect of patient care delivery, Hinkle says “a sense of camaraderie between clinicians and IT support teams” will prove “critical to moving forward as we attempt to leverage technology in patient care.”</p>
  <p>Davis agrees. She advises healthcare providers to “form teams with individuals from IT, education, and clinical areas to develop plans [that will address the challenges of telehealth]. Having a very strong project management team is key. And there has to be a standardized process for communication and implementation.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15c53b10537cebadb0372ca58083993aa82192426.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15c53b10537cebadb0372ca58083993aa82192426.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15c53b10537cebadb0372ca58083993aa82192426.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Doctor in scrubs with digital tablet and clipboard" src="./media_15c53b10537cebadb0372ca58083993aa82192426.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2600" height="1733">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="a-new-landscape">A new landscape</h2>
  <p>No one can dispute the invaluable contributions telehealth has made to providing patients with quality care and compassion in the midst of a global pandemic. “There’s been enormous innovation on the part of the healthcare industry in terms of getting people care and keeping them safe, while at the same time allowing people with chronic illnesses to be monitored at home as opposed to getting in their car and going to the hospital or a physician’s office,” says Mond Johnson.</p>
  <p>And for many, there’s no turning back. “There have been so many successes in the world of telehealth since the pandemic that I don’t see it going back to the prepandemic world,” says Hinkle. “It’s going to continue to evolve.”</p>
  <p>What shape telehealth takes remains to be seen. But one thing is certain: telehealth is more than a hasty response to COVID-19. Rather, it marks a tipping point in how healthcare providers grant access to medical services and the ways in which patients are willing to receive care.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Connect Remote Workforces, Strengthen Corporate Culture | SAP Insights]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/connect-remote-workforces-strengthen-corporate-culture</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/connect-remote-workforces-strengthen-corporate-culture</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A strong corporate culture often correlates with satisfied employees and higher productivity. Find out how to instill this during COVID-19.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Science, Tech, and Dogs Make the World Safer]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/science-tech-dogs-make-world-safer</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/science-tech-dogs-make-world-safer</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Dogs have natural abilities to protect humans. Advances in medicine and technology elevate their role to make lifesaving contributions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11853256069cf5a8a502d8c881c62049e90f642f1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11853256069cf5a8a502d8c881c62049e90f642f1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11853256069cf5a8a502d8c881c62049e90f642f1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Smiling man with dog using laptop in kitchen at home" src="./media_11853256069cf5a8a502d8c881c62049e90f642f1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="522">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-tech-and-dogs-make-the-world-safer">How Tech and Dogs Make the World Safer</h1>
        <p>Medicine and technology advances are elevating humanity’s best friend to roles in public health and workplace safety.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Not every hero enlisted to help stem the spread of COVID-19 can claim a winning pedigree, years of medical education, or frontline experience. Take Kossi, for example. Although a blond, finely featured mixed-breed dog from the streets of Spain, Kossi is expertly trained to detect the scent of coronavirus – a potentially lifesaving skill.</p>
  <p>Kossi was discovered in a cardboard box along a European highway and brought to an animal shelter, where a Finnish family eventually adopted her. After demonstrating remarkable skills in a one-year course on scent detection, Kossi’s owner brought her to Helsinki University, where Anna Hielm-Björkman and her team were training dogs to detect cancer, a practice that dates back nearly thirty years.</p>
  <p>In 2020, Hielm-Björkman, an adjunct professor at the University of Helsinki, worked with Finland’s Helsinki-Vantaa Airport to use <a href="https://news.sky.com/story/coronavirus-dogs-deployed-at-helsinki-airport-to-sniff-out-virus-12079289">detection dogs</a>, including Kossi, to sniff out passengers infected with COVID-19.</p>
  <p>Kossi joins a legion of dogs serving a wide variety of service roles, from bomb-sniffing canines to pets that assist people with disabilities and serve as compassionate-therapy companions. Advances in medicine and technology are elevating their role, enabling dogs to make lifesaving contributions to public health and safety in the workplace. Wearable devices, augmented reality, smartphone apps, COVID-19 test kits – they’re all complementing dogs’ natural capabilities to protect humans from harm.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_121e1ba4c7f787d48ea8511653726be44aee72e4b.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_121e1ba4c7f787d48ea8511653726be44aee72e4b.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_121e1ba4c7f787d48ea8511653726be44aee72e4b.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Police Dog Sniffing Bag" src="./media_121e1ba4c7f787d48ea8511653726be44aee72e4b.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2559" height="3840">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Dogs famously have acute senses of smell thanks to 300 million scent receptors – about 295 million more than humans and 10,000 times more accurate.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Work environments range from military training fields to airport lounges. Breeds include border collies, Labrador retrievers, German shepherds, and the DNA-ambiguous. And while some hail from university training centers, others have sketchier pasts, like Kossi. But there is one thing they all share: the ability to make the places where we work safer. Better yet, some are protecting workplaces at a fraction of the cost of conventional solutions and with unprecedented accuracy.</p>
  <p>Yet for all the benefits of uniting dogs with innovative tools and technologies, there are challenges, including heightened security risks, scarce funding, and biological limitations. Overcoming these obstacles, however, promises to forever change the health and safety of workers in an often-dangerous world.</p>
  <h2 id="the-nose-knows-covid-19">The nose knows COVID-19</h2>
  <p>Dogs have already proven their ability to sniff out diseases ranging from cancer to malaria. However, by training them to identify airport passengers and employees infected with the coronavirus, they stand to resurrect an ailing industry and protect millions of people.</p>
  <p>To teach dogs like Kossi how to detect COVID-19, Hielm-Björkman, who specializes in clinical research of companion animals, begins by showing the dog a variety of COVID-19-positive samples, pressing on a clicker (a positive-reinforcement dog-training tool), and providing a treat each time the animal approaches the sample.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="biometrics-sensing-a-healthy-society">Biometrics: Sensing a Healthy Society</h3>
        <p>We need technology that can evolve with us to ensure our health and safety.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/blogs/biometrics-sensing-healthy-society">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Dogs famously have acute senses of smell thanks to 300 million scent receptors – about 295 million more than humans and 10,000 times more accurate. And Hielm-Björkman says her brightest canine student learned how to detect a positive sample in fewer than seven minutes.</p>
  <p>“We humans haven’t used our senses for such a long time, but most animals use them to a very high extent – all of the time,” she says. The result? “Thirty million years of perfected machinery,” says Hielm-Björkman, adding that dogs can detect the infectious disease up to five days before symptoms show – considerably faster than a nasal swab polymerase chain reaction (PCR) test for the coronavirus – and with nearly 100% accuracy. Results are available in 30 seconds.</p>
  <p>Today, Hielm-Björkman says four of her highly trained dogs now work at Finland’s Helsinki-Vantaa Airport, conducting between 100 and 160 tests a day on passengers. Passengers must volunteer for testing, at which point an airport authority swipes the passenger’s neck with a gauze and places it in a sterile container. Next the container is carried to another room for a dog to sniff. The dog will quickly pass over a negative sample but will be attracted to a positive one.</p>
  <p>Although Hielm-Björkman experimented with other types of samples, such as urine and saliva, she says sweat is the most convenient for passengers and least contagious for all involved, including the dogs. Approximately 6.3% of all people who pass through the airport volunteer for the free-of-charge testing, and about 0.3% test positive for COVID-19, says Hielm-Björkman.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1258de56945c35d199a7655f0daab5482cf0d948e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1258de56945c35d199a7655f0daab5482cf0d948e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1258de56945c35d199a7655f0daab5482cf0d948e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Female IT engineer works on desktop computer" src="./media_1258de56945c35d199a7655f0daab5482cf0d948e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2309" height="1299">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="a-virtual-view-for-soldiers">A virtual view for soldiers</h2>
  <p>Militaries around the world rely on dogs for lifesaving activities, such as detecting explosives and searching for targets. But the limitations of human-canine communication can hamper these missions. For instance, issuing a command to a dog by using hand signals requires that the animal remain within the line of sight. And while laser pointers can extend a command’s physical reach, they increase the risk of alerting enemy factions.</p>
  <p>A.J. Peper believes he’s found a viable solution. Founder and CEO of Command Sight, Peper has developed <a href="https://www.army.mil/article/239705/augmented_reality_dog_goggles_could_help_protect_soldiers">augmented reality-equipped goggles</a> for military working dogs. These goggles, which fit snugly around a dog’s eyes and wrap tightly around the back of its head, contain built-in image sensors that transmit live footage of a dog’s environment remotely to its handler. “The handler can see everything the dog can see and everything that’s in the dog’s environment,” says Peper.</p>
  <p>From there, a display screen allows the handler to deliver commands to the dog by transposing an indicator, such as a simulated laser point, over a particular area or item within the dog’s line of sight. The handler stays hidden while the augmented laser point appears to the dog, indicating where possible explosives or enemy troops are hidden.</p>
  <p>“We can basically simulate what an indicator would look like in real life through an optic that fits over the dog’s eye,” says Peper. “That way we’re able to provide some specificity for the animal while keeping everyone safe – the enemy can’t discern who’s directing the dog, or where the dog is heading.”</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In a military application, dogs are equipped with augmented-reality (AR) goggles with image sensors that can transmit live footage of their environment to a handler at a different location.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Peper began working on his AR-equipped goggles in his home kitchen with his dog Mater, a Rottweiler, in 2017. Since then, his company, Command Sight, has partnered with the U.S. Army and Navy Special Operations to build wireless prototypes for their military working dogs. Once ready for the field, Peper says he’ll be able to collect critical data that can help improve the apparatus’ system performance, ruggedization, and miniaturization.</p>
  <p>“The system is really focused on increasing mission capabilities,” says Peper. “But for me, it’s about increasing the chances of survivability for people who are willingly putting their lives in harm’s way.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11f32c20051b345e3cb72615f6bbeb30c764cabac.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11f32c20051b345e3cb72615f6bbeb30c764cabac.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_11f32c20051b345e3cb72615f6bbeb30c764cabac.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Team of sled dogs traveling in snowy landscape" src="./media_11f32c20051b345e3cb72615f6bbeb30c764cabac.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="a-touchscreen-system-for-personal-safety">A touchscreen system for personal safety</h2>
  <p>At the Georgia Tech Animal-Computer Interaction Lab, researchers are also exploring how enhancing dog-human communication can significantly improve workplace safety. For the past several years, the team has been developing a vest, outfitted with lightweight computers and sensors, that allows dogs to communicate critical information to their handlers and others in emergency situations. Essentially, dogs tap a capacitive sensor located on the side of the vest with their noses. This action immediately triggers a text alert – messages vary based on the pattern in which the dogs touch the sensors. For example, touching the blue dot once and an orange dot twice would call for a medic.</p>
  <p>“It’s very similar to the way the touchscreen on an iPhone works,” says Melody Moore Jackson, director of the Georgia Tech Animal-Computer Interaction Lab, who founded the project, known as FIDO (Facilitating Interactions for Dogs with Occupations).</p>
  <p>Jackson considered new uses for her sensor-equipped dog vest after learning of a young boy on the autism spectrum who had gone missing in the Georgia mountains. Despite sending a canine-led search-and-rescue team to find him, Jackson says “it took authorities much longer to locate this young man than it should have.”</p>
  <p>Frustrated, she thought, “What if a dog could find a person, activate an affordance on a wearable vest to immediately notify the search team, summon a drone to gain an aerial view and GPS coordinates, and then have the dog stay with that individual until help arrived – it could save lives.”</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Researchers are working on a project to train a dog to touch a sensor on its vest that calls for help for workers on the job or to find a missing person in the mountains.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In fact, by allowing dogs to “speak” in ways humans can easily understand, Jackson believes the team’s nose-activated vests could play a valuable role in the workplace. An assistance dog, for example, could warn workers if an employee is about to have an epileptic seizure or tell a person who suffers from diabetes if their blood sugar is dangerously low. Jackson and her team are also examining how to easily adapt the nose-activated vest for police work, where drug-sniffing dogs could report their finds, and military work, where dogs could communicate the location and type of improvised explosive devices (IEDs).</p>
  <p>“There’s so much information working dogs have to impart to their handlers and they don’t really have a good way of doing it,” says Jackson. “This technology gives dogs a voice and helps them communicate with people more clearly.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fccbe97cfe7e08ef90fc2e7fd0e418e09fc09e0b.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fccbe97cfe7e08ef90fc2e7fd0e418e09fc09e0b.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1fccbe97cfe7e08ef90fc2e7fd0e418e09fc09e0b.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="MISSING" src="./media_1fccbe97cfe7e08ef90fc2e7fd0e418e09fc09e0b.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="jumping-over-hurdles">Jumping over hurdles</h2>
  <p>For all its benefits, there are considerable challenges when it comes to training and managing science-supported and tech-powered canines. “When you add a layer of technology between a dog and an outcome, there are many ways for it to go wrong,” warns Tarun Wadhwa, CEO of Day One Insights, a strategy and advisory firm.</p>
  <p>Some complicating factors exist:</p>
  <p><strong>Design considerations:</strong> One way is by underestimating the physical limitations of designing wearable devices for dogs. “The challenge is the amount of real estate you have on a dog vest,” says Jackson, referring to her FIDO project. “Trying to <a href="/blogs/tiny-tech-big-bang">miniaturize</a> all of the electronics, speakers, and lights that you need is hard.”</p>
  <p><strong>Comfort:</strong> “Unlike humans, while dogs are forgiving, you can’t make a compelling argument for them to put on a fifty-pound backpack to test out equipment,” says Peper. Misplaced ruggedized components can also impede a dog’s natural movement, such as walking and running, especially if an apparatus fits the dog poorly. Proper fit is tough to determine when two species don’t speak the same language. In fact, without “a lot of qualitative feedback” from animals, Peper says it’s critical that researchers keep “a dog’s best interests in mind” by relying on “strong empirical research to understand what works for the dog” and to look for signs of discomfort or unhappiness.</p>
  <p><strong>Security of the systems used by dogs:</strong> Wadhwa warns of “issues around cybersecurity that could come up once you intermediate a relationship with a dog” and technology. In the case of AR-powered goggles, for instance, he notes that ill-intentioned hackers could deliberately manipulate the images in a dog’s field of vision by overlaying the screen with fake virtual objects.</p>
  <p>And what if a dog were to act on such misinformation? Potential errors range from mistakenly detecting an explosive device on the battlefield to misidentifying an airline passenger as having COVID-19.</p>
  <p>“I worry about issues like if a dog suspects that someone has COVID-19,” says Wadhwa. “We’re talking about suspending people’s liberties, making sure they stay at home, and restricting their rights and interactions with other people. It raises a lot of complicated questions.”</p>
  <p><strong>The importance of training:</strong> Excellent training can minimize the likelihood of some of these risks. Oftentimes, dogs are quick studies, eager to learn in exchange for a treat. In fact, Jackson, the Georgia Tech researcher, says, “The fastest that any of our dogs learned to use the [vest’s] sensors was 27 seconds.” The slowest was a pit bull who required nearly half an hour. Still, says Jackson, “27 minutes in the grand scheme of things is nothing. We tested everything from a basset hound to a little Jack Russell terrier to a papillon to a German shepherd and we have yet to find a dog that can’t do this.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a6a99d6c83673ab5378d7a73033734bb2fd4b4f4.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a6a99d6c83673ab5378d7a73033734bb2fd4b4f4.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1a6a99d6c83673ab5378d7a73033734bb2fd4b4f4.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Happy dog sitting on couch while owner pets it" src="./media_1a6a99d6c83673ab5378d7a73033734bb2fd4b4f4.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><strong>Selecting the right dogs for the job:</strong> Just because a dog can perform a task, however, doesn’t mean he’s fit for a career in workplace safety. For this reason, Jackson has worked with Canine Companions for Independence, a nonprofit organization, to develop smart toys that can help gauge a dog’s suitability for a lifelong career as a service dog.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Training service dogs is costly. Sensor data from a ball or a tugging toy can help predict if a German shepherd or Jack Russell terrier will perform well in the role.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The toys, a silicone ball and a silicone tug, are outfitted with sensors. By observing how a dog interacts with these toys, collecting sensor data, and developing classifiers that correlate the sensor data to the success (or failure) of assistance dogs, Jackson says the team “can predict with 90% accuracy which dogs are going to make it through a program and which dogs are going to fail.” The result, she says, is a technique that could save an organization an estimated US$5 million a year in training expenses spent on dogs ill-suited for service.</p>
  <p>Bottom-line advantages such as these could drive greater investment in systems and techniques that combine the natural capabilities of dogs with scientific and technological advances. For instance, Hielm-Björkman says running her COVID-19 testing program at Finland’s Helsinki-Vantaa Airport costs much less: only 2.1% of the amount the airport would have to pay for PCR tests. “It’s a no-brainer that people around the world should fund such a program – it’s cheap and fast,” she says.</p>
  <p>Yet as it stands, Peper of Command Sight says “one of the biggest challenges is finding funding” for innovative projects that introduce dogs to new roles in the workplace. That could change, however, if employees themselves advocate for the increased presence of canines, especially as people gradually return to the workplace. Organizations that listen, and embrace new ways of working with dogs, stand to not only improve the health and safety of their workers, but enhance employee experience when it matters most.</p>
</div>
<div>
  <p>Behind every bark is a wealth of information that could safety-proof the workplace – if only humans and dogs shared the same language. Furbo hopes to solve this dilemma by deciphering the various noises dogs make using video footage and machine learning algorithms.</p>
  <p>Essentially, Furbo is a streaming camera designed to take photos of a dog, dispense treats, and provide pet owners with a live feed of their pet through a smartphone app. Furbo plans to expand these capabilities with a feature that can translate the sounds of dogs into data, according to <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/04/08/technology/ai-pets-apps.html">The New York Times</a>.</p>
  <p>This entails gathering video data of dogs barking from thousands of the device’s users and training the machine learning algorithms within the device to distinguish among these sounds based on pet owners’ feedback. Using this technology, owners will not only know when their dog is barking, but if the dog is howling or whining – a sign of a possible break-in or other emergency.</p>
  <p>Although the goal is to provide pet owners with greater peace of mind, Furbo can assist in other ways. For instance, Furbo can alert business owners of intruders or emerging crises that threaten to impact the safety of work environments, such as warehouses or factories, that are protected by guard dogs.</p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>Style</div>
      <div>Additional Reading</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Workplace Wellness: Well-Being in a Changing Workforce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/workplace-wellness</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/workplace-wellness</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The definition of workplace wellness and employee well-being is evolving. Explore why today’s employers place increasing value on workforce wellness and the solutions that support it.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_180b860a1f1a94d7e17ff91c893c1b4c911eb5c04.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_180b860a1f1a94d7e17ff91c893c1b4c911eb5c04.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_180b860a1f1a94d7e17ff91c893c1b4c911eb5c04.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Woman jogging on lunch break" src="./media_180b860a1f1a94d7e17ff91c893c1b4c911eb5c04.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="workplace-wellness-for-a-changing-world">Workplace wellness for a changing world</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The definition of workplace wellness has broadened steadily over the past 10 years. An initial focus on physical health and safety has grown to encompass a more holistic view, inclusive of employees’ emotional, psychological, social, and even financial well-being.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Workplace wellness is also gaining traction as a business priority. In Deloitte’s <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/insights/focus/human-capital-trends/2020/designing-work-employee-well-being.html">Global Human Capital Trends 2020</a> report, 80% of respondents cited it as an “important” or “very important” priority, making it the year’s top-ranked trend. Today, successful companies are also adopting this broader, more inclusive view of employee well-being. Why? The data supports it. Businesses see the long-term organizational benefits that can accompany a well and happy workforce. According to a 2020 article in <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ellevate/2020/05/13/three-reasons-social-health-should-be-part-of-your-corporate-wellness-program/?sh=216191d61d5f">Forbes</a> magazine, some of the many ways that workplace wellness initiatives are paying off for modern businesses include increased loyalty, improved performance, and better engagement.</p>
  <p>With the COVID-19 pandemic came a sudden and seismic shift to a remote workforce. Workplace wellness initiatives that were already well underway were disrupted as the focus shifted – almost overnight – to the challenges of supporting a newly-remote employee base. With this “new normal” still in flux, and the health of many employees at even greater risk, the pressure on large companies to have flexible, scalable, and innovative wellness solutions to meet the needs of the changing world of work is even larger.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>What is workplace wellness? Any activity or program designed to support the physical, emotional, social, or financial well-being of employees.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="benefits-of-wellness-in-the-workplace">Benefits of wellness in the workplace</h2>
  <p>Wellness in the workplace begins with individual employees and extends across teams and departments to the organization as a whole. According to Deloitte’s <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/insights/focus/human-capital-trends/2020/designing-work-employee-well-being.html">Human Capital Trends 2020</a>, organizations implementing workforce well-being initiatives may find that it “reduces the need for remediation of work’s negative effects, freeing up resources to invest in other areas and increasing individual and team contributions to organizational outcomes.” Thus, immediate productivity benefits also drive long-term gains, such as worker resilience and higher organizational performance.</p>
  <p>A recent McKinsey article demonstrates how “<a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/mgi/overview/in-the-news/good-health-is-good-business">good health is good business</a>.” When businesses make a meaningful commitment to workplace wellness initiatives, they can expect lasting and long-term benefits, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Healthier employees with fewer sick days</li>
    <li>Greater ability to focus on work</li>
    <li>Fewer early retirements</li>
    <li>Lower healthcare costs</li>
    <li>An expanded workforce</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="how-retail-can-lead-the-wellness-economy">How retail can lead the wellness economy</h3>
        <p>Retailers can use new tech to become partners in consumers’ wellness journeys.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/blogs/how-retail-can-lead-the-wellness-economy">Here's how</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="how-forward-thinking-businesses-are-improving-employee-well-being">How forward-thinking businesses are improving employee well-being</h2>
  <p>With up to 90% of their employees working remotely, HR leaders are redefining employee wellness, creatively adapting and expanding programs beyond the standard gym memberships and employee assistance programs. According to research from <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20200618005185/en/New-Research-From-Fidelity-and-Business-Group-on-Health-Finds-95-of-Employers-Now-Include-Emotional-and-Mental-Health-Programs-in-Well-Being-Platforms">Fidelity Investments and Business Group on Health</a>, 78% of global employers now help employees improve their work–life balance, and 95% include emotional and <a href="/resources/why-mental-health-matters">mental health</a> programs in their corporate well-being platforms.</p>
  <p>"Now more than ever, employers are highly focused on employee mental health and well-being as they adjust to the pandemic, economic disruption, and heightened focus on the impact of racial and societal issues."</p>
  <p>- Ellen Kelsay, President and CEO, Business Group on Health</p>
  <p>Here is a small sample of specific ideas that HR leaders can build into employee well-being programs:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Develop personalized support tools to help employees navigate their healthcare options and the healthcare system.</li>
    <li>Subsidize healthy activities or offer financial wellness incentives, giving employees a choice of various wellness activities – such as “lose the COVID 15” or “10,000 steps per day.”</li>
    <li>Create an online portal to offer small classes, such as yoga or healthy cooking, exclusively for team members. Encourage members to bond by sharing ideas and suggestions.</li>
    <li>Provide subsidized and confidential online counseling to help employees transition to new ways of working and manage work–life stressors.</li>
    <li>Consider flexible work hours and stipends for work-related technologies to support remote workers.</li>
    <li><a href="https://news.sap.com/2020/06/sap-successfactors-visa-and-permits-safe-healthy-workplace/">Support employees</a> as they return to the physical workspace, by minimizing risks and implementing clear and supportive health and safety procedures.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19549d4b386bc84a42d3cd876338479f3bcb3a4c7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19549d4b386bc84a42d3cd876338479f3bcb3a4c7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19549d4b386bc84a42d3cd876338479f3bcb3a4c7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Woman participating in virtual meditation class." src="./media_19549d4b386bc84a42d3cd876338479f3bcb3a4c7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1680" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="how-hr-technologies-are-supporting-workplace-well-being">How HR technologies are supporting workplace well-being</h2>
  <p>HR technologies can help employees both feel and perform better. Smart, data-driven solutions are already helping HR teams identify and address employees’ physical issues, such as ergonomic discomfort or fatigue, and mental–emotional problems such as feeling overworked or anxious.</p>
  <p>Sensors and wearables, gamification of wellness goals and milestones, and fitness and wellness apps allow for high levels of engagement. <a href="/resources/ai-for-hr">Artificial intelligence (AI) for HR</a> and advanced data analytics can help create effective, personalized programs for individuals and recommend improvements to the overall employee wellness initiative.</p>
  <h2 id="how-to-implement-wellness-solutions-and-change">How to implement wellness solutions and change</h2>
  <ol>
    <li><strong>Be selective.</strong> Start small when choosing and implementing new wellness initiatives and technologies. Roll them out in a trickle rather than a deluge. Use <a href="/blogs/hr-tech-trends">intelligent HR solutions</a> to determine the most positive employee reactions – and to assess ROI.</li>
    <li><strong>Be transparent.</strong> Demonstrate and explain how these technologies and programs work. Show employees that sensors and other wellness technologies are voluntary and designed to improve their workplace experience, not oversee it.</li>
    <li><strong>Keep the trust.</strong> Reassure employees about their privacy and anonymity. Use examples like: “Here are sensor readings of an anonymous employee. We noticed high levels of frustration and fatigue, so we gave her less repetitive admin work and more creative problem-solving tasks – which she thrives at and enjoys.”</li>
    <li><strong>Don’t presume.</strong> Everyone has a different level of stress tolerance, and some are more “joiners” than others. The beauty of modern HR technology is that it customizes solutions to suit individual needs. Give employees access, support, and encouragement to use wellness tools and programs, but don’t nag them or make them mandatory.</li>
    <li><strong>Listen and learn.</strong> Many HR leaders are in uncharted territory in a workplace that has changed rapidly and drastically. It’s vital to leverage new HR technologies for their ability to gather and analyze data. Use advanced analytics as much as possible to help determine where employees need the most support and which solutions are working best.</li>
  </ol>
  <h2 id="corporate-wellness-solutions-for-the-changing-world-of-work">Corporate wellness solutions for the changing world of work</h2>
  <p>The past year has produced unforeseen challenges that have permanently changed the world of work. Fortunately, knowledge and data-driven technology already exist to help companies transform their workplace. Even if the vast majority of employees return to a physical workplace, the emphasis on workplace wellness will continue – and that’s good news for both companies and their employees.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="tools-that-support-workplace-wellness">Tools that support workplace wellness</h3>
        <p>Help your people be their best with SAP SuccessFactors solutions.</p>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/solutions.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why Mental Health Matters | SAP Insights]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/why-mental-health-matters</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/why-mental-health-matters</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[When it comes to mental health, accommodating employees’ needs can lead to increased productivity and higher retention. Read to learn more!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainability as a Strategy: Profits Follow Purpose]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/sustainability-strategy-profits-follow-purpose</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/sustainability-strategy-profits-follow-purpose</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Many companies implement environmental, social, and governance measures. But having a core sustainability business strategy is more important than ever.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13f8756a2d3488919cb5461c73fd4a06cfae0de8c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13f8756a2d3488919cb5461c73fd4a06cfae0de8c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_13f8756a2d3488919cb5461c73fd4a06cfae0de8c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Wind turbines in sunset" src="./media_13f8756a2d3488919cb5461c73fd4a06cfae0de8c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="522">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sustainability-as-strategy-when-profits-follow-purpose">Sustainability as Strategy: When Profits Follow Purpose</h1>
        <p>How leaders can reconfigure their offerings to place sustainability at the core of their business.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Decades after the company he founded made the transformation to using sustainable materials, Ray Anderson, CEO of Interface, remembered the realization “like a spear in the chest.” The large manufacturer of commercial flooring needed a higher purpose, a mission that included chasing profits but went beyond. The <a href="https://www.interface.com/US/en-US/sustainability/our-history-en_US#557997371">epiphany</a> came in 1994, as he recounted in a company video. Business was booming, and Anderson was thinking about retiring.</p>
  <p>At the time, several employees who had joined Interface during a recent acquisition were asking what the company was doing to help the environment. “It was a question for which we had no answers,” said Anderson, who recalled the experience in a company video before his death in 2011. “It was awkward for our salespeople, manufacturing people, research people.” So Interface senior leaders convened a task force to develop the company’s position. They asked Anderson to kick it off by sharing his vision.</p>
  <p>“I didn’t have an environmental vision, and I didn’t want to make that speech. I was really sweating,” says Anderson. Then Paul Hawken’s book, <em>The Ecology of Commerce</em>, landed on his desk. It immediately influenced Anderson and the speech he gave. He ended up challenging the task force to make Interface and its products sustainable, starting by inventing carpeting made from fully recycled materials. Anderson soon found himself a full-time advocate.</p>
  <p>“I continued to articulate the vision over and over and over, even when people thought I had gone around the bend. I was talking and didn’t know if I was connecting. People were looking at me with blank faces. I didn’t know if they had heard me or cared,” he said.</p>
  <p>Soon enough, the tiny task force gained traction. And one by one, Interface employees backed sustainability as their unifying corporate strategy. Sustainability gave them a higher purpose to motivate and challenge everyone, while driving profit.</p>
  <p>Interface initially identified key areas in which it needed to make progress. Then the task force set aggressive targets, including zero waste to landfills, zero fossil fuel energy use, zero process water use, and zero greenhouse gas emissions. Interface continues to be a leading light of <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/interface-recognized-as-global-sustainability-leader-for-20th-consecutive-year-by-globescan-and-sustainability-300468600.html">sustainable business strategy</a>, following a set of “EcoMetrics” that tracks materials and energy flowing in and out of the company. Most of its tile and carpet line is now made from waste products. In 2019, its net sales rose by 14% to US$1.3 billion.</p>
  <p>Anderson could not have foreseen that his work at Interface would leave a legacy of sustainability as corporate strategy for others to follow.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17033b29e9ecbccdb0037b46c2285976c9fe3276f.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17033b29e9ecbccdb0037b46c2285976c9fe3276f.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_17033b29e9ecbccdb0037b46c2285976c9fe3276f.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Father explaining how solar panel works to young daughter" src="./media_17033b29e9ecbccdb0037b46c2285976c9fe3276f.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="sustainability-redefined">Sustainability redefined</h2>
  <p>Other executives have light bulb experiences similar to Anderson’s that launch them on a journey to sustainability, says C. B. Bhattacharya, H. J. Zoffer chair of sustainability and ethics at the Katz Graduate School of Business, University of Pittsburgh and author of the book <em>Small Actions, Big Difference</em>.</p>
  <p>“Epiphany is an important part of the process,” he says. The executives might have pressure from shareholders to do more. Some have even faced boycotts of products that have fallen out of favor as tastes and customs change.</p>
  <p>What follows after that moment is the process of defining a new corporate purpose, one that is broader than merely being an engine for profits – and then, a massive change management effort that enables a large organization to pivot.</p>
  <p>The concept of sustainability has expanded as societies grapple with issues such as fair labor practices and ethical behavior.</p>
  <p>Today, most public company executives know they need a plan – and a good set of talking points – directing toward more sustainable business practices. Pro-environment measures like cutting down on paper use and reducing carbon emissions are not enough.</p>
  <p>That’s not just because addressing climate change will require more than these pro forma environmental moves. The concept of sustainability has expanded as societies around the world grapple with a range of issues.</p>
  <p>For example, in response to the social justice movement of 2020, business leaders are now getting involved in efforts to rebalance racial inequities. Fair labor practices also have become part of the conversation as <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/16/ceos-see-pay-grow-1000percent-and-now-make-278-times-the-average-worker.html">pay gaps</a> between management and workers have stretched. Increasingly, investors, consumers, and employees are becoming keenly interested in companies’ actions on these issues. <a href="/resources/generation-z-behavior-explained">Younger consumers</a> are gaining influence as customers and workers, and their preference to work for companies that <a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90306556/most-millennials-would-take-a-pay-cut-to-work-at-a-sustainable-company">prize sustainability</a> is clear. Millennials and their younger peers also demand more environmentally and socially responsible practices as investors, according to Ioannis Ioannou, associate professor of strategy and entrepreneurship at London Business School. They’re saying, “I care, and I care profoundly about how my pension fund, for instance, is investing in my savings. What sort of world will I retire in if that pension fund, for instance, is investing in fossil fuels right now?”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1710e65e38fbf9855b7cc6a69b2f7c2d93020b192.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1710e65e38fbf9855b7cc6a69b2f7c2d93020b192.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1710e65e38fbf9855b7cc6a69b2f7c2d93020b192.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1710e65e38fbf9855b7cc6a69b2f7c2d93020b192.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="745" height="560">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Leaders have noticed. In 2019, Business Roundtable released a <a href="https://www.businessroundtable.org/business-roundtable-redefines-the-purpose-of-a-corporation-to-promote-an-economy-that-serves-all-americans">statement</a> signed by 181 CEOs of large U.S. public companies declaring that the purpose of a corporation should be to promote an economy that serves everyone. It’s not enough to make money for shareholders. All stakeholders – customers, suppliers, the communities in which they operate – should benefit. In one press release, these leaders broadened the traditional Environmental, Social, and Governance (ESG) goals. Sustainability means being accountable to people and the planet as well as corporate shareholders.</p>
  <p>While some were skeptical of the pronouncement, Yale professor and author Dan Esty believes companies have little choice but to follow through. Consumers simply will not tolerate organizations that fail to redress the downstream negative effects on society that they produce (such as pollution, carbon emissions, and unequal pay).</p>
  <p>“It’s going to be increasingly unacceptable for companies to privately gain by imposing costs on the public,” says Esty, author and editor of 14 books relating to sustainability and governance, including the best-selling <em>Green to Gold</em> in 2006 and <em>Values at Work: Sustainable Investing and ESG Reporting</em> in 2020. Over time, he says, “the market will punish companies that fail to recognize this.”</p>
  <p>Leaders are coming around to this idea, albeit slowly. In a recent <a href="https://www.engieimpact.com/insights/global-executive-survey-preview">survey</a> of 200 top executives of large multinational corporations, which was conducted by ENGIE Impact, 75% said that sustainability strategy done well drives competitive advantage. Only 30% of those surveyed called their sustainability efforts successful, however. The results suggest that the executives do see sustainability having an increasingly significant effect on corporate revenues and profits in the next five years. ENGIE Impact, it is worth noting, is a sustainability consulting firm spun off from ENGIE, a French multinational electric utility.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="re-evaluating-business-operations">Re-evaluating business operations</h3>
        <p>What does supply chain sustainability look like in a changing world?</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/what-is-a-sustainable-supply-chain.html">Find out</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“We’re seeing more and more companies realize that putting sustainability at the core of their business strategy is actually a strategic advantage and is profitable,” says ENGIE Impact CEO Mathias Lelievre. While less than one-third of executives surveyed felt their sustainability efforts had been successful to date, the majority expected that to rise in five years.</p>
  <p>For example, Lelievre sees large companies like Unilever and Microsoft greatly stepping up their move toward carbon neutrality both within their own organizations and throughout their far-reaching supply chains. But the real story does not concern only traditional eco-friendly measures. The standard-bearers of the new, holistic view of sustainability are companies that have taken a traditional product or line of business and reimagined it to be better for people and the environment. These companies are transforming their entire business strategies to make the world a better place.</p>
  <p>In a recent survey of 200 top executives, 75% said sustainability strategy done well drives competitive advantage.</p>
  <p>Not surprisingly, as Interface’s Anderson discovered, shifting an organization’s strategy to sustainability requires a major effort, says Bhattacharya. It’s driven by relentless communication and change management efforts from the top, with leaders helping the company’s people to incubate, launch, and entrench sustainable practices. A shift toward sustainability also requires a new set of metrics beyond traditional measures that are found on company financial reports.</p>
  <p>At its heart, effective change happens when leaders mobilize the organization and manage resistance to the shift before the opportunity dries up. It’s about communicating what is being done and why, so employees can make sustainable strategy their own. “Successful strategic shifts require intensive organizational change management, the more so the further the pivot tries to move the company from its existing culture and capabilities,” says Paul Strebel, professor emeritus of governance and strategy, International Institute for Management Development (IMD).</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_171cb33471eb2bcbafe08130ba3cf41cdb60616be.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_171cb33471eb2bcbafe08130ba3cf41cdb60616be.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_171cb33471eb2bcbafe08130ba3cf41cdb60616be.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Hand holding lightbulb up to sun" src="./media_171cb33471eb2bcbafe08130ba3cf41cdb60616be.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="managing-change-for-the-better">Managing change for the better</h2>
  <p>It’s hard to imagine a bigger shift in strategy than the one cigarette maker Philip Morris International (PMI) undertook in 2016. The company identified what it saw as a tremendous opportunity to begin shifting completely away from its core product, cigarettes, to alternatives scientifically substantiated as better choices for adults who would otherwise continue to smoke. PMI believed doing so could meet consumer demand for better choices and positively impact public health. PMI CEO André Calantzopoulos reaffirmed this commitment at the company’s 2017 annual shareholder meeting, saying the company was committed to a smoke-free future and shifting its resources toward the development and responsible marketing of scientifically backed alternatives.</p>
  <p>The change in strategy was driven by the realization – a long time coming – that PMI had to address the negative effects of its product, according to Huub Savelkouls, a 26-year PMI veteran who was its chief sustainability officer until his recent retirement. (Jennifer Motles is the new CSO.) Since its change in strategy, PMI hired an army of scientists, now numbering 900, who have spent the last 10 years and $7 billion researching smokeless tobacco.</p>
  <p>Its first main smoke-free product, IQOS, is now sold in 61 markets, recently including the U.S. IQOS is an electrically heated tobacco system that heats tobacco rather than burning it. Because the tobacco is not set on fire, there is no smoke or ash, and the levels of harmful chemicals are significantly reduced compared to cigarette smoke. This benefits the individual user, bystanders, and the environment. In July 2020, the U.S. Food and Drug Administration authorized the marketing of IQOS as a modified risk tobacco product, the first (and so far, only) product to receive such approval. However, the company states that IQOS is not risk-free and delivers nicotine, which is addictive, and that the best choice is to quit or never start smoking.</p>
  <p>According to Savelkouls, PMI explicitly refrains from marketing to youth, as well as former smokers and those who have never smoked, and only markets its smoke-free products to current adult smokers who would otherwise continue to smoke. The message is to fully switch and replace cigarettes with better choices.</p>
  <p>Savelkouls says the effort has been working: “Our current switch rate is 70%. Consumers don’t use both products.”</p>
  <p>For sustainability to take hold as a strategy, leaders are in constant communication with shareholders, the media, customers, and other stakeholders about the ongoing efforts and what they mean to each group.</p>
  <p>PMI’s journey has been marked by the need for constant communication, both inside and outside the organization.</p>
  <p>To start with, PMI employees were naturally concerned when they heard their company intended to sunset their mainstay product. Would they have jobs in the near future? What would remain after the company’s main product was gone? Senior leaders spent – and still spend – much effort communicating with employees about the company’s new direction and why it was necessary.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a5e8b546f5e52075e8ff18b9fcb467613b585b83.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a5e8b546f5e52075e8ff18b9fcb467613b585b83.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1a5e8b546f5e52075e8ff18b9fcb467613b585b83.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Coworkers working together on complex problem" src="./media_1a5e8b546f5e52075e8ff18b9fcb467613b585b83.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>As Anderson discovered at Interface, in order for sustainability to take hold as strategy, communication – to shareholders, the media, customers, and a wider group of stakeholders – is endless. Suppliers are another important group to include in change management. PMI’s CEO and Savelkouls’s team were cognizant that the shift would affect others in its value chain, such as the tobacco farmers. (PMI has closed 10 cigarette factories in the last 10 years and plans to close more.) Also, the IQOS devices have an electronic component, so for the first time, Savelkouls and his team needed to start learning about practices for sustainable electronics manufacturing.</p>
  <p>Since announcing its commitment to move away from cigarettes, the growth of PMI’s revenues and profits have <a href="https://www.macrotrends.net/stocks/charts/PM/philip-morris/revenue">dipped a bit</a> as the giant company refocuses on its smoke-free offerings. Still, the company says sales of its “reduced risk products” have grown to $4.9 billion, or about one-quarter of its total net revenues. And the market is following PMI’s lead. The global e-cigarette market was valued at $14 billion in 2018 and is expected to grow to <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/vaping-market-to-reach-a-value-29-39-billion-at-a-cagr-of-20-3-from-2018-2022--a-report-from-tbrc-300904265.html">$29.39 billion</a> by 2022, according to The Business Research Company.</p>
  <p>Savelkouls believes the transition to new smoke-free products gives PMI 15 to 20 years of relative security from a revenue standpoint. In the meantime, the company is open to possibilities for entirely new product lines driven by its sustainability work. For instance, it has a small venture in Europe that offers life insurance to consumers who used to be smokers but who now have switched to smoke-free alternatives. In the past, these people would not have been able to buy life insurance; now they can – from PMI, which is backing up its belief that smoke-free products are a better choice than cigarettes. “We will for sure develop new competencies,” says Savelkouls.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1753d8333022880381ee58cfe7ff7ee897d763161.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1753d8333022880381ee58cfe7ff7ee897d763161.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1753d8333022880381ee58cfe7ff7ee897d763161.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Two paths in a forest going in opposite directions" src="./media_1753d8333022880381ee58cfe7ff7ee897d763161.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="pivots-with-a-purpose">Pivots with a purpose</h2>
  <p>PMI is not alone in shifting its traditional business strategy in a new, more sustainable direction.</p>
  <p>The trend cuts across industries.</p>
  <p>CVS, for example, has transcended its role as the corner drugstore where you stop in for a pack of cigs and a candy bar. It officially became <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/cvs-caremark-announces-corporate-name-change-to-cvs-health-to-reflect-broader-health-care-commitment-273717081.html">a healthcare company</a> in 2014 with high-profile moves to stop the sale of cigarettes and offer minute-clinic health services and vaccinations at its stores, which now number 9,900. CVS Health revenues have increased every year since 2015, and <a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/articles/cvs-stock-verticle-integration-health-care-benefits-insurance-pharmacy-51571147790">its competitive position is strong</a>.</p>
  <p>Unilever, the consumer-packaged goods giant, is another interesting case. It plans to put sustainability squarely in the face of consumers by <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-06-14/unilever-to-cut-emissions-to-zero-by-2039-adopt-carbon-labeling">labeling the carbon emissions</a> associated with 70,000 of its products as it cuts emissions to zero by 2039. Lelievre of ENGIE Impact says Unilever is also working to hold suppliers accountable on sustainability goals. That’s a critical step, since the supply chain typically represents 90% of a company’s carbon reduction opportunity.</p>
  <p>H&#x26;M, Sweden’s giant of fast fashion, was the first large fashion retailer to offer transparency about its manufacturing, starting with its Conscious collection. Consumers can click on a <a href="https://www2.hm.com/en_us/productpage.0920357001.html#modalSustainability">mock-turtleneck sweater</a>, for example, and see that it’s made of acrylic, polyester, and wool (the retailer’s goal is to use all recycled or sustainably sourced materials by 2030) and that it was made in China by H&#x26;M supplier Shanghai Jingrong Science &#x26; Technology Co. Ltd.</p>
  <p>Even energy companies have made moves to less carbon-centric lines of business. Examples in Europe abound:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>The former coal producer Dutch State Mines, now Royal DSM, has morphed over a decade into a science-based health and nutrition company. Its revenues showed growth up until the pandemic.</li>
    <li>Danish Oil and Natural Gas <a href="https://www.corporateknights.com/channels/climate-and-carbon/black-green-energy-15554049/">transformed itself</a> from one of Europe’s most coal-intensive companies into Orsted, a green-energy leader, <a href="https://orstedcdn.azureedge.net/-/media/q2_2020/interim-financial-report-h1-2020.ashx?la=en&#x26;rev=824777a016f8424fa0d34822df2993cb&#x26;hash=FEBEE5E445A7B1D7AEA06252D60712D9">without sacrificing profitability</a>.</li>
    <li>Enel, the Italian electric utility, is shifting a majority of its power generation to renewables, which offer a faster return on investment, more consistent earnings, and a better earnings before interest, tax, depreciation, and amortization (EBITDA) margin than fossil fuel power generation plants, according to a <a href="https://www.sharedvalue.org/resource/hybrid-metrics/">recent report</a> from the Shared Value Initiative.</li>
    <li>Spanish utility Iberdrola comes in as the second fastest in decarbonization and rates highly on many ESG scoring systems, according to the report. It also comes out significantly better when one considers decarbonization and profit together.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>These strategic shifts don’t occur overnight. Take DSM, which Strebel studied. Its transformation took nearly 10 years and hundreds of meetings to complete. “DSM used a rolling series of strategy dialogues with managers to gradually articulate the new biotech vision,” says Strebel.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1872c86c75ad7bbc6a0170dabc9e139e24aa54a2a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1872c86c75ad7bbc6a0170dabc9e139e24aa54a2a.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1872c86c75ad7bbc6a0170dabc9e139e24aa54a2a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Electricity meter displaying kWh" src="./media_1872c86c75ad7bbc6a0170dabc9e139e24aa54a2a.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="measuring-sustainability-by-the-books">Measuring sustainability, by the books</h2>
  <p>Neil Stewart, director of corporate outreach at the Sustainability Accounting Standards Board (SASB), is in the metrics business. His organization provides the means for enterprises around the world to report on financially material sustainability issues.</p>
  <p>It’s important for companies to identify the right factors that drive both sustainability and financial performance.</p>
  <p>“They can begin to build their strategy around those opportunities,” says Stewart. “This is an exciting time for companies and for investors where we start to see the markets drive solutions, innovation, and growth on pressing world problems. There has been this enormous public awakening, and it’s reflected in companies and in investors.”</p>
  <p>SASB standards identify the ESG issues that are financially material within 77 vertical industries, from apparel and automotive to technology and transportation. Companies aren’t necessarily managing the factors that matter to financial performance, Stewart says, “and as a result, they may not be seeing the impact of the increases in performance that they deserve for the effort they’re putting in.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-news-story">Read the news story:</h3>
        <p>A maturing approach to embedding sustainability in business.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://news.sap.com/2022/10/embedding-sustainability-business-maturing-approach/">Dive in</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The industry standards that SASB provides lay out in detail how companies can change this. Take the example of an electronics manufacturer that Stewart recently spoke with. Like many companies, it had been working hard to reduce greenhouse gas emissions and to better manage its water use. “These two issues are front of mind, but in the standard for electronics manufacturers, neither one is financially material,” says Stewart.</p>
  <p>That means that from the point of view of the company’s income statement, balance sheet, and cash flow, reducing greenhouse gases and better managing water use will not affect company performance. What is material for electronics manufacturers, adds Stewart, are things like energy management, hazardous waste disposal, and – beyond those factors – an energy-efficient product line.</p>
  <p>So if this company uses energy wisely and disposes of waste properly and then increases its focus on energy-efficient products, that will drive performance and increase customer loyalty. “For management, they might be thinking so much about what comes out of their smokestacks that they’re missing the factors that actually will drive better performance and enable it to attract the capital from investors who want to believe their investment will make an impact,” says Stewart.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1710e65e38fbf9855b7cc6a69b2f7c2d93020b192.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1710e65e38fbf9855b7cc6a69b2f7c2d93020b192.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1710e65e38fbf9855b7cc6a69b2f7c2d93020b192.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Team of three working on building plans" src="./media_1710e65e38fbf9855b7cc6a69b2f7c2d93020b192.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="745" height="560">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f5859c53c9b6bf15ea11b18824ff94a4f379c4cc.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f5859c53c9b6bf15ea11b18824ff94a4f379c4cc.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1f5859c53c9b6bf15ea11b18824ff94a4f379c4cc.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="placeholder" src="./media_1f5859c53c9b6bf15ea11b18824ff94a4f379c4cc.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="1">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="measuring-sustainability">Measuring Sustainability</h2>
  <p>The Sustainability Accounting Standards Board (SASB) provides standards that identify the Environmental, Social and Governance issues tied to financial performance in 77 industries. Each industry has its own set of disclosure topics and accounting metrics that will help companies in that space move the needle on profitability.</p>
  <p>SASB’s standard-setting process includes evidence-based research, participation from companies, investors, and subject-matter experts, and oversight and approval from an independent <a href="https://www.sasb.org/governance/standards-board/">standards board</a>. (For more detail, see the SASB Rules of Procedure, which in November 2020 were open for public comment.) SASB standards are increasingly cited by <a href="https://www.sasb.org/investor-use/investor-perspectives/">financial asset managers</a> in their proxy voting guidelines, including those from BlackRock, Goldman Sachs Asset Management, Neuberger Berman, and State Street Global Advisors.</p>
  <p>The following are examples of three industries from the 77 classified by SASB with their disclosure topics. The accounting metrics within each disclosure topic can be found in the full SASB standards, which are available to download on the SASB Web site:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Apparel, accessories, and footwear:</strong> Disclosure topics include management of chemicals in products, environmental impacts in the supply chain, labor conditions in the supply chain, and raw materials sourcing.</li>
    <li><strong>Restaurants:</strong> Disclosure topics include energy management, water management, food and packaging waste management, food safety, nutritional content, labor practices, supply chain management, and food sourcing.</li>
    <li><strong>Software and IT services:</strong> Disclosure topics include environmental footprint of hardware infrastructure, data privacy and freedom of expression, data security, recruiting and managing a global, diverse and skilled workforce, intellectual property protection and competitive behavior, and managing systemic risks from technology disruptions.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_168b7cff413833055104c35650bfccdc8f060404b.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_168b7cff413833055104c35650bfccdc8f060404b.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_168b7cff413833055104c35650bfccdc8f060404b.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Hand feeling tall grass in a field" src="./media_168b7cff413833055104c35650bfccdc8f060404b.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1958" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="meeting-the-needs-of-a-changing-world">Meeting the needs of a changing world</h2>
  <p>Global climate change is threatening the fate of the world. Unrest and economic inequality are destabilizing both governments and populations. And then there’s the peril to the business entity itself. Senior executives face the choice of adapting their strategy toward sustainability or risking displacement by companies that do just that. “It might be the Teslas of the world, it might be the Beyond Meats of the world that enter established industries and replace the incumbents,” Ioannou says.</p>
  <p>Stewart calls the shift to a sustainable business strategy a “genuine awakening.”</p>
  <p>“It’s continuing despite COVID-19. So this concern about climate, about inequality, about diversity, there’s an enormous will to address ESG issues. These are fundamental business issues,” says Stewart.</p>
  <p>We are now at a watershed moment, says sustainability consultant Mike Barry. Many decades of globalization have lifted millions of people out of poverty and raised the standard of living for virtually everyone on the planet. But globalization also brought about economic losers as jobs migrated east, created a hyperconnected world where a pandemic can spread with ease, and plundered nature. Says Barry, “These problems are increasingly evident as wildfires burn, plastics choke sea life, and citizens take to the streets to protest. Most business leaders are recognizing the need for profound change to an economy that has the tenets of fairness, equality, inclusion, and well-being at its heart.”</p>
  <p>And once they see the need for that kind of change, it is unlikely executives will ever un-see it. In the words of the late Ray Anderson, “There are no ex-environmentalists.”</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/environmental-compliance</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diversity in the Workplace: Strategies and Best Practices]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/diversity-in-the-workplace</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/diversity-in-the-workplace</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Explore strategies and best practices for diversity in the workplace. Diversity training alone isn't enough to drive real, lasting change.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ERP Implementation Team Structure]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/erp-implementation-team-structure</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/erp-implementation-team-structure</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Your ERP implementation project team is critical to success. Learn how to structure and manage your ERP project team to avoid common errors and pitfalls.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_195fbfca6e0c53b88223d55dcc2df40cbe167bf60.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_195fbfca6e0c53b88223d55dcc2df40cbe167bf60.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_195fbfca6e0c53b88223d55dcc2df40cbe167bf60.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="ERP implementation team in a meeting" src="./media_195fbfca6e0c53b88223d55dcc2df40cbe167bf60.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="structuring-your-erp-implementation-team-for-a-successful-project">Structuring your ERP implementation team for a successful project</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>When implementing new ERP software, companies often spend a lot of time identifying their requirements but relatively little assembling the team that will drive the implementation. Yet, the ERP project team is without question the biggest success factor, one that can make the difference between on-target implementation and a project that goes sideways.</p>
  <p>Deceptively simple, here is the formula for a successful implementation: the right people, with the right skills, following the right steps. Make sure you start your ERP planning in tandem with the team selection process. These eight steps will help you structure your project team, create your plan, and put the right measures in place.</p>
  <p>The formula for a successful implementation: the right people, with the right skills, following the right steps.</p>
  <h2 id="recognize-that-its-not-an-it-project">1. Recognize that it’s not an IT project</h2>
  <p>Because ERP systems are based on information technology, people often assume that ERP implementations are IT projects. Not so. An <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp.html">ERP system</a> is the backbone of your company’s entire operation so you need engagement and commitment from every department. Without sufficient organizational support, an IT-driven implementation is likely to result in expensive delays, user resistance, dissatisfaction, or even outright failure.<br><br>Your IT department will take care of hardware and software installation (if the new system is installed on-premise). IT will also be responsible for compatibility and integration with other data-dependent systems and equipment – both within and connected to the enterprise. However, the responsibility to define the new business processes that will drive system configuration falls squarely on the shoulders of the system users.</p>
  <h2 id="secure-executive-commitment">2. Secure executive commitment</h2>
  <p>While your CIO or CTO undoubtedly endorsed the implementation project, their involvement does not end there; signing off on the ERP investment is only the beginning. Executives must understand the impact of a large <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/what-is-erp/erp-implementation-best-practices.html">ERP implementation project</a>, be willing to make the necessary trade-offs to allow people to devote time and energy to the project, and provide visible evidence of their support.</p>
  <p>Executives should voice their commitment from the earliest kick-off meetings. They should stay involved, following the team’s progress and offering encouragement when and where appropriate. They must also serve as the final authority when conflicts or issues arise that cannot be resolved without executive involvement.</p>
  <p>In any project there will be times when other priorities interfere with project commitments. Customer demands, training sessions, or competing projects can easily pull team members away. Employees will be hard-pressed to resist those distractions without visible executive commitment and “permission” to stay focused.</p>
  <h2 id="choose-the-right-project-team-leader">3. Choose the right project team leader</h2>
  <p>An effective project team, led by a smart and dedicated project leader, is required to drive an ERP project to successful completion, on time and on budget. The team leader should come from the operations side of the business and be the person that most people turn to when they have a question or a problem, someone who knows the company’s business, internal politics, and how things work in your organization. The project leader could be a department head but in many cases will not be. If possible, identify this person as early as possible to allow for participation in the selection process.</p>
  <p>The team leader must be – or become – proficient in the use of project management software for tracking tasks, schedule, and costs. Previous project management experience is helpful but not required; there are plenty of resources available to train the designated individual in project management techniques and tools.</p>
  <h2 id="get-the-right-people-on-your-erp-implementation-team">4. Get the right people on your ERP implementation team</h2>
  <p>Your implementation team structure should reflect your organization. Project team members should represent all major functional departments, particularly those that are primary users and beneficiaries of the system. Departments may include engineering, sales and customer field service, procurement, finance and accounting, IT, physical plant and maintenance, human resources, or others depending on how your business is organized and the breadth of your system’s reach.</p>
  <p>The team is responsible for planning and organizing the project and should meet regularly to review progress and address any issues that arise. Each team member will assume responsibility for coordinating activities within their functional area, often establishing and leading individual task teams to accomplish various tasks. Members will report back to the project team as these tasks are undertaken and completed.</p>
  <p>In most cases, the project team will meet weekly – or more frequently during critical or high-activity periods. While C-level executives are not expected to attend team meetings, they should be kept aware of all implementation activities and decisions through regular reporting by the team leader. Company-wide status reporting is also highly recommended to help keep enthusiasm and interest high.</p>
  <h2 id="follow-a-structured-and-inclusive-implementation-planning-process">5. Follow a structured and inclusive implementation planning process</h2>
  <p>Planning must start early, when the project is first suggested or identified. The project plan will be continually updated as new information becomes available – but it should be “locked in” at the start of each phase. While additional changes may be necessary after that point, changes in mid-process should be avoided if at all possible. “Scope creep,” the tendency to keep adding to or changing the project’s objectives, is probably the greatest threat to successful project completion. Good ideas will likely emerge during the process but even seemingly small changes can slow down or derail your project. Set these ideas aside for phase two.</p>
  <p>Get the (future) user community involved in the early planning process. Why is this so important? They are the main source of information for the “as-is” description of the business and its processes. You’ll need this in the requirements definition portion of your <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/what-is-erp/how-to-evaluate-erp-software.html">ERP request for proposals</a> (RFP). You’ll want them involved in the selection process so they can tell you if the system really meets their needs in the context of their day-to-day processes. Most importantly, early and continuous involvement in the specification and selection process will help overcome any resistance to change that is often present among the user community when something new is thrust upon them.</p>
  <p>These and other <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/what-is-erp/erp-implementation-best-practices.html">ERP implementation and planning best practices</a> can help you get the most of your investment.</p>
  <p>Get the (future) user community involved in the early planning process.</p>
  <h2 id="track-your-project-plan">6. Track your project plan</h2>
  <p>Use project management tools to schedule and track the project and its progress. There are many relatively inexpensive project management software packages to choose from. The software will help lay out the schedule, identify resource needs, and spot potential conflicts. Once the entire project plan is loaded, it will help you track each task and the overall progress against the plan, as well as identify the impact of any slippage – delays caused by the late completion of tasks that may affect other timelines. The tools will also track expenditures compared to budget and keep senior management informed of funding and resource needs.<br><br>As deviations from the project plan are identified, the project team must quickly address them. Small slips become major problems if not resolved while they are still small. Each task team leader should report up-to-the-minute status of active projects to the rest of the project team at the weekly meeting. The project team can then figure out how to bring any delayed or disrupted task back on schedule. The schedule is paramount – don’t let any planned activity slip as there will be other impacts downstream. (It’s okay to build a little cushion into critical tasks and phases of the plan. You might consider adopting some of the project management principles from Eli Goldratt’s <em>Critical Chain</em>, including ways to make these buffers more effective.)</p>
  <h2 id="make-sure-that-users-own-the-system">7. Make sure that users “own” the system</h2>
  <p>This point bears repeating: the success of your implementation rests on the user community feeling a sense of ownership of the system. If users are a part of the process from the beginning, they will feel a greater sense of responsibility for its success – since it was their idea, at least in part, to choose this particular system and configure it as you did.<br><br>In any implementation, there will be moments when times get tough or unanticipated obstacles appear. If users do not feel that it is their system, it’s easy to blame someone else – executives, managers, IT, or the system itself – rather than digging in and fixing the problem. The key to gaining ownership commitment is early involvement in project planning and goal setting.<br><br>The “What’s in it for me?” factor is also important in earning that sense of ownership. Each user must see benefits from the new system – whether ease-of-use, convenience, more faith in the accuracy of information, the ability to accomplish more and have a bigger impact on the organization, or reduction of stress, overtime, and frustration. Some of these “soft” benefits are important in motivating users to adopt the system and make it a success. Education and training are key to helping users understand how the system will improve their work lives and job performance.</p>
  <p>The success of your implementation rests on the user community feeling a sense of ownership of the system.</p>
  <h2 id="measure-your-erp-project-teams-success">8. Measure your ERP project team’s success</h2>
  <p>The ultimate measurement of project team effectiveness is, of course, a successful implementation, completed on time and on budget. However, intermediate measures are just as important. The project plan is made up of a number of interdependent tasks laid out on a timeline, with resources assigned for each task. The team’s responsibility, after the plan has been approved, is to manage the completion of all tasks as planned.</p>
  <p>Individual tasks, when completed, serve as milestones. Each week, individual task managers should report on task progress, including time and resource utilization as well as any challenges, conflicts, or issues to be addressed – so that the project team as a whole can decide on corrective actions or resource reallocation needed to keep tasks on target. The successful completion of all tasks along the way acts as a measurement for both the performance of task leaders as well as the larger project team.</p>
  <p>Achieving <a href="/resources/erp-roi-calculation-worksheet">ERP ROI</a> (return on investment) expectations is also a measure of team accomplishment, especially if those ROI expectations have been realistically time-phased to show progress or continuous improvement.</p>
  <p>And finally, the project team’s communication, while a less direct measure, is another indicator of achievement. How well did the team communicate project status to the company at large and up the chain to department managers and company executives? Strong communication is an essential ingredient of a successful project.</p>
  <h2 id="summary">Summary</h2>
  <p>ERP implementation requires enterprise-wide participation and support. The project team is at the heart of the implementation even though they don’t really “do” the implementation themselves. The team’s primary job is to plan and manage the project, to enlist support, and to keep the enterprise motivated and moving forward toward the achievement of all of the planned tasks and activities – until the project is successfully completed.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="on-premise-cloud-or-a-hybrid-erp">On-premise, cloud, or a hybrid ERP?</h3>
        <p>Learn about the many options available in planning your cloud ERP deployment.</p>
        <p><em><a href="/resources/cloud-erp-deployment-options">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Benefits of an In-Memory Database]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/in-memory-database</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/in-memory-database</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how a modern in-memory database can deliver the processing speed and responsiveness that is essential to businesses today.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1afe2d158b906c4a7256f0c11ff30c34ac6a1cadb.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1afe2d158b906c4a7256f0c11ff30c34ac6a1cadb.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1afe2d158b906c4a7256f0c11ff30c34ac6a1cadb.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Person using in-memory ERP" src="./media_1afe2d158b906c4a7256f0c11ff30c34ac6a1cadb.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="real-benefits-of-an-in-memory-database">Real benefits of an in-memory database</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>What is an in-memory database? Simply stated, it’s a database that is held in computer memory rather than in a traditional location such as disk storage. For most business applications, the time needed to store and retrieve data is the biggest factor in determining how quickly tasks can be completed – and while a few milliseconds to retrieve data from a disk may seem trivial, when multiplied by thousands or millions of records these delays can seriously affect system speed and performance. When the data is already in memory, access is almost instantaneous.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Businesses today need real-time information – in other words, they need to know what is happening now, not what may have occurred yesterday or even a few minutes ago. Businesses expect their computer systems to do more and to do it faster than legacy systems so they can keep up with a rapidly changing world. An in-memory database is the obvious answer, but until recently, memory was too expensive and computer systems were not built to efficiently handle the large amount of memory needed. Now, all that has changed. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/hana.html">Modern databases</a> can deliver the speed and responsiveness today’s business users need. Programs written for in-memory data require fewer instructions that execute more quickly. User queries deliver the information without the delays that are common with traditional database systems.</p>
  <p>In-memory databases, also referred to as real-time databases (RTDB), have been around since the 1980s and were used in industries where rapid response times were critical, such as telecommunications, banking, travel, and gaming. Now, affordable memory and system hardware are available to all industries and applications, including <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/what-is-erp.html">ERP systems</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="where-are-in-memory-databases-used-today">Where are in-memory databases used today?</h2>
  <p>The emergence of affordable in-memory-capable systems has opened opportunities for faster processing and more responsive systems for business applications of all kinds, not just the high-volume, transaction-oriented systems mentioned above. In-memory databases are ideal for applications that process a lot of data (think advanced planning, simulation, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics/what-is-analytics.html">analytics</a>), as well as for supporting transaction processing where demand is random with large, unpredictable spikes in incoming traffic. And, they are especially good for companies where the data is expanding rapidly, such as:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Medical device monitoring</li>
    <li>Real-time financial analytics</li>
    <li>Online banking and credit card sales</li>
    <li>E-commerce sites and online auctions</li>
    <li>Real-time market data on new products or offers</li>
    <li>Machine learning for billing and subscriber applications</li>
    <li>Geographic information system (GIS) processing</li>
    <li>Streaming sensor data (IoT)</li>
    <li>Network and grid management</li>
    <li>Advertising results (A/B testing for online ads)</li>
    <li>Interactive gaming</li>
    <li>And more …</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="benefits-of-in-memory">Benefits of in-memory</h2>
  <p>Speed of reading and writing data is the primary characteristic of in-memory data, which enables faster processing and improved response in business applications. But application developers have been quick to realize that this faster response and increased capability are also valuable in allowing the re-design of several other tools and programs that deliver more value. When the database is architected and built from the ground up on an in-memory database, numerous improvements can be made in the design of internal data models and processes.</p>
  <p><strong>Data model:</strong> A number of different database structures have been developed for legacy technologies to optimize data access for different tasks:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Data stored in rows (traditional schema)</li>
    <li>Column-oriented architecture, which provides high-volume, fast access response for a limited subset of data</li>
    <li>Special databases for unstructured data, and</li>
    <li>Others that may speed up access in limited use cases or accommodate special requirements.</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="try-our-in-memory-database">Try our in-memory database</h3>
        <p>Test drive SAP HANA Cloud and discover the benefits of an in-memory database.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/pricing.html">Free trial</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>A <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/hana.html">modern in-memory database</a> allows all types of data to be stored in a single system, including structured transactions and unstructured data such as voice, video, free-form documents, and emails – all with the same fast access capability.</p>
  <p><strong>Faster processing:</strong> In-memory databases are faster than legacy databases because they require fewer CPU instructions to retrieve data. Developers can exploit this benefit by adding more function without the accompanying drag on system response. Also, using parallel processing so that multiple subsets (columns) can be processed simultaneously adds even more speed and capacity.</p>
  <p><strong>Combined tools:</strong> Traditional systems store transaction data in a legacy database that is accessed by online transactional processing (OLTP). Then, to get a view for analytics, the data is often moved to a separate database (data warehouse) where online analytical processing (OLAP) tools can be used to analyze large data sets (or <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/what-is-big-data.html">Big Data</a>). Modern, in-memory databases can support both OLAP and OLTP, eliminating the need for redundant storage and the delays between data transfers, which in turn eliminates any concerns about completeness or timeliness of the warehouse data.</p>
  <p><strong>Smaller digital footprint:</strong> Traditional databases store a large amount of redundant data. For example, the system creates a copy of each row that is updated, and it adds tables of combined data sets that increase space needs and maintenance requirements. In addition to the redundancy avoided for OLAP/OLTP mentioned above, column-oriented databases save changes as they are applied to the database.</p>
  <p><strong>Immediate insight:</strong> A modern, in-memory database provides embedded analytics to deliver business insight for real-time alerts and operational reporting on live transactional data.</p>
  <h2 id="how-does-a-modern-in-memory-database-work">How does a modern, in-memory database work?</h2>
  <p>It would be inefficient and unnecessary to hold all a company’s data in memory; some information is held in-memory (called hot storage) while other data is stored on disk (cold storage). The hot and cold designations derive from information handling paradigms developed by the cloud computing industry.</p>
  <p>Hot data is deemed mission-critical and is accessed frequently, so it is held in memory for fast retrieval and modification.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1deee8d5134b0043603500811961fea40d532a2d1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1deee8d5134b0043603500811961fea40d532a2d1.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1deee8d5134b0043603500811961fea40d532a2d1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Example of hot vs cold storage" src="./media_1deee8d5134b0043603500811961fea40d532a2d1.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="1080">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Example of hot vs cold storage for an ERP system.</em></p>
  <p>Data that is more static – in other words, data that is requested infrequently and is not normally required for active use – can be stored in a less expensive (and infinitely expandable) way on disk drives or solid-state devices (SSD). Cold storage data does not benefit from the fast access of an in-memory database, but it is still readily available when needed for less time-critical applications. Cold storage is best for historical data, closed activities, old projects, and the like.</p>
  <p>In planning the migration to an in-memory database, the implementation team decides how to sort existing data into cold storage for past requirements and hot storage for ongoing activities. Archiving criteria for keeping the active systems and data in top condition must also be determined.</p>
  <p>In-memory database systems are designed with “persistence” for logging all the transactions and changes to provide standard data backup, and system restore. Persistence in modern systems allows them to run at full speed while maintaining data in the event of power failure.</p>
  <h2 id="the-time-to-move-to-in-memory-data-is-now">The time to move to in-memory data is now</h2>
  <p>A modern in-memory database is an important foundational building block for digital transformation. Why? Because a digital enterprise cannot use yesterday’s data to make today’s decisions. Now that in-memory pricing is lower and memory capacity is steadily expanding, an in-memory database is a good choice for enterprises that need real-time insight to thrive in today’s economy.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="what-is-sap-hana">What is SAP HANA?</h3>
        <p>Explore SAP’s in-memory database and the benefits it delivers.</p>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/hana.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Circular Economy: Path to Sustainable Profitability]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/circular-economy-sustainable-profitability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/circular-economy-sustainable-profitability</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The circular economy isn’t just—or even mainly—about saving the planet. It’s the best way forward as a business strategy.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-supply-chain</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Data Privacy: Can You Keep a Secret?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/data-privacy-can-you-keep-a-secret</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/data-privacy-can-you-keep-a-secret</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[As business increasingly crosses borders, companies must institute data ethics policies that satisfy customer expectations without dampening innovation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c34ed4d7480b67b0385b0990e9b5182432dc36cb.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c34ed4d7480b67b0385b0990e9b5182432dc36cb.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1c34ed4d7480b67b0385b0990e9b5182432dc36cb.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Abstract programming code." src="./media_1c34ed4d7480b67b0385b0990e9b5182432dc36cb.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="data-privacy-can-you-keep-a-secret">Data Privacy: Can You Keep a Secret?</h1>
        <p>The era of data ethics is upon us – and only the companies with the highest standards will win over global customers.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The Web is worldwide, but data privacy depends very much upon where you live.</p>
  <p>In Germany, for example, data privacy is an issue that citizens take seriously. The country’s laws are some of the most stringent in the world and are based on a long-standing aversion to sharing data with both business and government entities.</p>
  <p>In fact, the world’s first data protection law came into effect in (then West) Germany in 1978.</p>
  <p>Germans long ago realized that their personal safety and self-determination included their data. Consumers around the world are slowly coming to the same realization while our global dependence on distributed computing forces a worldwide reckoning of privacy and data ethics.</p>
  <p>Consumers now see that many “We protect your data” statements aren’t designed with their welfare in mind or aren’t backed up with the firepower to make that happen. In 2019, there were 1,314,388 records <a href="https://privacyrights.org/data-breaches">breached</a> in the United States, according to Privacy Rights Clearinghouse, and an all-time total of 11,613,626,078. (Because of differences in state laws around reporting, Privacy Rights Clearinghouse notes, these numbers are probably less than the actual amount.)</p>
  <p>As business increasingly crosses borders, the companies with the highest degree of data ethics will gain a competitive advantage. The first step toward that goal is instituting data ethics policies that satisfy customer expectations without dampening innovation.</p>
  <p>On your mark, get set, go.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19f9b9dbb7080037dd58eea64ba28c4f7adceb6da.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19f9b9dbb7080037dd58eea64ba28c4f7adceb6da.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_19f9b9dbb7080037dd58eea64ba28c4f7adceb6da.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="data breach" src="./media_19f9b9dbb7080037dd58eea64ba28c4f7adceb6da.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="a-change-years-in-the-making">A change years in the making</h2>
  <p>In the years following the passage of Germany’s 1978 data privacy law, few other countries followed suit – making Germany the model island of privacy in an otherwise no-holds-barred data-collection world.</p>
  <p>It could have continued that way for the foreseeable future if not for a series of data attacks, breaches, and intentional data harvesting that didn’t sit well with consumers, consumer advocates, and, eventually, regulators.</p>
  <p>But, of course, the regulators would have had little sway were it not for a major shift in customer thinking about privacy. Consumers are better educated now and asking for more transparency and accountability. They’re better informed and savvier about security, privacy, and rights to data, and they’re thinking about the trade-offs between usability and risk.</p>
  <p>Part of this has been prompted by the advent of products like Internet of Things (IoT)-enabled wearables, connected home gadgets, and facial recognition and <a href="/blogs/biometrics-sensing-healthy-society">biometrics</a> technology. These products have helped make consumers more aware of the risks of data and of how their personal data has been, or can be, used. Now corporate customers are thinking along the same lines when considering products in the B2B world.</p>
  <p>The market is paying attention: no company wants to be the poster child for privacy neglect. The pendulum has swung toward privacy, and companies must now show customers that they’re taking it seriously.</p>
  <h2 id="privacy-as-a-competitive-advantage">Privacy as a competitive advantage</h2>
  <p>Privacy begins with trust. Trust is now the most powerful digital currency and it powers today’s economy. Its constituent elements are data protection and privacy. Together, they must be part of every company’s operational DNA.</p>
  <p>The implementation of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) in May 2018 threw a spotlight on global privacy and forced companies to reevaluate their data trail because the regulation is backed up with firepower in the form of penalties – fines of up to €20 million or up to 4% of annual global revenue, whichever is greater.</p>
  <p>Depending on the security maturity levels within companies, the GDPR has been either an easy adaptation or a heavy burden. The GDPR has prompted other non-EU countries and their citizens to take a serious look at their current data protection laws. Although the GDPR is a European law, it affects more than just Europe-based companies and EU citizens. If your competitor is GDPR compliant and you’re not, guess who’s going to win business?</p>
  <p>The GDPR is, essentially, very close to a certification (more on certifications later). The companies that are GDPR compliant are showing that they take privacy and security seriously and have privacy policies that are accessible and understandable by the general populace so that customers (not just the in-house legal department) know what they’re signing up for.</p>
  <p>However, there have been reports of many companies ignoring GDPR. A <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2001.02479">study</a> from early 2020 found that only 11.8% of consent management platforms (CMPs) conform to GDPR requirements. Further, the designs of popular CMPs manipulate consent (see: <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2018/07/01/wtf-is-dark-pattern-design/">dark pattern design</a>). Within a year and a half after GDPR was enacted, companies have been hit with £100 million in <a href="https://www.itpro.co.uk/policy-legislation/general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/354577/data-protection-fines-hit-ps100m">fines</a> – and counting (investigations and fees are the responsibility of individual EU member countries).</p>
  <p>Companies earn trust by being transparent. Every company needs a “trust model.” There are some basic principles for developing such a model. They include incorporating security into software development from the very beginning, creating strict rules when it comes to who can access data and for what reason, and installing a program of consistent monitoring.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17a3d1ae0803ac4aa530ea17721b6e4ac7217c57a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17a3d1ae0803ac4aa530ea17721b6e4ac7217c57a.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_17a3d1ae0803ac4aa530ea17721b6e4ac7217c57a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Lady of justice" src="./media_17a3d1ae0803ac4aa530ea17721b6e4ac7217c57a.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="toward-an-ethical-foundation">Toward an ethical foundation</h2>
  <p>Codes of ethics for data already exist, like that of the <a href="https://ethics.acm.org/code-of-ethics/">Association for Computing Machinery</a>. “The question is whether those high-level statements and principles actually provide meaningful guidance because they’re often difficult to translate to day-to-day thinking as technology products are being built,” says Solon Barocas, assistant professor in the department of Information Science at Cornell University in New York. “But high-level statements have value because they signal that the community itself values these things.”</p>
  <p>Barocas teaches a data science ethics course, one of a wave of such courses that have recently appeared at universities across the United States. The core thought is to train the next generation of data scientists to incorporate these ideas into their work from the get-go. Recognizing a competitive edge, this is the kind of training that globally ambitious companies will be looking for when hiring data scientists.</p>
  <p>The tech industry has existing practices and policies, Barocas says, but they haven’t been particularly well conveyed outside of the industry. That’s beginning to change, however.</p>
  <h2 id="how-to-create-a-data-ethics-policy">How to create a data ethics policy</h2>
  <p><strong>Data has become a tool for building trust with customers.</strong></p>
  <p>What does a data ethics policy look like? Here are six categories, adapted from the <a href="https://dataethics.eu/en/data-ethics-principles/">guidelines</a> created by DataEthics.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Human first:</strong> Data is always borrowed, never owned. Individuals’ interests, rights, and well-being are prioritized. Individuals benefit from companies’ use of their data. Systems emphasize privacy by design.</li>
    <li><strong>Individual control:</strong> Individuals have primary control over, and should be fully aware of, how their data is collected, used, and kept.</li>
    <li><strong>Transparency:</strong> Companies must be transparent in how and where data is stored and must be able and willing to explain the artificial intelligence and algorithms they use.</li>
    <li><strong>Behavioral design:</strong> Companies must not try to influence customers’ behavior in ways that are not beneficial to their interests.</li>
    <li><strong>Accountability:</strong> The protection of personal data that informs data processing should extend to all business agents involved with the data.</li>
    <li><strong>Equality:</strong> Companies must pay attention to ensure that data is used without bias.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Done right, data ethics isn’t anticompetitive but is a competitive advantage, says Pernille Tranberg, co-founder of Copenhagen-based DataEthics and co-author of the book <em>Data Ethics: The New Competitive Advantage</em>.</p>
  <p>But we should beware of “ethics washing” and “privacy washing,” she says. Think back to the early days of environmental sustainability when there were companies that took serious steps to improve their ecological impact. However, there were also plenty of companies accused of “green washing” – not backing up the talk with actions. This is a real danger, and it’s already happening, says Tranberg.</p>
  <p>The answer is developing third-party certification and verification schemes like the ones for the environmental movement. “A lot of companies say, ‘We really anonymize data, we can’t go back and identify you,’” says Tranberg. “That’s very cool if they really do it, but they need to have somebody to check that independently.”</p>
  <p>Companies are also recognizing the value in independent certifications for data ethics and privacy. “I already see some companies that are asking for it,” says Tranberg</p>
  <p>She thinks it’s likely we’ll start out with many small certification schemes before they mature and grow into larger organizations and governments need to become involved. One example is European Privacy Seal (EuroPriSe), a privacy certification for IT products. The (surprise) German organization was started in 2009 as an EU-funded project and is now a global certification.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>Companies that are transparent will thrive. Those that don’t do this will have a much harder time in the future.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>- One.Thing.Less Co-Founder James Aschberger</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13dad59834670637ec8e5b676881346bd8414be2f.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13dad59834670637ec8e5b676881346bd8414be2f.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_13dad59834670637ec8e5b676881346bd8414be2f.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Team hand stack" src="./media_13dad59834670637ec8e5b676881346bd8414be2f.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="you-can-take-it-with-you">You can take it with you</h2>
  <p>But it’s not enough to assure customers that their data is being treated with kid gloves. Soon, customers will expect to be able to take their data wherever they want. <a href="https://www.privacy-regulation.eu/en/article-20-right-to-data-portability-GDPR.htm">Article 20</a> of the GDPR outlines the rules for data portability (the ability to take data from one platform to another).</p>
  <p>Although many big companies that depend on data might not appreciate Article 20, it’s intended to increase competition by opening the field to other platforms. It also gives consumers the power to express their displeasure with a particular company by taking their data away.</p>
  <p>Achieving portability could initiate new ideas about data monetization. Startups are appearing with products to do just this. There are several new models.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="whats-your-data-management-strategy">What's your data management strategy?</h3>
        <p>From collecting to processing and storage, here's how to ensure compliance.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/what-is-data-management.html">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="new-models-for-data-management">New models for data management</h2>
  <p>Inspired by opportunity, outrage, or concern – or all three – plenty of ideas aim to change how data is managed and monetized. If any of these ideas take off, we’ll experience a massive change in the data economy.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Personal data brokers:</strong> Think financial adviser but for personal data. Upending the passive role of the consumer, the (maybe) up-and-coming industry promises to help consumers manage and monetize their data.</li>
    <li><strong>Self-sovereign identity:</strong> First conceived in the 1970s, self-sovereign identities, unlike today’s distributed digital identifiers, are central, singular, and created and maintained by the individual. Individuals can store and share – or not – as they like. Calling itself a “decentralized, global public utility,” Sovrin.org provides an infrastructure for self-sovereign identities.</li>
    <li><strong>Personal data marketplace:</strong> Personal data marketplaces aim to sell data for cash (or cryptocurrency, in some cases) by managing the sales with buyers. One startup (and there are many), Universal Basic Data Income allows users to sell their anonymized personal data that has been collected by an app called Digi.me. However, while the idea of selling personal data isn’t new, the question remains whether a significant mass will sign up for these marketplaces.</li>
    <li><strong>Data labor unions:</strong> The book <em>Radical Markets: Uprooting Capitalism and Democracy for a Just Society</em> by Eric A. Posner, a professor at University of Chicago’s law school, and E. Glen Weyl, a senior researcher at Microsoft, posits that data is a form of labor and suggests the creation of data labor unions that will enable fair compensation for data.</li>
    <li><strong>Personal data storage:</strong> From the famed Sir Tim Berners-Lee, creator of the World Wide Web, comes Solid, a decentralized, open-source Web platform. A Solid Pod stores personal info and Solid Pod owners can decide who to share access to their Pod with. Personal data can be shared across apps.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15d274c845187517ab7ca47a39f12e34cfdf96b17.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15d274c845187517ab7ca47a39f12e34cfdf96b17.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_15d274c845187517ab7ca47a39f12e34cfdf96b17.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Business woman looks at tablet with enthusiastic expression." src="./media_15d274c845187517ab7ca47a39f12e34cfdf96b17.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="how-can-everyone-win">How can everyone win?</h2>
  <p>Consumers want to see benefits from the use of their data, and companies want to grow. The two aren’t mutually exclusive.</p>
  <p>Providing transparency can smooth the path to consent. A company that provides consumers with a clear understanding of how their personal data is used and secured, and that makes clear how consumers can benefit from sharing their data, is more likely to win approval for that data use.</p>
  <p>Switzerland-based startup One.Thing.Less wants to take the work out of privacy for both consumers and organizations. Its app that facilitates the communication about data privacy and use policies creates an opportunity for companies to engage their customers, says co-founder James Aschberger, and is a win for both parties. Making the data relationship clear and simple will be another competitive advantage. It gives consumers some peace of mind and signals that a corporation isn’t hiding its real intentions behind a wall of terms of use agreements that few actually read.</p>
  <p>But a future in which individuals are in complete control of their own data isn’t a given. It’s not clear that people are better at managing privacy than companies are, says Cornell’s Barocas. The idea already has a long history, beginning in the 1990s, and an equally long track record of failure.</p>
  <p>One.Thing.Less’s Aschberger isn’t convinced that there’s enough money in personal data for it to ever become a substantial source of income for individuals. But he does think that we’re moving toward a future that’s more collaborative, allowing individuals to control their data and provide, if they so choose, more accurate data. And companies might not have much choice in the matter.</p>
  <p>“It will become very interesting because I believe that those companies that are transparent and that give people enough reasons to trust them will thrive,” Aschberger says. “Those that don’t do this will have a much harder time in the future.”</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>