<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sales-performance-management/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kyndryl Adopts Next-Generation Tools for Sales Performance Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/kyndryl-adopts-tools-for-sales-performance-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/kyndryl-adopts-tools-for-sales-performance-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Kyndryl adopted SAP SuccessFactors sales performance management solutions to streamline compensation and territory and quota management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sales-performance-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sales Performance Management: Empowering Sales Teams for Better Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-north-america-sales-performance-management-customer-summit-better-outcomes</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-north-america-sales-performance-management-customer-summit-better-outcomes</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At the SAP Sales Performance Management Customer Summit, customers shared how to optimize sales compensation for better business results.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_151d6d5f5e440d033f2105cfba96ee66afebd464e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_151d6d5f5e440d033f2105cfba96ee66afebd464e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_151d6d5f5e440d033f2105cfba96ee66afebd464e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Sales Performance Management: Empowering Sales Teams for Better Outcomes" src="./media_151d6d5f5e440d033f2105cfba96ee66afebd464e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sales-performance-management-empowering-sales-teams-for-better-outcomes">Sales Performance Management: Empowering Sales Teams for Better Outcomes</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In today’s dynamic business environment, organizations need highly efficient sales teams to generate revenue and stay ahead of the competition. But while advances in AI-powered tools have accelerated the sales process, they have also increased the value of soft skills and the relationship-building acumen that talented salespeople bring to their jobs. That’s why savvy organizations are more committed than ever to keeping their sales teams engaged and productive.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="accelerate-business-outcomes-with-sales-performance-management-products-from-sap">Accelerate business outcomes with sales performance management products from SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/sales-performance-management.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>High-performing sales teams are using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/sales-performance-management.html">sales performance management</a> solutions from SAP SuccessFactors to manage and optimize sales compensation and incentives – rewarding sales reps for their performance – while streamlining sales processes and using real-time insights to improve operational efficiency and drive revenue.</p>
  <p>“There’s this renewed emphasis on efficiency,” said Rahul Iyer, general manager, Sales Performance Management, SAP SuccessFactors, speaking to SAP customers at the <a href="https://events.sap.com/us/sap-north-america-spm-customer-summit-2024/en/home">SAP North America Sales Performance Management Customer Summit</a>, held February 13-14, 2024, in Dallas, Texas. “Customers want faster, simpler outcomes – and they want to provide a great seller experience, as well. At SAP SuccessFactors, we’ve threaded the intelligence of connected cloud applications throughout the SPM solution portfolio. This allows us to deliver the efficiency, transparency, and rich experience of SAP in a comprehensive platform that covers a full range of end-to-end processes in sales compensation.”</p>
  <h2 id="together-for-success">Together for Success</h2>
  <p>Under the banner “Together we can make it better,” the summit event provided a venue for SAP customers – some of whom came from as far away as South America – to meet one-on-one with experts and gain valuable knowledge from product road maps, demos, and deep dive sessions, as well as learn from one another’s experiences in customer sessions.</p>
  <p>Iyer affirmed SAP’s commitment to deliver the advanced innovations customers need to be competitive: “As a strategic partner to our customers, we have the moral responsibility to help them receive progressively more out of technology innovations, while accelerating with the best-in-class capabilities SAP has to offer. We are simplifying from every angle to make it easy for our customers to adopt, so they can achieve business outcomes faster.”</p>
  <p>Barbara Rubis Linning, SAP SuccessFactors global vice president, Product and Engineering, presented the latest innovations and features across the sales performance management solution set, which includes <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/incentive-compensation-management.html">SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/territory-and-quota.html">SAP SuccessFactors Territory and Quota</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/agent-lifecycle-mgmt.html">SAP SuccessFactors Agent Lifecycle Management</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/agent-performance-management.html">SAP SuccessFactors Agent Performance Management</a>. With features like territory planning and incentive compensation, SAP sales performance management solutions enable organizations to optimize their sales performance for better business results. The solutions use advanced features – for tasks such as drive time analysis and mapping to optimize territories – to streamline processes and make workflows easier so that customers realize value faster. The ongoing introduction of the <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/technology-blogs-by-sap/sap-fiori-evolution-horizon-now-generally-available-in-ui-technologies-and/ba-p/13532969">Horizon</a> visual theme on key administrative pages delivers a fresh, modern user interface (UI) for an elevated user experience.</p>
  <p>“We want our customers to have winning sales teams,” said Linning. “Their success is why we continuously look for new ways to build innovations and relevant features into the portfolio to accelerate business outcomes. SAP is building intelligence that is relevant, responsible, and reliable because we believe it leads to smarter, data-driven decision making and results in better sales performance. Our new intuitive UI helps simplify tasks and puts people at the center of business for improved productivity.”</p>
  <p>SAP SuccessFactors solutions deliver <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">Joule</a>, SAP’s natural language processing AI copilot, to help people be more productive in their jobs using SAP business solutions.</p>
  <p>The integration of sales performance management solutions with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> and <a href="/2023/03/sap-datasphere-power-of-business-data">SAP Datasphere</a> enables seamless access to real-time data and analytics, empowering organizations to make informed decisions and drive sales success.</p>
  <h2 id="winning-with-sales-compensation">Winning with Sales Compensation</h2>
  <p>As the all-important link between an organization’s products and services and its customers, the sales team is a principal driver of bottom-line growth for the whole organization. Correctly incenting sales teams requires the use of proven strategies and solutions to align the pay program with organizational goals, said David Cichelli, revenue growth advisor at <a href="https://www.alexandergroup.com/">The Alexander Group</a>, who presented “Leading the Sales Design Compensation Project.”</p>
  <p>He advised sales compensation leaders adopt an annual review process that includes assessment, strategic alignment, taskforce design, and comprehensive communication phases. “Sales compensation design needs to reflect the consensus of key stakeholders: sales, finance, product management, and HR,” he said. “By following a proven design process, you can develop a strategically aligned, effective, and motivational pay program.”</p>
  <h2 id="supporting-customer-success-for-better-outcomes">Supporting Customer Success for Better Outcomes</h2>
  <p>The summit showcased the SAP ecosystem with sponsorships and informative sessions from <a href="https://spectrumtek.com/">SpectrumTek</a>, <a href="https://canidium.com/">Canidium</a>, <a href="https://www.opensymmetry.com/">OpenSymmetry</a>, <a href="https://www.cahabaconsultinggroup.com/">Cahaba Consulting Group</a>, <a href="https://www.thelcfirm.com/">The LC Firm</a>, and <a href="https://www.aspiredigital.com/">Aspire Digital</a>.</p>
  <p>SAP experts highlighted SAP’s message of ongoing support for customer success: “We’re here for you,” said Tak Kusano, global chief operating officer of SAP SuccessFactors. “SAP has a tight-knit community of sales performance management experts that bring deep domain knowledge to this niche space. That’s why we’re able to work so closely with customers to gain consensus on the road map and product innovations, like AI. We’re passionate about bringing the best of technology to SAP customers.”</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sales-performance-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Game-Changing Role of Incentive Compensation Automation in the Retail Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/incentive-compensation-automation-in-retail</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/incentive-compensation-automation-in-retail</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management, retailers can incorporate key performance indicators into their incentive structure.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10fff8c20499512be48a61b55b1b6ecdb00d8656a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10fff8c20499512be48a61b55b1b6ecdb00d8656a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10fff8c20499512be48a61b55b1b6ecdb00d8656a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Game-Changing Role of Incentive Compensation Automation in the Retail Industry" src="./media_10fff8c20499512be48a61b55b1b6ecdb00d8656a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-game-changing-role-of-incentive-compensation-automation-in-the-retail-industry">The Game-Changing Role of Incentive Compensation Automation in the Retail Industry</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In the dynamic world of retail, staying ahead means adapting to evolving customer expectations and embracing innovative solutions. The era of omnichannel retailing has ushered in demand for seamless, personalized shopping experiences, compelling businesses to think outside the box to support seamless experiences and minimize friction by providing the right product at the right time in the right place. Moreover, recognizing the intricate dance between employee satisfaction and customer experience, businesses are weaving a narrative where a better employee experience becomes the cornerstone for elevating customer delight.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At the recent <a href="/topics/nrf">NRF event</a>, the world’s largest retail conference, the mantra of “adjust and adapt” echoed through the halls. AI and digital acceleration took the center stage, making innovation the heart of the conversation. Retailers also highlighted a crucial focus on a motivated workforce, emphasizing how an empowered workforce is critical to delivering exceptional customer experiences.</p>
  <p>In a landscape challenged by high turnover rates, retailers showcased their commitment to navigating complexity through strategic investments in their most valuable asset – their people. One of the pivotal elements that drives employee motivation and engagement in the retail industry is incentive compensation, where associates are often paid on commission.</p>
  <p>During NRF, Daniel Jasper from Neiman Marcus shared insights into how incentive compensation automation transformed the company’s commission payment process. With over 40 stores and a complex commission structure, Neiman Marcus faced challenges in managing incentive compensation. Its previous incentive management system was cumbersome and complex, which led to errors, delays, and frustration among sales associates. Implementing <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/sales-performance-management.html#products">the SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management solution</a> helped streamline the process, providing real-time monitoring of commission calculations. This allowed Neiman Marcus to identify and resolve issues proactively, resulting in improved accuracy and timeliness of commission payments. “Rather than waiting to hear from associates that something is wrong, we can monitor the calculations in real-time and resolve issues in advance,” said Jasper. This shift has been a game-changer for Neiman Marcus, driving better sales and revenue growth.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="empower-sales-teams-with-the-tools-they-need-to-create-effective-sales-experiences">Empower sales teams with the tools they need to create effective sales experiences</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/sales-performance-management.html">Find out how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management is one of the sales performance management solutions in the SAP SuccessFactors portfolio, and it offers a sophisticated platform for tailoring incentive programs to suit the unique needs of retail associates. With powerful analytics, embedded intelligence, and built-in workflows, this solution can revolutionize compensation management. Its intelligent design can not only foster trust but also ignite motivation among store associates. Through a user-friendly mobile app, retail customers can enjoy a comprehensive and easily accessible view of both store and individual performance metrics, promoting transparency and a unified understanding of team dynamics and trends. Personalized recommendations, relevant insights, and interactive monitoring help enhance the user experience, while the mobile app helps ensure that store associates can access their incentives anytime, anywhere, from any device.</p>
  <p>The solution’s agility helps facilitate a swift rollout of new and updated compensation plans, offering the flexibility to manage broadly or tailor plans to individual needs. With a steadfast commitment to accuracy and traceability, associates can trust the fairness of calculations, fostering a positive work environment. The effective dating functionalities help further empower organizations, allowing seamless management of associate promotions and transfers.</p>
  <p>“Retail businesses more than ever need the ability to design and manage incentive plans that align with ever-changing organizational goals, with a focus on store-level personalization and granularity that allow for improved accuracy and timeliness of commission payments,” said Rahul Iyer, general manager of Sales Performance Management at SAP. “With SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management, retailers can incorporate key performance indicators, such as sales per hour and units per sale, into their incentive structure. The mobile app can provide visibility and transparency into individual and store performance, effectively motivating and ensuring optimal performance from their associates.”</p>
  <p>In essence, SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management emerges as an indispensable tool, helping to empower retail customers to optimize workforce performance and drive sustained success. Displaying key performance indicators and incentives has proven to be a game changer, helping to drive focus on store and individual performance. The result? Associates are more attentive to customers, guiding them through purchasing decisions and enhancing overall satisfaction.</p>
  <p>In the always-changing retail world, success comes down to three things: using better technology, having happy employees, and keeping customers in focus. The story of Neiman Marcus proves that automating incentives can be a game changer. It shows how a motivated and well-connected team can not just boost how things work but also bring in more sales and money.</p>
  <p>To stay ahead in retail, you need to be ready for change and invest in both tech and your team. This is a clear lesson for retailers planning for the future. Learn more about how <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/03/509d257a-677e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">sales performance management can simplify the retail industry</a>. To learn more about how sales performance management solutions can support your organization, visit the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/sales-performance-management.html">sales performance management product page on sap.com</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Kevin Coxwell is vice president of GTM for Sales Performance Management at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Follow us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/nrf</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sales-performance-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CallidusCloud to SAP: Evolution to Running Better Smarter and Faster]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/calliduscloud-to-sap-evolution</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/calliduscloud-to-sap-evolution</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is excited to help CallidusCloud customers make the strategic move to the SAP SuccessFactors portfolio. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sales-performance-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-hana</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[VMware Builds Trust Through a Positive Seller Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/vmware-builds-trust-positive-seller-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/vmware-builds-trust-positive-seller-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[VMware embarked on an initiative to modernize its incentive compensation management tools and processes, implementing SAP Commissions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19b84561a38e1a51128d381b67642d6fa28a050bb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19b84561a38e1a51128d381b67642d6fa28a050bb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19b84561a38e1a51128d381b67642d6fa28a050bb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="VMware Builds Trust Through a Positive Seller Experience" src="./media_19b84561a38e1a51128d381b67642d6fa28a050bb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="vmware-builds-trust-through-a-positive-seller-experience">VMware Builds Trust Through a Positive Seller Experience</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>VMware, a software giant founded in 1998, has significantly influenced the information technology market, offering businesses both large and small a vast array of virtualization, networking, storage, security, and digital workplace products and services. One of the driving forces behind VMware’s mission to help customers accelerate innovation is <a href="/topics/sales-performance-management">its sales team</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With several acquisitions in recent years, the number of sellers at VMware dramatically increased. Yet the company did not have a reliable means of paying everyone accurately and on time. The company knew it needed to improve the experience for its sellers to maximize business performance.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18ac25bf39ae42c1c7459ea8b6011f799304db41b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18ac25bf39ae42c1c7459ea8b6011f799304db41b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18ac25bf39ae42c1c7459ea8b6011f799304db41b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="VMware Drives Winning Sellers Experiences in the Cloud" src="./media_18ac25bf39ae42c1c7459ea8b6011f799304db41b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/5ie1lpncmtA">VMware Drives Winning Sellers Experiences in the Cloud</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="the-burden-of-legacy-tools">The Burden of Legacy Tools</h2>
  <p>For years VMware had been burdened by legacy tools that not only impacted seller productivity but also caused significant inefficiencies when it came to business operations. Reporting capabilities were limited and the company couldn’t support payouts for multiple metrics, which was problematic as the company transitioned to a model of both license and subscription sales.</p>
  <p>In addition, introducing new plans or emphasizing specific products or geographies was highly manual, requiring significant time and effort. This impacted VMware’s ability to adapt to business needs quickly enough to remain competitive.</p>
  <h2 id="the-companys-transformation-journey">The Company’s Transformation Journey</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="motivate-sales-shape-behavior-and-increase-revenue-with-sap-commissions">Motivate sales, shape behavior, and increase revenue with SAP Commissions</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/commissions.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>VMware embarked on an initiative to modernize its incentive compensation management tools and processes, implementing <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/commissions.html">SAP Commissions</a>.</p>
  <p>The decision to implement SAP Commissions at VMware was based on many factors, namely the need to improve payment accuracy, gain more sophisticated reporting capabilities, and strengthen auditing capabilities.</p>
  <p>Leaders at VMware across HR, sales ops, finance, and IT agreed that what the company required was a system that was both flexible and scalable – one that was purpose-built to handle change and provided the kind of transparency that the company’s 9,000 sellers would love.</p>
  <p>According to Anushree Kalra, director, IT Engineering at VMware, “We used to have more than 700 compensation plans that were very difficult to manage at scale. Our goal with the modernization project was to reduce the number of comp plans to less than 50 and make it easy to change plans or add new ones. That’s exactly what we did.”</p>
  <p>The company successfully implemented SAP Commissions in nine months, ahead of the proposed one-and-a-half-year plan, which included the switch from Oracle to SAP HANA.</p>
  <h2 id="realizing-the-benefits-of-a-modern-tool">Realizing the Benefits of a Modern Tool</h2>
  <p>According to Kalra, VMware now has a streamlined incentive compensation management process complimented by a system that’s capable of accommodating various compensation plans and multiple metrics for commissions. The company now changes plans every six months and can adapt to market conditions much more quickly.</p>
  <p>“Best of all, with SAP Commissions we have a tool that allows us to pay our sellers accurately and on time,” said Kalra. “In fact, the time required for commission calculations and the time for processing commissions for VMware has been reduced from several days to a few hours.”</p>
  <p>This is due in large part to workflows and approvals that were made much easier with SAP Commissions. Now VMware can confidently process commissions at scale even as the dynamics of its sales organization change.</p>
  <p>The benefits of more robust reporting capabilities have also been significant. The solution helps provide personalized dashboards, allowing sellers to access the information they need – how, when, and where they want. This means VMware can load plans for sellers and instantly provide them visibility into their commissions. The company says this has helped to build trust among sellers, which has had a direct impact on satisfaction and retention.</p>
  <p>With better operational reporting, the company is also more efficient, according to Kalra. Now, finance has what it needs for forecasting and setting quotas, for example.</p>
  <p>Looking forward, Kalra says the team at VMware is excited about having a tool that helps to provide strategic direction for the enterprise. It’s another way VMware is leveraging technology advancements to accelerate business growth and success.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/commissions.html">Learn more about the SAP Commissions solution.</a></div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Lara Albert is global vice president for Solution Marketing at SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sales-performance-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-hana</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sales Performance Management for Better Customer Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sales-performance-management-better-customer-outcomes</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sales-performance-management-better-customer-outcomes</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At the SAP Sales Performance Management Customer Summit, SAP customers learned about the latest innovations, vision, and strategy.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sales-performance-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-compensation</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>