<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/content-type/business-case/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Commerce Cloud solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/l3-proxy-cards/products-sap-commerce</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/topics/l3-proxy-cards/products-sap-commerce</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The SAP Commerce Cloud portfolio offers trusted e-commerce solutions that can help you innovate at scale and use enterprise-wide data to boost profits and customer satisfaction.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <h1 id="sap-commerce-cloud-solutions">SAP Commerce Cloud solutions</h1>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Revamping Sales Processes for Consumption Pricing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/revamping-sales-processes-for-consumption-pricing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/revamping-sales-processes-for-consumption-pricing</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A consumption-based sales model requires looking at the entire business with a new lens.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bb4fc748beb0ebc85bf3a07e3187d1b073bc57bf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bb4fc748beb0ebc85bf3a07e3187d1b073bc57bf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1bb4fc748beb0ebc85bf3a07e3187d1b073bc57bf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="A White person with their hands on a laptop keyboard. The laptop screen shows the words &#x22;Transaction completed,&#x22; along with a green checkmark and a blue button." src="./media_1bb4fc748beb0ebc85bf3a07e3187d1b073bc57bf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="revamping-sales-processes-for-consumption-pricing">Revamping Sales Processes for Consumption Pricing</h1>
        <p>A consumption-based sales model requires looking at the entire business with a new lens.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Consumption-based pricing (CBP), also known as usage-based pricing (UBP), seems straightforward at first blush. Instead of paying a set price up front for a software or service subscription, customers only pay for what they consume, a.k.a. pay-as-you-go. And rather than earn commissions when deals close, sales reps earn compensation that typically <a href="/resources/compensating-sales-for-consumption-based-pricing">is tied to how much the customer actually consumes</a>.</p>
  <p>But when a company rushes into this enticing model too quickly, chaos can ensue.</p>
  <p>Case in point: a company that sells software as a service (SaaS) to energy businesses was tired of losing deals to the same competitor. As many SaaS businesses do, the company licensed its software based on subscriptions, but the competitor offered a CBP model, with its software at a quarter of the normal up-front costs and with more flexible pricing. The energy company was being pushed into the CBP pool – and seeing the potential for more wins, it jumped right in.</p>
  <p>The company came up with new product usage prices and software packaging options, and tweaked the underlying data pipeline to make sure it could accurately meter customers’ usage for billing purposes. This created an option for customers to prepay for their expected software use. Otherwise, though, customers still had the option to stick with purchasing the software at an annual subscription rate.</p>
  <p>The company soon learned this wasn’t enough to consistently win competitive deals.</p>
  <p>The pricing change was clearly a step in the right direction, providing customers with better flexibility in the products they used and when, over the course of the contract. But in the following months, the company still struggled to beat the competitor, which offered much more flexibility in committed contract size for a highly commitment-phobic customer base.</p>
  <p>Without changing the sales team’s key performance indicators (KPIs) to reorient from up-front commitments toward CBP, nothing changed in how the sales team structured its proposed contracts. Salespeople continued to press customers for maximum commitment amounts, while offering aggressive discounts to counteract concerns about accurately forecasting future demand. They continued to lose deals as a result.</p>
  <p>The company realized it needed to embrace the strategy it had put on its pricing page – and take a closer look at how this strategy should affect the entire sales process.</p>
  <p>It’s a familiar dilemma for many organizations beginning their CBP journeys: there’s more to it than just changing the pricing terms.</p>
  <p>The <a href="/resources/compensating-sales-for-consumption-based-pricing">consumption-based pricing model</a> is a no-brainer for consumers because they know their bills match their actual use of the products. Software vendors like CBP because it brings new customers in the door faster – due to little or no up-front commitment – while opening the door wider for long-term potential growth, since they can continue to up-sell new features or encourage more usage over time.</p>
  <p>Sounds like a win-win – but creating a new pricing option is just the tip of the iceberg. A consumption-based sales model requires looking at the entire business with a new lens. It’s no longer a sales process but an end-to-end business process, from sale through data collection all the way to payment. Every piece of the business has to support that consumption-based economy. With that said, the underlying sales processes that are needed to maintain a CBP model are still in a state of flux. A lot of companies are still trying to figure it out, and no single solution fits all organizations.</p>
  <p>Navigating the right path could mean the difference between success and failure. Answering three critical questions will help you find that path.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b2b0676663ad0c58668262b1e7a98c0c7db34907.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b2b0676663ad0c58668262b1e7a98c0c7db34907.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1b2b0676663ad0c58668262b1e7a98c0c7db34907.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="A young professional Black woman looks at a financial business analytics data dashboard on two monitors." src="./media_1b2b0676663ad0c58668262b1e7a98c0c7db34907.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="what-new-data-will-we-need-to-collect">What new data will we need to collect?</h2>
  <p>Determining customers’ rate of “consumption” may involve transforming data you already have but it also may require collecting new data entirely.</p>
  <p>“It’s hard to offer a consumption product if you don’t have a metering system. It’s foundational,” says Chris Semain, principal and tech practice leader at Alexander Group. It’s similar to a meter in a cab; you pay depending on how far you go. Metering solutions ensure that both customers and software vendors have near-real-time information on how much they’re using the product.</p>
  <p>But there’s a lot of company-by-company uniqueness to data collection because there are many forms of consumption or usage, Semain says. “The unit of measurement for consumption is a variety of types of measurements. Some companies have tokens, like popping in a quarter into a video machine, where you can pay for 100 tokens to use the product. In other cases, usage is based on defining the number of ‘workloads,’ or it might be the number of software modules you’re using,” he adds.</p>
  <p>As the SaaS provider, of course, you’ll want the customer’s cost for each unit to accurately reflect how your own infrastructure costs increase as your users require more computation, storage, or seat management.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="xaas-and-subscription-business-models">XaaS and subscription business models</h3>
        <p>Subscription-based business models are helping many companies increase profits.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/business-model-innovation-xaas">Find out how</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Many organizations don’t yet track and report granular product usage data or trends to help inform and prioritize their sales teams’ activities. But the high-tech, insurance, and telco industries are among the best-positioned for data use tracking and consumption-based sales models.</p>
  <p>Telcos are well positioned for usage-based sales models because they have long monitored minutes spent on phone calls and specific apps as well as amounts of data used with streaming, downloads, backhauling data, and related services.</p>
  <p>Examples in the insurance industry show how this idea is expanding. Insurance companies collect data through GPS to offer a type of CBP. For instance, U.S.-based insurer Progressive offers Snapshot, a consumption-based model that measures not just how much customers drive but how well they drive. It monitors driver behavior through GPS and its mobile app; presumably, the customer gets a better insurance rate for being a safe driver. The data is tracking the driver’s actual exposure to risk in order to determine the rate.</p>
  <p>Health insurance companies are also trying to use GPS for data collection. In India, for example, some offer customers <a href="https://www.indiatimes.com/worth/news/health-insurance-companies-encourage-fitness-through-low-premiums-600815.html">discounts on insurance if they exercise</a> a certain number of days per month. To validate this, at least one company tracks customers by GPS to fitness clubs (with permission), although they don’t know if the customer is actually working out, Semain says.</p>
  <p>Organizations that can collect vital usage data and track customer behavior have the foundation for a consumption-based sales model; they will be able to compensate sales reps, come up with innovative sales models, and better forecast usage and revenue.</p>
  <p>The pipelines that deliver the collected data throughout an organization will need considerable reengineering too. You’ll see why this is necessary in the next question.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ae1b7f1802b610e98446be17ba5d6c551be06d69.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ae1b7f1802b610e98446be17ba5d6c551be06d69.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1ae1b7f1802b610e98446be17ba5d6c551be06d69.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="A businessperson seated at a conference table with other professionals, using a laptop that displays several sales-related charts." src="./media_1ae1b7f1802b610e98446be17ba5d6c551be06d69.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="how-will-we-measure-and-forecast-future-revenue">How will we measure and forecast future revenue?</h2>
  <p>Revenue predictability is the biggest challenge for any sales organization. Companies take different approaches to the extra uncertainty that comes with fewer up-front commitments, but it’s going to affect everything from data pipeline engineering to how salespeople are compensated.</p>
  <p>Historically, SaaS models were architected around the “deal” or the opportunity. Deals being closed were the singular catalyst for change in recognized revenue – the natural unit of measurement for tracking and planning revenue growth.</p>
  <p>In usage-based models, revenue growth could happen before, during, and after a deal cycle. Customers can buy more up front to get a better price – but, for example, if they anticipate just a one-time spike in their usage needs, they might be inclined to risk paying a premium for any overruns rather than overcommitting up front.</p>
  <p>A 2022 study by consulting firm Bain shows that more than 90% of users who prefer subscription models to consumption models <a href="https://www.bain.com/insights/topics/technology-report/2022/">cite a lack of predictability</a> as the main downside of the latter. So the challenge becomes rethinking and rearchitecting how to predict the flow of future revenue.</p>
  <p>At Datadog, a SaaS-based monitoring and analytics software provider, UBP has been a part of the business since its inception and has led to much of the company’s success, according to former VP of finance Scott Buxton. Its infrastructure monitoring product is still sold on a “price per host monitored” basis, and this model also accounts for discounts based on annual commitment, volume, and tier. But Buxton acknowledges in an OpenView Partners <a href="https://openviewpartners.com/blog/implementing-usage-based-pricing-what-your-financial-teams-need-to-know/">blog post</a> that sales predictability was a lot more challenging with UBP.</p>
  <p>Datadog implemented a drawdown model option that allowed a customer to adapt their usage pace according to the needs of their business. This helped balance the business’s need for predictability with the customer’s need for flexibility.</p>
  <p>With this drawdown model, “Customers can commit a certain sum, say $1 million, pick a term, and draw down on their sum over that time period. They could use zero dollars in the first six months of their three-year term to account for business delays… and as soon as they’re up and ready, they can go as fast as they want,” Buxton writes.</p>
  <p>Having commitment built into the pricing model can certainly mitigate some of these concerns about predictability, but it’s far from perfect, Buxton says. “First of all, not all customers elect this type of plan. Second, relying exclusively on monthly commitments in your calculations will lead to pretty inaccurate numbers.”</p>
  <p>The energy company found other ways to tackle its predictability challenges.</p>
  <p>First, the company ditched overage fees. In the original pricing model, it had maintained overage charges when customers finished their commitments (at the “rack rate” or standard pricing). Terms like “overage” turned off customers, so the company moved to a utility-based charge on par with the unit-based prices that customers were paying on their committed contracts.</p>
  <p>Next, they redefined core business KPIs. They devised different ways to define revenue events and architect sales plans around them.</p>
  <p>Establishing what those KPIs should be is all about priorities, says Ben Chambers, a consultant specializing in consumption-based sales models. Some companies want to solve for simplicity and choose the path that’s most comfortable to veteran sales reps: subscriptions. Others opt for more nuanced, usage-based measures of incremental sales performance. If product usage is seasonal (such as in the retail industry) or erratic and spiky (as with project-intense organizations), that likely influences the design of the KPI. For instance, it might make sense for a non-seasonal type of business to create a usage-based annual recurring revenue (ARR) metric that takes recent usage from the last one to three months and annualizes it to come up with ARR. However, that type of KPI would present more challenges and issues for companies with erratic or seasonal usage patterns.</p>
  <p>The energy company also chose to define revenue events in a fairly straightforward way – total billable usage, regardless of whether or not it’s precommitted. Every quantity of product usage was translated into a dollar amount and attributed back to the user.</p>
  <p>Once the core KPIs were defined, the energy company began architecting the data pipeline for this new KPI usage value – translating product usage into a dollar amount and thinking about all the legacy contracts that would be affected before it rolled out pricing changes. The company also attributed every dollar of usage to the responsible salesperson to determine their quota.</p>
  <p>The new data pipeline requires not only new data but determining where it goes and how it’s combined and transformed. When switching from subscription to CBP models involved only a pricing and packaging change, the in-product and customer-facing billing systems needed this usage data pipeline, while the internal business and go-to-market systems simply continued to manage the business around contracted ARR. In this case, a standard customer relationship management (CRM) system is generally well equipped to manage a fixed-subscription business model.</p>
  <p>But when flipping to a dedicated usage-based model, many more internal parties need their systems, processes, and reporting on the product usage data, as this is now the direct basis for revenue recognition, quota crediting, and commissions, Chambers says. CRM tends not to be the most logical or natural source of truth for tracking and reporting daily updates to product usage, he adds.</p>
  <p>Chambers has seen a shift toward the enterprise data warehouse developing into the source of truth for internal reporting. Product usage data from product and billing systems could be integrated with sales territory and attribution data or contract specifics from CRM and fed into business intelligence dashboards for field-facing reporting, revenue forecasting systems, and commission calculations.</p>
  <p>With usage now taking precedence over revenue commitment, a company’s primary metric becomes <em>how much</em> the accounts in a territory are using the product, not what they’re committed to. Usage-based KPIs can keep customers from being oversold or underutilized, and the KPI becomes the primary measure for how organizations define territories.</p>
  <p>With the data collection and data pipeline in place, the energy company is now building a compensation plan for sales and customer success teams. This process has its own complexities and decision points, which we previously discussed in <a href="/resources/compensating-sales-for-consumption-based-pricing">Compensating Sales for Consumption-Based Pricing</a>.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19acd9e985f649cd0f0e1cea3a6aae86812283904.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19acd9e985f649cd0f0e1cea3a6aae86812283904.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19acd9e985f649cd0f0e1cea3a6aae86812283904.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Sales and support teams discuss business results shown onscreen in a boardroom." src="./media_19acd9e985f649cd0f0e1cea3a6aae86812283904.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1493" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="how-will-revenue-generators-sales-and-revenue-enhancers-service-support-and-customer-success-teams-work-together">How will revenue generators (sales) and revenue enhancers (service, support, and customer success teams) work together?</h2>
  <p>CBP requires more cooperation between sales and customer success managers, and rethinking how you want sales spending their time is a top priority. The good news: CBP presents a huge opportunity for customer success functions to own a metric that more naturally reflects the impact of their efforts than booking-oriented metrics.</p>
  <p>In traditional go-to-market models in the software sales world, teams adhere to swim lanes. The sales team, or revenue generator, is accountable for leading new business acquisition and growth. The customer success team or another account management function, the revenue enhancer, is responsible for client retention.</p>
  <p>Those roles will remain, but they’ll need to collaborate when engaging with the client after the sale – including onboarding, monitoring usage, and scrutinizing consumption patterns at the end of a term commitment so they can forecast more accurately at renewal time, Semain says. The day-to-day activities of these roles need to focus on improving the adoption and value realization stages of the customer journey.</p>
  <p>“Your customer success managers and sales reps need to stay on clients, because if they don’t and the client isn’t consuming, they’ll probably cancel,” Semain says. “There need to be resources holding their hands to make sure they’re getting value from the products.”</p>
  <p>But how much time should a salesperson spend on building customers’ usage? On the one hand, organizations could determine what tools and dashboards are needed to best improve how they spend their time to maximize product usage. “That may be a little different from a traditional fixed-subscription model where their activities were around identifying potential opportunities and swooping in on a new account to generate a commercial transaction,” he says.</p>
  <p>Sales reps could spend 40 hours a week trying to identify where their customers are going to use more software, but is that the best use of their time? “Probably not,” Chambers says. “Primarily, they should be using their skill sets to unlock demand and identify and win new business – things that take persuasion and selling skills.”</p>
  <p>Many organizations, including the energy company, are still figuring this out. Sales compensation models still haven’t caught up with UBP in most organizations, so they’re sticking with more familiar models, Semain says.</p>
  <p>When it comes to compensating those teams, he says, “A lot of companies want to compensate their customer success managers and potentially their sales reps on usage, adoption, and/or value realization. But because of the difficulty with tracking usage or defining the right metric, they’ve decided just to compensate customer success managers and reps on renewals because they haven’t quite figured out what ‘good’ usage is.”</p>
  <p>While the consumption-based sales process is still in nascent stages, CFOs are warming to the idea that it is essentially the future. “It may be choppier waters than subscription-based models, but it's a better path to revenue growth, especially in competitive environments where core competitors are also offering usage-based pricing arrangements,” Chambers says.</p>
  <p>“Companies are getting pushed into the pool. If they don’t start swimming, they won’t be able to win against the competitor that designs and delivers a lower-friction sales cycle requiring far less money up front.”</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Replacing Water Cooler Moments]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/replacing-water-cooler-moments</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/replacing-water-cooler-moments</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how hybrid companies can encourage greater innovation and new ideas by encouraging collaborative interactions no matter where employees work.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Currency of Customer Trust in Retail]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/the-currency-of-customer-trust-in-retail</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/the-currency-of-customer-trust-in-retail</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Building trustworthy customer experiences means sharing information and devoting resources to enhancing consumers’ trust.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Repair a Toxic Workplace Culture]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-to-repair-toxic-workplace-culture</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-to-repair-toxic-workplace-culture</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To fix a bad corporate culture, leaders must demonstrate that their actions match their words.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Business Value of Sustainability Is Here]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/the-business-value-of-sustainability-is-here</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/the-business-value-of-sustainability-is-here</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn why sustainable business practices are investments that pay, like R&D and customer relationships, from author Andrew Winston.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unleash Your Citizen Developers – With Guardrails]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/unleash-your-citizen-developers</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/unleash-your-citizen-developers</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how no-code and low-code tools open the doors for innovation, as long as you balance flexibility with support, guidance, and controls.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Addressing Digital Distractions to Focus on Work]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/addressing-digital-distractions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/addressing-digital-distractions</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Strategies managers can deploy to minimize interruptions in a multi-app, multi-screen workplace.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Who's in Your Sustainability Department?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/whos-in-your-sustainability-department</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/whos-in-your-sustainability-department</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Sustainability programs need effort from the whole company. Staffing your department right is a key step to achieving that company-wide support.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Know Where to Spend Your Security Budget]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-to-spend-your-cybersecurity-budget</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-to-spend-your-cybersecurity-budget</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how cyber risk measurement and management is growing up, with data-informed methodologies and tools for better cybersecurity investment decisions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What to Do About Supply Chain Crime]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/crime-in-the-supply-chain-and-what-to-do-about-it</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/crime-in-the-supply-chain-and-what-to-do-about-it</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New ways to assess risk, better employee awareness, and strong supply chain visibility can help reduce the chance of having assets stolen in transit.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HR Compliance and Risk Management for the Global Workforce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/hr-compliance-and-risk-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/hr-compliance-and-risk-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Explore the top HR compliance issues affecting businesses today and learn how technology can help address these concerns.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Merge Ahead: Smarter Tech Integration Is Critical to M&A Success | SAP Insights]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/merge-ahead-smarter-tech-integration-critical-to-ma-success</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/merge-ahead-smarter-tech-integration-critical-to-ma-success</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Digital assets and skills are the targets of today's M&A mania. Here are five strategies to avoid IT pitfalls and deliver the full value.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gamification Helps Our Employees Learn Cybersecurity]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/spotlight-gamification-helps-employees-learn-cybersecurity</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/spotlight-gamification-helps-employees-learn-cybersecurity</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Gamification, like creating immersive game worlds such as escape rooms and haunted houses, can make training stick. Read to learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Win-Win Potential of Hiring Neurodiverse Workers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/the-win-win-potential-of-hiring-neurodiverse-workers</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/the-win-win-potential-of-hiring-neurodiverse-workers</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Successful programs designed to employ neurodiverse candidates make important alterations to the recruiting and onboarding processes.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Apprenticeships: Using an Old Model to Recruit Fresh Talent]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/apprentice-opportunity-using-old-model-to-recruit-fresh-talent</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/apprentice-opportunity-using-old-model-to-recruit-fresh-talent</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Apprenticeships offer a “try before you buy” model that supplies needed labor and expanded opportunities for a diverse population.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Industry 5.0: Adding the human edge to industry 4.0]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/industry-5-0</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/industry-5-0</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn what Industry 5.0 means and how collaborative robots and smart manufacturing solutions help drive resilience and sustainability in the factories of the future.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Nurture Relationships with Your Contract Workers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/nurture-relationships-with-your-contractors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/nurture-relationships-with-your-contractors</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To realize the flexibility, agility, and value of an external workforce with minimal risk, leaders need to get better at managing contractors.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17548b2898480807ad95dbfe9eae56e106729797c.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17548b2898480807ad95dbfe9eae56e106729797c.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_17548b2898480807ad95dbfe9eae56e106729797c.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Connecting puzzle pieces represents value of integration - seeing the big picture" src="./media_17548b2898480807ad95dbfe9eae56e106729797c.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="nurturing-relationships-with-contract-workers">Nurturing Relationships with Contract Workers</h1>
        <p>Hiring external contractors is the “talent as a service” approach to staffing, and like any other shift to an “as a service” model, it takes careful planning to do right.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As technology has become sophisticated and powerful enough to let people work productively from anywhere at any time, work has become increasingly untethered from the workplace. That has also made it easier for companies to bring in more contractors to provide necessary skills on an as-needed basis. In 2010, 80% of major U.S. companies said they planned to <a href="https://http-download.intuit.com/http.intuit/CMO/intuit/futureofsmallbusiness/intuit_2020_report.pdf">significantly increase</a> their use of contractors. By 2020, 90% of companies said they believed a workplace that blends full-timers and freelancers provides a competitive <a href="https://www.hbs.edu/news/releases/Pages/high-skills-freelance-economy-surges.aspx">advantage</a>.</p>
  <p>External workers have never been in more demand, both to supplement full-time staff and to replace the 41% of people who say they intend to <a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/work-trend-index">leave</a> their current jobs in the imminent future. And with the number of self-employed people currently at a six-year <a href="https://fred.stlouisfed.org/graph/?g=GaiG">high</a>, companies have a deep pool of talent to dip into. But while companies may be ready to hire more contractors, the managers who will be responsible for them aren’t as well prepared. According to a survey by SAP SuccessFactors and the Society for Human Resource Management (SHRM), one in three managers don’t feel sufficiently trained to manage external workers.</p>
  <p>To realize the full flexibility, agility, and value of an external workforce with minimal risk to the organization, leaders need to get better at managing people who work for the company but are not employed by the company. That means tackling the challenges of integrating contractors into a team and the broader corporate culture without crossing the complicated regulatory lines that prohibit treating them the same as employees – a line that the new normal of distributed teams and <a href="/resources/remote-work-new-normal">remote</a> or <a href="/resources/hybrid-workforce-overcoming-challenges">hybrid</a> work environments has made blurrier than ever.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1db9df889bbac5cfe4120e9bb6e97c9213a6402ab.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1db9df889bbac5cfe4120e9bb6e97c9213a6402ab.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1db9df889bbac5cfe4120e9bb6e97c9213a6402ab.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Woman working from home" src="./media_1db9df889bbac5cfe4120e9bb6e97c9213a6402ab.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="the-growing-independent-workforce">The growing independent workforce</h2>
  <p>Companies that want to rent specific skills by the hour or project instead of hiring a full-time employee increasingly have their pick of talent. That wasn’t always the case, particularly in the U.S., where as recently as 2014, only <a href="https://www.entrepreneur.com/article/356632">17%</a> of the workforce was full-time freelance. However, by 2021, that had more than doubled to 35%, an <a href="https://www.upwork.com/research/freelance-forward-2021">increase</a> driven in no small part by skilled professionals who are deliberately opting for more flexible alternatives to traditional employment.</p>
  <p>MBO Partners, which helps large companies find the right independent professionals, has tracked trends in the freelance marketplace for the last decade, issuing its findings in an annual State of Independence <a href="https://info.mbopartners.com/rs/mbo/images/MBO_2021_State_of_Independence_Research_Report.pdf">survey</a>. By its most recent count, there are now 51 million independent workers in the U.S. Miles Everson, CEO of MBO Partners, estimates that 7.6 million – or nearly 14% – of these workers provide services full-time to enterprise organizations, and he predicts this will grow as large companies increasingly see using contractors as a strategic choice.</p>
  <p>“Enterprises that are reimagining productivity are by necessity moving from hiring for head count to hiring for outcomes,” he says. “So they’re turning to more specialized consultants to drive growth, reduce costs, and increase agility.”</p>
  <p>Working with contractors is essentially taking a “talent as a service” approach to staffing: paying for only the skills you need when you need them, without having to invest in training, benefits, and other overhead. But like any other shift to an “as a service” model, adding external talent to your internal teams takes planning to avoid common pitfalls.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13d5812537cfea2afada5db5c0c143ea7be84d3b4.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13d5812537cfea2afada5db5c0c143ea7be84d3b4.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_13d5812537cfea2afada5db5c0c143ea7be84d3b4.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Group of business people working in office" src="./media_13d5812537cfea2afada5db5c0c143ea7be84d3b4.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="understanding-different-types-of-external-talent">Understanding different types of external talent</h2>
  <p>In the context of this article, gig workers (e.g., Uber drivers, Instacart delivery drivers) are in a different category from external employees. Gig workers are contractors in a broad sense, but they’re more like part-time employees who can set their own schedules but are required to work under the platform provider’s brand. They must use the required tools and processes to get paid. This article will not address the challenges of managing them; it will focus on contract employees who fall into one of the following categories.</p>
  <p><strong>Short-term project contractors:</strong> People who consistently work 20 hours or more per week on a contract ranging from one to three months. Generally, they’re hired for a specific purpose, then move on when their part of the work is done. A typical example is a software developer with a distinct skill set that’s only needed for one task in a longer-term project.</p>
  <p><strong>Long-term project contractors:</strong> People who consistently work 20 hours or more per week on a contract of up to a year. They’re often brought in because the company needs their skills for multiple short-term projects or because they’re needed to lead a team through a significant transition. However, this is sometimes a way to circumvent hiring freezes.</p>
  <p><strong>Independent freelance contractors:</strong> People who provide services simultaneously to multiple clients, all of whom need their specialized skills regularly, but not on a full-time basis. This is the classic consultant model, commonly used for accounting, legal advice, and other specialized skills.</p>
  <p>Project contractors often work full-time, are typically treated as nonpayroll members of the workforce, and even have company e-mail addresses. Other employees and customers may not even realize they’re contractors. By contrast, freelance contractors tend to maintain a strong corporate identity separate from the company that employs them. People know they are consultants. They still need to be integrated into the broader team but not in the same way or to the same extent as project contractors.</p>
  <h2 id="challenges-in-managing-external-workers">Challenges in managing external workers</h2>
  <p>From the time you start considering whether to bring in a contractor to the day you issue their final check, you need to be cognizant that they need to be managed differently from your in-house staffers to avoid legal, logistic, and cultural risks.</p>
  <p>Many companies struggle with the most basic question: when to hire a contractor instead of an employee. This became an especially urgent issue as pandemic-related employee hiring freezes created or exacerbated <a href="https://insights.sap.com/strategic-workforce-planning/">skills gaps</a>. To get people into empty positions quickly, managers have invested in contractors who are already qualified and need no training. However, this requires managers to understand how to establish and maintain clear guidelines for engaging these workers.</p>
  <p>Without a clear understanding of the legal line between contractor and employee – a line that varies from one region to the next – it’s easy to stumble over it, as some of the world’s leading companies have notoriously done. Under U.S. law, for example, duration of employment is a significant factor in whether someone is considered an employee. A company cannot treat someone as a temp or contractor for years at a time as a strategy for avoiding the costs of providing them with the benefits and protections of employment. Indeed, Microsoft settled the famous 2000 <a href="https://www.latimes.com/archives/la-xpm-2000-dec-13-fi-64817-story.html">lawsuit</a> against it that coined the word “permatemp” by agreeing to pay US$97 million to employees it had classified as contractors on a long-term basis to deny them benefits. Yet despite this cautionary tale, Google’s global workforce in 2019 consisted of more freelancers (54%) than full-timers (46%), and contractors <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/28/technology/google-temp-workers.html">complained</a> that even though they made up the majority of the workforce, they were shut out of meetings and denied the information they needed to perform their jobs.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="remote-in-office-hybrid">Remote? In-office? Hybrid?</h3>
        <p>How managers can help employees thrive in every work environment.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/reinventing-high-touch-management-for-remote-work">Read the story</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To be fair, while many freelancers are committed to their independence, others see a contract job as an audition for in-house work. But if someone doesn’t volunteer that information early in the engagement, a manager needs to tease it out to clarify both sides’ expectations, responsibilities, and risks. Committing to a freelancer’s professional development – for example, not just offering them the option of taking a training course but requiring them to take it – puts you at risk of crossing that blurred legal line between contractor and employee. Employees also need to understand that contractors will be leaving after their contracts end. Even if a manager wants to extend a contract, the company may be legally prevented from doing so. That means it’s critical that managers plan for the transition of contractor responsibilities to permanent employees.</p>
  <p>It’s also important to make sure contractors have a positive experience during their contract assignment. This includes providing the tools needed to do their work and helping them establish the work relationships needed to be effective in their roles.</p>
  <p>But even companies that have been using external workers for some time are inconsistent about who is responsible for them. Some managers bring in freelancers on their own initiative, creating the HR equivalent of “shadow IT.” Some go through HR or procurement. Some use a talent agency as an intermediary. And many companies do all of these at once, with different contractors managed by different people, depending on what they’re doing and whose team they’re on. This mixed bag of approaches can leave an organization unclear on how large its external workforce actually is, with disastrous results for staffing levels, budgeting, project management, provisioning, and other areas.</p>
  <p>“We hear stories about independent workers not getting access to the technology they need for 30 days or more, which is something no manager would tolerate for full-time staffers,” Everson says, noting that since this prevents the contractors from starting work, it delays the projects they’re needed for, which amplifies the need for companies to have a strategy to onboard independent workers efficiently.</p>
  <p>Even HR departments are unclear on how to handle contractors. Legal classification and compliance are HR areas of expertise, yet 25% of HR professionals told SAP/SHRM researchers that managers who hire and work with external workers also have primary responsibility for legal compliance. This exposes companies to significant legal risk by placing compliance with local, national, and possibly international employment laws in the hands of managers who aren’t trained to address it and may not even realize that they’re expected to do so.</p>
  <p>The SAP/SHRM survey also found that most managers have teams that blend external and internal workers. This is unsurprising; contracting isn’t appropriate for every job or every person, so few companies or teams are made up entirely of contractors. But since one in three managers say they haven’t been enabled to manage blended teams effectively, it’s critical for leaders to plan for and prepare managers for friction between different types of employees who have different relationships with the organization.</p>
  <p>For example, if managers don’t point out that internal compensation packages include benefits that contractors don’t receive, in-house employees may bristle at having smaller paychecks than contractors on the same team. Leaders should also develop strategies to include freelancers appropriately in their team without crossing the contractor/employee line, including checking regularly with the legal department to understand what is and isn’t allowable. For example, it may be fine to give external employees a corporate e-mail address and access to the company’s shared workspace but not to other corporate systems.</p>
  <p>Finally, the same flexibility that makes working with contractors desirable can also create challenges for long-term planning, particularly by making it difficult to maintain consistent, predictable funding as they come and go.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b7fb70ad2becf367c388ae6c44083be9321b1e07.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b7fb70ad2becf367c388ae6c44083be9321b1e07.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1b7fb70ad2becf367c388ae6c44083be9321b1e07.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Colleagues standing in a small group discussing something while working at an office" src="./media_1b7fb70ad2becf367c388ae6c44083be9321b1e07.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="six-steps-for-building-a-blended-workforce">Six steps for building a blended workforce</h2>
  <ol>
    <li><strong>Clarify external workers’ relationships with the organization.</strong><br><br>A <em>transactional</em> relationship is defined by a worker’s deliverables. Managers must articulate clear expectations and goals, identify the limits of the contractor’s responsibilities, and conduct regular check-ins to assess their progress. In addition to providing the information, connections, and tools that contractors need to meet their goals, team leaders must respond to questions and provide regular feedback. This ensures that the contract is successful and that both sides get what they want: timely, quality work performed under reasonable terms and conditions, delivered at a fair price.<br><br>A <em>relational</em> relationship is defined by the time spent on the project. Contractors who are likely to spend an extended period of time on a project (for example, helping to produce a series of webinars) are as reliant on their relationships as they are on information and tools. They need to be integrated fully into the team, with steps such as giving them internal e-mail addresses, including them in meetings, and encouraging in-house colleagues to treat them as peers. Yet managers must also provide defined timelines with outcomes and clear completion dates. In addition, they must avoid interfering with the contractors’ responsibilities to other clients in order to protect their legal status as a nonemployee.</li>
    <li><strong>Ensure that managers understand the risks and requirements.</strong> Offer training and leadership management courses about the legal landscape to help managers feel more confident about building and managing blended teams. Establish official policies about when to use a contractor and when to hire in-house to avoid “shadow HR.” Clarify the start and end dates of every contract (and projects, if those differ) to emphasize that external workers aren’t employees and will not be classified as such.<br><br>Consider using an onboarding system to provide a standardized, self-guided onboarding process for contractors. This protects managers and the organization by automating the process of providing necessary information such as nondisclosure agreements, relevant contacts, billing and payment processes, and applicable policies and procedures for safety and compliance.</li>
    <li><strong>Use tools that support your contractors’ specific needs.</strong><br>When you deploy productivity tools for internal staff, make sure they’re fit for purpose for external workers, too. Integrate your contractors into your messaging, videoconferencing, and other communication tools to facilitate regular check-ins and teamwork. Set up workflows that accommodate project-based work with the ability to track progress against performance goals.</li>
    <li><strong>Give contractors a way to fill your needs proactively.</strong><br>Many organizations set up a talent marketplace for internal openings, including not just full-time positions but also part-time roles, fellowships, volunteer opportunities, and other possibilities for career advancement. Opening this marketplace to external workers is a proactive way to connect them with additional projects that match their skills. However, the platform should require managers to specify whether each listing is open to freelancers – or even show contractors only the opportunities for which they’re eligible, such as an opening for a full-time short-term contract position that could not be considered an extension of their current contract. Providing the option to browse other openings saves you from having to recruit more contractors down the line. And because many contractors take on projects to test-drive a potential employer or get their foot in the door at a place they’d like to be on staff, showing them what’s available in your talent market also expands your pool for internal positions.</li>
    <li><strong>Treat external workers as a critical part of your staffing strategy.</strong><br>Support planning and budgeting by maintaining data about how many contractors are being hired and for what projects. Keep track of current and past freelancers (and the agencies you hired them from, if relevant) so you can rate their performance, decide whether or not to work with them again, and justify why. Then make this information accessible across the organization to create a database of talent to draw on for future projects or open positions.</li>
    <li><strong>Solicit honest feedback.</strong><br>If you’re building a formal strategy for expanding your external workforce, you need continuous feedback on how well it’s working – both whether you get what you need from them and whether they get what they need from you – so you can adapt accordingly. Use employee listening tools to measure the experiences that contractors have in your organization. Applying the same exit interview and survey tools you use with internal employees to explore external workers’ experiences at the end of their contracts will help you understand how to get more value from your strategy and build your external worker employment brand.</li>
  </ol>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17c1beddd6c172484ea4e146878af2e49ae7170a2.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17c1beddd6c172484ea4e146878af2e49ae7170a2.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_17c1beddd6c172484ea4e146878af2e49ae7170a2.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Bunch of hands together" src="./media_17c1beddd6c172484ea4e146878af2e49ae7170a2.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="nurturing-the-relationship-with-your-contract-workforce">Nurturing the relationship with your contract workforce</h2>
  <p>Even in transactional relationships, you can increase the chances of getting what you need from your contractors by making sure they get what they need from you. When you make onboarding and technology provisioning easy, invite them to meetings and off-sites, and include them in celebrations and announcements so that they aren’t surprised by promotions and other changes, you’ll help them feel like a valued part of the team, even if only for a few months.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="come-together-right-now">Come together, right now</h3>
        <p>Learn how to build remote teams where everyone can do their best work.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/come-together-building-remote-digital-collaboration">Read the story</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This also includes inviting them to social and team-building events when appropriate. Everson says he’s aware of one company with an explicit policy barring contractors from attending employee birthday celebrations because it believes this would violate legal restrictions. This is almost certainly legally inaccurate, he notes – and it’s insulting to individuals whose time and knowledge are supporting the company. “Treating contractors as valued team members is not the same as treating contractors like employees,” he emphasizes. “Notifying them of company events isn’t going to get you in trouble.”</p>
  <p>Indeed, 90% of independent professionals in the MBO Partners State of Independence survey say that being treated as part of the team is important or very important in their choice of whom to work with. Nurturing your external workers also creates opportunities to get cream-of-the-crop expertise and drive significant change. Everson points out that it’s increasingly common for companies to bring in contractors for keystone positions such as directors and department heads, especially at times of major disruption. While their tenure in these plum positions may be brief, making it a rewarding experience may encourage them to cycle through repeatedly, adding more expertise and value as their knowledge of the company deepens.</p>
  <p>Ultimately, the goal of better managing your contractors is to have access to the best talent when you have a skills gap to fill. Do it well, and you’ll be the company that independents choose to work with on an ongoing basis, refer other talent to, or even give up freelancing for.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Circular Path to Sustainability for Manufacturers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/circular-path-to-sustainability-for-manufacturers</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/circular-path-to-sustainability-for-manufacturers</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Manufacturers are building business models that embrace circular economy principles. Learn more about how it's good for business and the planet.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-supply-chain</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Omnichannel retail today: The seamless shopping experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/omnichannel-retail-shopping-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/omnichannel-retail-shopping-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how omnichannel retail technologies and changing consumer demands are driving online retail, m-commerce, and a more seamless shopping experience.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11592a67af62e39d40b1802e4cb534d4a67ba605a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11592a67af62e39d40b1802e4cb534d4a67ba605a.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_11592a67af62e39d40b1802e4cb534d4a67ba605a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Man using AR in retail store" src="./media_11592a67af62e39d40b1802e4cb534d4a67ba605a.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="omnichannel-retail-today-the-seamless-shopping-experience">Omnichannel retail today: The seamless shopping experience</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The rapid onset of the pandemic led to an almost-overnight shift in shopping behaviors, including a sharp rise in online and omnichannel retail. Demand for things like faster delivery, curbside pickup, and personalized, omnichannel fulfillment options grew at a robust pace. Retailers also got a taste of just how fickle their customers could be, as supply chain disruptions caused shortages and delays.</p>
  <p>Further insight into retail trends comes from <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/business-functions/marketing-and-sales/our-insights/%20survey-us-consumer-sentiment-during-the-coronavirus-crisis">McKinsey</a> and demonstrates that when shoppers are faced with out-of-stock items “only 13% waited for the item to come back in stock versus the 39% who switched brand or products and the 32% who switched retailers.”</p>
  <div class="fast-facts">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h4 id="13"><em>13</em></h4>
        <h5 id="-3">%</h5>
        <p><strong>of shoppers wait for items to restock</strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h4 id="39"><em>39</em></h4>
        <h5 id="-1">%</h5>
        <p><strong>switch brand or products</strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h4 id="32"><em>32</em></h4>
        <h5 id="-2">%</h5>
        <p><strong>switch retailers</strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For the past couple of decades, retailers have understood that if they are to thrive, they need to offer customers a choice. <a href="https://www.cbinsights.com/research/report/omnichannel-retail-technology/">Research</a> shows that up to 85% of shoppers prefer using <em>both</em> physical and digital channels, and, increasingly, customers want to entirely set their own terms as to how they pay for, receive, and even return their goods.</p>
  <p>But today – in a climate of unprecedented competition and change – the best retailers have learned that omnichannel is not just about offering more options; it’s about service, personalization, and providing an ever smoother and more seamless journey for customers as they move across shopping and fulfillment channels.</p>
  <h2 id="multichannel-versus-omnichannel">Multichannel versus omnichannel</h2>
  <p>Just as all poodles are dogs but not all dogs are poodles – all omnichannel retail is multichannel but not all multichannel is omnichannel. So, what’s the difference?</p>
  <p>In business terms, multichannel shopping has been with us for well over a century when, in the late 1800s, many prominent brick-and-mortar retailers also began distributing mail order catalogs. Today, most companies that offer customers a choice of different shopping and e-commerce channels consider themselves to be omnichannel retailers, but are they really?</p>
  <p>Let’s look at the Latin root words <strong>multus</strong> and <strong>omnis</strong>, with multi meaning many or multiple and omni meaning everything or all. In a multichannel model, yes, the customer has multiple choices and flexibility as to how, where, and when they purchase items. But in many cases, these shopping channels are disparate and disconnected. In other words, if a customer switches from one channel to the next, they have to start from scratch. Putting an item in an online shopping cart does not mean it will be put aside in the physical store. Nor will a shopper’s preferences or profile be reflected from one channel to the next.</p>
  <p>Whereas in a true omnichannel shopping experience <em>all</em> the channels integrate into a more seamless experience where customers can pick up wherever they left off – in real time, anywhere. Not only does this let them see their preferences and past actions across channels, it also allows businesses to better leverage data collection to ensure a more personalized and relevant customer experience.</p>
  <h2 id="why-is-m-commerce-mobile-commerce-so-important">Why is m-commerce (mobile commerce) so important?</h2>
  <p>Typically, shoppers go to their laptop when they want a larger view of products. They visit the store if they want a more experiential shopping environment. However, it’s the mobile commerce channel that is the make-or-break for many businesses. After all, there are over seven billion smart phones in the world and most people keep theirs within easy reach for most of their day.</p>
  <p>When it’s executed well, m-commerce can offer customers unparalleled speed and simplicity, leading to a more convenient shopping experience. According to a National Retail Federation survey from January 2020, <a href="https://cdn.nrf.com/sites/default/files/2020-01/cv8-convenience-final-jan-9-2020.pdf">83% of shoppers</a> prize convenience more than ever before. Today, most e-commerce tools work best on mobile devices and many offer one-click solutions that can help minimize customer indecision and lead to fewer abandoned carts.</p>
  <p>Since mobile users account for most of the traffic on social media, it’s essential that retailers offer users a shopping experience that’s not only seamless across their branded channels, but also throughout their social media pages as well. Every moment of delay, every additional click, and every step away from the original portal leads to a corresponding reduction in purchasing and rise in cart abandonment.</p>
  <p>Furthermore, with delivery speed demands on the rise, it’s important that customers are receiving texts and notifications with tracking and delivery information. This service is easiest and most straightforward when done using a mobile device.</p>
  <h2 id="top-five-omnichannel-retail-trends">Top five omnichannel retail trends</h2>
  <p>Customer expectation is for increasingly seamless omnichannel retail that meets them where they are and offers services that are flexible and personalized across the board. Here are a few more emerging omnichannel retail trends:</p>
  <ol>
    <li><strong>More personalization and control</strong> Personalization means creating a customized experience across shopping and purchasing channels as well as advertising, marketing, and sales channels.<br>Shoppers want to be able to make changes to their account or purchase options and have those changes and preferences remembered across both digital and in-store experiences. For example, when you touch an app to let the retailer know you’re coming, you’ll arrive in store to find an assortment of suggestions preselected for you in a dressing room – based upon your online shopping preferences.<br>Also, with easy shipping comes the expectation of easy returns, so tracking refunds and exchanges across every channel will also become a key aspect of omnichannel personalization that businesses will need to offer.</li>
    <li><strong>Shoppertainment and social channels</strong> Shoppertainment, of course, is a combination of shopping and entertainment. It had a particularly noticeable impact during the pandemic, as many consumers who were stuck at home were eager to create more engaging experiences. This can mean things like in-video shopping or sharing clickable and buyable productions within a social media platform.</li>
    <li><strong>Demand for speedy delivery</strong> Every year, the baseline for minimum acceptable delivery speed is dropping, spurred on by the Amazon effect and a growing prioritization of convenience above other factors – to the extent that we are now looking at an increase in consumers who measure this by the hour rather than the day. Furthermore, <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/industries/retail/our-insights/retails-need-for-speed-unlocking-value-in-omnichannel-delivery">research</a> shows that if businesses are unable to offer speedy delivery times of at least one to three days, “almost half of omnichannel consumers will shop elsewhere.”</li>
    <li><strong>More fulfillment options (and more sustainable ones at that)</strong> Greenhouses gases produced as a result of supply chain operations account for as much as <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/business-functions/sustainability/our-insights/starting-at-the-source-sustainability-in-supply-chains">80%</a> of our total global emissions. To improve fulfillment, achieve faster delivery speeds, and protect the environment, businesses are increasingly investing in smart technologies to help them make their operations more efficient, streamlined, and transparent.</li>
    <li><strong>Cloud-connected supply chain technologies</strong> These technologies help to power growing micro-mobility delivery networks, as well as more sustainable options for both fulfillment and returns.</li>
  </ol>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ae66e6dcbd4fc845ba316adf557608c6b8f6e204.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ae66e6dcbd4fc845ba316adf557608c6b8f6e204.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ae66e6dcbd4fc845ba316adf557608c6b8f6e204.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="women looking at ipad in store" src="./media_1ae66e6dcbd4fc845ba316adf557608c6b8f6e204.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1493" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="omnichannel-retail-benefits">Omnichannel retail benefits</h2>
  <p>With more data available from more channels – and more interactions that cross channels – retailers can understand their customers in a way that was simply not possible before.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Collect and analyze data.</strong> The ability to collect data is one thing, but it’s just noise until retailers can use it effectively. Leveraging data analytics allows retailers to receive highly granular information that’s useful in real-time product customization and demand forecasting.<br>This knowledge isn’t just convenient for businesses looking to minimize waste – it can also offer customers a better prediction of shipping and delivery times, allowing them to get what they need exactly when they need it.</li>
    <li><strong>Make the customer experience better.</strong> When businesses are working with more information, they can offer a customer experience that is not only faster but also more transparent, personalized, and flexible. Ultimately, this provides a competitive edge in the crucial areas of customer trust and loyalty.</li>
    <li><strong>Improve sales.</strong> Attention spans are shorter than ever, so eliminating delays and barriers between “considering” and “buying” is crucial. One of the main drivers of cart abandonment is a flawed or complex checkout process. When this is streamlined through a one-click checkout or by using personalization to auto-populate the checkout form, businesses can lower their rate of cart abandonment and improve sales.</li>
    <li><strong>Expand your brand image.</strong> With the world’s most successful brands, all you have to see is a color or one letter of font and you know who it is and how you feel about them. Omnichannel marketing gives retailers an invaluable opportunity to synergize their brand elements across channels, creating a brand experience that is both seamless and highly consistent regardless of where or how consumers are shopping.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="omnichannel-retail-challenges">Omnichannel retail challenges</h2>
  <p>Modern retail and supply chain technologies are helping businesses to better understand and even predict trends in the increasingly complex omnichannel landscape – and this is opening up new opportunities and business models across the globe. However, as demands grow more complex, retailers must also be aware of the challenges they face and the steps they need to take to stay ahead of the game.</p>
  <h3 id="micro-fulfillment-and-inventory-management">Micro-fulfillment and inventory management</h3>
  <p>If shipping takes too long, shoppers will simply abandon their carts and try someplace else. Free and fast delivery often makes the difference between a purchase and a lost sale.</p>
  <p>This has led to intense demands for speed, as well as other <a href="/resources/store-of-the-future">micro-fulfillment options</a> like buy online, pick up in store (BOPIS) and delivery lockers that can give customers more flexibility on when and where they receive their goods. This evolution in fulfillment makes omnichannel an enormously complex supply chain and logistical challenge and drives the need for greater cross-business connectivity and data management.</p>
  <h3 id="cross-channel-messaging-content">Cross-channel messaging content</h3>
  <p>The best brands <em>always</em> have consistent messaging. They can’t offer special discounts or conditions on one channel and not the other – everything must be the same across the board. This seems obvious but, nonetheless, many large retailers continue to struggle with administrative issues like siloed departments and a lack of connectivity and agreed-upon messaging.</p>
  <h3 id="customer-support-and-experience">Customer support and experience</h3>
  <p>The goal of omnichannel retail is to ensure that the customer’s experience is just as terrific no matter how they shop or where they receive their support. For many businesses, this can be a challenge, as it typically involves the use of multiple support channels such as live chat, in-person, telephone, and digital assistants. Today, many legacy business systems are pushed past their capacity to cope, and modern retailers are turning increasingly to artificial intelligence (AI)-driven cloud solutions to integrate their entire customer service network in real time.</p>
  <h3 id="managing-returns">Managing returns</h3>
  <p>With omnichannel shopping comes an increased demand for omnichannel returns. Customers want a variety of options as to how, where, and when they undertake the <a href="/resources/business-of-returning-things">returns process</a> – and they expect it to be as effortless as possible.</p>
  <p>Unfortunately, this can be expensive for retailers, with returns amounting to roughly <a href="https://knowledge.wharton.upenn.edu/article/high-cost-of-returns-should-retailers-rethink-policies/">10% of total retail sales</a>. Services like Amazon Wardrobe are setting the bar, and customers expect that the liberal and convenient return policies they enjoy there will be offered by all their favorite brands. To grow and compete, retailers must incorporate tools and solutions that help them coordinate and connect their increasingly complex logistics networks.</p>
  <h3 id="outdated-systems">Outdated systems</h3>
  <p>During the pandemic, many retailers tried to respond quickly to increased demand and supply chain disruption by bolting a variety of not-for-purpose software and database solutions on to their existing legacy systems. This is a temporary fix that – if it hasn’t already – will break down at some point, causing a dangerous risk of long-term failures or system shutdown. This can cause a worrying lack of trust in today’s competitive retail climate, where online shoppers will quickly abandon their shopping carts and move elsewhere if they don’t trust a site.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f1c17b92506caf143f129b8bb338b638c026213a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f1c17b92506caf143f129b8bb338b638c026213a.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1f1c17b92506caf143f129b8bb338b638c026213a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="man looking at ipad" src="./media_1f1c17b92506caf143f129b8bb338b638c026213a.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="retail-technologies-are-transforming-omnichannel-commerce-and-fulfillment">Retail technologies are transforming omnichannel commerce and fulfillment</h2>
  <p>By now, you may have noticed that many of the benefits and challenges related to omnichannel commerce have to do with both agility and resilience – or the lack thereof. At this point, the difference between a challenge that costs money and a benefit that makes money is the ability to understand the stakes and handle issues quickly and consistently. That’s where retail technologies come into play: using AI, machine learning, and advanced analytics technologies to transform commerce and facilitate omnichannel fulfillment.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Live chat support:</strong> Live chat support is a critical tool that businesses can use to offer customer service through their social media channels, Web sites, and apps. Many businesses have invested in live chat that uses AI and machine learning to help chatbots become more lifelike and personalized for different users and demographics.</li>
    <li><strong>Recommendation engines to personalize the shopping experience:</strong> Again, AI and machine learning can be utilized to help personalize the shopping experience. Some of the best include recommendation engines with algorithms that can do more than just compare recent purchases. They can also leverage other types of data to build a psychographic profile of the types of products customers would be interested in, allowing them to make more accurate recommendations and predict future preferences and trends.</li>
    <li><strong>Headless content management and marketing automation:</strong> The potential for automation in marketing and content management is endless. By freeing up IT departments from constantly tweaking storefronts, companies can be more responsive than ever before. It also puts marketing teams in the driver’s seat, so they can respond rapidly to the data that gives them insight into changing trends and customer behavior.</li>
    <li><strong>Edge computing for greater retail agility:</strong> When retailers can bring the power of smart, cloud-connected business systems to the retail centers themselves, they empower the ability to interact and respond in real time to inventory risks as well as sudden consumer demands or behaviors. This helps improve communication and collaboration between on-premise staff and the rest of the organization and allows all employees to seamlessly plug into their customers profiles and needs.</li>
    <li><strong>Microservice infrastructure:</strong> This supports omnichannel payment options, including BOPIS, POS, m-commerce, in-store scan, bag and go, and more. Creating omnichannel payment options by tying them together in this way benefits both customers and businesses. This microservice infrastructure can also be tied into fulfillment processes to better facilitate returns, creating a smoother and more convenient process from payment to potential return.</li>
    <li><strong>Micro-fulfillment infrastructure:</strong> Responsive, on-demand logistics networks depend upon strong cloud-connected systems and easy-to-use applications. Modern delivery and fulfillment networks need to be agile and close to the ground. To facilitate ever-faster delivery speeds, businesses must coordinate loads, communicate in real time with fleets and customers, and provide applications that support easy on-demand driver response and tracking, for scalable last-mile delivery networks.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="next-steps-to-omnichannel-and-online-retail-transformation">Next steps to omnichannel and online retail transformation</h2>
  <p>As retailers continue to modernize and transform their omnichannel operations, they should remember that change can be hard – for customers and employees alike. The good news is that smart, AI-powered technologies provide the perfect tools for breaking down internal silos and helping to support your customers as they quickly learn to love your omnichannel services.</p>
  <p>And when you embark on your <a href="/resources/digital-transformation-strategy-road-map">digital transformation journey</a>, remember to prioritize people. With a good change management strategy and clear communication, you can unearth and leverage the powerful insights and skills that already exist across your team.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="transform-omnichannel-and-online-retail">Transform omnichannel and online retail</h3>
        <p>Innovate, grow, and win customers with omnichannel and retail technologies.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/retail.html">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Is Your Business Ready for the “New-Collar” Worker?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/is-your-business-ready-for-the-new-collar-worker</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/is-your-business-ready-for-the-new-collar-worker</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Many organizations are hiring a new breed of IT candidate – "new-collar" workers – with proven skills but without a four-year college degree.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cf811aae2be075b2182438bc32d1d599ee0e95ec.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cf811aae2be075b2182438bc32d1d599ee0e95ec.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1cf811aae2be075b2182438bc32d1d599ee0e95ec.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Woman using tablet device to look at data" src="./media_1cf811aae2be075b2182438bc32d1d599ee0e95ec.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="is-your-business-ready-for-the-new-collar-worker">Is Your Business Ready for the “New-Collar” Worker?</h1>
        <p>Companies are hiring IT candidates with proven skills but without a four-year college degree. Getting the payoff requires new HR strategies.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Lawrence Dearth, leader of one of the largest staffing companies in the United States, gently brings a reality check when he sits down with a new client to talk about filling desperately needed IT roles. “We help our customers shape their understanding of what the talent market is, especially nowadays,” says Dearth, president of Insight Global, a US$3.4 billion Atlanta-based company that places approximately 80,000 people annually.</p>
  <p>A customer from the greater Pittsburgh area might come in seeking recent Carnegie Mellon computer science grads – widely viewed as the crème de la crème of tech hires – to fill key entry-level software engineer spots. “That’s one of the greatest technology schools in the country. But they’ve probably already exhausted that talent pool if they’re coming to us,” says Dearth.</p>
  <p>But it’s not all bad news. “We tell our customers, ‘Actually, here’s how much better the talent pool will look if you remove the four-year degree requirement for that position.’” Dearth says that for the past five years, they’ve seen a shift to skills-based hiring, especially in contract positions, and this shift is now showing up in permanent roles.</p>
  <p>“What [candidates have] done in the last five to six years is so much more important than whether or not they have a degree in management information systems or computer science,” Dearth says, adding that they’re not seeing the four-year degree being mentioned in job descriptions anymore. Only about one-third of the 3,400 permanent positions for which Insight Global is currently recruiting mentions a four-year degree, even as a “nice to have.” The average salary for these positions? Around $120,000, which is striking when you consider the widespread perception that <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2021/04/22/jobs-no-college-degree/">lacking a college degree will result in a minimum-wage job.</a></p>
  <p>When it comes to hiring IT professionals, things are tough all over. <em>The Wall Street Journal</em> <a href="https://www.wsj.com/story/where-are-all-the-missing-workers-c7f432dc">says</a> that as the novel coronavirus outbreak begins to transition from pandemic to endemic, U.S. employers are looking to fill more than 10 million roles, driven in part by surging consumer demand. The prolonged hiring drought is threatening our recovery and reshaping major segments of the economy.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1473d4daa14c4e8a3f425a26116981fa13ba64849.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1473d4daa14c4e8a3f425a26116981fa13ba64849.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1473d4daa14c4e8a3f425a26116981fa13ba64849.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Smiling businessman handshaking partner at meeting" src="./media_1473d4daa14c4e8a3f425a26116981fa13ba64849.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Technology roles have been notoriously <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2010/may/18/skills-shortage-worsens">hard to fill for a decade or two</a> but are now coming into glaring focus as companies undertake <a href="/resources/what-are-the-essentials-for-successful-digital-transformation-dx">key digital transformation initiatives</a>. IT leaders see the shortage of talent as the biggest barrier to adoption of two-thirds of the emerging technologies that power digital transformation, according to a <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2021-09-13-gartner-survey-reveals-talent-shortages-as-biggest-barrier-to-emerging-technologies-adoption">Gartner report</a>. Clearly, human capital organizations need to act fast.</p>
  <p>Now, a few years after the concept first appeared, HR and human capital organizations are getting real about making the transition to hiring people without four-year college degrees as a way to quickly onboard people with essential digital skills. These “new-collar” workers develop the skills needed to work in technology jobs through nontraditional education paths – community colleges, vocational schools, software boot camps, technical certification programs, high school technical programs, and on-the-job apprenticeships and internships.</p>
  <p>Hiring new-collar workers immediately opens access to a pool of potential employees who would previously have been overlooked by most hiring managers. Expanding talent pools can pay significant dividends in terms of not only filling important roles but also improving organizational in terms of <a href="/resources/diversity-in-the-workplace">diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI)</a>. The <a href="https://oneten.org/">OneTen</a> organization, for example, specifically aims to enable the hiring of 1 million Black individuals who do not have four-year college degrees into “family-sustaining careers” over the next 10 years. The payoffs for DEI can be huge by filling important roles and bringing new perspectives into the workforce. But experts say hiring new-collar workers means you’ll have to take another look at your <a href="/resources/talent-management-strategy">talent strategy</a>. You’ll need a solid plan for vetting candidates’ hard skills and measuring and developing their critical soft skills, such as collaboration and problem-solving.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b9b1c87e980525d8bca38a454bca202869ddea0b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b9b1c87e980525d8bca38a454bca202869ddea0b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b9b1c87e980525d8bca38a454bca202869ddea0b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Woman in server room" src="./media_1b9b1c87e980525d8bca38a454bca202869ddea0b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1837" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="faster-ways-to-develop-needed-skill-sets">Faster ways to develop needed skill sets</h2>
  <p>Observers agree. Around 2016, Ginni Rometty, then-CEO of IBM, <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/ibm-ceo-ginni-rometty-talks-new-collar-jobs-at-davos-2019-1">coined the term “new collar.”</a> Certainly, the concept was then coming into focus at other major employers of tech staff, where it was called shifting to “skills-based” hiring. Whatever the term, the practice chips away at the primacy of the four-year degree for IT jobs, whether entry-level or higher up the organizational hierarchy, thereby widening the applicant pool and providing access to career paths that previously would have been out of reach for many people.</p>
  <p>“Like many companies, IBM was competing for talent to fill the entry-level software engineering and data science job roles that were critical to its business,” says Eric Bokelberg, innovation leader for IBM Talent Transformation Services. “IBM as a company has always had a strong commitment to education. Our HR leaders realized that we could use that commitment to build new technical resource pools.” Since 2011, IBM has been developing access to STEM-related jobs through its P-TECH partnership with public high schools and community colleges in underserved communities. This program helps high school students learn marketable tech skills and obtain coveted internships – with IBM and other companies – providing an alternative pathway into high-paying tech jobs that offer upward mobility. “There’s a multiplier effect,” adds Bokelberg. “P-TECH’s success has encouraged other companies to join the program, thereby creating more opportunities for nontraditional students and filling more tech jobs for businesses large and small.”</p>
  <p>IBM also enables job access to other communities, such as <a href="https://www.ibm.com/thought-leadership/passion-projects/neurodiversity">neurodiverse</a> people and those who are <a href="https://www.ibm.com/employment/techreentry/">reentering the tech job market</a>. There are many pathways to success in an IT career; these programs recognize that the standard-issue four-year college diploma is not for everyone and doesn’t have to be.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b0157957081370087599e795e59927603078efea.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b0157957081370087599e795e59927603078efea.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1b0157957081370087599e795e59927603078efea.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="In-office coffee area" src="./media_1b0157957081370087599e795e59927603078efea.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="using-ai-responsibly-for-hiring">Using AI responsibly for hiring</h3>
        <p>With the right groundwork, AI can help companies make hiring more inclusive.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/how-ai-can-end-bias">Read the story</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="new-collar-hiring-what-it-takes-to-succeed">New-collar hiring: What it takes to succeed</h2>
  <p>Human capital organizations are rethinking their talent strategies in the face of talent shortages, when the skills are most critically needed for transformation initiatives. Many are pursuing <a href="https://www.hcamag.com/ca/specialization/reward-recognition/making-the-most-of-the-new-borderless-talent-pool/250338">borderless talent</a>; they’re now able to recruit and hire people from larger swaths of the world than they could before. Hiring managers are recasting what an acceptable candidate looks like, with an emphasis on both hard skills and soft skills such as collaboration, problem-solving, flexibility, and empathy. New-collar workers come through the door with qualifications (certifications and proven mastery of technical skills), but they often need some support to help develop and amplify innate human capabilities, including creativity and <a href="/resources/human-factors-build-resilience">resilience</a>, which are very important in an atmosphere of constant change, says Cathy Gutierrez, workforce transformation leader and senior manager at Deloitte.</p>
  <p>Hiring managers are recasting what an acceptable candidate looks like, with an emphasis on both hard skills and soft skills such as collaboration, problem-solving, flexibility, and empathy.</p>
  <p>“Organizations are jumping at the chance to gain access to these new tech talent pools,” she says. HR and business leaders need to recognize that new-collar workers may require a different type of upskilling, however. The four-year college experience provides opportunities for class project work with exposure to different points of view and ways of working, as well as experience with leadership roles in student organizations or athletics, all of which are beneficial to the work world. “Someone who did not have those experiences at school will need support to gain skills in these areas,” she adds. Mentoring can help bridge those gaps.</p>
  <p>Cultural resistance to hiring non-degreed workers is another potential obstacle to embracing new-collar workers: the talent organization has never worked this way and may not trust that getting rid of the university-degree requirement can result in employees who are just as productive as traditional hires. A certain type of college degree carries cues – “This is our type of person.” When those cues are no longer in play, many hiring managers are left unsettled.</p>
  <p>One way that some talent organizations come to accept new-collar workers? By first removing the traditional-degree requirement for contract positions where the need is urgent. If that approach works well, says Dearth, managers tend to become more accepting of the new pathways into the organization.</p>
  <p>Dearth sees the willingness to develop employees’ skills as particularly relevant for hiring younger people. “<a href="/resources/millennials-passions-influence-decisions">Millennials</a> realize they can do anything once they put their minds to it. They are very self-taught. They’re looking for companies that have a culture of developing their potential: ‘We don’t expect that it’s something you have necessarily learned in school,’” he says.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c5e5fa37ad0d36536b109b12fc4528ebbf225f57.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c5e5fa37ad0d36536b109b12fc4528ebbf225f57.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1c5e5fa37ad0d36536b109b12fc4528ebbf225f57.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Finger tapping tablet screen with data on it" src="./media_1c5e5fa37ad0d36536b109b12fc4528ebbf225f57.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sustainability-is-an-all-hands-effort">Sustainability is an all-hands effort</h3>
        <p>Here’s how to staff your sustainability department for company-wide success.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/whos-in-your-sustainability-department">Read the story</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="ai-eases-the-transition">AI eases the transition</h2>
  <p>There is no question that new-collar hiring increases the burden of writing job descriptions and reviewing resumes, because it increases the volume of applicants significantly. Both tasks are made easier through technology tools such as eightfold.ai talent acquisition. Billing itself as a “Talent Intelligence Platform that delivers diverse talent and hidden gems who have the skills to succeed in any role,” <a href="https://eightfold.ai/products/talent-acquisition/?utm_source=google&#x26;utm_medium=cpc&#x26;utm_campaign=HR_Applications_B&#x26;utm_term=Automated%20recruiting%20system&#x26;gclid=CjwKCAjwq9mLBhB2EiwAuYdMtTfJ3hs6dC2xewTLr4v0VZ5VHIlJA6qE7x6fqP4BxFwlDoR9ag8W4xoCMqkQAvD_BwE">eightfold.ai</a> helps automatically match candidates to job profiles based on their existing and adjacent skills. “If you have data analytics on your resume, that’s not too far from being a data scientist, so this tool will catch you for those jobs too,” says Gutierrez. At the same time, the algorithm can identify and weed out résumés that are not right for the position – whether or not the candidate has a college degree. “This area has been very hot in the last two to three years because without AI, [dealing with resumes] can be very tough.”</p>
  <p>Building job descriptions traditionally has been an especially tough task for hiring managers, says Stephen Donnelly, strategic/enterprise developer for eightfold.ai. “AI can help if you’re struggling to name a skill. Let’s say we know Joe is good at this job. You tell our system we’re trying to find more Joes and the AI will prompt, ‘Are you looking for these skills?’” says Donnelly. If Joe is good at project management, the system will put that into the job description. But on the other hand, the system will flag that requiring “project management” in the job description will weed out a lot of good applicants. Eightfold.ai loads data from a company’s systems of record and builds from there, learning which types of candidates had the most success.</p>
  <p>Technology platforms for assessment are also helpful in this regard; <a href="https://www.codility.com/">Codility</a> is a popular cloud-based platform for assessing skills. According to Jeremy Schmidt, director of global talent acquisition for Codility, the platform removes a lot of the unconscious bias that creeps in at the top of the hiring funnel. “It helps give everybody the same opportunity for a role based on their technical skill set rather than their name and where they went to college,” says Schmidt.</p>
  <p>Codility helps hiring managers narrow the ever-burgeoning flood of resumes they receive for hot positions. For example, assume Microsoft needs to hire C# engineers. If they post a job, they will likely receive a minimum of 2,000 applications; that number might reach 10,000 if there is no requirement for a four-year degree. “There’s no way for a recruiter to go through all of those to pick out which ones might be the best fit,” says Schmidt.</p>
  <p>So the Microsoft hiring manager works collaboratively with the Codility customer service team to define what they’re trying to measure, ultimately putting together a practical candidate assessment that is delivered securely online to the entire group of applicants. “The test measures their skill sets in a certain area. And then [managers] can take the top 50 candidates from the list based on the technical aptitude and start there,” he says. This makes the process much more manageable.</p>
  <p>AI also comes to the rescue for one of the most onerous of HR tasks: writing job descriptions. “This is a challenge in so many ways and always has been,” says Bokelberg. “Jobs are constantly evolving. You want to standardize them for efficiency’s sake, but every manager thinks the job they’re hiring for is unique and needs its own description.” AI can provide enormous assistance, he adds, helping identify the right terms in the job description to reach a diverse and qualified pool of candidates.</p>
  <p>At the intersection of the <a href="https://hbr.org/2021/09/who-is-driving-the-great-resignation">Great Resignation</a>, the emerging post-pandemic period, and the <a href="/resources/remote-work-new-normal">work-from-home explosion,</a> there is no question that this is a challenging time for hiring managers. From his vantage point as head of a large staffing firm, Dearth is philosophical.</p>
  <p>“Companies are attracting candidates at higher rates and hiring people at very high rates, but they’re also losing talent at really high rates, so many people are looking for new opportunities, in part driven by the new element of remote work,” he says. “It’s just a really dynamic time. There are so many changes in America in the work marketplace right now. Companies are trying to figure this out while at the same time just trying to hire enough to keep the lights on and their digital initiatives going.”</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reinventing High-Touch Management for Remote Work]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/reinventing-high-touch-management-for-remote-work</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/reinventing-high-touch-management-for-remote-work</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For employees to adapt and thrive in remote and hybrid workplaces, high-touch managers need to reevaluate their approach. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_157412cddee1f27b0b054d30a6f18fca3589b6b4b.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_157412cddee1f27b0b054d30a6f18fca3589b6b4b.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_157412cddee1f27b0b054d30a6f18fca3589b6b4b.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Young office worker sticking notes to window" src="./media_157412cddee1f27b0b054d30a6f18fca3589b6b4b.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="reinventing-high-touch-management-for-remote-work">Reinventing High-Touch Management for Remote Work</h1>
        <p>For employees to adapt and thrive in remote and hybrid workplaces, it’s time to reevaluate three key management skills.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>When SoftBank Robotics sent its employees home in early 2020, Josh Harcus didn’t slack off, as executives feared employees would. Instead, as he <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/06/09/magazine/remote-work-covid.html">tells the New York Times</a>, he quickly adapted his sales pitches to a digital environment and began running product demo videos in the background of calls. The tactic worked, and he landed new clients – more than 30 over a four-month period – while other sales reps struggled to win any.</p>
  <p>Harcus, who now consults independently, says he’s surprised by how much time he spent on the road pre-pandemic (about 80%) and how much money the company spent per trip (about US$5,000 for demos that lasted about 10 minutes). And although leaders were concerned that productivity would plummet with employees working off-site, the reality was that they reinvested the time once spent in back-to-back meetings or commuting to the office into sales calls and customer training. “It turns out we were more productive,” Harcus says. “You just needed to trust us to work.”</p>
  <p>Businesses have spent decades perfecting management techniques for giving employees support in an office context. Manager-employee relationships were built on proximity since troubleshooting, advice, and encouragement were just a cubicle away. At the pandemic’s start, sudden work-from-home orders sent organizations scrambling to implement new technologies and adjust to a <a href="/resources/remote-work-new-normal">remote workplace</a>. The transition was rocky for some high-touch managers, who relied on being available to their team to give detailed coaching in real time. An inside sales manager, for example, could walk the floor listening to employees give sales pitches and relay feedback once they completed the calls. With employees working remotely, this was no longer possible.</p>
  <p>The migration to remote work exposed many serious cracks in the foundation of high-touch management, says Ben Wigert, director of research and strategy for Gallup’s workplace management practice. “Some managers struggled to lead their team without having employees at arm’s length, and some leaders were concerned that employees couldn’t be optimally productive at home,” he says.</p>
  <p>Early in the transition, many managers expressed concerns about how to lead remote teams. According to a May 2020 <a href="https://hbr.org/2020/07/remote-managers-are-having-trust-issues">report</a> from Harvard Business Review (HBR), 40% of supervisors and managers expressed low self-confidence in their ability to manage workers remotely. Nearly a quarter (23%) reported that they could not confidently manage a remote team, while 16% were unsure.</p>
  <p>As many organizations plan for remote work and hybrid work environments to persist <a href="/resources/tailoring-post-pandemic-work-environment-to-employee-strengths-personality">beyond the pandemic</a>, managers need to take the pulse of their remote teams now to evaluate what’s working and what isn’t, determine how to improve shortcomings, and sharpen their management techniques. These new skills will become the backbone of a redefined management role for the hybrid workplace.</p>
  <h2 id="a-tale-of-two-managers">A tale of two managers</h2>
  <p>Leaders in high-touch roles had varying success in supporting their teams in the transition to remote work. Traditional managers who exercised control over work processes with little flexibility have struggled, while those who built a culture of trust transitioned more easily and thrived.</p>
  <p>Last year, Antonios Christidis, partner at consulting firm Oliver Wyman’s organizational effectiveness practice, hosted a series of discussions with a global bank and 60 of its employees to consider back-to-office policies. In sessions with both leadership and junior employees present, Christidis noticed very little disagreement among the two groups. “You could see that the junior people in the group weren’t challenging anything the senior leaders were saying,” Christidis says.</p>
  <p>In breakout sessions without leadership present, however, the discussions were more open, and everyone contributed. “That told me, oh – there’s safety here, and we’ll be able to implement changes faster with this group. Without that security, you’ll have a much longer timeline,” Christidis explains.</p>
  <p>Christidis says these are two management philosophies that the abrupt shift to remote work highlighted. He identifies the first type – the “command and control” managers – as rigid and top-down. These managers provide very specific objectives and steps for their teams to get from Point A to Point B, and they monitor them every step of the way. If an employee were to identify a better process, they often wouldn’t feel comfortable suggesting it, or if they did, the manager might turn it down because they believe they know better. Because this management style breeds little trust among teams, these were the managers who struggled when they went remote, Christidis says.</p>
  <p>“Trust has been a serious point of concern, especially for high-touch roles,” adds Wigert. “Leaders and managers were concerned that remote workers who were out of sight either weren’t working or weren’t as productive as in-office employees. Leaders had their doubts that their managers could effectively guide remote teams.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="come-together-right-now">Come together, right now:</h3>
        <p>Learn how to build remote teams where everyone can do their best work.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/come-together-building-remote-digital-collaboration">Read the story</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>According to the HBR report, quite a few managers reported not trusting the competence of their own employees, with almost one-third (29%) questioning whether their employees had the required knowledge to do their work.</p>
  <p>Wigert says this distrust led to bad behaviors, such as micromanagement. Some managers forced employees to keep video on during the workday to verify that they were working. Other managers required their employees to check in and out with them every day, he says.</p>
  <p>By contrast, managers who established <a href="https://hbr.org/2021/04/what-psychological-safety-looks-like-in-a-hybrid-workplace">psychological safety</a> focused on output rather than the steps employees take to get there. Christidis says these managers empowered employees to make on-the-spot decisions and trusted them to get work done.</p>
  <p>The HBR study shows that workers with relatively hands-off managers who reported low levels of monitoring were more relaxed at their jobs; just 7% said they were often or always anxious. By contrast, 49% of workers experiencing high levels of monitoring reported feeling that amount of anxiety.</p>
  <p>Teams with managers who had established psychological safety prior to the pandemic made a smoother transition to remote work because there were no behavioral blockers, Christidis explains. “They already had trust. They naturally knew how to develop quality relationships and how important that was. When the pandemic hit, they figured out ways to carry those philosophies over to the virtual space.”</p>
  <p>The past year-plus took a toll on employees and managers alike. In a survey of 1,200 people from May 2020, 51% told <a href="https://learnmore.monster.com/poll-results-from-work-in-the-time-of-coronavirus">Monster</a> that they were experiencing burnout working at home during the pandemic. In April 2020, 79% <a href="https://learnmore.monster.com/community-insights-during-coronavirus">reported</a> that they felt that their stress and anxiety due to the pandemic was impacting overall productivity, and half of those respondents still felt that way by February 2021.</p>
  <p>This puts managers in a challenging position. Pushing employees too hard or in the wrong direction could sacrifice their well-being and lead to turnover. “Managers are stressed – even more so since managing remote teams,” Wigert says. Remote work highlighted the strategic imperative of <a href="/resources/why-mental-health-matters">supporting mental health</a> and well-being within the organization – leaders supporting managers and managers better supporting employees.</p>
  <p>To maintain engaged and productive distributed teams, experts agree that high-touch managers should reexamine their traditional practices.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1325983c16fb28bdaa5628058738e2cc27784d673.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1325983c16fb28bdaa5628058738e2cc27784d673.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1325983c16fb28bdaa5628058738e2cc27784d673.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="High-touch manager discussing data with employees" src="./media_1325983c16fb28bdaa5628058738e2cc27784d673.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="reevaluating-three-key-management-skills">Reevaluating three key management skills</h2>
  <p>Successfully converting high-touch, in-person jobs to a remote environment has largely hinged on leaders adjusting their approach to communication, performance management, team cultural norms, and employee welfare.</p>
  <p>Eric Reddy, who leads a sales team at human resources software company Reward Gateway, used to sit in an open office where he and his team could hear and react to each other’s sales calls throughout the day. “Hearing a great question your colleague asks a prospect or laughing off a terrible call is a great learning opportunity on a daily basis when you’re physically together,” Reddy says.</p>
  <p>About two months of remote work, Reddy noticed a drop in morale in the company’s sales development team. “The team was still showing up each day, but it was hard for them to stay fully engaged since they weren’t seeing the same successes as before,” he says.</p>
  <p>In response, Reddy held more team meetings and check-ins; he encouraged salespeople to listen to their recorded calls and use messaging apps to share wins and failures. He also encouraged the global sales team to collaborate on projects, which helped them learn from one another. After those changes and a shift in sales strategy, sales picked up and engagement quickly followed.</p>
  <p>Not every manager demonstrates Reddy’s agility. As the reality of a hybrid workplace emerges, experts suggest evaluating managerial skills in the following areas.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14cf742e970ae301b18ac4972a619aa72624ec62d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14cf742e970ae301b18ac4972a619aa72624ec62d.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_14cf742e970ae301b18ac4972a619aa72624ec62d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Woman smiling, holding her phone" src="./media_14cf742e970ae301b18ac4972a619aa72624ec62d.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="communication-establish-the-right-tempo-and-tone">Communication: Establish the right tempo and tone</h2>
  <p>High-touch managers must reassess how they communicate with their distributed teams and how frequently they do so. Failing to reinvent communication practices causes employees to be anxious, unsure of their priorities, and fearful of not meeting expectations, Wigert says.</p>
  <p>To at least maintain, if not improve, relationships, high-touch managers should prioritize one-on-one check-ins with team members. They should thoughtfully consider the frequency and method of these check-ins, too, says Benjamin Granger, head of EX advisory services at Qualtrics. For some, a weekly check-in using video is sufficient, while others might prefer a daily check-in with chat.</p>
  <p>Setting check-in expectations is a gesture of trust, Granger says. “You’re making it clear that even though we can’t be together in person, we’re still going to connect regularly.” The focus of these touchpoints is not to monitor their work but to make sure they have what they need to get their work done, he says. “Framing it this way makes it more collaborative and less like micromanagement.”</p>
  <p>While check-ins are important for establishing work priorities, they’re also critical for maintaining employee well-being. In a June 2020 <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/business-functions/organization/our-insights/covid-19-and-the-employee-experience-how-leaders-can-seize-the-moment">report</a> on employee experience, McKinsey found that trusting relationships, social cohesion, and inclusion were among the top factors that improved well-being, bested only by job and financial stability.</p>
  <p>Kevin Eikenberry, founder of business consulting company The Kevin Eikenberry Group, suggests starting check-ins with a personal question – ask how the employee, their kids, or their family is doing, for example. This signals that the manager is interested in the employee’s holistic health and that the relationship is important.</p>
  <p>“Managers need to know and appreciate every employee as a whole person,” Wigert says. “Understand what engages and drives them at work. Now more than ever, employee performance hinges on each employee’s engagement and personal well-being.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1da64e86c486206d30024399cef1eff68c2a24d55.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1da64e86c486206d30024399cef1eff68c2a24d55.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1da64e86c486206d30024399cef1eff68c2a24d55.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Group of young adults, photographed from above, on various painted tarmac surface, at sunrise." src="./media_1da64e86c486206d30024399cef1eff68c2a24d55.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="performance-management-assign-clear-goals-and-trust-your-people">Performance management: Assign clear goals and trust your people</h2>
  <p>High-touch managers should clearly define performance metrics and communicate them to employees.</p>
  <p>Reconceptualizing what productivity looks like will reduce a micromanager’s counterproductive impulses. Eikenberry says, “Many managers were used to looking over employees’ shoulders and defaulted to micromanaging. Employees looked like they were busy, but the problem was that they assumed that busy equaled productive.”</p>
  <p>Instead of defining success as hours worked, e-mails sent, and meetings planned – which don’t necessarily translate to successful business outcomes – Wigert says managers can assess performance based on the goals they achieved and the quality of their output.</p>
  <p>Clear performance metrics also help managers establish how often to provide feedback. Infrequent feedback, a Gallup <a href="https://www.gallup.com/workplace/318029/performance-management-evolve-survive-covid.aspx">poll</a> found, is tied to low engagement: For employees working remotely 80% to 100% of the week who received feedback only a few times per year, just 16% reported they were engaged. For those receiving feedback a few times per week, however, engagement was significantly higher, at 63%.</p>
  <p>“Static performance reviews, annual goals, and infrequent feedback never really cut it before the crisis, and they certainly won’t cut it now,” Wigert says. “You need to set these clear expectations and be agile about how you adjust those goals as the work and needs of employees change.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c2af411b377ed02063e982870a42db488617dfe0.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c2af411b377ed02063e982870a42db488617dfe0.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1c2af411b377ed02063e982870a42db488617dfe0.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="One hiker helping another climb up a rock" src="./media_1c2af411b377ed02063e982870a42db488617dfe0.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="team-cultural-norms-invest-in-relationship-building">Team cultural norms: Invest in relationship-building</h2>
  <p>High-touch managers help their organizations build a strong culture of connectedness, which is even more critical in a disorienting time. In 2020, a sense of belonging emerged as one of the strongest drivers of employee engagement, according to the Gallup survey. Just 20% of employees who felt they didn’t belong were engaged, compared to 91% of those who felt they did. One key factor that influenced employee sentiment around belonging: manager effectiveness.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="managers-assemble">Managers, assemble</h3>
        <p>Six key ways companies can support virtual, remote, and on-site employees.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/how-managers-can-support-virtual-and-remote-employees">Read the guide</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In Novant Health’s digital products and services group, Misti Fragen, the group’s VP of learning, research, and culture, <a href="https://enterprisersproject.com/article/2021/2/how-build-virtual-culture-2021">tells</a> The Enterprisers Project that she knows how important connections and a positive virtual culture are to remote work.</p>
  <p>To keep her group connected, she created opportunities for casual online interactions. This included opening a Zoom meeting room at different times of the day for people to gather and scheduling 25-minute mindfulness activities. She developed a theme day calendar to encourage employees to dress up, planned virtual tours of museums, and hosted comedians and tea times.</p>
  <p>“We owe it to our teams to invest, connect, and lift them up,” Fragen says. “Shining a light on engagement, learning, culture, and connecting has helped keep us united during this time.”</p>
  <p>According to Wigert, high-touch managers must assess the health of their teams’ culture and create ways to foster this sense of belonging. He says, “Often, finding shared purpose and accountability makes work more meaningful for each individual team member.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13d5812537cfea2afada5db5c0c143ea7be84d3b4.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13d5812537cfea2afada5db5c0c143ea7be84d3b4.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_13d5812537cfea2afada5db5c0c143ea7be84d3b4.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Group of business people, including high-touch managers, working around a table" src="./media_13d5812537cfea2afada5db5c0c143ea7be84d3b4.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="managers-set-the-tone-for-future-employee-engagement">Managers set the tone for future employee engagement</h2>
  <p>A manager’s success – their team’s performance, engagement, and retention – hinges on their ability to show that they value their team.</p>
  <p>In a Qualtrics <a href="https://www.xminstitute.com/blog/candidates-want-good-managers/">survey</a>, 10,000 Americans were asked to choose between several pairs of hypothetical job packages. The job pairs differed slightly in characteristics. In one option, respondents might have the best imaginable manager and a flexible workplace but company values that are misaligned with their own and a below-average compensation package. In another, they might have a compensation package that exceeds their expectations and company values that align perfectly with theirs but the worst imaginable manager and an inflexible workplace.</p>
  <p>Of all workplace characteristics, direct managers ranked as the most important – above the immediate team, benefits, workplace flexibility, and even compensation.</p>
  <p>As high-touch managers brace for yet another change – <a href="/resources/healthy-offices-healthy-people">returning to the office</a> and managing hybrid teams – it’s important to absorb the experiences from the past year-plus and use them to sharpen management techniques.</p>
  <p>“Blended teams present their own unique set of challenges since bringing people together through multiple modes of communication tends to be even more challenging than when everyone works 100% remotely,” Wigert says. “Communication, rules, and norms can become very difficult to prescribe in a way that works for everyone. That’s why it’s important to get this right now.”</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Make Sustainable Materials Use Matter]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-to-make-sustainable-materials-use-matter</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-to-make-sustainable-materials-use-matter</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[By utilizing sustainable materials, companies can take steps toward a circular economy that saves money and conserves raw materials.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bf0c510aec39014a5318d3e55975930ea0d19dad.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bf0c510aec39014a5318d3e55975930ea0d19dad.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1bf0c510aec39014a5318d3e55975930ea0d19dad.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Glass globe with green foliage background" src="./media_1bf0c510aec39014a5318d3e55975930ea0d19dad.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-to-make-sustainable-materials-use-matter">How to Make Sustainable Materials Use Matter</h1>
        <p>By recapturing resources and rethinking packaging, companies can take steps toward a circular economy that saves money and conserves raw materials.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>A recent SAP Insights survey on sustainability <a href="/research/environmental-sustainability-affects-competitiveness">found</a> that companies’ biggest barrier to taking more environmental action is their uncertainty about how to embed sustainability into business processes and systems. Making more sustainable choices about materials use is one way to address that challenge.</p>
  <p>Apple, for example, gives customers the option of returning their used phones, laptops, and other products. Newer items <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/trade-in">earn</a> trade-in credit, which the company recoups by refurbishing and reselling them. It also disassembles unrepairable and obsolete technology, both for parts and to extract and recycle or reuse materials like aluminum and gold. As one result, the latest MacBook Airs, Mac Minis, and iPads are encased in 100% recycled aluminum from Apple’s own manufacturing <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/trade-in">scrap</a> as well as postconsumer building and construction waste. This approach recaptures the value of materials that would otherwise be discarded while keeping e-waste out of landfills and incinerators.</p>
  <p>Indeed, the SAP survey identified sustainable materials use as one of respondents’ top two priorities for investing in the environment, roughly equal to their commitment to addressing climate change. We also found a minority of companies, which we call the Nows, that believe sustainability is financially material* to their operations today and are already profiting from their investments in it. The Nows are significantly more committed than other survey respondents to investing in sustainability across the board, including <a href="/blogs/the-road-to-regeneration">sustainable materials use.</a></p>
  <p>And the business case for that investment is incontrovertible. In 2020, the Center for Sustainable Systems at the University of Michigan <a href="https://css.umich.edu/factsheets/us-material-use-factsheet">found</a> that raw materials use has grown at more than three times the speed of population growth in the United States alone. Given an expanding global population that insists on an ever-higher standard of living, combining reuse and recycling with more sustainable raw materials would help ensure companies have enough resources to keep up with demand.</p>
  <p>There are, of course, trade-offs. Companies may have to spend more up front to redesign their products and manufacturing processes to make better use of current materials or substitute different ones. But it’s likely they can build on their existing processes and systems, which will help them see a fairly prompt return on investment. Along the way, it’s possible they may also identify previously unnoticed opportunities to cut costs and create new income streams.</p>
  <p>“There’s increased interest in materials choices because they can fit into a larger sustainability narrative,” says Kevin Dooley, chief scientist at The Sustainability Consortium, a nonprofit helping the global consumer goods industry create more transparent and environmentally sound supply chains. “And there are many ways to approach materials use based on what will appeal to customers while meeting sustainability goals.”</p>
  <p>Dooley offers the example of a university that wants to make its logo T-shirts “greener.” Arguably, the university has multiple choices of more sustainable materials. Synthetic fabric from recycled plastics is highly durable and requires less water to produce than cotton. Cotton, on the other hand, can be recycled, is biodegradable, and doesn’t shed microplastics into the water when it’s laundered. If the university can source organic cotton (or an alternative material like hemp) from a nearby farmer, it can promote its support for the local economy. The fabric the university chooses will depend on how it wants to balance multiple sustainability priorities with traditional factors such as cost, quality, and price.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-balance-sheet-blind-spot">The Balance Sheet Blind Spot</h3>
        <p>Learn how sustainability affects your competitiveness and profits.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/research/environmental-sustainability-affects-competitiveness">Read the research</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b10c409a4c3013adea53f443c26fd7b92045007f.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b10c409a4c3013adea53f443c26fd7b92045007f.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1b10c409a4c3013adea53f443c26fd7b92045007f.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Woman using laptop in a small gardening shop" src="./media_1b10c409a4c3013adea53f443c26fd7b92045007f.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="the-business-value-in-sustainable-materials">The business value in sustainable materials</h2>
  <p>To some degree, a combination of consumer demand and government regulation is driving many companies toward more sustainable sourcing and use of materials. Consider the current pressure to eliminate single-use plastics, driven by both heartrending photos of animals that starved to death with stomachs full of trash and predictions like that of the World Economic Forum: that without intervention, the oceans in 2050 will contain more plastic waste than fish. Consumers are reacting with demands that companies use less plastic. Meanwhile, governments are responding with increasingly stringent regulations and are ratcheting up taxes, fees, and bans on single-use plastics. At the same time, they’re pushing companies to take responsibility for the disposal <a href="/resources/circularity-taking-trash-out-of-global-economy">costs</a> as a way to encourage them to choose different materials, or at least to design products and packaging that contain less plastic and can be reused multiple times.</p>
  <p>There’s also significant evidence that customers are putting their money where their demands are. From 2015 to 2021, sales of sustainably marketed products grew 2.7 times <a href="https://www.stern.nyu.edu/experience-stern/about/departments-centers-initiatives/centers-of-research/center-sustainable-business/research/csb-sustainable-market-share-index">faster</a> than those of other consumer packaged goods and accounted for more than one third of overall growth in the category. Nonetheless, Dooley notes that while The Sustainability Consortium members he works with are finding current value in selling sustainable products to consumers, they’re getting even more value from their overall sustainability efforts in the form of cost savings.</p>
  <p>Companies discover savings opportunities when they invest the time and effort into collecting data about their current materials use. The more data they have, and the more visible and accessible it becomes, the more useful it is for generating insights that lead to greater efficiency, increased cost savings, and potential new opportunities.</p>
  <p>Calculating the true costs of your materials use – not just to manufacture and package a product, but also the way it’s used and eventually disposed of – may initially seem burdensome or impractical to the point of impossibility. But the more you understand those costs and how you incur them, the more you can identify opportunities to create value, recapture it, or both.</p>
  <p>It makes sense to start exploring new approaches to materials use in two key areas: resource recapture and packaging. After all, every resource you recapture is one you don’t have to buy.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="circularity-is-the-economy-of-the-future">Circularity is the Economy of the Future</h3>
        <p>Treating waste as a valuable resource is good for the planet and bottom lines.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/circularity-creates-value-from-waste">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Exploring the full lifecycle costs of materials contributes to a comprehensive view of sustainability in the markets where you do business, which in turn provides metrics for areas where you can set goals and take action. For example, you may identify ways to avoid materials (like plastic) that can’t currently be recycled in a key market. You might also develop new product designs based on more sustainable materials. Sportswear brand Cariuma makes knit sneakers from thread that combines plastic reclaimed from the ocean with highly renewable bamboo – an approach that reduces manufacturing waste and promotes alternative textiles while creating new markets among eco-conscious consumers.</p>
  <p>You may even discover new ways to shift or extend your entire business model. Seventh Generation, which makes eco-friendly cleaning products, created an ultraconcentrated <a href="https://www.seventhgeneration.com/easydose-ultra-concentrated-laundry-detergent-freeclear">version</a> of its flagship laundry detergent that contains 50% less water and requires 60% less plastic to package. By having consumers reconstitute the detergent from their own taps instead of paying to ship water around the world, the company distributed more product at less cost while making that product even more sustainable.</p>
  <p>Meanwhile, in places where governments are using regulations to promote recyclable materials and minimize waste, companies willing to pay more for materials that include recycled content will find opportunities to recoup these costs through lower taxes and fees in those markets.</p>
  <p>It’s likely one reason the Nows in the SAP Insights survey are so enthusiastic about investing in better materials use is because they see its potential to deliver an impressive ROI, even though that may take some effort to achieve.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13c9635d2c68aa3f710b6d1dec58970a3d3017443.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13c9635d2c68aa3f710b6d1dec58970a3d3017443.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_13c9635d2c68aa3f710b6d1dec58970a3d3017443.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Stacked wood planks" src="./media_13c9635d2c68aa3f710b6d1dec58970a3d3017443.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="two-approaches-to-sustainable-materials-use">Two approaches to sustainable materials use</h2>
  <p>The ultimate goal for sustainable materials use is a <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability/what-is-circular-economy.html">circular economy</a> that increases value by eliminating waste. However, changing materials in products or using them differently can be complicated and expensive. You had good reasons for choosing the plastics, fabrics, metals, or minerals in your company’s products and packaging. It takes planning to account for all the potential impacts from choosing differently.</p>
  <p>“One area of saving can come from your logistics operations,” says Ian Catley, director at Turnkey Group, whose software provides real-time data collection and analytics to help companies more effectively manage environmental, social, and governance efforts and associated risks. “Perhaps you can’t easily switch the materials you use, but with better planning you could switch air freight to ocean freight, with a significant reduction in both cost and greenhouse gas emissions.”</p>
  <p>Catley notes that even a seemingly minor decision to change a product wrapper made of polyethylene to one made from compostable materials may require new manufacturing and shipping processes to ensure the revamped wrapper performs as well as what it replaced.</p>
  <p>Still, it makes sense to start exploring new approaches to materials use in two key areas: resource recapture and packaging. After all, every resource you recapture is one you don’t have to buy. And every product has to be packaged, even if only for the trip from producer to purchaser.</p>
  <h3 id="recapturing-resources">1. Recapturing resources</h3>
  <p>Manufacturers are developing alternatives to purchasing raw materials, particularly by reclaiming valuable materials from complex products as Apple does. In fact, these efforts are especially common with electronics: a single circuit board can contain more gold and copper than an entire ton of mined ore, while the cobalt necessary for lithium-ion batteries is increasingly scarce and expensive. In some cases, recovering and reusing resources can be more cost-effective, as well as more environmentally sound, than extracting raw materials.</p>
  <p>"The product lifecycle from cradle to grave is on every company’s agenda."</p>
  <p><em>– Ian Catley, director at Turnkey Group</em></p>
  <p>A handful of manufacturers are creating products that actively sequester climate-changing greenhouse gases. One example is Interface, a flooring manufacturer with a line of carpet <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2021/06/23/magazine/interface-carpet-carbon.html">tiles</a> that combine recycled nylon and vinyl with latex extracted from exhaust captured on its way out of factory smokestacks. By locking these industrial emissions into flooring instead of letting them drift into the air, each 10’x20′ installation of these tiles keeps about 12 pounds of CO2 out of the atmosphere – the equivalent of driving more than 13 miles in an average passenger vehicle.</p>
  <h3 id="rethinking-packaging">2. Rethinking packaging</h3>
  <p>Manufacturers are doing <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/industries/paper-forest-products-and-packaging/our-insights/the-drive-toward-sustainability-in-packaging-beyond-the-quick-wins">more</a> to recycle and reuse packaging. They are also moving away from petroleum-based plastic that lingers in landfills for thousands of years to create new forms of packaging made of cardboard, organic fibers from renewable sources like wool and bamboo, and compostable plastics made from corn or sugarcane that degrade within months.</p>
  <p>Catley says that even though manufacturers’ focus on packaging is predominantly driven by opportunities to reduce costs, such as transportation and compliance fees, companies may also see their efforts as benefiting their reputation. As he points out, “Companies don’t want customers to see their branded materials washed up on the beach.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19dec91049d37235dd4529a104a6e8b6cd4a434e6.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19dec91049d37235dd4529a104a6e8b6cd4a434e6.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_19dec91049d37235dd4529a104a6e8b6cd4a434e6.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Giant spool of sustainable material, fabric" src="./media_19dec91049d37235dd4529a104a6e8b6cd4a434e6.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="sustainable-materials-use-takes-leadership">Sustainable materials use takes leadership</h2>
  <p>The SAP Insights survey found that companies are more likely to take action on sustainability when their leaders consider it a priority. This finding points to an approach for exploring how to use materials more sustainably.</p>
  <p>The Nows report that their top motivation for taking environmental action is CEO and board commitment. They also assign accountability for it to significantly more roles across the organization than other companies do, ensuring a sustainability mindset permeates the enterprise.</p>
  <p>The Nows have also been collecting data around sustainability longer, are taking more actions in pursuit of sustainability, and are achieving better business outcomes as a result.</p>
  <p>Business leaders can apply these insights in three specific ways:</p>
  <p>First, create a sustainability vision and agenda to make clear to the organization why sustainable materials use matters and to get buy-in at multiple levels.</p>
  <p>Second, identify and explain the business benefits, such as cost savings or <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/integrated-business-planning/what-is-a-resilient-supply-chain.html">supply chain resilience</a>, of reducing, reusing, and recycling the materials your company already uses, as well as the potential benefits of transitioning to other materials.</p>
  <p>Third, spread the responsibility for making materials use more sustainable throughout the organization, from purchasing to design to manufacturing. Getting more parts of the business involved, invested, and actively experimenting with alternatives increases the <a href="https://www.sap.com/insights/viewpoints/sustainability-data-isnt-perfect-but-its-benefits-will-be.html">volume and variety of data</a> you can use to develop and refine your approach.</p>
  <p>“The product lifecycle from cradle to grave is on every company’s agenda,” Catley comments. “Even renewable materials aren’t all that renewable yet, so it makes sense to make that a high priority. Materials use sits squarely in the middle of the supply chain, and any smart company is looking at that from end to end to find ways to reduce risk and increase value.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">*By material, we mean an event, fact, or issue that is reasonably likely to affect the financial condition or operating performance of a company and should be publicly disclosed (along with the corresponding financial statements).</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-supply-chain</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Business of Returning Things]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/business-of-returning-things</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/business-of-returning-things</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Stop viewing returns as a necessary evil and start viewing them as an opportunity for your business to create great customer experiences.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cc65e3aa6fab8d96641f9146e93d86c9e0df33f4.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cc65e3aa6fab8d96641f9146e93d86c9e0df33f4.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1cc65e3aa6fab8d96641f9146e93d86c9e0df33f4.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Smiling woman holds up a tablet and a credit card to make a purchase." src="./media_1cc65e3aa6fab8d96641f9146e93d86c9e0df33f4.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-business-of-returning-things">The Business of Returning Things</h1>
        <p>Instead of treating the returns process as a cost of doing business, look at it as a pathway to winning customer experiences.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It used to be that surly cashiers, crumpled receipts, and lengthy negotiations determined if a customer could return an unwanted item, whether it was a pair of ill-fitting jeans or a malfunctioning toaster.</p>
  <p>Those days are long gone. Today, customers demand easy and convenient returns – and in response, some sellers are making returns part of their value pitch to customers. Take Stitch Fix, for example. The online retailer relies on sophisticated algorithms to send clothing to customers based on their style preferences. Customers only pay for what they decide to keep, so there’s no waiting around for a refund or navigating a cumbersome returns process. By integrating returns into its business model, Stitch Fix has found a way to not only please customers but also gain a competitive advantage in a crowded marketplace.</p>
  <p>The numbers prove it: although founded only a decade ago, Stitch Fix is now worth US$5 billion and has about four million customers in the United States and United Kingdom. It’s no wonder: according to a <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20201221005180/en/Voxware-Returns-Survey-Retailer-Mistakes-Lead-to-Costly-Returns">survey</a> by Voxware, 97% of consumers “agree or strongly agree” that the way retailers handle returns influences whether they will purchase from that retailer again in the future.</p>
  <p>Stitch Fix joins a growing number of retailers, including brick-and-mortar behemoth Home Depot and online eyeglasses outfit Warby Parker, that are discovering the bottom-line benefits of customer-centric return policies.</p>
  <p>But the emphasis on returns as a strategic advantage for B2C and B2B companies alike is a relatively recent phenomenon. “No one ever thought about returns until America embraced a satisfaction-guaranteed culture driven by big-box retail stores that use return policies as a competitive sledgehammer,” says Tony Sciarrotta, former director of asset recovery for Philips and current executive director of the Reverse Logistics Association, a global trade association for the returns and reverse logistics industry.</p>
  <p>Wielding that sledgehammer takes more than an open-arms returns strategy. Companies must shift their mindsets to stop viewing returns as a necessary evil – and instead start viewing them as an opportunity to create great customer experiences, differentiate themselves from competitors, and protect the planet.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19abc8ca33f85c1bac7269b6bdacc9bd8f688b57a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19abc8ca33f85c1bac7269b6bdacc9bd8f688b57a.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_19abc8ca33f85c1bac7269b6bdacc9bd8f688b57a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Man using tablet, tower of cardboard boxes beside him, returning items to stores" src="./media_19abc8ca33f85c1bac7269b6bdacc9bd8f688b57a.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="an-urgency-for-change">An urgency for change</h2>
  <p>There couldn’t be a better time for a seismic shift in thinking. COVID-19 continues to reshape the retail landscape, compelling customers to move from brick-and-mortar stores to the safety of stay-at-home online shopping. E-commerce sales reached $792 billion in 2020 – an increase of 32% over the past year, according to the <a href="https://www.census.gov/retail/mrts/www/data/pdf/ec_current.pdf">U.S. Department of Commerce</a>.</p>
  <p>Customer-friendly return policies lure shoppers and improve market share. But they also can increase the likelihood of returns – and their labor-intensive processes and wasteful costs. This has been compounded by recent changes in customers’ online purchasing behaviors. For instance, many customers now buy multiple items at a time and simply return the ones they don’t want. This increasingly common practice, known as bracketing, is driven by the promise of free shipping and returns as well as customers’ desire to mimic the in-store experience of trying on clothes to find the perfect fit and size.</p>
  <p>The steady rise of e-commerce over the past decade has contributed to a 33% increase in the return rate of overall retail sales, <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/pages/consulting/articles/reverse-logistics-management-for-supply-chains.html">reports</a> Deloitte. And last year alone, total returns accounted for over <a href="https://nrf.com/research/customer-returns-retail-industry">$400 billion</a> in lost sales for U.S. retailers. With e-commerce revenues growing 15% annually, return rates are likely to escalate.</p>
  <p>Part of the problem is that once returned goods are back in the hands of a retailer, less than half the units are resold at full price. Some are sent for refurbishing or repackaging, while others are funneled to wholesale channels, where a retailer “might get pennies on the dollar,” says Sciarrotta.</p>
  <p>Another ugly aspect of returns is its negative impact on the environment. Transporting returned inventory in the U.S. creates over <a href="https://info.optoro.com/hubfs/Optoro%202019%20Impact%20Report.pdf">15 million metric tons</a> of carbon dioxide emissions annually. What’s worse is that five billion pounds of returned goods end up in U.S. landfills each year, resulting in a huge environmental footprint. At the same time, customers are <a href="/research/passionates-how-they-are-changing-your-strategy">increasingly weighing</a> companies’ sustainability commitments (or lack thereof) into their buying decisions. That’s all the more reason for companies to treat returns as a key part of a good customer experience.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="running-in-circles">Running in Circles</h3>
        <p>5 key areas where circularity creates value from waste.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/circularity-creates-value-from-waste">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17d3193a2b355df99ec599507b87e53e38ce932ac.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17d3193a2b355df99ec599507b87e53e38ce932ac.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17d3193a2b355df99ec599507b87e53e38ce932ac.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Two coworkers chatting" src="./media_17d3193a2b355df99ec599507b87e53e38ce932ac.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1493" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="an-ounce-of-prevention">An ounce of prevention</h2>
  <p>This new mindset, and the best practices needed to support it, can be divided into two main categories: preventative measures and proactive responses. Together, these steps can help both traditional businesses and e-commerce outfits transform returns into a valuable tool for increased customer engagement and profitability. Here’s how: “The best return is no return,” says Sciarrotta. He would know. During his years at Philips, Sciarrotta made sure that the company’s returns management department focused on how it could stop returns before they entered the reverse supply chain. Strategies included enhancing products’ ease of use, enforcing realistic return policies, and bolstering collaborative customer support networks. The result: the electronics giant reduced its return rate from 12% to 4% over a 10-year period, amounting to savings of $100 million per year.</p>
  <p>The first step toward stemming the tide of returns is to design a more customer-friendly Web site. Nearly a quarter <a href="https://www.returnlogic.com/blog/shopify-returns-prevention-and-management-best-practices">(23%)</a> of returns are made because of inaccurate depictions of a product. “What you see on a screen is not always what you get when it arrives at your home,” says Sciarrotta.</p>
  <p>Fortunately, there are a number of ways that companies can set more realistic expectations for online shoppers. High-quality visuals, zoom-in capabilities, sizing charts, detailed product descriptions, and even photos of influencers or other customers using a product can go a long way toward building trust and confidence in purchase decisions.</p>
  <p>Technologies such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-artificial-intelligence.html">artificial intelligence (AI)</a> and augmented reality (AR) are also playing an increasingly important role in staving off returns. For instance, AI can conduct a real-time assessment of an online shopper’s cart and compare it to their purchase history and preferences, such as fit, to determine the likelihood of the product being returned. Next, these insights can automatically trigger a response, such as offering a product discount or suggesting a more suitable alternative, based on whether it’s better to incentivize or dissuade the sale.</p>
  <p>Similarly, AR can prevent returns by allowing a customer to overlay physical objects and images on the screen of a mobile device, creating a three-dimensional, immersive visual experience. Furniture and housewares retailer Crate &#x26; Barrel developed a 3D mobile app that lets customers visualize how a product would look in their homes and offices. Users input their room measurements and select from more than 3,000 models of items to transform a digital photo into a 3D virtual room. AR tools not only allow shoppers to examine products in detail before making a purchase but also raise a company’s profile as a tech-savvy brand.</p>
  <p>Retailers are also partnering with suppliers and manufacturers to ensure that customers’ buying expectations are being met. “For example, some companies send computer schematics to suppliers and vendors of the items they’re producing at different locations around the world to ensure conformity to a single standard,” says James Stock, a professor of supply chain management at the Muma College of Business, University of South Florida. “You want to make sure that a given shoe size, for example, is exactly the same fit whether it’s a loafer, a tie shoe, a sneaker, or a sandal, which can automatically reduce returns based on size.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16c6f10be181a5c3aa49ab8328385f470c2b0b86f.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16c6f10be181a5c3aa49ab8328385f470c2b0b86f.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_16c6f10be181a5c3aa49ab8328385f470c2b0b86f.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Women walking with shopping bags" src="./media_16c6f10be181a5c3aa49ab8328385f470c2b0b86f.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-profit-center-of-the-future">The profit center of the future</h3>
        <p>Technology is transforming customer-agent interactions into new revenue gains.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/blogs/customer-service-is-the-profit-center-of-the-future">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="getting-proactive">Getting proactive</h2>
  <p>Despite every effort, however, as long as products are sold, there will always be some returns. To maintain a competitive edge, according to Stock, retailers must look beyond simply minimizing the cost of processing returns. Rather, he says, the real profit potential comes in disposing of those items in a way that generates ROI.</p>
  <p>Stock adds that the overall goal is to have as many options as possible to handle a returned item, including repairing, refurbishing, and repackaging it. The more options available, the greater the potential for cost savings. Stock cites a mail order catalogue company where he once worked that had no less than ninety options for handling returns, each one with a specific ROI so that the company would know the best way to handle a particular item.</p>
  <p>The good news is that there’s no longer a shortage of ways to proactively manage product returns. Online liquidation market sites, such as B-Stock Solutions and Overstock.com, work by allowing retailers to auction off bulk quantities of products across all categories and conditions. Some retailers, such as Best Buy, are taking matters into their own hands by selling open-box items online and hosting sales events for returned goods after the holiday season. And technologies such as returns management platforms allow retailers to automate workflows and increase visibility into the entire returns process.</p>
  <p>In addition to preserving the value of returned goods, these initiatives reduce the amount of waste that winds up in landfills – a critical selling point for a growing contingency of customers. According to a <a href="https://www.cgsinc.com/en/infographics/CGS-Survey-Reveals-Sustainability-Is-Driving-Demand-and-Customer-Loyalty">survey</a> by CGS, more than two-thirds of respondents consider sustainability when making a purchase and are willing to pay more for sustainable products. <a href="/resources/generation-z-behavior-explained">Gen Z shoppers</a> are some of the most planet-conscious buyers – a demographic that is certain to shape the future of retail and return best practices.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fe5ac50b13ec7d76abc8395e0b72c99f80395c91.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fe5ac50b13ec7d76abc8395e0b72c99f80395c91.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1fe5ac50b13ec7d76abc8395e0b72c99f80395c91.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Hands holding a tablet in a corridor of distribution warehouse" src="./media_1fe5ac50b13ec7d76abc8395e0b72c99f80395c91.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="data-to-the-rescue">Data to the rescue</h2>
  <p>Drilling deep into how, when, and why customers return products is critical to improving overall customer experience. Data can help. “Companies can use <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-machine-learning.html">machine learning</a> and AI to determine why returns are happening in the first place,” says Curt Bimschleger, a supply chain leader and managing director at Deloitte.</p>
  <p>By analyzing data on returns, companies can identify pain points in the process and determine how best to improve. This can also be helpful in managing partners. Case in point: “With analytics, retailers have powerful data that can be used to negotiate better buying agreements with suppliers,” says Bimschleger. For example, a retailer may negotiate better terms with a supplier whose products are associated with higher return rates.</p>
  <p>Data analytics can also help retailers broker better arrangements with customers. Lenient return policies can have the adverse effect of encouraging customers to engage in costly behaviors, such as bracketing or returning products after their market value has diminished.</p>
  <p>However, by crunching vast volumes of data, companies can distinguish between overly aggressive returners, legitimate returners, and nonreturners and treat them accordingly with personalized messaging and targeted offers. For example, a data analytics system can flag a customer who repeatedly purchases and returns items by offering them smaller discounts on sale items than those offered to more profitable customers.</p>
  <p>But even data-driven insights can’t replace the personal touch of face-to-face interactions when it comes to the returns process. This is an opportunity for the brick-and-mortar store to seem like a feature rather than a bug. That’s why a growing crop of traditional retail brands, such as Saks Fifth Avenue and J. Crew, are turning to Buy Online, Return in Store (BORIS). BORIS offers a win-win situation for retailers and customers. “First, customers can receive credit for a purchase right away,” says Bimschleger. “Second, the retailer has a huge opportunity to find the right size or style for the customer or up-sell them other products.”</p>
  <p>Bimschleger predicts a time when businesses will allow customers to return items curbside – a particularly attractive option when dealing with large and heavy purchases. “Customers would be able to pull up and receive a credit right there, without even leaving their car,” says Bimschleger. “I see that coming in the near future.”</p>
  <h2 id="a-look-to-tomorrow">A look to tomorrow</h2>
  <p>Getting to this new world of returns, however, will require many retailers to part with the past. “Sometimes you simply can’t generate more sales to generate profits,” says Stock. “That’s the traditional way of doing business.”</p>
  <p>Instead, more and more retailers are making innovative technologies, hybrid business models, and online marketplaces part of a returns strategy that promises not only to minimize costs and waste but, more importantly, to keep customers coming back.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Performance Management Strategies and Best Practices]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/performance-management-strategy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/performance-management-strategy</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Explore this best practice guide to creating a successful performance management strategy to improve employee performance.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_101d2e9a5a202015393dc96ce78b37379534c6250.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_101d2e9a5a202015393dc96ce78b37379534c6250.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_101d2e9a5a202015393dc96ce78b37379534c6250.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Two co-workers talking" src="./media_101d2e9a5a202015393dc96ce78b37379534c6250.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="performance-management-strategies-and-best-practices--future-proof-your-workforce">Performance management strategies and best practices – future-proof your workforce</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>When it comes time for a performance review, both employees and managers are likely to let out a sigh. Employee reviews tend to be time-consuming endeavors, with managers and employees spending time scraping through emails for examples of successes and shortcomings. And anyone who’s been in the workforce long enough to experience performance management at different companies has received limited feedback followed by a big pay bump or glowing praise and limited compensation.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>A performance appraisal can feel like a black box, which is why some companies abandon employee evaluations altogether. It’s hard to blame them, especially if, due to the COVID-19 pandemic or an unrelated shift in business strategy, the manager and employee haven’t interacted for months – making an assessment seem awkward at best.</p>
  <p>Instead, companies should reevaluate their strategic approach and consider shifting some functions and roles to continuous performance management (sometimes referred to as CPM, but often confused with other acronyms). It’s an always-on approach that’s a smarter, faster form of performance assessment that benefits both people and the company.</p>
  <p>An always-on approach might sound like a scary concept, but once everyone understands it and how it helps their careers, it’s an easy idea to embrace. Not only is continuous performance management less time-consuming, it also removes ambiguity and creates a culture of trust that extends throughout and across the organization. And that’s always good for business.</p>
  <h2 id="what-is-the-traditional-performance-management-process">What is the traditional performance management process?</h2>
  <p>The classic model of performance management involves managers and employees working together at the start of the year on defining a set of objectives and aligning on the measurement against those goals. On a regular basis, either quarterly or twice a year, the manager and employee meet to determine progress made against the objectives.</p>
  <h2 id="a-shift-in-performance-management-strategy">A shift in performance management strategy</h2>
  <p>At a high level, a continuous framework to performance management isn’t about doing employee evaluations all the time. It’s about using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/performance-goals.html">performance technology</a> to set and track goals in an open and efficient way in real time and to support ongoing coaching, feedback, and alignment as priorities shift over time. Then it’s clear who accomplished what and when; if a task was re-prioritized or wasn’t completed, everyone involved understands when or why.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15ab1cc691770672d19ae7c2214ba16c8abe31167.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15ab1cc691770672d19ae7c2214ba16c8abe31167.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_15ab1cc691770672d19ae7c2214ba16c8abe31167.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Continuous performance management process" src="./media_15ab1cc691770672d19ae7c2214ba16c8abe31167.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="722">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Diagram of the stages in a continuous performance management process.</em></p>
  <p>Over time, this strategy feels less like having goals and more like having a to-do list – which most everyone has already. From there, it becomes easier to fold in all the other aspects of employee performance management that can help people feel like the review process is less a burden and more a benefit. Compensation can be tied directly to areas of performance and initiative, and coaching and feedback programs can address areas where people need to improve or want to advance their careers.</p>
  <p>Telling an employee, “You did a great job this year” isn’t particularly helpful if the details aren’t apparent to manager and worker alike, especially if the recipient of such feedback is looking to improve even further. Essentially, CPM becomes the enemy of ambiguity and a welcome assist for anyone looking to grow and become more successful.</p>
  <h2 id="what-is-continuous-performance-management-a-strategic-approach-to-employee-performance-management-that-is-less-like-a-formal-review-and-more-like-a-to-do-list">What is continuous performance management? A strategic approach to employee performance management that is less like a formal review and more like a to-do list.</h2>
  <p>When organizations adopt a CPM model, several changes materialize quickly along with creating an environment of accountability and a true meritocracy. For one, retention improves because people feel more satisfied in their work and their growth – especially if goals clearly ladder up to a strong set of environmental or social values the company has woven into its strategy. Additionally, internal mobility and promotion rates improve because people are able to recognize the paths for moving into new positions of interest. And more broadly, people become more productive because the entire system is geared toward effectively communicating outcomes. When using a continuous performance management system, the annual review practically “writes itself” since all the supporting information about the year’s achievements are already fully documented. It’s easy, then, to draw a direct line from the annual review to compensation planning.</p>
  <h2 id="how-to-roll-out-continuous-performance-management">How to roll out continuous performance management</h2>
  <p>It’s important to note that a company shouldn’t shift from no review process or a traditional one to CPM overnight. It requires time and a comprehensive strategy with a few key pillars, all enabled with the right technology so performance management becomes easier, faster, and more transparent.</p>
  <p>Here are some key employee performance management best practices:</p>
  <h3 id="set-up-cascading-goals">1. Set up cascading goals.</h3>
  <p>In a modern <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/performance-goals.html">performance management system</a>, goals start at the top, with the C-level, then cascade down. Under each goal is a set of activities that are required for completion, and, in theory, any individual can track their activities and goals back to the top. As people complete their activities, they simply check them off. And if the business needs to change at some point, so can the goals – without ambiguity or delay since the technology allows for the quick revision and distribution of new goals and KPIs, top to bottom.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1def7ec5924fb9c898ac9e890ffd4abd8d6bc8e25.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1def7ec5924fb9c898ac9e890ffd4abd8d6bc8e25.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1def7ec5924fb9c898ac9e890ffd4abd8d6bc8e25.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Graphic showing how goals get cascaded." src="./media_1def7ec5924fb9c898ac9e890ffd4abd8d6bc8e25.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="1080">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Cascading goals help ensure employee and team goals are aligned with overall company objectives to maximize organizational success.</em></p>
  <h3 id="add-learning-to-the-mix">2. Add learning to the mix.</h3>
  <p>Goal setting shouldn’t be limited to the idea of hitting targets solely for the good of the company. Personal goals matter as much as business goals. Incorporating <a href="/resources/importance-upskilling">upskilling and training</a> initiatives into the performance management framework shows that the organization cares about every individual’s career growth. What’s more, keeping track of people’s development and the expansion of their skills expands a pool of internal talent and creates a more engaged, agile workforce ready to adapt in the face of change.</p>
  <h3 id="keep-it-simple--and-go-mobile">3. Keep it simple – and go mobile.</h3>
  <p>Ease of use is one of the most important aspects of any performance management software. One of the biggest inhibitors to any performance strategy is complexity. Where things get difficult and time-consuming, adoption drops off. Any system should be cloud-based and have a user-friendly interface so people spend less time filling out reviews. Better yet, putting your performance management solution on people’s smartphones makes tracking, changing, or completing an activity or goal as easy as sending a text.</p>
  <h2 id="change-to-employee-performance-management-is-necessary-but-not-instant">Change to employee performance management is necessary, but not instant</h2>
  <p>The better people understand their own goals and achievements, the more they’ll understand that performance management is as much for their benefit as it is for the company’s. When performance reviews are too time-consuming or convoluted, people and the organization alike can start to become rudderless. That’s why it’s important to adopt a new approach strategically and at a comfortable pace.</p>
  <p>Because annual employee reviews have been around for so long in their mostly imperfect form, it’s very difficult to change behavior and, ultimately, an entire culture. People are often afraid to give constructive criticism as well as receive it. But if an organization starts in a department where there’s the greatest appetite for a culture of continual feedback and growth, eventually a continuous performance management strategy just becomes a part of daily life. And the system can be evolved or iterated upon – based on listening to employees and acting on their feedback – as it trickles out to other departments and disciplines.</p>
  <p>In a time more or less defined by disconnectedness and constantly shifting strategies, there’s really no better situation under which to begin instituting a new approach to performance management – and leveraging technology to do it well. If the traditional ways of assessing people’s performance (or not even bothering) weren’t effective under normal business conditions, they certainly aren’t now – and probably won’t ever be.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-started-today">Get started today</h3>
        <p>Improve employee performance with tools that support continuous development.</p>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/performance-goals.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="performance-management-faqs">Performance management FAQs</h2>
  <div class="accordion">
    <div>
      <div>What is performance management?</div>
      <div>Performance management is the process of a manager and direct report aligning on a set of goals, as well as how the employee should be measured against those targets. At regular times (traditionally, quarterly, every six months, or annually), the manager and employee meet to determine how effective the person has been at reaching the agreed-upon goals – and if not, what changes need to be made to improve performance.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>What are the stages in a continuous performance management process?</div>
      <div>In a continuous performance management process, goals are set at the corporate level. These goals are then broken down into components, or “cascaded” down through the appropriate functions. Managers then assign goals to the employees responsible for tasks or objectives that have cascaded down, but employees also create their own personal and business goals to supplement the larger objectives. People regularly review their goals with their managers and discuss tactics on how to achieve each of them. As employees complete their goals, there’s a clear chain of how each goal contributes to broader targets that originated at the corporate level.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>What are the types of performance management?</div>
      <div>
        <p>In a traditional performance management process, goals are typically set at the beginning of the year. Brief assessments may occur at regular times throughout the year, but a full employee review tends to take place after 12 months’ time, when the person is assessed in terms of having achieved their goals. Other factors may come into consideration as well, such as agility, creativity, and collegiality.</p>
        <p>In 360 reviews, employees tend to review each other, usually within their own department and even their own manager. These reviews tend to take place on a biannual or annual basis and tend to be anonymous. But, they are viewed as a good way for peers to improve their interactions with each other to foster a more collaborative and productive environment.</p>
        <p>In continuous performance management, measurement against one’s goals happens on a rolling basis. When people meet a goal or objective, they simply mark it as complete. This then informs the manager that the goal is met; and this can be radioed all the way to the C-level, identifying which pieces of larger strategies and objectives are being achieved and which are not. When the time comes for the annual review, it’s easy to see which goals were achieved and which were not.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Change Is Changing and What to Do About It]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/you-say-you-want-an-evolution-how-change-is-changing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/you-say-you-want-an-evolution-how-change-is-changing</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[COVID-19 flipped the world on its head, but there's one thing that has yet to change: how we approach change. The time for that has come.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d3857c4b42636f69ead9c8f35f6aa69d8e2ac208.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d3857c4b42636f69ead9c8f35f6aa69d8e2ac208.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1d3857c4b42636f69ead9c8f35f6aa69d8e2ac208.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Digital data of particle wave and network connection" src="./media_1d3857c4b42636f69ead9c8f35f6aa69d8e2ac208.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-change-is-changing-and-what-to-do-about-it">How Change Is Changing and What to Do About It</h1>
        <p>Change is not a threat. It’s the basis for the foreseeable future and it will impact business processes. Here’s how to adapt.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It may be tempting to point to the digital initiatives that were pushed through during COVID-19 as proof that organizational cultures, processes, and employees have learned to change quickly. After all, as Greg Layok, managing director of technology at consultancy West Monroe, writes: “[During COVID-19], for the first time, behavior is changing faster than technology … companies are achieving the goals they have long strived for under the banner of ‘digital transformation.’”</p>
  <p>In many cases, we made those changes because we had no choice. In some cases, boards and C-suite executives approved expenditures as a matter of survival. IT teams and businesspeople adapted out of necessity.</p>
  <p>Indeed, companies “spent the equivalent of around US$15 billion more each week on technology to enable safe and secure home working during COVID-19,” reveals the <a href="https://home.kpmg/ro/en/home/media/press-releases/2020/11/covid-19-forces-one-of-the-biggest-surges-in-technology-investme.html">2020 Harvey Nash/KPMG CIO Survey</a> of more than 4,200 leaders with a combined tech spend of $250 billion. A statement accompanying the survey research notes, “This was one of the biggest surges in technology investment in history – with the world’s IT leaders spending more than their annual budget rise in just three months as the global crisis hit and lockdowns began to be enforced.”</p>
  <p>Not surprisingly, the crisis is taking a heavy toll on employees, especially those in IT, where change is hitting hardest. What leaders expect of their teams right now – working at all hours with fewer breaks – is actually killing productivity and will thwart innovation in the long term.</p>
  <p>“We haven’t really changed the way we’re working. Fatigue levels are off the chart at every level. The bandwidth for managing anything that goes wrong at most major organizations right now is zero,” says Wanda Wallace, leadership coach and managing partner, Leadership Forum. “While managers have adapted to the available technology, they’ve missed the real opportunity here, which is to help their teams to be more efficient and more effective.”</p>
  <p>So what happens when that external pressure dissipates and things go back to something like normal?</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18a9c654b7794068b484e1f6c6daae9cae913f47e.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18a9c654b7794068b484e1f6c6daae9cae913f47e.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_18a9c654b7794068b484e1f6c6daae9cae913f47e.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Mature man standing on empty beach, using binoculars" src="./media_18a9c654b7794068b484e1f6c6daae9cae913f47e.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>If it wasn’t clear before, the global pandemic has brought it home: change has changed.</p>
  <p>As <a href="/resources/future-of-leadership-full-spectrum-thinking">futurist Bob Johansen tells SAP Insights</a>, pandemics and other global crises demand that we look beyond solutions that worked in the past. Disruptions such as COVID-19 will become more prevalent and persistent and will have exponentially greater impacts on businesses, governments, and the world for at least the next decade.</p>
  <p>So what can be done to maintain the speed and ambition of the response to COVID-19 without breaking the bank – or the backs of employees? “If work is disrupted, maybe management should be disrupted, too,” says Jeff Schwartz, principal and U.S. leader for the Future of Work at Deloitte Consulting and author of <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/pages/human-capital/articles/digital-workforce-transformation-roadmap.html">Work Disrupted: Opportunity, Resilience, and Growth in the Accelerated Future of Work</a>. “Although we’ve been using the language of ‘continuous change,’ there’s a lot of work to be done in terms of practice and mindsets and culture.”</p>
  <p>To make continuous change a feature rather than a bug, it must be crystal clear – to everyone from the C-suite to the factory floor – that staying where you are is no longer an option. Change is not a threat. It’s the basis for the foreseeable future, as the threat of pandemics and other big disruptions increases over time.</p>
  <p>Adapting well will require accepting this reality. But not acceptance of capital-C change – behemoth projects with start and end dates that put everyone through the wringer and then they’re done. More like small-c change – ongoing, less tumultuous, but potentially more successful.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>Change is not a threat. It’s the basis for the foreseeable future, as the threat of pandemics and other big disruptions increases over time. Adapting well will require accepting this reality.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1386850f9505bbab3b6a5ffb124bc4a524d4d8f54.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1386850f9505bbab3b6a5ffb124bc4a524d4d8f54.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1386850f9505bbab3b6a5ffb124bc4a524d4d8f54.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Swimmer in lake" src="./media_1386850f9505bbab3b6a5ffb124bc4a524d4d8f54.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="240" height="160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>The net result is increased stress and fatigue, decreased emotional intelligence and cognitive capacity, and thus, suboptimal performance. To illustrate the consequences for work performance, Wallace uses performance technology on her business leader clients like sports coaches use it with Olympic athletes. Cycles of stress followed by recovery optimize athletic performance both physically and mentally; the same is true for executives. Wallace measures accumulated stress, calculates the recovery needed, and helps executives find moments of recovery in the courses of their days.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="how-to-navigate-uncertainty">How to navigate uncertainty</h3>
        <p>Leaders that build employee resiliency are better equipped for constant change.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/human-factors-build-resilience">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Applied to organizational change, the process opens the eyes of executives and managers who are charged with leading (and adapting to) continuous change and enables them to manage their stress and take time to recover. It’s a way to make change constant but manageable for everyone involved.</p>
  <p>But to get there, organizations have to tackle people’s resistance to change. The struggle isn’t due to laziness or dysfunction; it’s science. When change is forced upon people, they quickly become overwhelmed, which activates the fight-or-flight response in the primitive emotional center of the brain, the amygdala. They bottle up that instinctive response, which reemerges as anxiety, depression, and poor health if not managed. The everywhere, all-the-time nature of the COVID-19 crisis was an unnatural force in overcoming our resistance to change. Employees proved to be resilient – but at a big cost to their mental and physical health.</p>
  <p>Some companies have begun to recognize this. <a href="https://thehill.com/homenews/media/549486-nyt-to-give-employees-global-days-off-to-address-burnout">The New York Times</a>, <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/02/success/linkedin-paid-week-off/index.html">LinkedIn</a>, and <a href="https://news.sap.com/2021/03/mental-health-day-sap-employees/">SAP</a>, among others, have given employees enterprise-wide days off to address or prevent burnout. Other companies are taking <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/companies-offer-creative-solutions-to-worker-burnout-during-the-pandemic-11604836834">creative approaches</a> to address the impact of constant change on workers, such as 30-hour work weeks.</p>
  <p>While these programs are novel, they’re just the beginning – bandages for a deep wound. To keep the change going in a healthy way, leaders need more small-c changes, more small-scale innovations, and more acceptance of them as the norm.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dcec56e7a6c4f06f5268c3168b719c747da4037a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dcec56e7a6c4f06f5268c3168b719c747da4037a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1dcec56e7a6c4f06f5268c3168b719c747da4037a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Young girl sitting in the street, studying and working with her laptop and drinking from a cup" src="./media_1dcec56e7a6c4f06f5268c3168b719c747da4037a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="213" height="160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="from-know-it-alls-to-learn-it-alls">From “know-it-alls” to “learn-it-alls”</h2>
  <p>One important way to make change more comfortable is to reconsider the longstanding – and still prevalent – model of a career as “one and done.” Individuals may switch employers, but they largely do the same kind of work at an increasingly higher level. “You go to school, get a job, hop on the career ladder, make a series of linear sequential moves for 20 or 30 years, and you retire,” says Schwartz. “But that’s not what a career is any more.”</p>
  <p>The half-life of skills is rapidly declining – it’s currently at about <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/insights/focus/human-capital-trends/2017/learning-in-the-digital-age.html">five years</a>, according to Deloitte University Press. Meanwhile, the average career length is increasing rapidly as healthcare improves and people live longer. Deloitte estimates that careers soon could span 60 to 70 years.</p>
  <p>When our minds are tied to the single career idea, it’s painful to go through multiple transitions. “But if we told people, ‘You know what, expect to have a dozen jobs and five major transitions in your life,’ then you’re more prepared,” Schwartz says.</p>
  <p>In 2017, Yuval Noah Harari, Israeli philosopher and author of international best-selling books <em>Sapiens: A Brief History of Humankind</em> and <a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/0062464310/?tag=timecom-20">Homo Deus: A Brief History of Tomorrow</a>, told <em>Time</em> magazine, “I think your best bet is to develop your emotional intelligence and your resilience, the ability to keep changing all the time.” Historically, he explained, life was divided into two main parts: the first part, in which you acquired your knowledge, skills, and identity, and the second part, in which you made use of them. The pace of change in the 21st century, he argues, makes much of what you learn quickly irrelevant.</p>
  <p>Organizations instead can foster what Stanford University psychologist Carol Dweck terms a “growth mindset,” whereby employees embrace the continuous change associated with market and business shifts because they believe they can grow and develop capabilities over time. In her research, Dweck distinguishes people with fixed mindsets, those who believe that basic qualities like intelligence or talent are static, from those who think they can develop talents and capabilities over time through effort. The growth mindset, Dweck argues, creates greater individual resilience and adaptability and makes individuals better at problem-solving and change.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>Organizations can foster what Stanford University psychologist Carol Dweck terms a “growth mindset,” whereby employees embrace continuous change associated with business shifts because they believe they can develop capabilities over time.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17c044bc1f2573ed360cea9a850931d51c3a39cc9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17c044bc1f2573ed360cea9a850931d51c3a39cc9.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_17c044bc1f2573ed360cea9a850931d51c3a39cc9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Group of young designers using sticky notes during a brainstorming session" src="./media_17c044bc1f2573ed360cea9a850931d51c3a39cc9.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>The need to shift mindsets is the biggest block to successful change, McKinsey <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/business-functions/organization/our-insights/getting-personal-about-change">notes</a> in a recent article: “The key lies in making the shift both individual and institutional – at the same time.” In the 2019 book <em>Beyond Performance 2.0</em>, <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/business-functions/organization/our-insights/getting-personal-about-change">McKinsey notes</a> that none of the executives at companies that disregarded an analysis of employee mindsets during a change program rated the transformation as extremely successful. At the same time, executives at companies that addressed their employees’ mindsets were four times more likely to rate their change programs as successful.</p>
  <p>The leaders at one engineering company featured in the book were consistently overoptimistic about results and underestimated competitors. The company realized that its issues stemmed from the idea that “winning means being peerless,” which leads to insular behavior. Shifting that thought to “winning means learning more and faster than others” encourages employees to look for best practices in competitors and beyond.</p>
  <p>Kevin Oakes, CEO and co-founder of the Institute for Corporate Productivity and author of <a href="https://www.amazon.com/Culture-Renovation-Leadership-Actions-Unshakeable/dp/1260464369/ref=sr_1_2?dchild=1&#x26;keywords=culture+renovation&#x26;qid=1614026013&#x26;sr=8-2">Culture Renovation: 18 Leadership Actions to Build an Unshakable Company</a> points to the benefits of such an approach at Microsoft. “Using the concept of growth mindset, Microsoft changed to an attitude that knowledge-sharing is power,” he says. “To reinforce this, [Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella] very publicly declared he didn’t want a company with a bunch of know-it-alls. Instead, he wanted a culture of learn-it-alls and continually stressed the importance of growth and development.”</p>
  <p>This approach has served employees and organizations well during the COVID-19 pandemic. <a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/athletes-improve-their-mindset">Researchers from the University of Zurich</a> found that employees who adopted a fixed mindset about <a href="/resources/remote-work-new-normal">remote work</a> (“I’m just not good at remote work”) experienced more negative emotions and less perceived productivity than those who held a growth mindset (“I can get better at this”).</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c2f5283de8c743a9d427038d5b708823ac59b10b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c2f5283de8c743a9d427038d5b708823ac59b10b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c2f5283de8c743a9d427038d5b708823ac59b10b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Father working from home plays with daughter" src="./media_1c2f5283de8c743a9d427038d5b708823ac59b10b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="240" height="160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="not-just-another-change-management-program">Not just another change management program</h2>
  <p>Executives also need to change their leadership mindsets. They tend to view change as highly structured and episodic, which is the opposite of continuous. “So much of what we’ve been doing in change management is to take an organization or program at rest, put an enormous amount of energy into putting it in motion, and then let it rest again, hoping that that reconfiguration will be good for more than a few years – five or ten would be amazing,” says Schwartz.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="digital-transformation">Digital Transformation</h3>
        <p>It’s more than just a technology initiative, it’s a cultural shift.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://insights.sap.com/digital-transformation-strategy-road-map/">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This approach to change may do more harm than good, says Tom Weeks, senior consultant with the Arbinger Institute, a consultancy that works with organizations to encourage change from within. “The change program becomes the change rather than the results you’re trying to achieve,” he says.</p>
  <p>Using the traditional management approach to change creates a short-term view and can drive short-term change. But it doesn’t do anything to shift mindsets to accept and welcome continuous change. And “if you’re not shifting fundamental mindsets,” Weeks says, “it doesn’t matter how much money or how many resources you put behind it.”</p>
  <p>Change will never again be discrete – if it ever was. To make small-c change continuous and sustainable requires something more like what <em>The New York Times</em> columnist Thomas Friedman has called “dynamic stability.” “It’s the stability you achieve when you are constantly in motion,” explains Schwartz, “which sounds like a contradiction until you think of riding a bike. You’re most stable when in motion. These shifts we’re going through – this constant change – it <em>is</em> exhausting, unless you create dynamic stability.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_185578f3393e8c1a4384acb02a4fb6739de334a21.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_185578f3393e8c1a4384acb02a4fb6739de334a21.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_185578f3393e8c1a4384acb02a4fb6739de334a21.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Motion-blurred abstract of people walking" src="./media_185578f3393e8c1a4384acb02a4fb6739de334a21.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="reorganizing-for-flow">Reorganizing for flow</h2>
  <p>Perhaps it’s time to stop using the <em>T</em> word altogether. Transformation, by nature, is radical and massive in scale – something that no company can maintain for extended periods of time. Sure, moon shots are exciting, but a small step is still a step <em>forward</em>. And in the digital era, that’s what most organizations are seeking to foster: forward momentum.</p>
  <p>But COVID-19 didn’t give us that capability, nor is our response to COVID-19 a good model for the future. We correctly viewed it as a crisis, but <a href="https://insights.sap.com/contingency-continuity-planning-best-practices/">crisis management and business continuity planning</a> aren’t sustainable. They are designed to respond to a disruption and then return to normal.</p>
  <p>We will always need crisis response, but we need to create change processes that make those crises less taxing on the organization and its employees. As Deloitte’s 2021 <em>Human Capital Trends</em> report found, business leaders are expecting the unexpected. “We’re recognizing a need to be prepared for more uncertainty than ever before,” Schwartz says.</p>
  <h2 id="a-sustainable-model-for-change">A sustainable model for change</h2>
  <p>A more sustainable model for change may be a hybrid one. Consider the step-and-slope approach: transformation will happen every once in a while, when external drivers are compelling big action, but continuous small-c change becomes the focus between significant change events. The approach reduces the number and size of each move, optimizes the business continuously, and ensures that step changes are maximized.</p>
  <p>However, these advantages are only possible if organizations let go of outdated change methodologies and focus on leading and embedding change with the right mindset, capabilities, and commitment.</p>
  <p>“If work and societies are being disrupted, our management must change in some fundamental ways. We have to seriously look at whether we can lead 21st century organizations and people with the same management canon of the 20th century, largely organized around supervision, control, predictability, accountability,” says Schwartz. “We’re moving to a world where what’s becoming important is orchestrating, navigating, coaching, cocreating, and being transparent. It’s not enough to look at how change management needs to change. We don’t need another change tool. It’s about a larger shift in how we lead and manage organizations.”</p>
  <p>Call it the end of the beginning of the future of work. “We spent 10 or 15 years exploiting and experimenting with all these new technologies,” Schwartz says. “In 2020, those side streets became our main avenues. Now we’re asking how we lead and live in new ways. And how we do that at scale and speed.”</p>
  <p>Everything about the way we work has changed drastically during COVID-19. And business leaders are hoping to remake their organizations to survive and thrive in the long term. The one thing that has yet to change: how we approach the change. The time for that has come.</p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><strong>More on leading modern business evolution:</strong></p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/insights/viewpoints/innovation-metrics-figure-out-which-projects-to-pursue.html">Innovation Metrics: Figure Out Which Ideas to Pursue</a></li>
    <li><a href="http://insights.sap.com/the-c-suite-gets-an-ai-upgrade/?url_id=text-glo-insights-text-cta">The C-Suite Gets an AI Upgrade</a></li>
    <li><a href="http://insights.sap.com/future-of-leadership-full-spectrum-thinking/?url_id=text-glo-insights-text-cta">Full-Spectrum Thinking and Leadership</a></li>
  </ul>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">style</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">additional reading</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Road to Virtual Safety Simulations and Crash Testing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/road-to-virtual-safety-simulations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/road-to-virtual-safety-simulations</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Virtual testing, like crash testing cars, uses simulations to support faster, less expensive, and less wasteful safety. Learn more!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b39a2b27d1709e27cb5f392654d634cc0935cfe0.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b39a2b27d1709e27cb5f392654d634cc0935cfe0.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1b39a2b27d1709e27cb5f392654d634cc0935cfe0.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Young boy businessman wearing jetpack" src="./media_1b39a2b27d1709e27cb5f392654d634cc0935cfe0.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-road-to-virtual-safety-simulations">The Road to Virtual Safety Simulations</h1>
        <p>Virtual simulations will mean faster and less costly safety testing – protecting reputations, profits, and lives.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By SAP Insights</p>
  <p>Sure, vehicles are safer than they’ve ever been. The automotive industry has used decades of crash-testing data to make cars safer and minimize the impact of accidents. But while vehicular design has changed drastically since Cadillacs ruled the roads, crash testing has evolved more slowly.</p>
  <p>And that’s a problem.</p>
  <p>The latest cars use different materials, are structured differently, and have different safety equipment. Humans aren’t all the same either. Yet crash test dummies are based on the average male in the <a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/car-safety/crash-test-bias-how-male-focused-testing-puts-female-drivers-at-risk/">1970s</a> – 5 foot, 9 inches tall and 171 pounds – and this model drives vehicle safety designs. And even though the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration has <a href="https://www.nhtsa.gov/nhtsas-crash-test-dummies">smaller dummies</a> available to test for women, children, and even infants, the agency’s recent studies have shown that female drivers and passengers, when wearing a seatbelt, are <a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/car-safety/new-data-expands-on-why-women-have-a-greater-risk-of-injury-in-car-crashes-a7451402105/">17%</a> more likely to die than a male occupant in a crash. It will take a lot more reengineered tests to provide more precise data on women and children.</p>
  <p>This time-warp effect means that today’s testing isn’t as effective as it could be, which puts revenues and profits – and especially lives – at risk.</p>
  <p>Not to mention that physical crash tests are expensive, time consuming, and wasteful. They mean, in the case of automotive testing, taking a finished prototype and destroying it.</p>
  <p>Nor is this situation limited to the auto industry. Many other industries that have traditionally used physical testing, like engineering, aerospace, and extractive industries, are looking for ways to expand their knowledge and efficacy of testing.</p>
  <p>Vintage testing techniques are ripe for disruption, and digital is that disrupter. Digital technologies are making testing quicker, simpler, and cheaper. Industries that are using virtual testing (also known as simulations) are beginning to implement them, or using them more in different industries such as transportation and construction engineering.</p>
  <p>These developments are still in the early stages, but they point to an urgent need: the sooner we adopt advanced digital techniques, the sooner we’ll be able to build better, save lives, and limit environmental impact. We’ll see less serious injuries in accidents and fewer physical faults, recalls, warranty claims, and injuries, plus better, more reliable components. All these things will save businesses time and money and help them manage risks and their reputations.</p>
  <p>The sooner we adopt advanced digital techniques, the sooner we’ll be able to build better, save lives, and limit environmental impact.</p>
  <p>Traditional testing is widespread. Almost every physical object we interact with, from construction materials to our smartphones, is stress tested for operational and safety assurances – but materials are often unpredictable given the many interactions and scenarios we can subject them to. Cohesive information from every possible collision, bump, or drop is difficult and expensive to measure. These factors make virtual testing harder to do than it sounds. And yet doing so is a matter of life and death.</p>
  <p>Moving testing to the virtual realm gives us methods like digital twins that use simulations to recreate a virtual copy of a physical item, neural networks, and self-aware structures that can predict structural problems and damage before they become problems. By using a virtual testing environment, we’ll be able to unleash even more innovations – and provide more safety.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11f1246131d107cc96f9c275adffd1990262bbde4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11f1246131d107cc96f9c275adffd1990262bbde4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11f1246131d107cc96f9c275adffd1990262bbde4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Lines on the road" src="./media_11f1246131d107cc96f9c275adffd1990262bbde4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="240" height="160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="modernizing-and-digitizing-vehicle-safety">Modernizing and digitizing vehicle safety</h2>
  <p>Many tests, both physical and virtual, are already being done on cars and the materials used to build them, but those tests are limited.</p>
  <p>By law, specific tests, like frontal impact and rollovers, are required to certify a car, says Michael Worswick, professor in the Department of Mechanical and Mechatronics Engineering at the University of Waterloo and executive director of the Waterloo Node of the Advanced Manufacturing Consortium. These are the final tests out of many. Yet making late-stage changes based on such testing is not always easy. If, for example, a car fails the crumple zone test – the section at the front of a vehicle designed to crumple on impact – change can be costly. “If there’s a problem with a crash, it’s very, very late in the game, and any changes can be really, really expensive,” Worswick says.</p>
  <p>Vehicle companies already model every component down to every spot weld – there can be 5,000 spot welds in one car – which requires massive models and large supercomputer clusters, says Worswick. These companies want to minimize the number of tests they have to do and ensure the tests they do perform run to perfection. That’s where most of the crash simulation work happens now.</p>
  <p>Vehicle manufacturers are also using more advanced materials, like ultra-high-strength steel and high-strength aluminum. But they require trade-offs: gaining strength for less ability to deform without cracking, for example. Part of Worswick’s job is to help companies with material property evaluation under crash conditions in their quest to find the best performing materials – metals and composites – for their vehicles. “We do an endless series of characterizations of all kinds of materials for these companies, and then we feed them the raw material data, or in some cases, we feed them the computer model for the material.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e2bdf053095091d43530d8f1ee2e4ceac73279be.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e2bdf053095091d43530d8f1ee2e4ceac73279be.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e2bdf053095091d43530d8f1ee2e4ceac73279be.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Engineer using augmented reality headset in crash testing an engine" src="./media_1e2bdf053095091d43530d8f1ee2e4ceac73279be.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="240" height="160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="navigating-the-data-sharing-problem">Navigating the data-sharing problem</h2>
  <p>But much of the research that engineers like Worswick conduct occurs in a vacuum because companies aren’t eager to share.</p>
  <p>Jessica Jermakian, vice president of vehicle research at the Insurance Institute of Highway Safety, says that sharing data is a roadblock to digitizing testing. An automaker’s computer model is part of its intellectual property, yet if it’s used to evaluate safety, then it needs to be shared with regulators, external testing agencies, and even other companies. Anyone on the sharing end would need to be confident in that model, she says, and that it does what it purports to do as well. “There needs to be some sort of verification of that,” she says. “There are a whole lot of data-sharing issues when you get to sharing proprietary data and having to evaluate it from an outside perspective.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="next-generation-capabilities">Next-Generation Capabilities</h3>
        <p>The automotive industry is racing into a new world of mobility.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://news.sap.com/2020/09/bosch-and-sap-automotive-industry-next-generation-capabilities/">Read the news</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Some sharing is already happening, however. Earlier this year, Toyota began to offer the company’s <a href="https://global.toyota/en/newsroom/corporate/32665896.html">virtual crash test</a> Total Human Model for Safety (THUMs) software for free. The company got much of the baseline data to build those six virtual human dummies from Stewart Wang, a trauma surgeon and researcher. Wang serves as executive director of the Morphomic Analysis Group and director of the International Center for Automotive Medicine, and he’s a professor in the division of acute care surgery and director of burn surgery at the University of Michigan in Ann Arbor. He’s seen firsthand results of vehicular crashes on people when they come to the emergency department and quickly realized preventative measures are better than post-collision treatment.</p>
  <p>Physical crash test dummies are created based on historical research from the 1960s through the 1980s. New technologies and data analytics are providing us with much more granular vehicle and crash data.</p>
  <p>To improve accuracy, Wang works on calibrating the data from virtual dummies with data from humans who have been in crashes. He used custom software to analyze thousands of emergency room scans of patients who have been in vehicle crashes. The extremely detailed <a href="https://www.med.umich.edu/surgery/morphomics/">resulting measurements</a> were assembled into a massive data set that helps link human body sizes, shapes, and anatomy with vehicle, crash, and injury outcomes. “We’ve used high throughput statistical techniques to identify what specific components of the body geometry are important for each class of injury,” like head injuries and chest injuries, Wang says.</p>
  <p>Physical crash test dummies are created based on historical research from the 1960s through the 1980s, when corpses were used in crash tests. But, as Wang points out, deceased bodies don’t behave the same as living bodies for a variety of reasons, like tissue stiffening. Virtual bodies allow car companies to model crash incidents on a variety of body shapes, sizes, and ages. New technologies and data analytics are providing us with much more granular vehicle and crash data.</p>
  <p>“There is a need for these virtual crash dummies,” Wang says. “The advantages are they can more efficiently reflect a broader segment of the population, which is very important.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cc138ab9d3c11afca7d05e600d3aa7c10a4d7e1b.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cc138ab9d3c11afca7d05e600d3aa7c10a4d7e1b.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1cc138ab9d3c11afca7d05e600d3aa7c10a4d7e1b.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Cars driving on a highway, boxes superimposed over each car to show AI capabilities" src="./media_1cc138ab9d3c11afca7d05e600d3aa7c10a4d7e1b.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="safety-testing-in-an-autonomous-future">Safety testing in an autonomous future</h2>
  <p>Over the past couple of decades, there have been significant improvements in modeling the design process of vehicles, says Jermakian. But for safety evaluations, physical tests are still necessary, even though these tests are often limited. “What happens out in the real world is much more diverse, the people are much more diverse, the crash configurations are much more diverse,” she says. Historically, testing has not taken into account the diversity of body types and crash configurations. “We are thinking about how we could incorporate computational modeling and virtual testing into our evaluation program, not to eliminate the physical testing, but to supplement it. To maybe look at a broader range of aspects of crashes that happen in the real world beyond what we can test in our physical test program.”</p>
  <p>One way Worswick sees virtual tests as being both possible and useful is in instances when car model variations occur. Car manufacturers tweak models from year to year in between major design overhauls, for example. Today, that would require a separate crash test, but down the road, it’s possible those iterations can be simulated instead.</p>
  <p>And what about autonomous vehicles? If <a href="https://panasonic.net/design/works/car-future/">fancy</a> and <a href="https://www.dezeen.com/2018/09/04/jaguar-land-rovers-prototype-driverless-car-makes-eye-contact-pedestrians-transport/">futuristic</a> predictions are any measure, passengers in fully driverless vehicles will be watching TV, napping, or playing video games. They will be positioned within and react to the movements of vehicles that differ from conventional automobiles. And that changes how we think of crash testing.</p>
  <p>“The physical dummies were designed to be in those standard seating positions, facing front with your hands on the steering wheel in a very specific position,” says Jermakian. “But when we remove the steering wheel and allow people to sit in different positions, our dummies aren’t designed to work that way. So they’re using computational modeling to look at those other scenarios.”</p>
  <p>Even with all these materials testing efforts, there is still a need for passive safety – protecting the vehicle’s occupants – says Wang. Without near-perfect safety for passengers, no autonomous vehicle company will survive, he explains, because they will be sued out of existence. “If you’re going to assume responsibility for driving the car, you better be perfect or darn near close to it.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_197e9f1eeaec8e0710302dc2195b03f8b13442072.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_197e9f1eeaec8e0710302dc2195b03f8b13442072.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_197e9f1eeaec8e0710302dc2195b03f8b13442072.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Engineer uses smartphone and augmented reality to see holographic projection of model" src="./media_197e9f1eeaec8e0710302dc2195b03f8b13442072.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="the-future-of-simulations-piece-by-piece-moment-by-moment">The future of simulations: Piece by piece, moment by moment</h2>
  <p>The future of ensuring safety for big objects like planes, trains, and automobiles – not to mention bridges, buildings, and other infrastructure – will start with extremely small parts of these larger wholes. Researchers are working on ways to virtually model objects by breaking them into many discrete data points. Simulations will improve as we are able to garner more granular information about different materials and their reactions to stressful situations.</p>
  <p>The improvements will require ongoing research. A big question is how to turn physics equations into physical simulations, says Dr. Joshuah Wolper, a recent doctoral graduate studying computer graphics at the University of Pennsylvania. Computer-generated simulations use physics from engineering and mechanics, fields that have studied how a material’s velocity or other properties like damage change over time. “With computers, we need a way to integrate these equations over space and over time,” he says.</p>
  <p>A challenge with crash testing is breaking material simulations down into small periods of time and varying time lengths. Environments with multiple materials are challenging to model because each material acts and reacts differently. The more rigid a material, the smaller a time step is required, says Wolper. “Something like glass, for example, is very stiff. And so explicit integration might be tricky, because you might have to take extremely small time steps to maintain simulation stability,” he says.</p>
  <p>Wolper is working on material point method (MPM), a mathematical technique used to simulate physical properties of objects. This method is promising in the context of fractures and crashes because it can manage really large material deformations, says Wolper. In other words, something can be very squashed or very stretched to extremes and MPM looks at how the strain is changing from time step to time step – how much the deformation changes with each step compared to the previous. (For more on MPM, see “Simulations Tech Stars in Animated Film” below.)</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14d628436445fba9b2a29d5e4a40e0009bee59938.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14d628436445fba9b2a29d5e4a40e0009bee59938.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14d628436445fba9b2a29d5e4a40e0009bee59938.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Hand holding tablet with performance check screen software" src="./media_14d628436445fba9b2a29d5e4a40e0009bee59938.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="257" height="160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="the-road-from-video-games-to-structures-that-set-off-alerts-when-theyre-broken">The road from video games to structures that set off alerts when they’re broken</h2>
  <p>While Wolper’s current research focuses on realistic effects for movies and video games, MPM holds potential for applications to many other sectors, he says. Apart from crash testing, medicine, bioengineering, and robotics could all benefit. For example, simulations performed with MPM can be used with soft robotics – robots that are flexible and bendy – to see how movement can stress parts. “I think there is real excitement about these methods,” he says. “Rather than busting up your robot, you can simulate it.”</p>
  <p>We’ll likely see simulations developed as part of digital twins, an increasingly popular method that creates a virtual representation of a physical object and often uses simulations as part of that process. Formula 1 race teams use digital twins with simulations to model parts, and now digital twins are increasingly being used in aerospace and other industries. For example, the German Aerospace Center recently opened its <a href="https://www.dlr.de/vph/en/#gallery/37893">Virtual Product House</a>, a project that will use simulations, among other technologies, to test and certify aircraft parts.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_168530313adad62726021aa030bf656394ae7fca9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_168530313adad62726021aa030bf656394ae7fca9.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_168530313adad62726021aa030bf656394ae7fca9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Cloud shape made out of digital network lines" src="./media_168530313adad62726021aa030bf656394ae7fca9.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="ai-and-machine-learning-that-optimize-simulations">AI and machine learning that optimize simulations</h2>
  <p>Advanced technologies, including <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-artificial-intelligence/">artificial intelligence (AI)</a> and machine learning, are being used more often as part of simulations. AI is already having a big impact on materials optimization, which is finding the best material for a given application, says Waterloo’s Worswick. Researchers in the electronics industry, for example, have fully automated material fabrication by brute-force programming a range of combinations and testing as they go. “So you’re generating this massive data set that the AI needs to train a neural network, and now you can start to identify where you should go in the material optimization,” he says.</p>
  <p>The boom in <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-machine-learning/">machine learning</a> is helping researchers figure out how to integrate data from traditional experiments with data from simulations and combining all of it into a unified framework, says Bianca Giovanardi, assistant professor of aerospace engineering at Delft University of Technology. “In many applications, people are putting together physics-based simulations and machine learning techniques in such a way that they can get answers much faster,” she says.</p>
  <p>The boom in machine learning is helping researchers figure out how to integrate data from traditional experiments with data from simulations. The combination has the potential to provide answers faster.</p>
  <p>The combination of the two would provide a best-possible view on the status of materials and structures, opening the door to innovations. But there are challenges to using machine learning and AI in simulations. One is feeding historical data from, for example, years of crash testing into an AI system because that data is often scattered and in various formats. Another is that computer simulations are often very expensive, particularly for something like real-time fracture simulations.</p>
  <p>And then there’s the fact that machine learning doesn’t have predictive power because it isn’t aware of the laws of physics. Traditional scientific computing, however, is based upon the laws of physics.</p>
  <p>Neural networks can be used as a surrogate for physics-based simulations. Offline simulations are run first, and then the network, which has been trained on the completed simulations, can be asked for specific results.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="what-is-machine-learning">What is Machine Learning?</h3>
        <p>Learn what it is and how its applications are all around us.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-machine-learning.html">Read more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>However, echoing Michigan’s Wang, a significant caveat is the issue of accuracy. Machine learning algorithms have traditionally been developed for fields where occasionally being wrong isn’t a big deal, says Giovanardi. Netflix’s movie-viewing recommendations may be frustrating when they’re off base, but certainly not life-threatening. In the context of building something like a car, bridge, or airplane, 98% or even 99% accuracy isn’t good enough. “The community has been trying to see how to make the tools much more reliable, before they can be applied on an everyday basis,” states Giovanardi.</p>
  <p>There’s an even newer idea: self-aware structures. These structures can report on their own condition by combining machine learning and data-driven digital tools that use real-time sensor data. The machine learning algorithms can be trained on physics-based models and learn “which one best represents the state of the structure,” says Giovanardi.</p>
  <p>For example, if a foreign object damages an airplane wing during flight, the sensor data will tell you how the wing is vibrating, deformed, or otherwise behaving unusually. Eventually, with that information, the computer simulations trained using machine learning will be able to tell you about the damage in real time and what actions to take before things get dangerous.</p>
  <p>“If you had this mechanism in place, then you could say, yes, this is a critical engine failure so I definitely need to land this aircraft as soon as possible. Or you can say, no, this is completely safe, you can still go to the destination and have the engine checked there,” explains Giovanardi.</p>
  <p>These are the types of advances that will minimize risk and danger in the real world. With the type of detailed information provided by simulations, driving a car, flying an airplane, and building a bridge will be quicker, less wasteful, and safer.</p>
</div>
<div>
  <h2 id="simulations-tech-stars-in-animated-film">Simulations tech stars in animated film</h2>
  <p>Fans of the animated film Frozen may not be surprised that material point method (MPM) – which has been around for about 25 years – was actually popularized by Disney. In 2013, Walt Disney Animation Studios and researchers from UCLA published a <a href="https://www.disneyanimation.com/publications/?drawer=/publications/a-material-point-method-for-snow-simulation/">research paper</a> about snow-simulation effects. (They’ve since published several more on MPM.) In the real(er) world, it’s been used to model landslides and avalanches.</p>
  <p>“We get really natural multimaterial coupling with MPM. You can model Jell-O in a pool of liquid and then throw some snow on top of it and throw a block of metal in there,” says Wolper, a doctoral student studying computer graphics at the University of Pennsylvania. “You can mix all these materials together and it can handle it all beautifully.”</p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>Style</div>
      <div>Additional Reading</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Circularity: Taking the Trash Out of the Global Economy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/circularity-taking-trash-out-of-global-economy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/circularity-taking-trash-out-of-global-economy</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read what author Ron Gonen has to say about the issues facing sustainability-minded CEOs who want to build circularity into their businesses.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c17bd132613df881d67ba8abc1d6306f5acf6373.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c17bd132613df881d67ba8abc1d6306f5acf6373.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1c17bd132613df881d67ba8abc1d6306f5acf6373.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Landfill compactor in a landfill" src="./media_1c17bd132613df881d67ba8abc1d6306f5acf6373.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="taking-the-trash-out-of-the-global-economy">Taking the Trash Out of the Global Economy</h1>
        <p>Eliminating waste from a product’s cradle to its grave lifts margins while meeting consumer sustainability demands.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Before World War II, the global economy was inherently circular. Manufacturers extracted resources to make items that were designed to last and were used until they could no longer be repaired. At that point, people repurposed the parts or components in any way possible. Discarding an item before it was worn out was unthinkable; even most trash was put to good use. But the deprivation of war on the heels of the Great Depression drove a backlash against thrift. Companies aggressively marketed the idea that consumers deserved things that were new and untouched – and that anything else was inferior, even shameful.</p>
  <p>The resulting demand turbocharged economic growth, but at a steep price. The linear way of manufacturing – extracting and consuming raw materials to make new products that are barely used before being thrown away – has befouled the planet and made precious resources increasingly scarce and expensive while literally shoveling billions of dollars into landfills. As the deputy commissioner of sanitation, recycling, and sustainability for New York City, Ron Gonen saw this every day, both in the streets and in the city budget: every penny of tax revenues that the city spent on landfills and other waste disposal could have been invested in delivering education, transportation, recreation, safety, and other public services.</p>
  <p>In 2014, Gonen left city government to become the founder and CEO of Closed Loop Partners, an investment firm and innovation center focused on making the economy circular again by connecting entrepreneurs with industry experts, global consumer goods companies, retailers, financial institutions, and municipalities. His book, <em>The Waste-Free World: How the Circular Economy Will Take Less, Make More, and Save the Planet</em>, encapsulates what he’s learned about maximizing growth while reducing waste.</p>
  <p>We asked Gonen about the challenges facing sustainability-minded CEOs who want to build circularity into their businesses and what enterprises can learn from how his firm invests.</p>
  <h2 id="q-what-does-closed-loop-partners-look-for-in-an-investment">Q: What does Closed Loop Partners look for in an investment?</h2>
  <p><strong>Ron Gonen:</strong> We chose all 45 of our portfolio companies because they provide solutions for other companies or people that want to become more circular – for example, by coming up with secondary uses and markets for materials that weren’t previously being recycled or by developing technology to reduce food waste by keeping perishable foods fresher longer. We want to invest in aspirins for issues that are causing a lot of pain on the path to circularity.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="what-is-the-goal-of-a-circular-economy">What is the goal of a circular economy?</h3>
        <p>It aims to redefine growth to benefit people and the planet.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability/what-is-circular-economy.html">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For example, Algramo sells name-brand household cleaning products in bulk from cashless kiosks using reusable containers with an embedded radio-frequency identification (RFID) chip that connects to the online payment capabilities of your mobile phone. You download the Algramo app and create an account, then go to the vending kiosk, where you select an Algramo “smart” container and fill it with detergent. The kiosk charges you for the product by weight and deducts that plus the cost of the container from your account. The next time you run out of detergent, you bring the container back to the kiosk, which charges you only for the refill. And you don’t have to fill the container to the brim. You can buy only as much as you need or can afford.</p>
  <p>By encouraging customers to use a single smart container over and over, Algramo helps eliminate single-use plastic, which is especially important in areas with no recycling infrastructure. It also increases manufacturers’ margins because it enables them to sell more product without needing to purchase additional materials to package items individually. And because the chip can keep track of how much and how often a consumer buys the products that Algramo dispenses, a shop or manufacturer can better manage inventory, offer coupons or frequent buyer discounts, and create opportunities for cross-sales.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a5bd0b380a38eca41917c02e987b0822dd47a79c.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a5bd0b380a38eca41917c02e987b0822dd47a79c.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1a5bd0b380a38eca41917c02e987b0822dd47a79c.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Sorted recycling in containers" src="./media_1a5bd0b380a38eca41917c02e987b0822dd47a79c.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="q-how-does-circularity-fit-under-the-broader-umbrella-of-sustainability">Q: How does circularity fit under the broader umbrella of sustainability?</h2>
  <p><strong>Gonen:</strong> Sustainability and circularity are concentric circles. Sustainability is a moral and ethical view of business that’s about recognizing how the “take, make, use, pollute” approach increases the risk that climate change, environmental degradation, resource scarcity, and so on will raise the costs of doing business. The circular economy is the tactical approach: you reduce risk, increase margins, and serve your customers by eliminating as much waste as possible from the system.</p>
  <h2 id="q-as-you-describe-in-your-book-the-concept-of-the-circular-economy-has-been-emerging-for-50-years-why-has-it-only-recently-started-to-gain-traction-with-senior-executives">Q: As you describe in your book, the concept of the circular economy has been emerging for 50 years. Why has it only recently started to gain traction with senior executives?</h2>
  <p><strong>Gonen:</strong> Leaders in the C-suite are recognizing that they’ve become too dependent on extracting raw natural resources to make their products. Doing so is becoming increasingly risky, costly, and volatile as resources become scarcer. As companies recapture more of the waste they create, they find more ways to <a href="/resources/circularity-creates-value-from-waste">extract value from it</a>, their margins are higher, and they become better positioned for long-term success.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>As companies recapture more of the waste they create, they find more ways to extract value from it, their margins are higher, and they become better positioned for long-term success.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At the same time, leaders in the public sector globally are realizing that they need to spend more taxpayer money on infrastructure and public services instead of waste disposal. So they are communicating to business leaders that companies can’t expect to sell their products while the community subsidizes the cost of recycling or disposing of them. Instead, municipalities are starting to demand that companies pay for landfills in perpetuity – or invest heavily in developing recycling infrastructure, which is a lot less expensive!</p>
  <p>Consumer demand also plays a role, but it’s not the main driver.</p>
  <h2 id="q-what-can-business-leaders-do-right-now-to-promote-the-case-for-circularity">Q: What can business leaders do right now to promote the case for circularity?</h2>
  <p><strong>Gonen:</strong> American business culture has assumed for decades that businesses can shunt onto the public the enormous costs of cleaning up after their products, but that’s changing quickly. This makes it a challenging time for CEOs. They’re not hearing a consistent message from all stakeholders. Some stakeholders are pushing for more circularity, which will generate enormous economic opportunity while healing the planet, while others are pushing to maintain the status quo, which is focused on short-term gains regardless of long-term cost.</p>
  <p>One way for leaders to promote the case for circularity is by making eliminating waste synonymous with cutting costs and reducing risk. Then they can challenge their internal teams to use materials science, supply chain technologies, and product design to eliminate waste streams, which will create measurable and profitable results.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>One way for leaders to promote the case for circularity is by making eliminating waste synonymous with cutting costs and reducing risk.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="q-where-should-companies-be-focusing-their-attention-if-they-want-to-be-in-the-vanguard-of-this-shift">Q: Where should companies be focusing their attention if they want to be in the vanguard of this shift?</h2>
  <p><strong>Gonen:</strong> The first step is for companies to explore and analyze their supply chain in detail to spot potential waste, from inefficient processes to excessive resource consumption. The second is to explore ways to utilize their materials that are not dependent on natural resource extraction. For example, you could replace the need to extract natural resources by using recycled content and locking in a lower price in the long term. And the third step is to change your product design so that materials get continually reused. For example, the typical toothpaste tube is made of a mix of plastic and aluminum that’s so hard to separate that it can’t be recycled. It’s hugely notable that Colgate has spent five years developing a tube made entirely of recycled plastic that works just as well and is 100% recyclable.</p>
  <p>Right now, only 16% of companies have taken significant steps toward circularity, and most of those efforts have been by manufacturers around cutting the cost of production by using recycled or renewable materials. To get closer to our goal of 80% of companies thinking circular, business leaders need to look at actually eliminating waste in the manufacturing process by using less material and making their processes and supply chains more efficient. Leaders who recognize that are the ones who are going to be out in front.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-supply-chain</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI for HR]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/ai-for-hr</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/ai-for-hr</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[AI solutions for HR are transforming the modern workforce. Learn more about how AI in HR is being used to meet, and solve, the challenges of a changing workplace.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>core-topic/responsible-ai</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Contingency and Business Continuity Planning Best Practices]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/contingency-continuity-planning-best-practices</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/contingency-continuity-planning-best-practices</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Beyond templates and checklists, crafting a business continuity plan requires a framework that balances the business with the employee experience.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16a006b504bd39a089d2370d7d2f7dcfac1ba07a1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16a006b504bd39a089d2370d7d2f7dcfac1ba07a1.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_16a006b504bd39a089d2370d7d2f7dcfac1ba07a1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Colleagues wearing masks planning on whiteboard" src="./media_16a006b504bd39a089d2370d7d2f7dcfac1ba07a1.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="contingency-and-business-continuity-planning-best-practices">Contingency and business continuity planning best practices</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Contingency planning is a broad term. In theory, any business continuity checklist can be developed around issues as mundane as organizing fire drills (don’t forget to take your laptop with you!). But if the COVID-19 crisis is any indication as to how quickly normal operations can be upended, today’s HR organizations should be thinking about and creating business continuity plans for a much wider range of scenarios.</p>
  <p>Everything should be on the table, from the next pandemic to preventable and unpreventable scenarios alike. Think natural disasters, accidents, intentional acts, IT outages, you name it. In each case, lay out how operations and resources must be shifted, refocused, removed, or added to maintain as much business continuity as possible.</p>
  <p>All this begs the question of where to begin.</p>
  <p>The short answer is anywhere and everywhere, all at once, so the organization isn’t caught flat-footed. But the long answer is that there are several emergency-preparedness best practices that HR managers should adhere to in part or in sum to ensure business continuity in the face of a crisis. Keeping these best practices in mind will inform the foundation of a business continuity plan template that can be followed, expanded upon, or customized to fit any situation as it develops.</p>
  <h2 id="how-to-create-a-contingency-plan-critical-elements">How to create a contingency plan: Critical elements</h2>
  <p>There’s power in communication and policy alike. So before developing tactical steps to suit any possible scenario, it’s important to think of contingency planning as encapsulating three ideas:</p>
  <ol>
    <li>What workers want, which is essentially the employee experience in an emergency situation;</li>
    <li>Perception, which comprises the rumors circulating about how the company is handling the situation; and</li>
    <li>Business needs, which is how the company is performing in terms of maintaining business continuity and serving customers effectively.</li>
  </ol>
  <p>Where these three overlap is the feedback loop – when, where, how, with what frequency, and the authenticity of communication between the company and its employees about the adverse event or situation.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16a38f159aedff0586a8a8fd4e00cba62a5e95ec5.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16a38f159aedff0586a8a8fd4e00cba62a5e95ec5.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_16a38f159aedff0586a8a8fd4e00cba62a5e95ec5.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Venn diagram graphic showing critical elements to consider in a contingency plan" src="./media_16a38f159aedff0586a8a8fd4e00cba62a5e95ec5.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="1080">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Critical elements to consider in a contingency plan.</em></p>
  <p>“The feedback has to be timely, and whoever delivers the communication has to be honest and transparent,” says Greg Selke, vice president and HR value advisor for SAP SuccessFactors. And as part of any business continuity plan, he explains, the methods of communication need to be planned well in advance. If, in the aftermath of unfortunate events, HR managers are deciding whether to send an email or text message to employees, the action plan is already lagging. But the more important thing to remember about the model above, Selke notes, is that it can work as well for a company of 20 employees as for one of 200,000.</p>
  <p>The model must, however, be underpinned by a robust examination and evolution of policy. That requires equal parts intelligence and agility, particularly for a situation like the COVID-19 pandemic, since no one knows what a return to normal even looks like, never mind if and when it will be possible. This should include everything from rethinking what <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/performance-goals.html">performance management</a> looks like to providing resources or even time off for employees to manage stress – or perhaps help with their school-age kids’ homework. It all speaks to a better <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/employee-experience-management.html">employee experience</a> while still holding workers accountable for results. Still, policy flexibility is essential.</p>
  <p>Think of it like this. What if a company asks sales reps to arrange in-person meetings, but some feel it’s unsafe? Or what if the clients don’t want to be visited due to safety concerns? What about employees with disabilities or those at a higher risk of severe coronavirus symptoms? HR managers need to weigh all these types of scenarios and more as they augment emergency preparedness strategies with new policies. The employee experience of any situation is what should drive the business continuity response.</p>
  <p>It’s only after the above three elements – what workers want, perception and business needs, and the overlapping feedback – are carefully considered that specific plans should be laid out.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1605518e6c1639afbb97048621372b5e4e5a3cfbd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1605518e6c1639afbb97048621372b5e4e5a3cfbd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1605518e6c1639afbb97048621372b5e4e5a3cfbd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Coworkers in masks sitting with clear barrier in between for COVID-19 protection" src="./media_1605518e6c1639afbb97048621372b5e4e5a3cfbd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2121" height="1414">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="find-the-right-framework-common-characteristics-of-continuity-plans">Find the right framework: Common characteristics of continuity plans</h2>
  <p>There are multiple business continuity plan samples to be found online, all of which help lay out the types of steps and procedures for different types of companies, nonprofits, and public services – even schools. As an HR leader begins determining tactical steps in any of those frameworks to preserve the business amid several unfortunate scenarios, a few key components should stay front and center of plans that address both small- and large-scale situations.</p>
  <h3 id="agility">Agility</h3>
  <p>While this is a broad and often overused term, in the context of business continuity it’s perhaps the most important consideration. It’s not just about people being able to work remotely; it’s about the company’s ability to communicate with everyone, wherever they are. Here are a few questions to start with:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Are emergency contacts in place for everyone?</li>
    <li>What are the key business-critical roles and who holds them?</li>
    <li>Are there tools in place that ensure worker safety?</li>
    <li>Do employees have the ability to view their personal data and manage <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/employee-central-hris.html">benefits</a>, time off, and scheduling to adapt to the crisis at hand?</li>
    <li>Does the organization have the ability to <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/employee-engagement.html">gather clear insights</a> on what employees are thinking and expecting from the company so HR can take quick, appropriate action?</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The more HR leaders can think about agility in these terms and employ the proper tools (many of them interconnected and cloud-enabled), the easier it will be to develop a more comprehensive set of contingency plans.</p>
  <h3 id="succession-modeling">Succession modeling</h3>
  <p>When talking about business-critical roles, HR needs to be able to identify the required skills, potential successors, and alternates who can step in at a time of crisis. As part of contingency planning, HR professionals should be constantly imagining and reconfiguring the organization for certain and uncertain times alike. That means thinking about positions or even entire departments that might need to be moved, reconfigured, or reallocated under various business conditions and scenarios. It’s also important to have insight and analytics that lay out the wider effects any of these emergency-situation reconfigurations will have on the company – to payroll or diversity, for example. After all, realigning resources to fit with new goals will only go so far if it doesn’t deliver the cost savings required in leaner times or if it adversely affects diversity and inclusion – some of the most important considerations in any company’s long-term plans.</p>
  <h3 id="worker-training">Worker training</h3>
  <p>Most would file training, upskilling, and reskilling under agility (above), but in the context of business contingency planning, training takes on a different meaning. In terms of keeping operations running during uncertain times, having a <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">robust training program</a> in place well in advance of any crisis helps HR managers avoid frantic hiring when and if the corporate strategy needs to shift.</p>
  <p>By defining the types of jobs that will be necessary and the requisite skills for each, then instituting the appropriate learning tools, HR managers can set up, launch, and track the needed training programs. This may constitute <a href="/resources/importance-upskilling">upskilling or reskilling initiatives</a> – or a combination of the two – in line with business objectives likely to arise in the face of specific emergency situations. Either way, this means setting the concept of skills at the center of the HR talent approach so that they are the foundation of both job descriptions and people’s careers – and are ready for further development before adverse conditions arise.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f48c77e3004f5db613f54f7b14fe183dda157b0a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f48c77e3004f5db613f54f7b14fe183dda157b0a.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1f48c77e3004f5db613f54f7b14fe183dda157b0a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Woman working from home" src="./media_1f48c77e3004f5db613f54f7b14fe183dda157b0a.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h3 id="realigning-and-reconnecting">Realigning and reconnecting</h3>
  <p>In times of normal operations, businesses tend to have little trouble setting goals and communicating them to employees. People tend to know the targets they’re working toward. However, when operations are disrupted by a pandemic, natural disaster, or some other short- or long-term situation, the goals tend to go out the window. But it’s not just about scaling back expectations. In order to preserve business continuity, objectives might have to be completely redefined, so it’s critical to <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/performance-goals.html">set new targets, communicate them clearly, and keep track</a> of how workers are performing toward those new objectives.</p>
  <p>It’s also important that everyone and everything is working in harmony, even mid-crisis. HR managers in particular should look for <a href="https://news.sap.com/2020/06/hxm-solution-updates-empowers-hr/">digital toolkits</a> that help teams, departments, groups of employees, HR – really anyone – communicate and collaborate without the hassle of adding IT infrastructure. The more employees can share knowledge and information with one another quickly and easily in times of uncertainty, the more resilient the business will be.</p>
  <h2 id="balancing-the-business-with-the-employee-experience">Balancing the business with the employee experience</h2>
  <p>While continuity planning is about having both the right mindset and set of tools in place so the company can pivot broadly or selectively in response to a crisis, HR managers must always walk the uncomfortable tightrope between employee advocacy and business strategy. At the same time, however, HR can’t and shouldn’t go it alone.</p>
  <p>Effective preparedness requires input and buy-in throughout the organization – from the CEO to legal to finance to health and safety. HR should take the lead, but the best-prepared companies bring all the aforementioned functions to the table to plan and act accordingly so no one person – not even the CHRO – is making critical decisions in a vacuum. This approach not only puts the company in a better place for crises on the horizon, it underscores the unique role that HR plays in caring for employees while simultaneously honoring a commitment to ensure business continuity. Making accessible, intuitive technology a part of those plans only strengthens the understanding of HR’s mandate up and down the organization.</p>
  <p>It shouldn’t take a once-in-a-generation earthquake or pandemic for everyone in the company to understand that. But if best practices are followed when developing continuity plans, a company’s preparedness will ensure business agility and resiliency in the short and long terms.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-sap-successfactors-hxm-suite">Explore SAP SuccessFactors HXM Suite</h3>
        <p>Access resources to help you manage your business in times of crisis.</p>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/solutions.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <h4 id="read-more-in-this-series">Read more in this series</h4>
  <div class="collection">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="explainer">Explainer</h6>
        <p><a href="/resources/contingency-planning">What Is Contingency Planning? How Emergency Preparedness Can Save Your Business</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="business-case">Business Case</h6>
        <p><a href="/resources/contingency-continuity-planning-best-practices">Contingency and Business Continuity Planning Best Practices – Beyond Templates and Checklists</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>sidebar</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>