<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/leadership/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Take Small Steps and Create Big Impact Through Volunteering]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/small-steps-big-impact-volunteering-maggie-ramaiah</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/small-steps-big-impact-volunteering-maggie-ramaiah</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Enabling others to make their mark creates lasting impact. SAP employee Maggie Ramaiah integrates CSR activities to build that mindset.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/leadership</category>
            <category>news-tag/pro-bono-for-economic-equity</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-employee-profile</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Four Essential Leadership Qualities for Modern Times]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/four-essential-leadership-qualities-for-modern-times</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/four-essential-leadership-qualities-for-modern-times</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In this new age of work, leaders need to adapt their leadership strategies if they are to continue to engage and inspire their teams.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11fc60b50473239cda925a21876f7cc901f507e86.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11fc60b50473239cda925a21876f7cc901f507e86.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11fc60b50473239cda925a21876f7cc901f507e86.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Four Essential Leadership Qualities for Modern Times" src="./media_11fc60b50473239cda925a21876f7cc901f507e86.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="four-essential-leadership-qualities-for-modern-times">Four Essential Leadership Qualities for Modern Times</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Steve Jobs, Satya Nadella, Bill Gates. What do these three people have in common? Of course, they have all made their mark on the technology world, but they are also exceptional leaders. All three possess a clear vision, demonstrate the courage required to realize that vision, and display integrity, honesty, and humility even in the most challenging times.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As someone operating in a leadership position, I often look to these three for inspiration. Leading teams can be complex in our digital age, where remote working is commonplace and seldom do you get the opportunity to sit with colleagues or clients face-to-face.</p>
  <p>There’s no doubt that in this new age of work, leaders need to adapt their strategies if they are to continue to engage their teams and inspire high performance. Taking some of the lessons I have learned from other leaders, I wanted to outline four vital qualities leaders need to succeed in modern times.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="simplify-digital-transformation-with-sap-services-and-support">Simplify digital transformation with SAP Services and Support</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/support.html#services-support-offerings">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="authenticity">Authenticity</h2>
  <p>All the leaders I mentioned have one thing in common: their credibility. I believe it’s essential to start from a place of authenticity. How you manage people should sit comfortably with who you are. For less experienced leaders especially, who may still be growing in confidence, don’t attempt to be someone you are not. Not only will this be difficult to maintain, but it could also be transparent to others.</p>
  <p>Authenticity is vital for another reason. Like your team, you will have tough days, you may feel exposed, and you will wish you had approached certain things differently. These things are what make us human. It may seem counterintuitive, but acknowledging our weaknesses takes strength and often earns more respect.</p>
  <p>And it’s in times of adversity and through shared experiences that we can connect more deeply with our teams. Humor is also an excellent coping mechanism and a way to forge bonds.</p>
  <h2 id="approachability">Approachability</h2>
  <p>Influential leaders are like magnets and draw people to them. Some tough and powerful personalities may be revered but, conversely, can also be feared. This fear can become a barrier that could inhibit your people from being open about their mistakes or seeking your advice. If you want to build a reputation for openness, greet everyone, make time to chat – even if virtually – and give them your full attention. And this applies to people you don’t work with directly, including catering and cleaning staff. Why? Because it says that everyone matters to you.</p>
  <h2 id="innovation">Innovation</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="leading-large-what-the-marketplace-wants-from-leaders-today">Leading Large: What the Marketplace Wants from Leaders Today</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://insights.sap.com/social-responsibility-of-business/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Innovation starts with having a vision, possessing an adaptive mindset, and being purpose-driven. It also demands collaborative leadership behavior to enable the exploration of ideas. Good leaders create and empower interdisciplinary teams and foster a culture of agile learning.</p>
  <p>Also, creating a culture where everyone feels their contributions and ideas are valued and welcomed helps innovation. Often, some of the quietest or most introverted people have the most brilliant ideas. Unless they are encouraged and empowered to speak up, their contributions will be lost.</p>
  <h2 id="empathy">Empathy</h2>
  <p>Empathy calls for compassion in communication and being an engaged and active listener. According to research referenced by <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/tracybrower/2021/09/19/empathy-is-the-most-important-leadership-skill-according-to-research">Forbes</a>, empathy is a critical leadership skill. It’s necessary because people are experiencing multiple layers of stress, including the impact of <a href="/covid-19">the pandemic</a>. And when people are stressed, research also shows they find it harder to concentrate, take longer to finish tasks, and can compromise their physical and mental health.</p>
  <p>How can you lead with empathy? You will be more successful when you not only consider how others might be feeling but when you reach out to them personally. For example, a simple inquiry <a href="/2021/03/mental-health-in-the-workplace">can go a long way</a>: “I’ve noticed you’ve not been yourself lately, is there anything you would like to talk about or that I can do to help?” You don’t need to be an expert in mental health – just pay attention and take your cues from your team members on how best to respond.</p>
  <p>Creating opportunities for people to feel heard and understood makes a tremendous difference. But of course, strong leadership requires action too, and how this plays out will depend on the circumstances. At SAP, we believe a healthy business starts with healthy people. We promote a caring culture where our employees can stay healthy and balanced in a highly competitive environment. SAP’s <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/purpose/mental-health.html">global health and well-being programs</a> are integral to our investment in our people.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Guido Schlief is senior vice president and head of Services for Middle &#x26; Eastern Europe at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/leadership</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Challenge for Leaders: Embracing Educational Diversity]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/embracing-educational-diversity</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/embracing-educational-diversity</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[People learn through different ways and experiences. Embracing educational diversity could mean finding your next top performer.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1db0ab4e5c57b8b4968862a58fe2bd6ba46346c13.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1db0ab4e5c57b8b4968862a58fe2bd6ba46346c13.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1db0ab4e5c57b8b4968862a58fe2bd6ba46346c13.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="A Challenge for Leaders: Embracing Educational Diversity" src="./media_1db0ab4e5c57b8b4968862a58fe2bd6ba46346c13.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="a-challenge-for-leaders-embracing-educational-diversity">A Challenge for Leaders: Embracing Educational Diversity</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learning-for-life-get-the-right-skills-to-thrive-with-meaningful-work-in-a-digital-world">Learning for Life: Get the right skills to thrive with meaningful work in a digital world</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability/education.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>I thought about how I’d write this article for a very long time, but I recently realized that it was time to stop over-analyzing and share my story, in the hopes that it would inspire others. The feedback I got when I shared my non-traditional educational background on LinkedIn was incredible. The support has motivated me to continue the dialogue and challenge my fellow leaders to reconsider how they view candidates with unique backgrounds.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>I don’t have a college degree.</strong> There, I said it. And you know what? That statement does not define me or limit me. It’s a fact, a part of my background, and is likely one of the reasons I’ve had the career I’ve had.</p>
  <p>Do I regret not finishing my degree? I do wish I had the life experience of college, the knowledge I would have gained, and the relationships I would have built. But I also know without a doubt that I would not be who I am today if I had gone down the path of a traditional education. Who knows, I may have accomplished “more.” But I have a husband and three daughters that I love, I have a job that I find tremendously fulfilling, and I’ve had the fortune to meet amazing people and travel to fantastic places.</p>
  <p>My career provided me the opportunity to stay home for seven years when my children were small. I now have the honor to lead and mentor others, and I hope to inspire and challenge them to achieve their own success. For me, that exceeds every expectation I had for my future when I entered — and re-entered — the workforce.</p>
  <p>The reality is, I’m in good company — many successful people did not finish college — but I’ve also been incredibly fortunate. Fortunate to have had people who took the time to look past my lack of a formal education, to get to know me and understand the skills, passion, and drive I bring to what I do. Those early leaders, mentors, and sponsors took a chance on me and supported my career growth. They saw my potential and opened doors that lead to a journey I would never have imagined. I’m beyond thankful for each of them and I am incredibly passionate about supporting and leading others as they grow and develop along their unique career paths.</p>
  <p>People learn through different ways and experiences. College is one way, but life and career experiences are tremendously valuable as well. For me, the lack of a formal education has made me more driven, more determined to create my own success, and very intentional when it comes to my personal development. In today’s world of rapid innovation and a tremendously competitive talent market, we all need to be lifelong learners, regardless of our educational background.</p>
  <p>If <a href="/covid-19">2020 taught us anything</a>, it’s that we need to be prepared to pivot, learn new skills, and adapt to ever changing circumstances. These and many other critical job skills, such as grit, empathy, and emotional intelligence, are not easily taught in a classroom, they are innate skills that are further developed through experience. These skills aren’t measured by a piece of paper or apparent on a resume or job application; they are evaluated through human-to-human interaction.</p>
  <p>Diversity comes in many forms, and educational diversity is one of those, one that isn’t often talked about or considered.</p>
  <p>With that, I challenge my fellow leaders to invest their time with someone from a non-traditional background. Get to know the person behind that resume or LinkedIn profile. You may find that they are a perfect for your team, you may not. Regardless, give them the gift of your time by providing feedback and, if appropriate, through mentorship. Help them network or find a role that is right for them. Take a chance, because you may find your next top performer hiding in places you never would have considered.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/katiemevis/">Katie Mevis</a> is head of North America High Growth at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-beyond-bias</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/leadership</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>