<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-certification/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Powering Business Transformation with Unprecedented Career Growth for SAP Professionals]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/powering-unprecedented-career-growth-sap-professionals</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/powering-unprecedented-career-growth-sap-professionals</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We all are facing a changing work environment. Read to learn how SAP Learning supports the career growth of SAP professionals.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Starts Pilot with Accenture and IBM to Co-Validate SAP Expertise for Advanced Professionals]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/accenture-ibm-pilot-co-validate-sap-expertise</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/accenture-ibm-pilot-co-validate-sap-expertise</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A new pilot to co-validate SAP expertise, with first partners Accenture and IBM, is paving the way for career growth and business success.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>news-tag/ibm</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-partner-connect</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Women Can Be the Key to Solving the Global Skills Gap in Tech]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/women-key-to-global-digital-skills-gap-in-tech</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/women-key-to-global-digital-skills-gap-in-tech</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The global lack of digitally skilled workers is increasing in the tech industry. Learn about SAP's initiative and how women are key.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/coursera</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills-gap</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-community</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The SAP Partner Enablement Journey: Why SAP Partners Invest in Getting Certified]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-partners-invest-in-certifications</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-partners-invest-in-certifications</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Through SAP Certifications, SAP partners are better prepared to lead true business transformation with SAP Business Technology Platform.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_129d3bf60136cb2f67f5f6bed2adc45a4c2fdfeeb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_129d3bf60136cb2f67f5f6bed2adc45a4c2fdfeeb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_129d3bf60136cb2f67f5f6bed2adc45a4c2fdfeeb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The SAP Partner Enablement Journey: Why SAP Partners Invest in Getting Certified" src="./media_129d3bf60136cb2f67f5f6bed2adc45a4c2fdfeeb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-sap-partner-enablement-journey-why-sap-partners-invest-in-getting-certified">The SAP Partner Enablement Journey: Why SAP Partners Invest in Getting Certified</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Business leaders typically spend considerable time and effort before investing in the services of a software provider or partner to help ensure they acquire the service quality and performance they need. Certification quickly conveys that proof of competency since such technical accreditation is considered a direct stamp of approval.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Acquiring new customers is one thing; retaining them is another. In both cases, continuously attaining the latest certifications – from trending topics to specialized capabilities – reassures customers and inspires them to make that first contact and keep coming back. Compared to their noncertified counterparts, certified consultants speed implementation times by up to 15% and deliver projects with less rework and higher customer satisfaction, according to <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/08/c00f44c1-f27d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">IDC</a>.</p>
  <p>Another advantage of certification is the potential to attract, develop, and retain the strong talent pool that customers expect. <a href="https://home.pearsonvue.com/voc">Pearson VUE’s global survey</a> of more than 10,000 IT professionals indicated that the value of IT certification surpasses that of training alone. Benefits include a culture that promotes confidence in abilities, greater job satisfaction, increased respect among peers, more work autonomy and independence, promotion and advancement, and higher salary and wages.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-btp-accelerate-business-outcomes-with-integration-data-to-value-and-extensibility">SAP BTP: Accelerate business outcomes with integration, data to value, and extensibility</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="a-competency-framework-for-competitive-certification">A Competency Framework for Competitive Certification</h2>
  <p>When working with SAP, partners have the added benefit of fast access to the learning content needed to prepare for and attain certification. They are also rewarded with a visual badge that can be included in their marketing materials and on their Web sites.</p>
  <p>In addition, through the recently announced <a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/partnership/manage/competency.html">Competency Framework</a>, SAP partners can achieve competencies and specializations by certifying a required number of their consultants and developers, enabling them to reach essential, advanced, or expert competency tiers. These competencies and corresponding specializations are then visible on <a href="https://www.sap.com/partner/find.html">SAP Partner Finder</a> to help prospective customers make informed partner selections based on the desired solution expertise.</p>
  <p>SAP provides a broad set of certifications so partners can build specific skill sets and offer highly specialized consulting and implementation services. More than <a href="https://training.sap.com/certification/validity">100 certifications</a> cover a wide range of expertise and skill levels across an expansive set of SAP solutions and services. In fact, <a href="https://groups.community.sap.com/t5/sap-business-technology-platform/sap-certifications-for-business-technology-platform-you-bet/ba-p/2032">eight dedicated certifications</a> are available for <a href="/topics/business-technology-platform">SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP)</a>, including SAP Integration Suite, SAP Extension Suite, the SAP HANA Cloud database, the SAP Analytics Cloud solution, and low-code and no-code development applications and automations.</p>
  <p>Partners can promote their certifications by using <a href="https://training.sap.com/content/certification-verification">SAP Certification digital badges</a>. This real-time verification demonstrates that the partner’s certification is valid and contains a description of the SAP-backed expertise.</p>
  <p>Learning content for certification exams for SAP BTP is available free of charge on the <a href="https://learning.sap.com/">SAP Learning</a> site. And as SAP technologies, such as SAP BTP, continue to evolve and bring new capabilities, partners can keep skills current with <a href="https://learning.sap.com/ready-to-get-certified">certification training and exams</a> continuously updated for every cloud release from SAP.</p>
  <p>SAP partners can also attend <a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/library/news/products/tech_platform/btp/certification_academies.html">partner certification academies</a> for SAP BTP. The academies are online, interactive trainings delivered by SAP experts who guide you through the content of selected learnings for SAP BTP and help prepare partners to pass the associated certification exams. After completing an academy and passing the related certification, partners are equipped with the skills, knowledge, and tools needed to efficiently implement future projects on SAP BTP.</p>
  <h2 id="proven-proficiency-drives-true-transformation">Proven Proficiency Drives True Transformation</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="build-extend-integrate-and-market-solutions-as-an-sap-partner">Build, extend, integrate, and market solutions as an SAP partner</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/partner/become/partneredge-build.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Technology is advancing exponentially. This reality requires people of all experience levels to grow their knowledge and take stock of how these new skills might be applied to improve productivity and efficiency, resolve existing challenges, and produce transformative outcomes.</p>
  <p>The more we share and grow our knowledge of technologies, tools, and platforms, the more significant the impact of innovation and the faster we can achieve our goals. But most importantly, our partners are well-positioned to drive future growth, better experiences, and more sustainable and profitable outcomes.</p>
  <p>With <a href="https://learning.sap.com/certification">SAP Certification</a>, our partners have the power to innovate with SAP BTP, among other SAP technologies, in ways that lead to true business transformation with unparalleled skill, confidence, and trust.</p>
  <p>If you have not done so already, please join us on the journey with SAP BTP, attend the partner certification academies, and get certified today! You can also engage with your peers through <a href="https://groups.community.sap.com/t5/sap-business-technology-platform/gh-p/SAP-BTP">the partner community for SAP BTP</a> (login required). We look forward to driving successful business outcomes together.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/library/education/partnership/licenses/e_ep_td_payg.html">Access to SAP BTP, including free tier services</a> (available to SAP partners only)</li>
    <li><a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/library/assets/products/tech_plat/dgl/33/96/SAP813396.html">Enablement path for SAP BTP</a> (available to SAP partners only)</li>
    <li><a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/library/assets/products/tech_plat/dgl/36/25/SAP813625.html">Top 10 SAP BTP partner enablement resources</a> (available to SAP partners only)</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/partner/become/partneredge-build.html">Software partnership opportunities through SAP PartnerEdge – Build</a></li>
    <li><a href="https://learning.sap.com/learning-journey">SAP Learning Journey guides, including certifications</a></li>
    <li><a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/library/news/products/tech_platform/btp/certification_academies.html">Partner certification academies for SAP BTP</a> (available to SAP partners only)</li>
    <li><a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/partnership/manage/competency.html">The Competency Framework</a></li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Pavel Penaz is global head of Partner Solution Adoption Strategy and Execution for SAP Business Technology Platform at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge-build</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Creating Opportunity through Learning: Growing a Tech Workforce through Targeted Training]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/creating-opportunity-through-learning-tech-workforce</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/creating-opportunity-through-learning-tech-workforce</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is creating opportunity through learning with new student offerings aimed to help upskill in a world where talent is in constant flux.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/low-code-no-code</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preparing Partners for Their Future with SAP Learning]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/preparing-partners-for-their-future-with-sap-learning</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/preparing-partners-for-their-future-with-sap-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read to learn how the SAP Learning organization supports the partner ecosystem through offering accessible upskilling opportunities.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1571d8c395f68455a08d2131f47a138e448c6652f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1571d8c395f68455a08d2131f47a138e448c6652f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1571d8c395f68455a08d2131f47a138e448c6652f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Preparing Partners for Their Future with SAP Learning" src="./media_1571d8c395f68455a08d2131f47a138e448c6652f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="preparing-partners-for-their-future-with-sap-learning">Preparing Partners for Their Future with SAP Learning</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>These days, it can be so easy to get bogged down in the day-to-day and lose sight over our big-picture career goals. Where do we want to be five years from now? What kind of skills do we want to have a year from today?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While professionals may know they want to advance, they underestimate how much <a href="https://insights.sap.com/importance-upskilling/">upskilling</a>, learning, and certification can help them along that path. A recent <a href="https://home.pearsonvue.com/About/News/2021/Value-of-IT-Certification-study-highlights-benefit.aspx">study</a> underscored the value of certification in career advancement, as more than 60% of participants garnered promotions following their IT certifications. Moreover, this study found intrinsic benefits to certification, including greater confidence, determination for professional success, autonomy, and job satisfaction.</p>
  <p>And it’s true: the more we invest in ourselves – by taking the time and energy to complete certifications and stay current on the latest technologies – the better we feel about the trajectory of our careers.</p>
  <p>As the SAP Learning team helps to expand the SAP ecosystem, which is <a href="/wp-content/blogs.dir/1/files/SAP_IG_US46867020.pdf">estimated</a> to grow the number of professionals by 60% and see partner opportunities reach $260 billion by 2024, we’ve kept this sentiment at the forefront of our commitment to creating easily discoverable and accessible upskilling opportunities for partners.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-sap-learning-hub-partner-edition">Explore SAP Learning Hub, Partner Edition</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/01/c4135f45-c97d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="expanding-opportunities-for-growth-among-partners-and-individual-learners">Expanding Opportunities for Growth among Partners and Individual Learners</h2>
  <p>Along the journey to the Intelligent Enterprise, it’s critical for organizations to upskill their workforce, not only to stay competitive but to foster professional development at the individual level. SAP has long supported learning and enablement throughout the ecosystem, and with the rapid speed of innovations today, we’re providing more and more affordable, role-based learning solutions.</p>
  <p>For example, in February, we launched a new <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/01/04065f45-c97d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">learning offering specifically designed for partners</a> to advance continuous learning across the entire SAP portfolio and help partners stay up-to-date with SAP solutions. Developed with the SAP partner organization, it is designed to fit our partner’s specific business and learning needs. Since launch, it has been successfully adopted by the SAP partner ecosystem, with 30% net-new partners reached in the first six months of being live and thousands of learners currently using the offering to increase their knowledge and skills on SAP solutions and achieve certification.</p>
  <p>What’s more, for the SAP PartnerEdge program, we recently launched a private cloud version of <a href="https://www.sapstore.com/solutions/61162/SAP-Learning-Hub---Partner-Edition">SAP Learning Hub, partner edition</a> to help with increased customization and reporting functionalities.* With this <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/01/c4135f45-c97d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">private cloud version</a>, various roles in a partner organization can benefit from specific options: learners can upskill in a more private environment with company-specific learning content, while administrators can better monitor learning activities and understand the value derived from the solution.</p>
  <h2 id="yielding-success-through-certification">Yielding Success through Certification</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-how-partner-opportunity-expands-as-the-sap-ecosystem-transforms">Read: How Partner Opportunity Expands as the SAP Ecosystem Transforms</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/wp-content/blogs.dir/1/files/SAP_IG_US46867020.pdf">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In addition to creating content to continuously build and maintain SAP skills, <a href="https://learning.sap.com/">SAP Learning</a> emphasizes validation of these skills through certification. As Nagesh Polu, SAP SuccessFactors lead consultant, YASH Technologies, noted, “<a href="https://learning.sap.com/certification">SAP Certification</a> is an important benchmark of expertise. It helps you gain key SAP knowledge and the confidence of your customers. It is a huge asset for any SAP partner.”</p>
  <p>A recent <a href="https://itcertcouncil.org/the-value-of-certification/">whitepaper</a> revealed several proven benefits of certification, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Fifty-nine percent of respondents agreed certifications improved implementation of technology.</li>
    <li>More than 71% of respondents agreed or strongly agreed it has increased their ability to solve problems.</li>
    <li>Ninety-four percent of IT decision-makers globally felt that having team members with certification provides value beyond the cost of achieving the certification.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Reflecting on her certification experience, SAP Analyst Stefania Pabon said, “Without a doubt, SAP Certification has brought me a wide range of possibilities in the job market because it is generally a requirement to have SAP software knowledge.” SAP Senior Analyst Abhishek Paul echoed this view: “SAP Certification opened up a massive sea of opportunities for me. It brings a certain level of respect and is an excellent step toward securing my future.”</p>
  <p>As we make our way through the final quarter of the year and look ahead towards 2022, let’s embrace the learning opportunities in front of us for both our organizations and our own individual growth.</p>
  <p>*The private cloud version is available exclusively for SAP PartnerEdge members (excluding basic SAP PartnerEdge open ecosystem) and requires a minimum subscription of 100 users.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Jan Meyer is senior vice president and head of Learning Systems for SAP Learning.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP ICC Celebrates 25 Years of Partner Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/sap-icc-celebrates-25-years-of-partner-success</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/sap-icc-celebrates-25-years-of-partner-success</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For 25 years, SAP customers have placed their trust in SAP ICC and SAP-certified statuses when selecting high-quality partner solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10719adb01d3c8025c6952d413fbd7b8b28c30c60.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10719adb01d3c8025c6952d413fbd7b8b28c30c60.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10719adb01d3c8025c6952d413fbd7b8b28c30c60.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP ICC Celebrates 25 Years of Partner Success" src="./media_10719adb01d3c8025c6952d413fbd7b8b28c30c60.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-icc-celebrates-25-years-of-partner-success">SAP ICC Celebrates 25 Years of Partner Success</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In the competitive marketplace of enterprise technology, one designation stands above all others for having earned the trust of SAP customers seeking high quality partner solutions that successfully integrate into their SAP environments: SAP-certified status.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With more than 14,000 certifications performed, <a href="https://www.sap.com/partner/certify-my-solution/software.html">SAP Integration and Certification Center (SAP ICC)</a> is celebrating 25 years of supporting SAP partners in their mission to deliver customer success across every solution category, industry, and geography. Since the first SAP ICC locations went live in Walldorf and Palo Alto in 1996, more than 4,000 partners and independent software vendors (ISVs) worldwide have relied on SAP ICC services to help ensure the technical integration and interface of their solution with SAP.</p>
  <p>“For 25 years, the SAP Integration and Certification Center has laid the foundation for a trusted relationship between SAP, partners, and customers by certifying a high quality ecosystem of partner solutions that integrate with the latest SAP technology,” says Karl Fahrbach, chief partner officer, SAP.</p>
  <p>“As a standard-bearer for partner innovation, SAP ICC is at the forefront of partner success, supporting SAP’s strategy toward partner profitability and providing agility to customers as they become best-run businesses,” Fahrbach says. “We congratulate SAP ICC and Partner Innovation Lifecycle Services on this remarkable milestone and applaud the dedication of the SAP ICC team who remind us that at SAP partner success is customer success.”</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bf809395d29b1ac982fd43959f2360d15d707d55.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bf809395d29b1ac982fd43959f2360d15d707d55.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1bf809395d29b1ac982fd43959f2360d15d707d55.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP ICC celebrates 25 years of enabling partner ecosystem innovation" src="./media_1bf809395d29b1ac982fd43959f2360d15d707d55.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VFz_eCzVNvk">SAP ICC celebrates 25 years of enabling partner ecosystem innovation</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="achieving-milestones-at-the-pace-of-innovation">Achieving Milestones at the Pace of Innovation</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="build-extend-integrate-and-market-solutions-with-sap">Build, extend, integrate, and market solutions with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/partner/become/partneredge-build.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As the SAP solution portfolio has evolved over the years, SAP ICC has kept pace with innovation by rolling out the most significant certifications on time to meet market demands for the latest technologies. In 1999, SAP ICC pioneered the first cloud-based SAP ERP test system. Shortly thereafter, the SAP ICC team provided the first ABAP add-on certification in 2001, followed by a solution manager ready certification in 2007, mobile device certification in 2009, and the SAP Certified powered by SAP HANA status in 2013 – along with many others – leading up to today’s focus on partner integrations with SAP S/4HANA and partner extensions based on SAP Business Technology Platform. Each successive designation demonstrates SAP’s ongoing commitment to helping customers reduce implementation effort, accelerate innovation, and gain agility through best-of-breed partner solutions that successfully integrate into SAP.</p>
  <p>“It takes a great team to consistently deliver success for 25 long years,” says Nandagopal Prasad B, senior vice president and head of <a href="https://www.sap.com/partner/certify-my-solution.html">Partner Innovation Lifecycle Services</a>, which oversees SAP ICC in its portfolio of services, including partner co-innovation services, that enable partners to develop innovative solutions on SAP platforms and products.</p>
  <p>As the SAP ICC team has grown, it has closed the distance to customer markets not only technologically, but geographically as well by opening new locations around the world to support partners in their regions. SAP ICC is now active in 11 locations: Australia, Canada, China, CIS, Germany, India, Japan, Korea, Latin America, the Middle East, and the United States.</p>
  <p>For SAP partners that have worked with the team over the years to bring new solutions to market, the 25-year anniversary of SAP ICC is a milestone marking a close working relationship of many years. “It has been a great experience working with SAP ICC colleagues,” says Samiullah Sheik, founder and managing director, Bizadept Consulting GmbH. “We worked with SAP ICC for both our product certifications, and information was provided upfront to reduce delays. SAP ICC colleagues also responded quickly whenever we faced problems during the packaging of the product. These experiences have given us more confidence to consider the possibility of going down the co-innovation path with SAP for design and development of complex products in the coming years.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WvB5kqY2ZPo">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WvB5kqY2ZPo</a></p>
  <p>Axel Janz, global head of SAP Products and Innovations at EY, was one of the first members of the former complementary SAP Software Solution PartnerEdge program team, the predecessor of the SAP ICC, and with SAP Labs Tokyo 25 years ago. “With the SAP ICC, the EY organization has found a highly trustful, super responsive, and top-level guiding collaborator, supporting us on our integration and extension needs, accompanied by highly efficient SAP Certification processes,” he says.</p>
  <h2 id="why-partners-benefit-with-sap-certification">Why Partners Benefit with SAP Certification</h2>
  <p>Partners can gain significant benefits from having SAP-certified status, but the most compelling reason is the improved profitability that can come from lowering integration costs, accelerating go-to-market, and shortening implementation times. Once their solution has SAP-certified status, partners can place it in SAP Store to be discovered by customers alongside SAP solutions. Membership in <a href="https://www.sap.com/partner/become/partneredge-build.html">SAP PartnerEdge</a> allows partners to gain additional benefits from the program’s resources and enablement tools to help enhance partner success and profitability.</p>
  <p>To earn SAP-certified statuses, partners submit their solutions to SAP ICC for stringent qualification procedures to check that the solution uses SAP-recommended integration technologies and stable interfaces. The entire process is carried out online. While the requirements vary, the certification focuses primarily on the quality of the technical integration of the partner solution with SAP, including the smooth flow of business data through SAP. Partners are allowed access to SAP test systems as well as essential enablement and consulting services. The certification is valid for three years in most on-premise scenarios and one year in cloud integration scenarios.</p>
  <p>SAP ICC plans to celebrate its 25<sup>th</sup> anniversary with a series of regional <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/08/25/partner-meet-up-virtual-edition-25-years/">virtual partner meetups</a>, promotions via SAP social channels, and additional activities.</p>
  <p><a href="https://youtu.be/VgL_B2RAqYk">https://youtu.be/VgL_B2RAqYk</a></p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/csd">Visit the SAP-certified solutions directory</a> for a complete listing of all SAP-certified solutions, <a href="https://xs01a3cae2a65.hana.ondemand.com/sap/App/AppForm/index.html">apply for an SAP Certification</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/partner/certify-my-solution.html">learn how the Partner Innovation Lifecycle Services group at SAP helps partners</a> develop innovative solutions on SAP platforms and products to enable customer success.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Getting Ahead of the Skills Curve]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/getting-ahead-skills-curve</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/getting-ahead-skills-curve</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Businesses can get ahead of the skills curve by aligning strategic workforce planning and business strategy. Read to learn more!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be3fe31204da0bc2c881ee5a27f5a8d1f0bd6231.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be3fe31204da0bc2c881ee5a27f5a8d1f0bd6231.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1be3fe31204da0bc2c881ee5a27f5a8d1f0bd6231.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Getting Ahead of the Skills Curve" src="./media_1be3fe31204da0bc2c881ee5a27f5a8d1f0bd6231.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="getting-ahead-of-the-skills-curve">Getting Ahead of the Skills Curve</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>What’s the uber skill? The ability to constantly learn, evolve, update, or even un-learn relevant skills. Today, training workforces to acquire that mindset of continuous learning is everything. We spoke with Stefan Haenisch, senior vice president of SAP Learning Strategic Initiatives at SAP, to dive deeper into his perspective, especially as he comes out of the World Economic Forum’s summer event, <a href="https://www.weforum.org/events/the-jobs-reset-summit-2021">The Jobs Reset Summit</a>, and recently published an <a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2021/05/back-to-school-4-lessons-in-workforce-skilling/">article</a> for WEF about the critical lessons in workforce skilling and lifelong learning.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-the-skills-you-need-anytime-anywhere-with-sap-learning-hub">Learn the skills you need anytime, anywhere with SAP Learning Hub</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://learninghub.sap.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="q-in-your-article-for-the-world-economic-forum-you-discuss-the-importance-of-connecting-business-strategy-to-workforce-skills-can-you-share-what-this-looks-like-and-why-its-so-essential">Q: In your article for the World Economic Forum, you discuss the importance of connecting business strategy to workforce skills. Can you share what this looks like and why it’s so essential?</h3>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> Every company plots out its business strategy. But how often does it think about how this relates and aligns with its people strategy and strategic workforce planning and skill building?</p>
  <p>For example, if our strategy is to use <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-artificial-intelligence/">artificial intelligence (AI)</a> to make our products smarter, we must simultaneously be asking ourselves how we can <a href="https://insights.sap.com/importance-upskilling/">upskill the workforce</a> on the required skills to drive this vision.</p>
  <p>Skill training shouldn’t be an afterthought. Instead, by connecting skills and strategy from the very beginning, companies can proactively adapt and more effectively position themselves for long-term success.</p>
  <h3 id="how-does-an-organization-develop-skills-for-the-future-when-things-are-changing-so-frequently-and-we-cant-possibly-know-what-the-world-will-look-like-in-the-next-couple-of-years">How does an organization develop skills for the future when things are changing so frequently and we can’t possibly know what the world will look like in the next couple of years?</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="how-to-upskill-staff-from-strategy-to-practical-steps">How to Upskill Staff: From Strategy to Practical Steps</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://insights.sap.com/how-to-upskill-guide/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As we saw with <a href="http://news.sap.com/covid-19">the global pandemic</a>, things may go differently than predicted. Companies must embrace ambiguity and disruption when it comes to skills for the future. A recent article in the <a href="https://hbr.org/2020/01/the-transformer-clo">Harvard Business Review</a> noted, “If you focus on building individual micro skills, you may be missing the bigger picture.” Indeed, there are ‘expiration dates’ on technical skills as innovation emerges, so companies must establish a culture that encourages agility and experimentation in the workforce – and, not least, motivates continuous learning – in order to yield sustainable success. Soft skills like dealing with uncertainty, staying curious, as well as embracing and tolerating ambiguity are the foundation of employees being ready for the future. They can then quickly and continuously keep up the relevant hard skills.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/content/dam/Deloitte/global/Documents/HumanCapital/gx-the-future-of-work-post-covid-19-poc.pdf">A recent report from Deloitte</a> asserts that the <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-future-of-work/">future of work</a> in our technology-driven world is about “creating an environment where organizations can optimize human potential” and “empowering workers with agency and choice over what they do, unleashing their interests and passions.” What this means is that the ultimate skill is being able to continuously learn in a constantly changing business environment. Fostering agile, innovative mindsets and curiosity throughout the workforce – promoting not only the <em>need</em> to learn, but the <em>want</em> to learn – helps companies to think big and earn a competitive edge.</p>
  <h3 id="how-do-offerings-at-sap-help-support-strategic-workforce-planning-and-continuous-learning">How do offerings at SAP help support strategic workforce planning and continuous learning?</h3>
  <p>At SAP, we value ongoing learning as part of the foundation for success. In the fast-moving tech sector where skill demand changes faster than in other industries, we’re constantly evolving our learning offerings to support the hard and soft skills needed to help people stay competitive.</p>
  <p>Inside SAP, for example, we look at a long and successful track record in deploying skills management to effective resource management in our consulting business and are now evolving this to support dynamic and forward-looking workforce planning and development.</p>
  <p>Our customers can benefit from our experience as we are incorporating the best practices we learned in people and skills management into our SAP SuccessFactors solutions. When it comes to helping our customers and partners build and sustain SAP product skills, our digital learning offerings, <a href="https://open.sap.com/">openSAP</a> and <a href="https://learninghub.sap.com/">SAP Learning Hub</a>, work to provide easy-to-use, engaging content for learners to explore, build, and maintain relevant skills. Additionally, we help support career planning around the skills that learners are honing, working to provide the right learning journey targeted to each learner’s goals.</p>
  <p>Our mission is to create learning and development opportunity for all across the SAP ecosystem. We aim to empower everyone to successfully build SAP software skills using future-oriented content delivered in different formats to fit individual ways of learning. By better aligning strategic workforce planning and business strategy at the onset, as well as becoming laser-focused on a workplace culture that values agility and curiosity, businesses can get ahead of the skills curve.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Learning With SAP: What's New and What's to Come]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/learning-with-sap-new-to-come</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/learning-with-sap-new-to-come</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[What's new and next for learning with SAP? Chief Learning Officer Max Wessel discusses SAP's work to accelerate digital skills of the future.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>