<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/master-data-management/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Master Data Governance Named a Leader in 2023 Master Data Management Analyst Report]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/sap-master-data-governance-leader-forrester</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/sap-master-data-governance-leader-forrester</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Master Data Governance has been named a Leader in The Forrester Wave™: Master Data Management, Q2 2023 report. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/master-data-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-master-data-governance</category>
            <category>news-tag/the-forrester-wave</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unipol Digitizes Master Data Management with SAP Business Technology Platform]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/unipol-master-data-management-sap-btp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/unipol-master-data-management-sap-btp</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Italian company Unipol worked with SAP to establish a consistent and harmonized master data management strategy across all areas.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/master-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Master Data Governance Named a Leader in the Grid® Report for Master Data Management by Real Users on G2]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/g2-grid-report-sap-master-data-governance-a-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/g2-grid-report-sap-master-data-governance-a-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In G2's Fall 2022 Grid Report, SAP Master Data Governance was named a Leader for positive reviews in the Master Data Management category.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/master-data-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-master-data-governance</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in “Master Data Management” by Independent Research Firm]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/sap-a-leader-forrester-wave-master-data-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/sap-a-leader-forrester-wave-master-data-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been positioned as a Leader in The Forrester Wave: Master Data Management, Q4 2021. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cfc99e7852a08ae4b9ae0ca5ec80f8611ead6f3b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cfc99e7852a08ae4b9ae0ca5ec80f8611ead6f3b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1cfc99e7852a08ae4b9ae0ca5ec80f8611ead6f3b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named a Leader in “Master Data Management” by Independent Research Firm" src="./media_1cfc99e7852a08ae4b9ae0ca5ec80f8611ead6f3b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-a-leader-in-master-data-management-by-independent-research-firm">SAP Named a Leader in “Master Data Management” by Independent Research Firm</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-master-data-governance-improve-the-quality-and-consistency-of-information-across-your-organization">SAP Master Data Governance: Improve the quality and consistency of information across your organization</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/master-data-governance.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced it has been positioned as a Leader in “<a href="https://reprints2.forrester.com/#/assets/2/702/RES176577/report">The Forrester Wave™: Master Data Management, Q4 2021</a>.”</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Forrester Research Inc., a leading global research and advisory firm, researched, analyzed and scored 15 vendors and named SAP a Leader. The report analyzed the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/master-data-governance.html">SAP Master Data Governance</a> application and noted its “good multidomain MDM capabilities at scale” as well as its “prebuilt data models, business rules, workflows, and user interfaces to support MDM deployments.” The 24 scoring criteria employed by Forrester Research covered three categories: Current Offering, Strategy and Market Presence.</p>
  <p>The report states that SAP “supports a multidomain MDM solution for on-premises, private, and public cloud deployment with quality, stewardship, and governance capabilities” and “focuses on extending the cloud services, increasing automation and intelligence, and delivering more integrated data management solutions.”</p>
  <p>The Forrester report points out that “reference customers mainly had positive feedback on SAP [Master Data Governance],” with one customer pointing out, “SAP [Master Data Governance] implementation brought us greater government control and streamlined efficiency.”</p>
  <p>“In our digital economy, having correct, comprehensive and timely views of data is paramount to success,” said Dr. Andreas Doehrn, head of Master Data Management Engineering, SAP. “SAP Master Data Governance improves the quality and consistency of information by consolidating and centrally governing the master data lifecycle. We believe Forrester’s recognition of SAP as a Leader in this evaluation is testament to our robust data solutions and the benefit we bring to our customers.”</p>
  <p>As part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a>, SAP Master Data Governance allows businesses to create a single source of truth by uniting SAP and third-party data sources and mass processing additional bulk updates on large volumes of data. Customers can establish a cohesive and harmonized master data management strategy across domains to simplify enterprise data management, increase data accuracy and reduce total cost of ownership.</p>
  <p>To learn more about SAP’s ranking, <a href="https://reprints2.forrester.com/#/assets/2/702/RES176577/report">read the full report here</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong><br>Julia Fargel, +1 (650) 276-8964, <a href="mailto:julia.fargel@sap.com">julia.fargel@sap.com</a>, PT<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/master-data-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-master-data-governance</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[More Than Data: Why Master Data Management Is a Critical Part of Digital Readiness]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/more-than-data-why-master-data-management-is-a-critical-part-of-digital-readiness</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/more-than-data-why-master-data-management-is-a-critical-part-of-digital-readiness</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Businesses gain a more profound and innovative edge by using MDM to open the door to more accurate, consistent, and predictive analytics.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e404247fbc4fba1e35a30b19b3cdae22b36d3149.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e404247fbc4fba1e35a30b19b3cdae22b36d3149.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e404247fbc4fba1e35a30b19b3cdae22b36d3149.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="More Than Data: Why Master Data Management Is a Critical Part of Digital Readiness" src="./media_1e404247fbc4fba1e35a30b19b3cdae22b36d3149.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="more-than-data-why-master-data-management-is-a-critical-part-of-digital-readiness">More Than Data: Why Master Data Management Is a Critical Part of Digital Readiness</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Collecting, unifying, managing, integrating, and using data that is clean, consistent, and accessible have been the ultimate goals of master data management (MDM) for most organizations. However, these activities only mark the beginning of a much more revolutionary digital transformation story.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As B2B and B2C customers continue to shift more of their commerce transactions toward digital channels and engage in product-based digital services, the volume of master data is set to explode. <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=prUS47560321">IDC</a> predicts that the “amount of digital data created over the next five years will be greater than twice the amount of data created since the advent of digital storage.”</p>
  <p>This growing trend is not only an opportunity, but also a challenge to how master data is managed. While considered a preparatory step for transitioning to the latest technologies, such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a>, MDM can also lay the foundation for future application development and business innovation.</p>
  <h2 id="harmonizing-data-to-drive-meaningful-transformation">Harmonizing Data to Drive Meaningful Transformation</h2>
  <p>While the pressure to innovate groundbreaking, sustainable value for customers and the business increases, many SAP customers are solving unique challenges quickly with less cost and risk. The key to their success is <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/advisory-development/business-transformation.html">SAP Advisory Services</a>, enabling a methodical, forward-thinking MDM approach to fostering innovation, nurturing new ideas, and building strong solutions.</p>
  <p>By enhancing the quality of master data with the assistance of SAP Advisory Services, our customers are overcoming significant challenges that many companies face in their MDM practices, including the following.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="transform-your-company-into-an-intelligent-enterprise-with-sap-advisory-services">Transform your company into an intelligent enterprise with SAP Advisory Services</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services/advisory-development/business-transformation.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="turning-a-lack-of-commitment-into-a-shared-vision">1. Turning a Lack of Commitment into a Shared Vision</h3>
  <p>Executive sponsors do not always connect how the benefits of an IT strategy can advance the overall business strategy, especially quick wins in MDM projects. Unfortunately, this level of detachment among decision-makers undermines the efforts of any solution implementation.</p>
  <p>Consider an organization that purchased a solution license without setting aside the budget to support activities such as creating a master data team, staffing new roles, and setting up governance procedures. By not addressing errors made along the way and reconsidering the need for better MDM support, stakeholders likely feel frustrated once the project goes live because business needs were not met as expected. Worse yet, gaining the executive confidence and commitment needed for future projects become increasingly tricky as stakeholders feel their input will not make a difference in the outcome.</p>
  <p>SAP Advisory Services help alleviate the situation by framing and solving various business and IT challenges and relaying how improved MDM processes can help. The organization can start its journey toward solution implementation by cultivating the business’s collective genius in an unconventional and creative atmosphere. This is accomplished with pragmatic design thinking workshops, pilots, prototypes, road maps, digital working models, and organizational expertise and enablement.</p>
  <h3 id="strengthening-communication-between-it-and-the-business">2. Strengthening Communication Between IT and the Business</h3>
  <p>IT departments typically lead MDM projects. However, users may still refuse to participate in the early discussions because they cannot see how the effort can benefit their business function. Over time, this lack of awareness turns into a lack of desire to fulfill MDM responsibilities, leaving behind any chance of leveraging data as a way to expand the company’s capabilities and help fuel revenue growth.</p>
  <p>To overcome this bidirectional misunderstanding, SAP Advisory Services help ensure that IT pays attention to the immediate needs of the business users and establishes MDM processes that are efficient and simple to maintain. Furthermore, the convenient delivery of training and timely knowledge allows closer collaboration between IT and the business and a better understanding of how the MDM project impacts the specific organization and overall business.</p>
  <h3 id="establishing-governance-and-common-data-definitions">3. Establishing Governance and Common Data Definitions</h3>
  <p>When MDM tools and best practices are not implemented globally, individual organizations often feel compelled to act locally on their terms – limiting the visibility and consistency to make decisions at the corporate level. Meanwhile, users working with the same data sets have little idea of how they are being processed in other departments or whether decisions are based on the same understanding of what the data means.</p>
  <p>Companies that rely on SAP Advisory Services can employ universal governance of their master data processes at any point of their MDM project. Setting up a change management team and conducting an initial assessment early on improves organizational understanding of the level and magnitude of change needed to ensure MDM capabilities support the digital investment or transformation initiative. Plus, every user can access the proven knowledge, tools, and templates required to adapt and comply with data standards.</p>
  <h3 id="speeding-business-optimization-and-innovation">4. Speeding Business Optimization and Innovation</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="gain-more-insight-into-data-mangement">Gain more insight into data mangement</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-data-management/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Although complex in theory, MDM is emerging as a critical part of digital readiness as companies recognize its long-term value and involve the right people to establish the right best practices. Even a standard approach to MDM can drive innovation when the right data strategy is in place and IT objectives are aligned with business strategies.</p>
  <p>However, with SAP Advisory Services, businesses can gain a more profound edge by using MDM to open the door to more accurate and consistent analytics tools. Data sets become more predictive and multidimensional by combining master data with <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-machine-learning/">machine learning</a>, <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-artificial-intelligence/">artificial intelligence (AI)</a>, graphical visualization, and other intelligent technologies. Different views on similar domains support the demands of various business groups on context-dependent insights.</p>
  <h2 id="realizing-the-full-potential-of-mdm-advancements">Realizing the Full Potential of MDM Advancements</h2>
  <p>From the viewpoint of the business, MDM is valuable when cost reduction and closer cross-departmental collaboration are achieved. IT organizations can deliver on those expectations by implementing solutions successfully on the first attempt, harmonizing the way technologies and people work, and avoiding any misunderstandings along the way.</p>
  <p>SAP Advisory Services enable IT and non-IT organizations to maximize the potential of their digital transformation by creating a master data foundation that drives greater visibility, agility, and focus. The service portfolio establishes emerging technologies and draws on the latest innovations, industry experts, and ecosystem of innovators from SAP. And for the business, this means an opportunity to further optimize operations and initiate change – faster and with less risk.</p>
  <p><em>Stay in the conversation by following the SAP Services and Support offerings on</em> <em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/sapsupportinfo">YouTube</a></em>, <em><a href="https://twitter.com/SAPDigitalSvcs">Twitter</a>,</em> <em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/138840">LinkedIn</a>, and</em> <em><a href="https://www.facebook.com/SAPDigitalBusinessServices">Facebook</a></em>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Gelena Artemenko is a business enterprise consultant for CPG &#x26; Retail Industries at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/master-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advisory-services</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrate Your Business Processes Today: Free Trial of SAP Master Data Governance, Cloud Edition]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/sap-master-data-governance-cloud-edition-free-trial</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/sap-master-data-governance-cloud-edition-free-trial</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has launched a free trial of SAP Master Data Governance, cloud edition. Learn how to integrate your business processes today.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11c1a09d77bc27ef959b3cfad0e477c0dcb4bf7d2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11c1a09d77bc27ef959b3cfad0e477c0dcb4bf7d2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11c1a09d77bc27ef959b3cfad0e477c0dcb4bf7d2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Integrate Your Business Processes Today: Free Trial of SAP Master Data Governance, Cloud Edition" src="./media_11c1a09d77bc27ef959b3cfad0e477c0dcb4bf7d2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="integrate-your-business-processes-today-free-trial-of-sap-master-data-governance-cloud-edition">Integrate Your Business Processes Today: Free Trial of SAP Master Data Governance, Cloud Edition</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sign-up-for-a-free-trial-of-the-cloud-edition-today">Sign up for a free trial of the cloud edition today</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/td/sap-mdg-cloud-trial.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For companies that strive to become integrated, intelligent enterprises, it has never been more important to have access to trusted, high-quality master data—whether it be to optimize operations, to better understand and service customers, or to speed up innovations to the market.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Companies are increasingly looking for modular applications that can be composed into integrated business processes across many applications. And, of course, there is also the trend to increasingly consume these applications in the cloud. To support these new realities, master data management (MDM) also needs to follow these trends. As a result, we are evolving SAP Master Data Governance in this direction.</p>
  <p>We are happy to provide a new version: the cloud edition of the <a href="http://www.sap.com/mdg">SAP Master Data Governance</a> application. And today, we have <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/td/sap-mdg-cloud-trial.html">launched a free trial to give you a sneak peek</a>.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18539ee7e7f42a3d6114bd7d74442eb706b8f6d3a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18539ee7e7f42a3d6114bd7d74442eb706b8f6d3a.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_18539ee7e7f42a3d6114bd7d74442eb706b8f6d3a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Graphic: SAP Master Data Governance" src="./media_18539ee7e7f42a3d6114bd7d74442eb706b8f6d3a.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1035" height="913">
    </picture>We expect that many companies will use the cloud edition in addition to—not as a replacement of—SAP Master Data Governance on SAP S/4HANA in order to establish a federated approach to master data governance in their enterprises. Federated data governance is a new MDM paradigm and adaptive model that allows the enterprise to manage data exactly where it’s best understood to optimize MDM scope, benefits, and effort.
  </p>
  <p>We are convinced that, for many companies, this new modular approach will provide faster time to value, better total cost of ownership, and a broader reach of enterprise-wide master data management initiatives.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-more-about-master-data-management-on-sap-community">Explore more about master data management on SAP Community</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://community.sap.com/topics/master-data-governance">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Today, SAP Master Data Governance is typically used to centrally manage master data of a complete enterprise with just one single SAP Master Data Governance on SAP S/4HANA. The new federated deployment option for SAP Master Data Governance works to provide an approach to extend the value proposition in areas of your company that may have been difficult to include in your program.</p>
  <p>SAP Master Data Governance, cloud edition, will help provide a non-disruptive path toward more agile and flexible master data governance that will fully leverage all investments that you have already made in SAP Master Data Governance on SAP S/4HANA. And for companies that have not yet started their MDM journey, it will work to provide a quick start through an easy to consume software-as-a-service (SaaS) solution.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Markus Kuppe is vice president and chief product owner of SAP Master Data Governance at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/master-data-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-master-data-governance</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>