<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-enable-now/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Creating a Local Language Experience for Global Software Users]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/local-language-experience-sap-enable-now-users</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/local-language-experience-sap-enable-now-users</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Enable Now, cloud edition now includes access to Document Translation for SAP Translation Hub. Learn more about the integration.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-enable-now</category>
            <category>product/sap-translation-hub</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Enable Now: The Digital Adoption Platform Powering Intelligent Enterprises]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-enable-now-digital-adoption-platform-powering-intelligent-enterprises</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-enable-now-digital-adoption-platform-powering-intelligent-enterprises</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[End users must be prepared for digital adoption, which is where a digital adoption platform like SAP Enable Now comes into play.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>product/sap-enable-now</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rethinking Learning and Change Management with a Cloud Mindset]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/rethinking-learning-and-change-management-with-a-cloud-mindset</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/rethinking-learning-and-change-management-with-a-cloud-mindset</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With companies adopting a cloud mindset, needs and expectations for learning and change management shift. Read to find out how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-activate</category>
            <category>product/sap-enable-now</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Closing the Gaps with SAP Enable Now]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/closing-the-gaps-with-sap-enable-now</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/closing-the-gaps-with-sap-enable-now</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's Kristina Kunad explains how SAP Enable Now helps drive adoption and upskill your workforce. Read the interview to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>product/sap-enable-now</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[People Drive Success: RISE with SAP Inspires and Empowers Employees]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/people-drive-success-rise-with-sap-training</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/people-drive-success-rise-with-sap-training</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For a successful business transformation, put your people first with a holistic strategy for change management and training. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-enable-now</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Becoming an Intelligent, Sustainable Enterprise: Why Adoption Matters]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-enterprise-adoption-intelligent-sustainable</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-enterprise-adoption-intelligent-sustainable</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Enterprise Adoption helps customers to realize value and business outcomes when it comes to resiliency, performance, and sustainability.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11add9f2e42b8b9d1eaf36cacfd0a404142b1e4e9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11add9f2e42b8b9d1eaf36cacfd0a404142b1e4e9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11add9f2e42b8b9d1eaf36cacfd0a404142b1e4e9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Becoming an Intelligent, Sustainable Enterprise: Why Adoption Matters" src="./media_11add9f2e42b8b9d1eaf36cacfd0a404142b1e4e9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="becoming-an-intelligent-sustainable-enterprise-why-adoption-matters">Becoming an Intelligent, Sustainable Enterprise: Why Adoption Matters</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Digitalization intensifies and further accelerates as businesses around the globe try to outpace the challenges of supply chain shortages and constantly evolving government regulations.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As we continue to further develop and explore the needs and opportunities of the new normal, digitalization keeps expanding while the need for businesses to upskill their workforce must be addressed at the same time. Indeed, according to a <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/content/dam/Deloitte/us/Documents/about-deloitte/us-fortune-deloitte-CEO-survey-january-2021-highlights.pdf">2021 Deloitte survey</a>, 85% of CEOs said that the pandemic significantly accelerated digital transformation plans for their business.</p>
  <p>This digital transformation can only become a working reality particularly for businesses operating globally and locally when the implications of operating in a country and across countries are considered and taken into account. Businesses must be able to plan and act holistically wherever they operate. While state-of-the-art enterprise software and solutions are needed to make this happen, adoption significantly supports businesses to generate the full value from these products. It is the key to realizing desired business outcomes.</p>
  <p>SAP Enterprise Adoption helps customers to realize value and business outcomes in three key aspects: resiliency, performance, and sustainability. Those aspects mean something quite specific for successful businesses. Here’s why adoption matters.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-localization-by-product-and-region">Learn more about localization by product and region</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/product/globalization.html#section_703941363">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="resiliency">Resiliency</h2>
  <p>In this context, resiliency means getting the full benefit of SAP software by adapting to new situations or conditions easily and without disruption. For example, many different countries have enacted different regulations, not only during the COVID-19 pandemic. We are providing those legal changes to our customers, so they can stay focused on their business and compliant with any existing or new regulations. On the other hand, a company opening a subsidiary — for example, in Brazil — would need to feel confident that it could implement its existing software solution while adhering to governmental policies. Operating locally and globally is one aspect, digitalization of business and meeting requirements for e-reporting and e-invoicing the other.</p>
  <p>Here, SAP Document and Reporting Compliance enables companies to comply with local regulations for e-invoicing and e-reporting in a huge number of countries. The solution is fully harmonized across countries and delivers approximately 350 statutory reports and electronic document processing scenarios out of the box and is kept up to date whenever a legal change happens.</p>
  <p>This harmonized and standardized approach enables customers to easily for example build up a shared service center and implement new obligations in almost no time. It provides the customer peace of mind doing business in multiple countries, especially when exchanging documents with governments.</p>
  <h2 id="performance">Performance</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-enable-now-reduce-learning-curves-with-contextually-relevant-timely-and-proactive-enablement-content">SAP Enable Now: Reduce learning curves with contextually relevant, timely, and proactive enablement content</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/enable-now.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP Enterprise Adoption helps customers to increase business innovation and productivity through the rapid adoption and automation of processes for SAP products and solutions. The most successful companies achieving greater efficiencies are those that balance automation and user performance.</p>
  <p>For example, SAP implemented localization capabilities for tax frameworks for an <a href="https://dam.sap.com/mac/app/p/pdf/asset/preview/TfNtmwE?ltr=a">international food and beverage company</a>, leading to a more than 60% efficiency gain in its fiscal department, which runs more than 16,000 tax obligations per year for its 20 million invoice items.</p>
  <h2 id="sustainability">Sustainability</h2>
  <p>SAP Enterprise Adoption helps customers to optimize the use of resources through transparency on respective regulations as well as through empowered users providing key abilities required for sustained adoption of SAP solutions.</p>
  <p>For example, a <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2020/01/e46fc525-7f7d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">large utility company</a> needed more than 1,000 users to become productive at the moment of go-live with SAP S/4HANA. To drive adoption readiness, the company began with the training and upskilling of its workforce four months before go-live, enabling users with embedded contextual help as they completed daily tasks. In addition, the company created e-learning materials, reference guides, and work instructions.</p>
  <p>This enablement and upskilling lead to empowerment of the workforce, an increase of motivation, and employee retention.</p>
  <p><strong>Resiliency, performance,</strong> and <strong>sustainability</strong> are the key levers of your desired business outcomes and make up what I like to call“the “whole enchilada” — the realization of intelligent, sustainable enterprises as a working reality.</p>
  <p>Adoption helps make the digital transformation a success, which is why, as enterprises continue their digital journey, it is essential to aid with adoption and enablement throughout the lifespan of SAP products, despite whatever future opportunities enterprises may face.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Eva Zauke is senior vice president and global head of SAP Enterprise Adoption.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-enable-now</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Enterprise Adoption Speeds Up Digitalization for Business Resilience and Sustainability]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-enterprise-adoption-speeds-up-digitalization-for-business-resilience-and-sustainability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-enterprise-adoption-speeds-up-digitalization-for-business-resilience-and-sustainability</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP Enterprise Adoption, leading-edge organizations can digitally transform to meet local and global resilient, sustainable goals.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-enable-now</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-adoption</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Going Beyond Business Processes for Digital Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/going-beyond-business-processes-for-digital-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/going-beyond-business-processes-for-digital-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Focusing on adoption and moving beyond business processes to span the entire global footprint can make digital transformations successful.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f9bd0cf220ad690c178c3ad212dd2b66d65dc899.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f9bd0cf220ad690c178c3ad212dd2b66d65dc899.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f9bd0cf220ad690c178c3ad212dd2b66d65dc899.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Going Beyond Business Processes for Digital Transformation" src="./media_1f9bd0cf220ad690c178c3ad212dd2b66d65dc899.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="going-beyond-business-processes-for-digital-transformation">Going Beyond Business Processes for Digital Transformation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="go-global-with-sap-globalization-services">Go Global with SAP Globalization Services</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/product/globalization.html#section_703941363">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Many companies are currently in the middle of their digital transformation. The <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> pandemic has accelerated this process dramatically. Not only were existing regulatory requirements being updated at a quicker pace, a large number of new COVID-19-specific requirements were introduced. In addition, the rapid switch to remote work brought a greater demand for digitalized processes and an increase in the number of technologies available. Although this new normal can be challenging, it has also offered the opportunity to rethink existing processes and examine new business opportunities.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As companies continue their transformation to the Intelligent Enterprise, applying advanced technologies and best practices as part of integrated business processes, they can drive adoption and create business value by providing the skills needed to use these business processes and technologies effectively. This, in turn, can help accelerate digital transformation by helping employees work productively with these processes and technologies, under a new set of circumstances, sooner.</p>
  <p>Applying advanced technologies is only one aspect of digitalization. When a business implements or updates a software solution, it also needs to adapt its business processes to go along with it. As the pace of digitalization increases, it will also increase the pace at which new business processes and introduced and existing processes are updated.</p>
  <p>Business processes can vary depending on where a company is located. Multinational companies operating in several locations around the globe are faced with a diverse set of processes and procedures depending on local regulations. Every time there is an update from a governmental institution, processes need to be updated to stay compliant. And each time the processes are updated, employees need to adapt to them and adopt them to use them effectively.</p>
  <p>So, how can businesses at all stages in their digital transformation drive adoption and achieve critical business outcomes? How can adoption help businesses realize value from their investment decisions?</p>
  <p>One way is to implement software solutions that have built-in support for compliance with governmental regulations in all locations where a business operates. Businesses can use software to <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2020/02/2005c4c5-877d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">automate processes</a>, which can lead to efficiencies. These real-time, essential software solutions in localized versions and in local languages can offer peace of mind and contribute to an organization’s resiliency, performance, and sustainability.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="provide-the-knowledge-your-employees-need-to-succeed-with-sap-enable-now">Provide the knowledge your employees need to succeed with SAP Enable Now</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/enable-now.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Additionally, providing enablement for users and employees across a wide variety of channels and as part of SAP solutions, facilitated by digital adoption platforms such as SAP Enable Now, businesses can provide their employees with the most up-to-date software, technology, and process documentation when and where they need it – right in the flow of their work and in the language of their choice.</p>
  <p>During the COVID-19 pandemic especially, SAP customers and partners were able to use SAP Enable Now to support their digital transformations by enabling their users to embrace and apply the latest technologies. For example, a <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/01/30c90974-c97d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">professional services company rolled out SAP Enable Now during COVID-19</a> to help empower and cultivate a local workforce that was quickly able to adopt new technologies.</p>
  <p>SAP has a long history of helping companies digitally transform, even in today’s extremely challenging environment, and remains committed to helping companies achieve the most impactful business outcomes with flexible and integrated services and solutions.</p>
  <p>A digital transformation to an intelligent enterprise can help a business prepare to meet and overcome the challenges of today and tomorrow. By focusing on adoption throughout the digital transformation, a business can make the Intelligent Enterprise a working reality – moving beyond business processes to span the entire global footprint as well as its workforce – to make the digital transformation a success.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Eva Zauke is senior vice president and global head of SAP Enterprise Adoption.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>product/sap-enable-now</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adoption Is the Key to Get the Most Out of SAP Software]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/sap-enterprise-adoption-key-localization-success</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/sap-enterprise-adoption-key-localization-success</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Enterprise Adoption empowers customers to succeed by delivering an exceptional localization experience across SAP solutions. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19e8a95939116e6dba0a457d1b2c66a000a7dfa05.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19e8a95939116e6dba0a457d1b2c66a000a7dfa05.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19e8a95939116e6dba0a457d1b2c66a000a7dfa05.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Adoption Is the Key to Get the Most Out of SAP Software" src="./media_19e8a95939116e6dba0a457d1b2c66a000a7dfa05.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="adoption-is-the-key-to-get-the-most-out-of-sap-software">Adoption Is the Key to Get the Most Out of SAP Software</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Customers need more than just outstanding software products to get the desired business value from their investment. SAP Enterprise Adoption provides the key capabilities necessary for fast adoption and empowers customers to succeed locally and globally by delivering an exceptional localization experience across SAP solutions.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>If purchasing enterprise software can be likened to putting tires on a car, adopting it stands for all the nuts and bolts that need to be tightened for the perfect fit.</p>
  <p>As <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/eva-zauke-4732b72/">Eva Zauke</a>, senior vice president and global head of SAP Enterprise Adoption, says: “A company can provide the most excellent and refined products. But if they are not fully adopted by the customer, it will not be possible to reap all the value they promise. For companies to make the transformation to the Intelligent Enterprise a success, business value realization needs to be at the center of the digital journey. From a customer’s perspective, adoption is key to realizing business value.”</p>
  <p>With responsibility for quality management, <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/product/globalization.html">globalization services</a>, and user enablement, SAP Enterprise Adoption is contributing to the success of SAP solutions and ultimately to the success of SAP customers.</p>
  <p>“SAP Enterprise Adoption is providing the key ingredients to help SAP’s customers to drive adoption and to create value with the Intelligent Enterprise,” Zauke says.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-globalization-services-helping-the-world-run-better-on-a-global-scale">SAP Globalization Services: Helping the world run better on a global scale</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/product/globalization.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="focused-on-quality">Focused on Quality</h2>
  <p>Cloud raises customer expectations for quality of software. Customers expect ease of use with a consistent user interface (UI) across products and embedded enablement. Cloud promises flexibility and scalability, requiring high system performance and availability.</p>
  <p>“As customer expectations about software change with cloud solutions, quality and compliance are criteria customers increasingly pay attention to in the decision-making process to purchase software,” Zauke explains. “SAP is taking a comprehensive view on quality along the software life cycle that matters to our customers. This includes high availability and performance, robust data security, ease of implementation and integration, user experience, and superior functionality.”</p>
  <h2 id="enabling-the-sap-user-leads-to-higher-productivity">Enabling the SAP User Leads to Higher Productivity</h2>
  <p>Even without a <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, roll outs of new technologies and processes can be challenging for companies. “Introducing a new business process without planning ahead for user enablement is simply not possible,” Zauke says. “The most successful companies are those that make the technical go-live the point in time when their users are enabled, and actively plan for a fast user on-boarding.”</p>
  <p>Research shows that enabled users are not only <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/training-value/index.html">50% more productive</a> when working with SAP applications, they are also <a href="https://keyush.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/IDC-SAP-Training-Impact-White-Paper-8-9-18-US43850418.pdf">15% more satisfied</a> with their work. One way to achieve broad user enablement is to collect and scale the knowledge of key users, as German retailer Lekkerland did for the implementation of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html?btp=11b93dac-26b0-4cba-9097-7dc7673a6e81">SAP S/4HANA</a>.</p>
  <p>“These key users possess a very deep knowledge in Lekkerland’s business processes and can assess what the company needs beyond SAP standard,” Zauke explains. “Lekkerland captured this knowledge with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/enable-now.html">SAP Enable Now</a> and made it available to 2,000 business users.” These 2,000 employees were thus enabled to work with the software from day one of the go-live.</p>
  <p>One of the largest American retailers uses <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/enable-now.html">SAP Enable Now</a> to fully digitalize enablement for its more than 450,000 employees, meaning they no longer had to attend classroom sessions because the training was embedded into their daily onscreen working environment. Store employees received specific learning material to help them with customer contact during the pandemic.</p>
  <h2 id="enabling-the-success-of-local-and-global-businesses">Enabling the Success of Local and Global Businesses</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="test-drive-sap-s4hana-today">Test drive SAP S/4HANA today</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As businesses have to be successful in a country as well as globally, they need support in achieving exactly this.</p>
  <p>“Doing business in accordance with regulations and local laws is a typical challenge our global and local customers are facing,” Zauke confirms. “Let’s assume a global company wants to open a local subsidiary in Hungary or South Africa. They have to move forward quickly with a localized version of the software in use, while not compromising their global compliance, their best business practices, and statutory reporting.”</p>
  <p>At the same time, the pandemic means that a variety of new laws and regulations were issued by governments that customers had to adhere to practically overnight.</p>
  <p>While some software vendors may simply offer their products in the local language and call it “localized,” SAP has invested heavily in developing truly localized solutions, with country-specific versions that address not only language variations, but also localization of the respective business functions, compliance, local tax and payment rules, statutory reporting, local human resources (HR) solutions, and more. For example, SAP solutions include 64 local versions of SAP S/4HANA and 101 localized versions of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/employee-central-hris.html?btp=11b93dac-26b0-4cba-9097-7dc7673a6e81">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</a>.</p>
  <p>When SAP customer Nestlé opened a subsidiary in Brazil, they were faced with managing compliance with the Brazilian tax declaration framework.</p>
  <p>“Brazil is considered to be the country with the most complex tax regulations worldwide,” Zauke says. “There are many details going into the tax calculation: where was the product developed, where does the material come from, who contributed, who will receive it – all these parameters have to be considered. These regulations had to be included in the Brazilian version of the SAP software Nestlé was using for them to be compliant with Brazilian tax law.”</p>
  <p>Supported by SAP, Nestlé Brazil now manages tax data for more than 20 million invoices and 60,000 legal filings per year.</p>
  <h2 id="adoption-drives-success">Adoption Drives Success</h2>
  <p>Solutions from the SAP Sports &#x26; Entertainment portfolio highlight the importance of adoption. Professional sport is a competitive environment, where maintaining and monitoring player performance has become very important. Digitalizing player performance and team management processes takes sports team management to a new level. SAP Sports One helps clubs and organizations digitalize sports performance management by coordinating all administrative, training, team management, scouting, and medical processes. Sport clubs can analyze and track player performance and players’ talent development and progress. Players, coaches, and scouts are empowered to collaborate on the go with intuitive, secure mobile team communications.</p>
  <p>Professional athletes, coaches, and support staff want to focus on the sport itself and don’t necessarily need to be experts in software usage. They require a software solution that engages athletes and teams with innovative technologies that empower users with intuitive functionality and allow ease of use to enable adoption across the organization.</p>
  <p>Zauke emphasizes the importance of adoption: “Adoption is key to getting the most out of SAP software. Or, in other words, adoption makes the digital transformation a success.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sign-up-for-the-weekly-sap-news-center-newsletter">Sign up for the weekly SAP News Center newsletter</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-enable-now</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-adoption</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>