<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-fiori/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Swedish Food Retailer Axfood Bring the Right Product Mix to Supermarkets]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-and-axfood-bring-right-product-mix-to-supermarkets</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-and-axfood-bring-right-product-mix-to-supermarkets</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP teamed up with Swedish food retailer Axfood to design an innovative assortment planning solution. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-assortment-planning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-design</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fiori</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Experience Mindset: Redesigning How We Build Products at SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/experience-mindset-horizon-visual-theme-sap-fiori</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/experience-mindset-horizon-visual-theme-sap-fiori</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the Horizon visual theme, SAP is evolving its product experiences, bringing the best experience for all generations of users. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fiori</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Everyone Can Be a Developer: SAP Introduces Tools for Citizen and Professional Developers, Embedded AI, and a Free Learning Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-teched-news-citizen-professional-developer-tools-embedded-ai-free-learning-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-teched-news-citizen-professional-developer-tools-embedded-ai-free-learning-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get the SAP TechEd news for 2021, which includes tools for citizen and professional developers, embedded AI, and a free learning experience.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-appgyver</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fiori</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inclusive Meeting Cards Improve Accessibility]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/inclusive-meeting-cards-improve-accessibility</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/inclusive-meeting-cards-improve-accessibility</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Creating an inclusive work culture is actually quite an easy thing to do. Find out how with these free inclusive meeting cards.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accessibility</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fiori</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nordic Electronics Leader Spearheads Retail’s Next Generation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/nordic-electronics-leader-spearheads-retails-next-generation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/nordic-electronics-leader-spearheads-retails-next-generation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Elkjøp Nordic’s new integrated architecture delivers a seamless customer journey with increased mobility and unified channels. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b3b9bdb6a22c4a5332b437dab7e4b4d3f060227b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b3b9bdb6a22c4a5332b437dab7e4b4d3f060227b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b3b9bdb6a22c4a5332b437dab7e4b4d3f060227b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Nordic Electronics Leader Spearheads Retail’s Next Generation" src="./media_1b3b9bdb6a22c4a5332b437dab7e4b4d3f060227b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="nordic-electronics-leader-spearheads-retails-next-generation">Nordic Electronics Leader Spearheads Retail’s Next Generation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Since its founding in 1962, Elkjøp had been known for the continuous improvement of its business processes. As the last decade ended though, the company faced a quandary – maintaining its reputation while being saddled with 12 different legacy software systems.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In order to support its vision for a next-generation retail experience, Elkjøp decided to replace all 12 systems with a new integrated architecture. The dramatic, cloud-based overhaul resulted in a next-gen retail platform that has both improved workflow and delivered 100% uptime.</p>
  <p>The strategy has yielded an array of other benefits for Elkjøp, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>100% in-store mobility for employees</li>
    <li>500 legacy interfaces evaluated and either replaced, updated, and/or re-connected</li>
    <li>4,500 employees trained on new systems using an e-learning platform</li>
  </ul>
  <p>But these achievements only came about because Elkjøp was willing to take a critical look at what employees and customers needed and honestly assess the changes that had to be made.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-elkjøps-sap-innovation-award-proposal">Read Elkjøp's SAP Innovation Award proposal</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2281">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="whats-in-a-name">What’s in a Name?</h2>
  <p>In Norwegian, the brand “Elkjøp” literally means “el buy” – with the “el” being a shortened version of elektrisk (electric) or elektronisk (electronic).</p>
  <p>It’s no surprise, really, since the Oslo-based company is the largest consumer electronics retailer in the Nordic region.</p>
  <p>A subsidiary of Dixons Carphone, a multinational consumer electrical and mobile retailer and services company, Elkjøp sells a variety of goods, including mobile phones, computers, and kitchen and other domestic appliances to both consumers and businesses.</p>
  <p>With a brisk online trade, as well as more than 400 stores, the company employs over 11,000 workers while operating under a number of names in its home country, as well as Sweden, Denmark, and Finland.</p>
  <h2 id="stepping-into-the-future">Stepping into the Future</h2>
  <p>The decision to create the next-generation retail platform did not come easily – Elkjøp had little choice but to take this dramatic step. Systems serving critical processes did not support the latest innovations, and the legacy retail systems could not provide mobility to the sales staff.</p>
  <p>In order to deliver certain services or close a sale, a store representative might be forced to leave a customer, seek out a desktop computer, then return. Other times, employees had to log in and out of multiple systems to complete a sale. In addition, legacy systems were incapable of adapting to new business models, like wireless subscriptions.</p>
  <p>Change was critical, yet daunting. Upgrades to systems capabilities meant adjusting all 12 different interconnected legacy systems, touching 500 different interfaces.</p>
  <p>As Elkjøp re-evaluated its strategy, it turned to a solution that had been serving the company well for several years.</p>
  <h2 id="cloud-first-advancement">Cloud-First Advancement</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="give-shoppers-and-consumers-the-products-and-personalized-shopping-experiences-they-want">Give shoppers and consumers the products and personalized shopping experiences they want</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/retail.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Elkjøp first deployed SAP ERP Central Component in 2015. The application is a core component in managing transactional and financial processes. Modules communicate with each other, working to create a fully integrated solution specific to customers in a variety of industries.</p>
  <p>Because of this successful experience, the company opted to base its next-gen retail platform on SAP ECC and other SAP solutions. A number of requirements were met with micro-services based architecture – software applications designed as suites of independently deployable services.</p>
  <p>Custom add-ons came from ASAPIO/Kafka, enabling information to flow between SAP and non-SAP applications, on premise and in the cloud, in real time.</p>
  <p>The monitoring challenges of Elkjøp’s high volume retail business were supported with an approach centered on SAP Fiori – a set of applications for business functions, like work approvals, and apps specializing in finance, calculation, and various self-service tasks.</p>
  <p>Failover architecture was created to protect computer systems from mishaps, allowing standby equipment to automatically take over if something went wrong.</p>
  <h2 id="unified-execution">Unified Execution</h2>
  <p>The next-gen retail platform went live in Denmark on May 8th, 2020 and was quickly deployed in 110 of the 460 stores. Changes were immediately evident. Using one unified customer master record, the new architecture <strong>delivered a seamless customer journey</strong> across in-store and online channels, with employees better prepared to anticipate clients’ wants and needs.</p>
  <p>Today, employees say the next-gen retail platform has enabled them to be more productive, while customers report quicker service times both online and in person.</p>
  <p>For “delivering the retail experience of the future,” Elkjøp Nordic earned the distinction as a finalist in the <strong>2021 SAP Innovation Awards</strong>, meeting the key requirements of improving customer experiences, solving complex challenges, and serving the greater good. Learn more in Elkjøp’s SAP Innovation Awards <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2281">proposal</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Keith Greenberg is an SAP Global Marketing contributor.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fiori</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SunRice Launches Grower and Administration Portal with SAP BTP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/sunrice-grower-administration-portal-sap-btp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/sunrice-grower-administration-portal-sap-btp</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP, SunRice to create a portal for rice growers, an enhanced digital self-service to strengthen the relationship with the growers.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f3c2d347c2f6fa7bf5dcc4072d246cf020a27fd4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f3c2d347c2f6fa7bf5dcc4072d246cf020a27fd4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f3c2d347c2f6fa7bf5dcc4072d246cf020a27fd4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SunRice Launches Grower and Administration Portal with SAP BTP" src="./media_1f3c2d347c2f6fa7bf5dcc4072d246cf020a27fd4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sunrice-launches-grower-and-administration-portal-with-sap-btp">SunRice Launches Grower and Administration Portal with SAP BTP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For Australian rice food company and leading branded exporter <strong>SunRice</strong>, innovation and collaboration are two of its values. Further, since its beginning in 1950, when early rice growers pooled funds to establish a co-operative, SunRice has had strong ties to growers. Today it works with a rice-growing community of more than 600 growers.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With SAP’s support, SunRice has extended existing systems to simplify, streamline, and enhance the user experience for rice growers and administrative staff.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-technology-platform-accelerate-business-outcomes-with-integration-data-to-value-and-extensibility">SAP Business Technology Platform: Accelerate business outcomes with integration, data to value, and extensibility</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="improving-the-connection-between-growers-and-administration">Improving the Connection Between Growers and Administration</h2>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d233c1de38796140c2b09b0929b0cb7ab9b13a8d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d233c1de38796140c2b09b0929b0cb7ab9b13a8d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d233c1de38796140c2b09b0929b0cb7ab9b13a8d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1d233c1de38796140c2b09b0929b0cb7ab9b13a8d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="605" height="453">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Growers had become frustrated with existing solutions, which could not provide them quick and easy access to functions that are key to supporting the auxiliary business processes associated with growing rice. Challenges included:</p>
  <ol>
    <li>There were difficulties accessing key industry information.</li>
    <li>Where real-time information on harvest deliveries was key, growers could only access dated reports.</li>
    <li>There was limited mobile access to the portal, preventing users from performing tasks and reviewing information when in the field.</li>
    <li>The legacy solution did not provide an intuitive experience, leaving growers unable to find the correct information at the right time.</li>
    <li>It was essential for the company to streamline administrative processes such as the existing process of creating a contract over the phone.</li>
  </ol>
  <h2 id="user-centric-design-process-to-involve-all-stakeholders">User-Centric Design Process to Involve All Stakeholders</h2>
  <p>SunRice teamed up with SAP and <a href="https://experience.sap.com/designservices/network">SAP AppHaus Network</a> partner <a href="https://experience.sap.com/designservices/location/melbourne">Bourne Digital</a> to transform its growers’ portal and yield significant user experience improvements by extending existing systems using SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP).</p>
  <p>Bourne Digital was responsible for the design of the user interface and the user experience (UX) design of the new solution. The company conducted several remote design thinking sessions proceeding along <a href="https://experience.sap.com/designservices/tools/process">SAP’s human-centered approach to innovation</a> to define requirements for the envisioned solution.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_189fc082358ce4b3889bd1495a876ec86bf9443e3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_189fc082358ce4b3889bd1495a876ec86bf9443e3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_189fc082358ce4b3889bd1495a876ec86bf9443e3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_189fc082358ce4b3889bd1495a876ec86bf9443e3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="605" height="453">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>On-site research and interviews with growers</em></p>
  <p>To understand the needs of the end user, the designers and a small subset of growers met and took a close look at a usual day in the life of a grower. This research helped to create several personas to better understand existing pain points. The approach allowed for deeper, holistic insights into the current processes for both grower and administrative tasks, their core frustrations, and opportunities for improvement.</p>
  <p>Throughout the design-driven process, designs were user-tested and iterated to address the common grower frustrations. Feedback from the end users was implemented to refine the solution in alignment with best practices regarding accessibility and user experience.</p>
  <h2 id="new-intuitive-and-innovative-portal-with-sap-btp">New Intuitive and Innovative Portal with SAP BTP</h2>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1483eb0636844520ade19f36a5a7b6ca1371f5629.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1483eb0636844520ade19f36a5a7b6ca1371f5629.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1483eb0636844520ade19f36a5a7b6ca1371f5629.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1483eb0636844520ade19f36a5a7b6ca1371f5629.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1400" height="562">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>As a result, SunRice and Bourne Digital developed a new Grower Portal and an Admin Portal on SAP BTP. This solution suite simplifies, streamlines, and enhances the user experience for growers and admins. What’s more, the platform is built on an extensible architecture, thus allowing the solution to be further extended and enhanced. Through a user-centered approach to design and implementation, the new portal addressed user pain points in a targeted way. It offers the following opportunities:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>In a new Harvest Dashboard, data visualization for harvest moisture, trash, and dry weight assist in making important decisions. Real-time updates for harvest deliveries helps ensure growers are both informed and engaged.</li>
    <li>Quick links to important information is available; via the My Payments tile, growers can view — in near real time — their payments received and upcoming. They can also download their tax and delivery documents at their convenience.</li>
    <li>Opt-in harvest delivery and other alerts help keep growers informed, giving them instant notification of delivery receipt, which is particularly helpful when they are out in the field harvesting.</li>
    <li>With mobility, growers no longer need to wait to access the portal on their desktop, they can now access information and perform tasks all from their mobile devices.</li>
    <li>Through online forms, wherever they are, growers can now access and submit key forms such as Trading and Farm details leveraging SAP BTP workflow. For the Admin team, approvals using the SAP Fiori app, “My Inbox,” are now a reality. Approvals and updates can thus be made seamlessly.</li>
    <li>With grower resources, growers can easily access the most relevant and up-to-date information to assist them.</li>
    <li>The user-friendly interface on the portal is built with <a href="https://community.sap.com/topics/fiori">SAP Fiori</a>, which allows for a <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2020/01/29/next-step-of-sap-fiori-3-available-quartz-dark-theme/">dark mode screen</a> to provide a better view in the sun.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="increased-convenience-and-simplified-work-for-growers">Increased Convenience and Simplified Work for Growers</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-how-sunrice-cultivated-its-growers-portal">Read how SunRice cultivated its growers' portal</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/07/54fe6f5a-ec7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The primary focus of the new solution was to make growers’ lives easier through the regular operational and communication touch points that connect them to SunRice. The refreshed look and usability of the new portal have made information more accessible with clear user guidance, tabs, and dashboards for simple navigation.</p>
  <p>Growers no longer have to access the portal on their desktop; they can now access information and perform tasks all from their mobile devices. In particular, growers can now view delivery information and other critical data instantly, remotely, and effortlessly, and can receive alerts direct to their phones for added mobility and convenience.</p>
  <p>The grower portal was released just prior to the rice harvest season in early 2021. During this time:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>More than 400 growers accessed the portal during harvest.</li>
    <li>Over 9,000 harvest alerts sent to keep growers informed about their deliveries. Growers opt in to these alerts via the portal.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="sunrice-ui5-admin-portal-as-the-perfect-counterpart">SunRice UI5 Admin Portal as the Perfect Counterpart</h2>
  <p>The Admin Portal is built using SAPUI5 and to be used by SunRice administrators for the following tasks: approve grower and farm detail changes; create and approve contract requests; post key messages to growers; and manage Grower Portal resources and forms.</p>
  <h2 id="whats-next">What’s Next?</h2>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19e0176c0880094ff30c2a73fe077bbda46a6db97.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19e0176c0880094ff30c2a73fe077bbda46a6db97.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19e0176c0880094ff30c2a73fe077bbda46a6db97.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_19e0176c0880094ff30c2a73fe077bbda46a6db97.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1400" height="562">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>New features such as contracts have already been added to the Grower and Admin portals after the initial implementation. Contracts provide the ability for growers to apply for contracts in the Grower’s portal and the ability for admins to create and approve contracts in the Admin portal.</p>
  <p>SunRice is exploring further ways to improve the portal, including bringing enhanced reporting capabilities to the new system and continuing to gather feedback directly from growers to inform new changes, design edits, and added functionality.</p>
  <p>By putting growers at the heart of decision making, SunRice is driving new innovations that make a real difference for the grower community.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fiori</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Positioned as a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Multiexperience Development Platforms (MXDP)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/sap-positioned-leader-2021-gartner-multiexperience-development</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/sap-positioned-leader-2021-gartner-multiexperience-development</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP, specifically SAP Extension Suite, has been recognized as a Leader in Gartner’s Magic Quadrant for Multiexperience Development Platforms.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13b3fd1155587d03ae3b143f3ac96420f515d20e6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13b3fd1155587d03ae3b143f3ac96420f515d20e6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_13b3fd1155587d03ae3b143f3ac96420f515d20e6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Positioned as a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Multiexperience Development Platforms (MXDP)" src="./media_13b3fd1155587d03ae3b143f3ac96420f515d20e6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-positioned-as-a-leader-in-2021-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-multiexperience-development-platforms-mxdp">SAP Positioned as a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Multiexperience Development Platforms (MXDP)</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="accelerate-business-outcomes-with-integration-data-to-value-and-extensibility">Accelerate business outcomes with integration, data to value, and extensibility</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that independent analyst firm <a href="http://www.gartner.com/technology/home.jsp">Gartner Inc.</a> has named SAP as a Leader in Gartner’s Magic Quadrant for <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/extension-suite.html?campaigncode=CRM-PM21-SIP-EXTSUITGMM&#x26;url_id=gartner-magic-quadrant-multiexperience-development-platforms&#x26;rc=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gartner.com%2Freprints%2F%3Fid%3D1-26YPI7NO%26ct%3D210728%26st%3Dsb">Multiexperience Development Platforms</a>* for the second year in a row. SAP has been recognized as a Leader based on its “ability to execute” and “completeness of vision” after evaluation of 13 vendors.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>According to Gartner, “Multiexperience development platforms provide software engineering leaders and teams with a unified way to create rich, interconnected user experiences across web, mobile, conversational, digital twin, IoT and AR applications. This research evaluates 13 MXDPs based on ten critical capabilities and five use cases.”</p>
  <p>“In a world that is more connected than ever, customers expect a harmonized digital experience across all of their applications to stay innovative and competitive,” said Juergen Mueller, chief technology officer and member of the Executive Board, SAP. “SAP Extension Suite is part of SAP Business Technology Platform and delivers consistent, personalized and unified experiences across multisensory touch points and modalities. Customers such as CLAAS benefit from accelerated time to value, increased engagement and productivity, and greater business resilience.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://claas.com">CLAAS</a>, a global agricultural machinery manufacturer, uses SAP Extension Suite to help achieve a 95% employee satisfaction, a 40% reduction in development costs and faster time to market.</p>
  <p>“By unifying our technology in the field of digital applications, with SAP Extension Suite we can respond quickly and efficiently to the requirements of our internal customers and employees,” said Bernhard Schuchert, CIO of CLAAS. “And we can provide innovative web and mobile solutions that are otherwise only experienced in the end-user context.”</p>
  <p>SAP’s multiexperience development offering consists of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/extension-suite.html">SAP Extension Suite</a>, including the SAP AppGyver tool, SAP Business Application Studio, SAP Conversational AI services, the mobile development kit service, native SDKs for iOS and Android, and the SAP Fiori design system.</p>
  <p>The offering enables customers to boost productivity and engagement by delivering tailored experiences for SAP customers and employees alike. SAP supports by enabling IT and citizen developers to deliver seamless multiexperience application practices with the ease and simplicity of low-code/no-code tooling. SAP also supports sophisticated pro-code development that is complemented by innovative AI services, APIs, prebuilt integration and extension components on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a>.</p>
  <p>Learn more about <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/extension-suite.html">SAP Extension Suite</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Julia Fargel, +1 (650) 276-8964, <a href="mailto:julia.fargel@sap.com">julia.fargel@sap.com</a>, PT<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>*Gartner, “Magic Quadrant for Multiexperience Development Platforms,” July 26, 2021. Gartner and Magic Quadrant are registered trademarks of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally and is used herein with permission. All rights reserved. Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-news</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/low-code-no-code</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fiori</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improving Field Service Employee Experience with Design Thinking and User Empathy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/patterson-field-service-employee-experience-design-thinking-user-empathy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/patterson-field-service-employee-experience-design-thinking-user-empathy</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP partner Mindset reimagined the field service experience for Patterson by improving customer satisfaction, with annual savings of US$1.3M.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e2df223a76801f41eb61f6867973e1a1b4eeb22e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e2df223a76801f41eb61f6867973e1a1b4eeb22e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e2df223a76801f41eb61f6867973e1a1b4eeb22e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Improving Field Service Employee Experience with Design Thinking and User Empathy" src="./media_1e2df223a76801f41eb61f6867973e1a1b4eeb22e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="improving-field-service-employee-experience-with-design-thinking-and-user-empathy">Improving Field Service Employee Experience with Design Thinking and User Empathy</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Mindset applied the design thinking process to reimagine the field service experience for Patterson Companies, a leading distribution and service company that serves the dental and animal health markets in North America and the UK.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It brought together field service technicians, business leadership, and IT experts to create a new mobile app that improved customer satisfaction, gave employees time back every day, and will continue to save Patterson over US$1.3 million annually. With just a few user experience (<a href="/topics/user-experience">UX</a>) champions, a diverse group of stakeholders was created to focus on empathy, find the real problem, and deliver an innovative solution.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-fiori-the-enterprise-user-experience-reimagined">SAP Fiori: The enterprise user experience, reimagined</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/fiori.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="modern-field-service-processes-require-access-from-anywhere">Modern Field Service Processes Require Access from Anywhere</h2>
  <p>The technical service team at Patterson spends much of its time at customer sites. Field technicians provide dentists and veterinary offices with the expertise, products, and services they need to keep their practices running smoothly and efficiently. Patterson’s customer experience sets it apart from other distributors. Not only does it sell and install products, but it provides services to make sure dentists’ equipment runs smoothly.</p>
  <p>Prior to working with Mindset to develop a mobile solution, the technicians needed to be back at the office or their home each night to load the information from their service appointments into the SAP system that ran the business.</p>
  <h2 id="walking-in-the-customers-shoes-and-riding-in-their-trucks">Walking in the Customer’s Shoes and Riding in Their Trucks</h2>
  <p>Patterson’s director of Technical Field Service and vice president of IT reached out to design thinking expert and UX champion, Mindset. To gain a complete understanding of the problem and underlying business processes, Mindset decided to team up with several field service reps for a series of “ride-alongs.” By riding in service tech vans, going on real service calls, and getting to know and interact with the service techs, Mindset project managers got a unique perspective on the pain technicians go through to deliver great service every day. This would prove very helpful when facilitating the design thinking sessions with a broader team.</p>
  <h2 id="with-design-thinking-people-focus-on-what-matters-most">With Design Thinking, People Focus on What Matters Most</h2>
  <p>After capturing the preliminary information from traveling to multiple sites in the field, Mindset set up a design thinking workshop at <a href="https://experience.sap.com/designservices/location/minneapolis">SAP AppHaus Minneapolis</a>, a space created specifically to cater to such workshops.</p>
  <p>The workshop included the technicians from the field research, business sponsors, IT experts, and Mindset facilitators. Jonathan Bragg of Mindset served as Patterson’s principal UX architect. Getting everyone together made a big difference in building empathy for everyone’s needs. The ability to ask “why” across roles led to a deeper understanding of the current situation and problems along the entire process flow.</p>
  <p>The design thinking workshop followed the typical steps for problem finding, problem solving, and iteration.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Empathize:</strong>– By bringing various stakeholders together, everyone was able to understand how their part of the process affected the entire company. In many cases, it was the first time the field service reps had a chance to speak with IT directly.</li>
    <li><strong>Define:</strong> Once everyone understood the overall situation with the current field service software, which was based on SAP Customer Relationship Management (SAP CRM), they were able to work as a team to narrow the scope and create a clear problem statement. Since the field service technicians spend most of their time at customer sites, one of the key requirements was that the solution needed to have a mobile-optimized design.</li>
    <li><strong>Ideate:</strong> With a clear problem definition, the cross-functional team suggested many ideas for improvement that spanned the entire business process. Not only did this make it easier to enter data during service calls, it also improved how Patterson used the information downstream to improve customer service and reduce company costs.</li>
    <li><strong>Prototype:</strong> During the workshop, the Mindset experts were able to create prototypes, gather feedback, and make improvements in an iterative and agile manner. With the insight from the design thinking session, they were able to develop an <a href="https://experience.sap.com/fiori-design/">SAP Fiori</a> app that could be tested in the field.</li>
    <li><strong>Test:</strong> The initial pilot version went to a group of 17 technicians in 17 locations. This allowed for further refinement of the app, using agile methodology to put new functionality into people’s hands quickly to see what worked and what needed further refinement.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Throughout the process, a dedicated product owner from Patterson helped the Mindset team prioritize development and ensure the features they developed addressed the user stories that were documented during the workshop.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Quote</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>A design thinking workshop is somewhat of a magical event for our customers. You get people from all walks of life into a room together for three to four days and out comes an amazing, thoughtful proposed solution that can be estimated, built, tested, live, and championed. It’s these workshops that form lasting bonds between business end users and IT, showcasing how everyone is one the same team and everyone wants to make a difference</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td>Jonathan Bragg, Director of Software Products, Mindset</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <h2 id="agile-development-process-added-validation-steps-for-clean-data">Agile Development Process Added Validation Steps for Clean Data</h2>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th colspan="2">Promo</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <h3 id="explore-sap-fiori-on-sap-community">Explore SAP Fiori on SAP Community</h3>
              </td>
              <td><strong><a href="https://community.sap.com/topics/fiori">Learn more</a></strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>The discussions in the workshop revealed that without a dedicated mobile app, field reps needed to return to the office or their home to enter details from their site visits. Besides being inconvenient, the complexity of a desktop screen sometimes led to data inconsistencies. During the prototyping phase, it became clear that adding validations into each step of a linear process would be successful in ensuring that only clean data can go into the system. Once they focused on this pain point, they were able to make small modifications to the app that accommodated the checks and balances they wanted to build into the new service process that weren’t available in the original system.</p>
        <p>The initial plan was to create a native iOS application. During the field observations, the team learned that not all the technicians had iPhones. Since SAP Fiori was already used in other areas at Patterson, the developers decided to create an SAP Fiori app that runs in a browser so it could be used on any device.</p>
        <h2 id="intuitive-screens-lead-to-high-adoption-and-measurable-business-benefits">Intuitive Screens Lead to High Adoption and Measurable Business Benefits</h2>
        <ul>
          <li>The new app was so compelling to use, that over a four-month period, 85% of the field reps chose the new app over the old process. The number of clicks and associated time to complete various processes dropped by over 50%.</li>
          <li>Better visibility into order status allowed the company to focus its resources and reduce the number of orders open longer than 60 days from 13,000 to 4,000. This translated into $1.3 million in annual savings for Patterson.</li>
          <li>On the human side, technicians were able to complete the administrative part of their jobs more quickly, so they were happier. And, they were able to check on tasks from anywhere, so they could be more responsive to their customers’ needs, adding to their job satisfaction. With the ability to complete work remotely, people could bypass a trip to the office for “paperwork” and switch to relaxation mode when they got home, rather than staring at their computer to document tasks they had completed hours earlier.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2 id="digitalization-will-drive-further-business-improvements">Digitalization Will Drive Further Business Improvements</h2>
        <p>The design thinking approach is more than just bringing a bunch of people into a conference room, either physically or virtually, and expecting magic to happen. If you have the right facilitators, who can ask the right questions, and the right development team, who can build apps quickly and make updates based on user feedback, along with the key business stakeholders, you greatly increase the chances of success. If you lack the skills in your organization, then bringing in an outside expert is a great way to gain the results you want while learning the process.</p>
        <p>To learn more about the SAP Fiori user experience, please visit the <a href="https://url.sap/cdpj3b">SAP Community topic page</a>. Bookmark the <a href="https://url.sap/s6hvhk">UX Champions tag</a> or follow the <a href="https://url.sap/alsori">UX blog tag</a> to catch all the stories in the series.</p>
        <p><em>Peter Spielvogel is senior director of Product Marketing for SAP UX Engineering.</em></p>
        <p>.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fiori</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrated Order Management Cockpit on SAP BTP at Border States]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/border-states-industries-integrated-order-management-cockpit-sap-btp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/border-states-industries-integrated-order-management-cockpit-sap-btp</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At Border States, an integrated order management cockpit on SAP BTP provides visibility into sales and purchase orders in real time.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13760278b7b7182c07df081bbf1d8cc472b06fb53.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13760278b7b7182c07df081bbf1d8cc472b06fb53.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_13760278b7b7182c07df081bbf1d8cc472b06fb53.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Integrated Order Management Cockpit on SAP BTP at Border States" src="./media_13760278b7b7182c07df081bbf1d8cc472b06fb53.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="integrated-order-management-cockpit-on-sap-btp-at-border-states">Integrated Order Management Cockpit on SAP BTP at Border States</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> impacted supply chains, Border States Industries Inc., the seventh largest <a href="https://www.borderstates.com/">electrical distributor in the U.S.</a>, needed to optimize and streamline its purchase and sales order management to manage delayed and escalated orders specifically. It was critical to consolidate disjointed systems and tools, increase cross-team visibility, and reduce the duplication of work in order to provide its innovative supply chain products and services to the construction, industrial, and utility markets.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The integrated order management cockpit on SAP Business Technology Platform provides end-to-end and real-time visibility into sales and purchase orders and can enable colleagues from procurement, customer service, and application engineering to collaborate in order to handle material delays, escalations, and other issues. This way, the business can experience improved customer experience (like on-time delivery), an optimized and streamlined order management with clear line of sight for all stakeholders, a reduction of duplicate work, the facilitation of hand-offs and material escalations, and increased visibility and accountability.</p>
  <p>Tony Serati, vice president of Procurement at Border States, said, “The solution will improve collaboration and speed of information within our company, resulting in an improved experience and service for our customers.”</p>
  <p>Border States is 100% employee-owned and has more than 2,300 employee owners and 98 branch locations in 22 states. Employee ownership drives Border States’ commitment to deliver total satisfaction. Border States was founded in 1952, when two entrepreneurs wanted to serve the electric utility industry. After nearly 70 years in business, the company’s mission and values haven’t changed; Border States remains a trusted advisor and problem solver, providing value to tens of thousands of customers in the construction, industrial, and utility markets. The company does this by delivering quality products, material management solutions, and industry expertise.</p>
  <p>The integrated order management cockpit provides a centralized space for all stakeholders to have visibility into order statuses, collaborate, and resolve escalations in a timely manner.</p>
  <p>“I am very excited about the collaboration piece. It is an immediate way of communication and will make the life of a buyer much easier,” said Christa Lavey, purchasing supervisor at Border States.</p>
  <p>The flag feature allows CSR teams to request specific actions from the procurement teams. They are also able to post comments on order status updates.</p>
  <p>With an escalation toggle, the subject matter experts can help resolve escalated orders proactively. The stakeholders can provide material level updates, too.
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e021ee5453216e1f5574b02dff2de811fa7568bc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e021ee5453216e1f5574b02dff2de811fa7568bc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e021ee5453216e1f5574b02dff2de811fa7568bc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot: escalation toggle" src="./media_1e021ee5453216e1f5574b02dff2de811fa7568bc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1440" height="806">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>“This tool allows us to escalate and collaborate on orders to find alternatives and work with customers and suppliers to prevent impacts,” said Lex Silbernagel, vice president of Alliances at Border States. “It will enable us to better manage and communicate as challenges arise.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-technology-platform-accelerate-business-outcomes-with-integration-data-to-value-and-extensibility">SAP Business Technology Platform: Accelerate business outcomes with integration, data to value, and extensibility</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="technological-foundation">Technological Foundation</h2>
  <p>The integrated order management cockpit is built on SAP Business Technology Platform, leveraging SAP Integration Suite, SAP Extension Suite, SAP HANA Cloud, and the SAP Fiori design system. It provides colleagues from procurement, customer service, and application engineering with a central place to manage escalated purchase and sales orders. With this solution, teams can have real-time, cross-team visibility, rather than working in multiple disjointed systems and unsynchronized tools. This allows for improved communication and direct feedback between stakeholders, working to improve process efficiency and eliminate the duplication of work. In addition, new team members can be onboarded quickly and raise and manage issues as they occur.</p>
  <p>The semantic data models on SAP HANA Cloud make the solution SAP ERP data agnostic, allowing for seamless integration with SAP ERP now and SAP S/4HANA in the future. SAP Integration Suite helps integrate the solution directly with data from backend solutions. SAP Fiori provides a simplified user experience, enabling users to manage escalations quicker and more effectively.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h2 id="key-results">Key Results</h2>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th colspan="2">Promo</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <h3 id="explore-border-states-2021-sap-innovation-awards-pitch-deck">Explore Border States 2021 SAP Innovation Awards pitch deck</h3>
              </td>
              <td><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2453">Learn more</a></strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <ul>
          <li>Approximately 16,000 hours saved annually for customer service representatives and buyer roles</li>
          <li>About 2% productivity gained for CSR and buyer roles</li>
          <li>About 1% improvement on material availability resulting in improved on-time delivery, improved customer experience and increased revenues</li>
        </ul>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fiori</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Process Improvement Means More Than Developing Apps at Sun Chemical]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sun-chemical-process-improvement-apps</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sun-chemical-process-improvement-apps</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Sun Chemical has brought 200+ SAP Fiori apps to life to support employees in their daily work. Learn about the UX transformation journey.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14c405e6c2cc1b477aab89285c9b5f33d1f24ad6b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14c405e6c2cc1b477aab89285c9b5f33d1f24ad6b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14c405e6c2cc1b477aab89285c9b5f33d1f24ad6b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Process Improvement Means More Than Developing Apps at Sun Chemical" src="./media_14c405e6c2cc1b477aab89285c9b5f33d1f24ad6b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="process-improvement-means-more-than-developing-apps-at-sun-chemical">Process Improvement Means More Than Developing Apps at Sun Chemical</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In 2016, the IT team behind Sun Chemical embarked on a journey to learn more about design thinking via <a href="https://open.sap.com/courses/dt1">a free openSAP course</a>. Since then, the team has been systematically improving the operational effectiveness and efficiency of business processes through design-led workshops, bringing over 200 SAP Fiori apps to life to support their daily work.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Sasi Reddy, senior SAP solution architect at Sun Chemical, shares the team’s user experience (UX) transformation journey, the biggest takeaways, and what it takes to be a UX champion.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="enroll-in-an-opensap-course-today">Enroll in an openSAP course today</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://open.sap.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="from-theory-to-action-with-an-opensap-course-on-design-thinking">From Theory to Action with an openSAP Course on Design Thinking</h2>
  <p>Sun Chemical is a recognized leader in printing inks, coatings, pigments, and supplies for the packaging, publication, commercial, industrial, and digital markets. With over 20,000 employees spread across 63 locations around the world, Sun Chemical relies on lean business processes to ensure its field service workers and customers can quickly and easily maintain field data and enter new requests on the go, both on- and offline.</p>
  <p>To further enhance their knowledge of design thinking and to learn how this methodology could be applied to both process improvements and application development, Reddy and his team took part in the openSAP course <a href="https://open.sap.com/courses/dt1">Developing Software Using Design Thinking</a> in 2017. The core of the methodology is developing empathy for users by putting oneself in their shoes. Design thinking also relies on prototyping and a strong iterative process rather than on intuition, something which Sun Chemical has embraced fully. Since completing the course, the team has worked with a few SAP partners, and later independently, to offer design thinking services to the entire company, with 15 major design-led projects to date.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-fiori-apps-support-lean-business-processes">SAP Fiori Apps Support Lean Business Processes</h2>
  <p>Over the past five years, Sun Chemical has groomed an elite team of UX champions that leverage design thinking to accelerate and digitize its processes. A key factor in the team’s success has been to build tailored SAP Fiori apps that support an agile development approach. This method scales and requires a minimal investment. It allows the team to build apps for a system that runs on SAP ERP, which plans to migrate to SAP S/4HANA later.</p>
  <p>If you ask Reddy which of the more than 200 existing apps he’s most proud of, there are many that come to mind, such as the Regulatory Inquiry App and the Raw Material Request App, both of which emerged from a prototype developed during the 2016 openSAP course and have since been rolled out globally.</p>
  <p>One example that captures the business impact of the UX transformation is the Field Service App.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17a816f25551901298d51f51c04309feac6f1e7a9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17a816f25551901298d51f51c04309feac6f1e7a9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17a816f25551901298d51f51c04309feac6f1e7a9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Sun Chemical product screenshot" src="./media_17a816f25551901298d51f51c04309feac6f1e7a9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="360" height="200">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Remote field service application on desktop device.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_101663f3bed90c2d6897740ae72640aec44732cf7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_101663f3bed90c2d6897740ae72640aec44732cf7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_101663f3bed90c2d6897740ae72640aec44732cf7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Sun Chemical product sceenshot" src="./media_101663f3bed90c2d6897740ae72640aec44732cf7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="360" height="200">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Remote field service application: Signature pad on iOS device.</p>
  <h2 id="from-workshop-to-real-life-the-field-service-app">From Workshop to Real Life: The Field Service App</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-fiori-the-enterprise-user-experience-reimagined">SAP Fiori: The enterprise user experience, reimagined</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/fiori.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>A remote design thinking workshop was kicked off in 2018 to determine how to better manage the day-to-day activities for European field service engineers who relied on using a mix of e-mails and spreadsheets to maintain their work order history and incoming requests. The workshop included the field engineers, their supervisors, the administrator who orchestrated the work orders, and developers from India. From the workshop emerged the idea to develop an application that contains all the information in one place.</p>
  <p>The app, which was developed in a few short weeks, makes it easy to track what service has previously been done for a specific customer and supports detailed reports on previous work orders. Naturally, it allows field service workers to easily enter new orders and incorporates a digital signature on native iOS mobile devices, something which the workshop participants were “really surprised that we could deliver on so quickly,” says Reddy. Since the rollout in Europe, the app has been immediately accepted by its users and has made its way to North and South American field service workers as well.</p>
  <h2 id="its-about-the-mindset-not-just-the-apps">It’s About the Mindset, Not Just the Apps</h2>
  <p>There is no doubt that the design thinking method requires a significant time investment from those involved. From the initial workshop, where research, user empathy, and ideation take place, to the design process that relies on numerous iteration cycles with end users, you have to put in the work to ensure the end result solves the problem at hand and meets users’ expectations.</p>
  <p>Reddy agrees that the effort is time consuming. He and his UX champion colleagues spend a lot of time taking part in collaboration calls with teams who are currently <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/03/31/sap-fiori-for-sap-s-4hana-recommendations-for-transitioning-users-from-sap-gui-to-sap-fiori/">switching from SAP GUI to SAP Fiori</a>. They receive feedback on the applications on a daily basis to ensure the transition to the new user experience goes smoothly.</p>
  <p>But Reddy has also seen the fruits of his team’s labor: “People are seeing the value of it. Our departments have seen our work. It’s been almost four years. Previously, we drove design thinking; now people request it from us. And not necessarily to build apps, though everyone’s now on board with SAP Fiori, but to improve processes in general. The mindset has really changed in our company.”</p>
  <p>To learn more about the SAP Fiori user experience, visit the <a href="https://url.sap/cdpj3b">SAP Fiori topic page on the SAP Community</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Andrea Waisgluss is a content strategist for SAP Design.</em><br><em><a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/04/20/process-improvement-means-more-than-developing-apps-sun-chemical-shares-why/">This article originally appeared in the SAP Community</a></em>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fiori</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>