<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/sap-event/sap-teched/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP TechEd in 2024: An Expanded Global Program to Meet You Where You Are]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-teched-in-2024-expanded-global-program</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-teched-in-2024-expanded-global-program</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP TechEd in 2024 offers three unique and convenient experiences so customers and partners can easily build skills and meet with experts.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cd2d1e153edaa50b3c6b55dcda64e30a680ce56f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cd2d1e153edaa50b3c6b55dcda64e30a680ce56f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1cd2d1e153edaa50b3c6b55dcda64e30a680ce56f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP TechEd in 2024: An Expanded Global Program to Meet You Where You Are" src="./media_1cd2d1e153edaa50b3c6b55dcda64e30a680ce56f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-teched-in-2024-an-expanded-global-program-to-meet-you-where-you-are">SAP TechEd in 2024: An Expanded Global Program to Meet You Where You Are</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>I’m thrilled to share a sneak peek of our <a href="/topics/sap-teched">SAP TechEd</a> program for 2024, which brings together developers, practitioners, enterprise architects, and global IT leaders to explore SAP’s latest innovations and gain hands-on learning.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This year, we’re offering three unique and convenient event experiences so customers and partners can build skills and meet 1:1 with SAP experts.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-teched-virtual">SAP TechEd Virtual</h2>
  <p>Held October 8-9, 2024, the free two-day virtual event will deliver SAP technology news and announcements via global keynotes, technical and developer enablement, and engaging sessions of live and pre-recorded content for everyone across the globe.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-teched-on-tour">SAP TechEd On Tour</h2>
  <p>Taking place on multiple dates throughout the year, the single-day in-person events hosted across the globe by SAP experts and the SAP Community will deliver deep learning, networking, and hands-on engagement. Locations will range in North America, Europe, the Middle East and Africa (EMEA), Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC), and Asian-Pacific and Japan (APJ) regions.</p>
  <h2 id="asug-tech-connect-in-partnership-with-sap-teched-west-palm-beach-florida">ASUG Tech Connect, in partnership with SAP TechEd, West Palm Beach, Florida</h2>
  <p>From November 12-14, 2024, the major three-day event stopover on the SAP TechEd program tour will deliver visionary keynotes, technical education and enablement, expert-led sessions, and a full-scale show floor community experience with networking, best practices, and hands-on engagement.</p>
  <p>I can’t wait to see everyone at an SAP TechEd event in 2024!</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>JG Chirapurath is chief marketing and solutions officer for SAP BTP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-notified-about-updates-and-news-on-the-2024-sap-teched-program">Get notified about updates and news on the 2024 SAP TechEd program</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/sap-teched-subscription/index.html">Sign up now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bringing Generative AI to Business: How a Platform Enables Systems of Intelligence]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2023/11/generative-ai-business-platform-systems-of-intelligence</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2023/11/generative-ai-business-platform-systems-of-intelligence</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[After SAP TechEd Bangalore, CTO Juergen Mueller shares his experience with the company's leap forward in AI evolution toward generative AI.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d3841225b19f51748f341443bd006926c3368989.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d3841225b19f51748f341443bd006926c3368989.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d3841225b19f51748f341443bd006926c3368989.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Bringing Generative AI to Business: How a Platform Enables Systems of Intelligence" src="./media_1d3841225b19f51748f341443bd006926c3368989.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="bringing-generative-ai-to-business-how-a-platform-enables-systems-of-intelligence">Bringing Generative AI to Business: How a Platform Enables Systems of Intelligence</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>What a week at <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/teched/bangalore.html">SAP TechEd</a>! No matter if you joined the two-day live experience in Bangalore, India, or virtually, you could not get around the topic of generative AI.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="enterprise-innovation-in-the-age-of-ai">Enterprise Innovation in the Age of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/teched/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP has been working on AI for more than eight years now. Regardless, the past year was special as it has shown a huge leap forward in AI evolution toward generative AI. Today, more than 24,000 of our SAP customers are using SAP Business AI solutions in over 130 use cases. And we are aiming to provide even more businesses the opportunity to benefit from our unique data, industry, and process know-how as we work to become THE leading business AI company.</p>
  <p>At the heart of that vision is SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP), THE platform of choice and key enabler for infusing SAP and partner applications with business AI.</p>
  <p>My keynote guest speaker Michael Nilles, chief digital and information officer (CDIO) of Henkel, said it well: “Generative AI disrupts economy and society like the internet, but at lightspeed. Look at the last 10 months only — I have never discovered an exponential technology like that. SAP BTP is our choice at Henkel for three years already; it’s our innovation platform. Together with SAP, we innovate at large scale, now also in the generative AI space.”</p>
  <p>To this end, we have been driving significant progress in the past months, from <a href="/2023/07/power-of-business-ai-sap-btp">SAP Business AI capabilities</a> across our portfolio to the launch of our generative <a href="/2023/09/joule-new-generative-ai-assistant">AI co-pilot Joule</a>. The <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/teched/news-guide.html">announcements made at SAP TechEd</a> are another testament to the innovation SAP provides.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <picture>
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18de9c188ebe8515efbb6b9e1e0a822f6405cc9ed.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18de9c188ebe8515efbb6b9e1e0a822f6405cc9ed.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
          <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18de9c188ebe8515efbb6b9e1e0a822f6405cc9ed.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_18de9c188ebe8515efbb6b9e1e0a822f6405cc9ed.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="626" height="357">
        </picture><br><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/posts/juergmueller_sapteched-sapbtp-activity-7127690708659916801-eVu_/">https://www.linkedin.com/posts/juergmueller_sapteched-sapbtp-activity-7127690708659916801-eVu_/</a>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="build-in-not-bolt-on">Build In, Not Bolt On</h2>
  <p>We believe that business AI capabilities need to be directly embedded into applications and extensions. Designed with security, governance, and trust in mind, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/business-technology-platform.html">AI Foundation on SAP BTP</a> is our new one-stop shop for developers to do exactly that. It provides ready-to-use AI services, AI runtimes, lifecycle management, as well as tooling for generative AI capabilities and business-data connectivity.</p>
  <p>As part of the AI Foundation, our generative AI hub provides instant access to the most powerful large language models (LLM), such as Azure OpenAI Service and Falcon-40b. On the other side, it offers grounding capabilities based on enterprise data to ensure context, for example, by leveraging our new SAP HANA Cloud vector engine that combines LLMs with relevant organizational data.</p>
  <h2 id="all-developers-will-be-ai-developers">All Developers Will Be AI Developers</h2>
  <p>Today’s dynamic technology and business landscape means every developer needs to become an AI developer. For coders using Java and Javascript, our new solution <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/developer-tools.html">SAP Build Code</a> increases developer productivity by offering a simplified experience with a unified lobby as an entry point, and generative AI capabilities. SAP Build Code also takes care of identity management, audit logging, secure access, and more.</p>
  <p>Does this sound too good to be true? Check out <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?app=desktop&#x26;v=6BsvzygS5Hg">my keynote</a> to see for yourself how SAP Build Code helped to create a full-blown application in just five minutes on stage!</p>
  <h2 id="raise-the-ecosystem">R“AI”se the Ecosystem</h2>
  <p>More and more businesses are seeking to benefit from AI. No single company can unlock generative AI’s potential alone. A vibrant ecosystem of partners is required in order to meet growing customer expectations.</p>
  <p>SAP is partnering with many key players that offer solutions connected to SAP BTP. Today, partners support 90% of SAP-based implementations and offer 2,000 solutions on our store — more than 400 of these include AI capabilities. Moreover, our partner solutions also enable developers to create AI-based apps on SAP BTP. One example is our partnership with DataRobot, announced earlier this year. We now brought its AI models to SAP AI Core as well as its predictive and generative AI capabilities to SAP Build.</p>
  <p>Apart from the partner context, we also invest in AI research. The recently announced <a href="/2023/11/sap-joins-stanford-hai-corporate-affiliate-program">membership at the Stanford Institute for Human-Centered AI</a> is an important step to reinforce our commitment to build ethical and trustworthy AI.</p>
  <h2 id="going-forward-looking-beyond">Going Forward, Looking Beyond</h2>
  <p>The future holds a lot. On our way to become THE leading business AI company we will continue to integrate AI into businesses’ everyday processes.</p>
  <p>For 2024 and beyond, we are exploring multiple use cases, such as AI-supported business simulations, AI-generated business correspondence replies and follow-up actions, composable business processes, or automated generation of code. We will also support fine-tuned LLMs to make them more suitable for business AI.</p>
  <p>This SAP TechEd has only been a first milestone — there’s a lot more to come! Don’t miss out on your journey to SAP BTP, THE choice for anything technology-related in an SAP context.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Juergen Mueller is CTO and a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-teched-virtual-live-and-on-demand-experiences">SAP TechEd Virtual: Live and on-demand experiences</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/teched/virtual.html">Watch replays</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/developers</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP TechEd in 2023: That’s a Wrap!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-teched-2023-wrap-up</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-teched-2023-wrap-up</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Last week at SAP TechEd, SAP announced new SAP BTP innovations that help organizations and developers bring their ideas to life. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1877c9283a8cddb4da2df0b65c45dc5a6351a2863.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1877c9283a8cddb4da2df0b65c45dc5a6351a2863.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1877c9283a8cddb4da2df0b65c45dc5a6351a2863.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP TechEd in 2023: That’s a Wrap!" src="./media_1877c9283a8cddb4da2df0b65c45dc5a6351a2863.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-teched-in-2023-thats-a-wrap">SAP TechEd in 2023: That’s a Wrap!</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP’s mission is to make the world run better and improve people’s lives. As we work to fulfill this purpose each day, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP) serves as the unified platform that enables our customers to accelerate their innovation with application development, integration, automation, data and analytics, and AI capabilities.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="enterprise-innovation-in-the-age-of-ai">Enterprise Innovation in the Age of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Last week at <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/teched/bangalore.html">SAP TechEd</a>, we announced new SAP BTP innovations that help organizations and developers bring their ideas to life.</p>
  <p>Thank you to everyone who attended the event virtually and in person at Bangalore. For those who couldn’t attend live, I recommend reading the <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/teched/news-guide.html">SAP TechEd news guide</a>, checking out the full list of <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/sapteched/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sapteched23/catalog/page/catalog?tab.sessionplanned=1602215152230002KZab">on-demand sessions</a>, and watching the <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/sapteched/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sapteched23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1692373933108001qRNV">executive keynote</a>, delivered by SAP CTO Juergen Mueller.</p>
  <p>Here are some of the key announcements we made.</p>
  <h2 id="turning-every-developer-into-an-ai-developer">Turning Every Developer into an AI Developer</h2>
  <p>Developers are essential to the modern world we live in, driving innovation and transformation forward across every industry. To help improve their productivity, we announced <a href="/2023/11/sap-teched-2023-sap-build-code-supercharge-developer-productivity">SAP Build Code</a>, a generative AI-powered application development solution, built on SAP BTP and optimized for Java and JavaScript development. It delivers a turn-key environment for coding, testing, integrations, and application lifecycle management.</p>
  <p>SAP Build Code has embedded generative AI capabilities with <a href="/2023/09/joule-new-generative-ai-assistant">Joule</a> to enable code generation to streamline application development. It also enables fusion development so developers can build rapidly, integrate seamlessly, and collaborate effectively with other developers and business experts. SAP Build Code complements <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/low-code.html">SAP Build</a>, our low-code solution that provides a unified environment to create and enhance enterprise applications, automate processes, and design business sites with drag-and-drop simplicity. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/developer-tools.html">Learn more here</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="generative-ai-for-everyone">Generative AI for Everyone</h2>
  <p>More than ever before, companies are seeking to unleash the power of AI in their applications and processes. We are thrilled to unveil <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">AI Foundation on SAP BTP</a>, a one-stop shop for developers to build and extend applications powered by AI and generative AI on SAP BTP. With AI Foundation, developers gain access to everything they need to quickly embed business-ready AI into their applications, leveraging the same powerful technology SAP development teams use today. This includes AI services, generative AI management, AI workload management, access to business data and context, and lifecycle management based on SAP AI Core, SAP AI Launchpad, and SAP HANA Cloud. <a href="https://sap.com/joule">Learn more here</a>.</p>
  <p>Later this quarter, AI Foundation will include a new generative AI hub capability in SAP AI Core for accessing a broad range of large language models (LLMs) from third-party providers. With the hub, developers will be able to use tooling for prompt engineering and experimentation to accelerate generative AI application development.</p>
  <h2 id="ai-powered-business-data">AI-Powered Business Data</h2>
  <p>SAP believes every data professional should have seamless and scalable access to mission-critical business data. To this end, we’ve announced new innovations that empower developers to build intelligent data applications with SAP HANA Cloud but also brings new capabilities that not only enhance the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/features.html#business-data-fabric">business data fabric</a> with SAP Datasphere.</p>
  <p>Good data is the foundation of good AI, and SAP HANA Cloud continues to pioneer innovation in the data space by adding new vector database features to its multi-model offerings at no additional cost. Vector datastores manage unstructured data — such as text, images, or audio — to provide long-term memory and better context to AI models. This makes it easy to find and retrieve similar objects quickly. For example, users can search for suppliers based on the language in their contracts to examine payment history and trace individual orders. These powerful new vector database features enhance interactions between LLMs and an organization’s mission-critical data. The innovation puts SAP developers at the forefront of delivering radically new levels of data insight within a secure, private framework that uses industry-specific customer data to reduce hallucinations.</p>
  <p>New semantic onboarding capabilities within <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">SAP Datasphere</a> enable customers to deliver business-ready data products at an accelerated pace. With the powerful semantic layer, organizations can build data products that maintain business context and application logic and forego the time-consuming tasks of extracting business data, creating data pipelines and rebuilding data context that was lost. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/guided-experience.html">Learn more here</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="enterprise-automation">Enterprise Automation</h2>
  <p>Integrating, analyzing, and automating end-to-end business processes is critical in today’s digital landscape. To help customers stay ahead of the competition, SAP offers <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/enterprise-automation.html?pdf-asset=d237f8b9-7e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=1">enterprise automation</a>, one solution that combines the value of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/integration-suite.html">SAP Integration Suite</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-process-transformation.html">SAP Signavio</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/low-code.html">SAP Build</a>. At SAP TechEd, we previewed new generative AI capabilities to simplify creating processes and integrations and to recommend pre-built content. Deeper integrations across the three technologies helps companies easily mine non-SAP processes to better analyze, integrate, automate, and monitor business processes across their environment. <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2023/05/17/introducing-new-capabilities-for-enterprise-automation/">Learn more here</a>.</p>
  <p>See you at SAP TechEd in 2024!</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>JG Chirapurath is chief marketing and solutions officer for SAP BTP and Artificial Intelligence at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-coverage-and-stories-from-sap-teched-in-2023">Get the latest news, coverage, and stories from SAP TechEd in 2023</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-teched">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/application-development</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/integration</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CTO Juergen Mueller at SAP TechEd: SAP at the Forefront of Generative AI Development]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-teched-cto-juergen-mueller-generative-ai-development</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-teched-cto-juergen-mueller-generative-ai-development</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[On stage at SAP TechEd, CTO Juergen Mueller shared the company’s bold vision to be the leading business AI company by 2025.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/application-development</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-build</category>
            <category>product/sap-build-code</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Turns Every Developer Into a Generative AI Developer at SAP TechEd in 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-teched-2023-generative-ai-developers</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-teched-2023-generative-ai-developers</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[From SAP TechEd, SAP has unveiled new innovations in generative AI, vector database capabilities, and new learning opportunities.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1372d56f0d8353651580c6665a37ae494d4534f9d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1372d56f0d8353651580c6665a37ae494d4534f9d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1372d56f0d8353651580c6665a37ae494d4534f9d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Turns Every Developer Into a Generative AI Developer at SAP TechEd in 2023" src="./media_1372d56f0d8353651580c6665a37ae494d4534f9d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-turns-every-developer-into-a-generative-ai-developer-at-sap-teched-in-2023">SAP Turns Every Developer Into a Generative AI Developer at SAP TechEd in 2023</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>BANGALORE</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p>At the SAP TechEd event in 2023, <a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) announced a comprehensive series of generative AI capabilities and advancements aimed at empowering developers of all skill levels to supercharge their businesses in the age of AI.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h2 id="sap-unveils-innovations-in-generative-ai-application-development-and-vector-database-capabilities-as-well-as-new-learning-opportunities-for-developers-in-the-era-of-ai">SAP Unveils Innovations in Generative AI Application Development and Vector Database Capabilities as Well as New Learning Opportunities for Developers in the Era of AI</h2>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="enterprise-innovation-in-the-age-of-ai">Enterprise Innovation in the Age of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/teched/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Today’s dynamic technology and business landscape means every developer needs to be an AI developer,” said Juergen Mueller, Chief Technology Officer and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “The innovations we’re launching at SAP TechEd, from AI-infused pro-code tools to a one-stop shop to create generative AI extensions and applications on SAP Business Technology Platform, support the developers at the heart of the AI revolution and provide them with resources they need to transform the way businesses run.”</p>
  <p>As organizations aim to derive business value from generative AI, effective collaboration between professional and citizen developers is essential. SAP is launching the SAP Build Code solutions, which streamline cooperation with business experts who use the low-code <a href="/2022/11/sap-teched-sap-build-business-expertise-coursera-partnership">SAP Build</a> solutions launched at SAP TechEd in 2022. Uniquely built for SAP applications and the SAP ecosystem, SAP Build Code solutions offer AI-powered productivity tools for developers and are optimized for Java and JavaScript development. SAP Build Code also draws on the power of SAP’s new generative AI copilot Joule – the copilot that truly understands business – to further boost productivity, embedding code generation capabilities for data model, application logic and test script creation.</p>
  <p>Good data is the foundation of good AI, and SAP HANA Cloud continues to pioneer innovation in the data space by adding new vector database features to its multimodel offerings at no additional cost. Vector data stores manage unstructured data – such as text, images or audio – to provide long-term memory and better context to AI models. This makes it easy to find and retrieve similar objects quickly. For example, users can search for suppliers based on the language in their contracts to examine payment history and trace individual orders. These powerful new vector database features enhance interactions between large language models and an organization’s mission-critical data. The innovation helps put SAP developers at the forefront of delivering radically new levels of data insight within a secure, private framework that uses industry-specific customer data to reduce hallucinations.</p>
  <p>AI Foundation on SAP BTP, a new one-stop shop for developers to create AI- and generative AI-powered extensions and applications on SAP BTP, will further help increase developers’ impact and efficiency. AI Foundation includes everything developers need to start creating business-ready AI tools on SAP BTP – from ready-to-use AI services and access to the top large language models to vector database capabilities and AI runtime and lifecycle management.</p>
  <p>The rapid pace of technological innovation has driven up global demand for skilled developers – and SAP is increasing its learning opportunities in tandem. As part of a commitment to upskill two million professionals by 2025 and complement free AI learning content already available, SAP today launched <a href="https://learning.sap.com/certification/sap-certified-associate-back-end-developer-abap-cloud?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-LSC-TechEd">new role-based certification</a> and free learning resources for back-end developers using the ABAP Cloud development model. The two new learning resources covering ABAP development tools on SAP BTP and SAP S/4HANA are available on the <a href="https://learning.sap.com/?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-LSC-TechEd">SAP Learning site</a>. They are designed for agile and cloud-compliant business transformation, providing developers with skills to build cloud-ready extensions that are aligned with SAP’s clean core strategy. SAP <a href="/">has also joined</a> the Stanford HAI (Institute for Human-Centered AI) <a href="https://hai.stanford.edu/corporate-affiliate-program">Corporate Affiliate Program</a>. Researchers and engineers at SAP will work with the Stanford academic community, including research faculty and students, on the intersection of generative AI and business.</p>
  <p>For details on all the announcements made at SAP TechEd in 2023, please <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/events/teched/news-guide.html">visit our news guide here</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-teched-in-2023-join-us-live-in-bangalore-or-attend-virtually">SAP TechEd in 2023: Join us live in Bangalore or attend virtually</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/teched/bangalore.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent, sustainable enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 26 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 (626) 265-0370, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a>, PT<br>Stacy Ries, +1 (484) 619-0411, <a href="mailto:stacy.ries@sap.com">stacy.ries@sap.com</a>, ET<br>Marcus Winkler, +49 6227-767497, <a href="mailto:marcus.winkler@sap.com">marcus.winkler@sap.com</a>, CEST<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2022 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2023 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/abap-cloud</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-build</category>
            <category>product/sap-build-code</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/stanford-hai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Supercharging Developer Productivity with SAP Build Code]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-teched-2023-sap-build-code-supercharge-developer-productivity</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-teched-2023-sap-build-code-supercharge-developer-productivity</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP TechEd Bangalore, SAP has announced SAP Build Code, a true game-changer for all SAP developers. Learn more about the new offering.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/application-development</category>
            <category>news-tag/developers</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP TechEd in 2023: Explore the Latest Innovations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/sap-teched-in-2023-explore-the-latest-innovations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/sap-teched-in-2023-explore-the-latest-innovations</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP announced SAP Build Code, SAP HANA Cloud vector engine, and many more innovations at SAP TechEd this year.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Power to the People: SAP Unleashes Today's Business Experts and Tomorrow's Tech Talent]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-build-at-sap-teched-power-to-the-people</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-build-at-sap-teched-power-to-the-people</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get the scoop on SAP Build at SAP TechEd, including what the low-code offering will give to the millions of people who use SAP every day.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/coursera</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-build</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Tech Integration Blurs Lines and Saves Time | SAP TechEd in 2022]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/how-tech-integration-blurs-lines-and-saves-time-sap-teched-in-2022</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/how-tech-integration-blurs-lines-and-saves-time-sap-teched-in-2022</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Day two of SAP TechEd 2022 was all about technology integration! Creating a seamless experience between SAP’s cutting-edge technologies saves users’ most valuable resource: time....]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12170eb30145b2da1ccda2e9ed68397aba417d373.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12170eb30145b2da1ccda2e9ed68397aba417d373.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12170eb30145b2da1ccda2e9ed68397aba417d373.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Integration, Technology and Innovation at SAP TechEd in 2022" src="./media_12170eb30145b2da1ccda2e9ed68397aba417d373.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-tech-integration-blurs-lines-and-saves-time--sap-teched-in-2022">How Tech Integration Blurs Lines and Saves Time | SAP TechEd in 2022</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12170eb30145b2da1ccda2e9ed68397aba417d373.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12170eb30145b2da1ccda2e9ed68397aba417d373.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12170eb30145b2da1ccda2e9ed68397aba417d373.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Integration, Technology and Innovation at SAP TechEd in 2022" src="./media_12170eb30145b2da1ccda2e9ed68397aba417d373.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/KC_ini_1Bhg">Integration, Technology and Innovation at SAP TechEd in 2022</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Day two of SAP TechEd 2022 was all about technology integration!</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Creating a seamless experience between SAP’s cutting-edge technologies saves users’ most valuable resource: time. Check out how blurring the lines between individual solutions can make productivity tools far more powerful – and why the SAP developer community is leveling up SAP’s game!</p>
  <p><a href="https://sap.to/6052M02YG">Learn more.</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Pledges to Equip Underrepresented Groups with Digital Skills, Announces Partnership with Coursera to Reach Millions of Learners Worldwide]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-coursera-partnership-digital-skills-underrepresented-groups</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-coursera-partnership-digital-skills-underrepresented-groups</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A Coursera partnership and global skills initiative are part of SAP's efforts to grow a more diverse ecosystem of tech professionals.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/coursera</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Build: What’s Under the Hood?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2022/11/sap-build-capabilities-under-the-hood-sap-teched</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2022/11/sap-build-capabilities-under-the-hood-sap-teched</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Take a deeper look at SAP Build capabilities and how the low-code offering helps SAP customers deliver new, innovative solutions quickly.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-build</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unleashing Business Expertise with SAP Build]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/business-expertise-sap-build-sap-teched</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/business-expertise-sap-build-sap-teched</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Organizations must tap into employees' business expertise to excel in the next era of rapid business transformation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-build</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Launches SAP Build to Unleash Business Expertise, Partners with Coursera to Empower a New Generation of Developers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-teched-sap-build-business-expertise-coursera-partnership</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-teched-sap-build-business-expertise-coursera-partnership</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[From SAP TechEd, SAP launched new low-code offering SAP Build, along with a partnership with Coursera. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/coursera</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-build</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Brings Cloud Software Repurchases in Minutes to Customers and Partners]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-for-me-on-sap-store-cloud-software-repurchases</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-for-me-on-sap-store-cloud-software-repurchases</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP for Me on SAP Store, customer and partners have efficiency, simplicity, insights, and transparency into repurchasing and upselling.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Build Launched at SAP TechEd in 2022]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/sap-build-launched-at-sap-teched-in-2022</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/sap-build-launched-at-sap-teched-in-2022</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP launched SAP Build, a powerful new offering to drive the next wave of business transformation by unleashing the expertise of those who know best...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>product/sap-build</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP TechEd Is Back in Las Vegas – What a Day!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/sap-teched-is-back-in-las-vegas-what-a-day</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/sap-teched-is-back-in-las-vegas-what-a-day</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP TechEd is back – live, global, in person, and virtual! One event, multiple experiences! Get the recap on our day: We kicked off with...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP CTO Juergen Mueller at SAP TechEd in 2021: We Can Reinvent the Global Economy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-cto-juergen-mueller-at-sap-teched-in-2021-we-can-reinvent-the-global-economy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-cto-juergen-mueller-at-sap-teched-in-2021-we-can-reinvent-the-global-economy</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get a recap of the SAP CTO Juergen Mueller at SAP TechEd on the keynote stage, including how SAP is helping reinvent the global economy.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_191f9de1ccd2063bf3ea2a6f2f28afd66142e5e26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_191f9de1ccd2063bf3ea2a6f2f28afd66142e5e26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_191f9de1ccd2063bf3ea2a6f2f28afd66142e5e26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP CTO Juergen Mueller at SAP TechEd in 2021: We Can Reinvent the Global Economy" src="./media_191f9de1ccd2063bf3ea2a6f2f28afd66142e5e26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-cto-juergen-mueller-at-sap-teched-in-2021-we-can-reinvent-the-global-economy">SAP CTO Juergen Mueller at SAP TechEd in 2021: We Can Reinvent the Global Economy</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Juergen Mueller, chief technology officer and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE, kicked off <a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapteched2021/portal/page/overview?source=social-glo-sap-newsblog1">SAP TechEd in 2021</a> with a hard-hitting strategic view of the major challenges business face and how leaders and developers are partnering with SAP to reinvent the global economy.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As companies and consumers struggle with the pandemic’s ongoing health and economic crises, supply chain disruptions remain the norm, and accelerated digital transformation demands cloud-based innovation. These challenges are taking place against the backdrop of increasing climate change and calls for equality.</p>
  <p>Mueller discussed how we can reinvent the global economy to meet climate change targets, rethinking how we deliver and consume products and services, how we manage waste, and how we use technology. Pointing out that inequality was causing social unrest worldwide, Mueller said that organizations needed to help everyone develop the right skills, which would open opportunities for people to work where they fit best.</p>
  <p>After going big with his global change vision, Mueller and his special guests went deep into SAP’s commitment to supporting its ecosystem of cloud-based innovators, spotlighting the latest <a href="/2021/11/sap-teched-news-citizen-professional-developer-tools-embedded-ai-free-learning-experience">solution announcements</a>, real-world customer examples, demonstrations of new developer tools, and free access to learning resources.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-replays-from-sap-teched">Watch replays from SAP TechEd</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/events/teched.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="sap-helps-developers-innovate-at-scale-in-the-cloud">SAP Helps Developers Innovate at Scale in the Cloud</h2>
  <p>Mueller explained how RISE with SAP provides customers with a transition path to the cloud, while SAP continues to offer developers low-code/no-code and other tools to extend innovation on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a> built on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP)</a>. In a preview of his developer keynote, SAP developer advocate Rich Heilman shared how the just-announced SAP S/4HANA Cloud, ABAP environment, equipped developers to build custom ABAP extensions for the public cloud offering SAP S/4HANA Cloud.</p>
  <p>Mueller said the objective was to make the ABAP environment for SAP S/4HANA Cloud <strong>the</strong> environment to build tightly coupled extensions for all cloud editions of SAP S/4HANA based on the public cloud APIs. This will help developers build upgrade-safe extensions and move toward a clean core. Equally important, it closes the last extension gap in SAP S/4HANA Cloud to ease the transition from on premise to the cloud.</p>
  <h2 id="making-it-easy-to-innovate-on-sap-btp">Making It Easy to Innovate on SAP BTP</h2>
  <p>As an example of how SAP continues responding to ecosystem innovation imperatives, Mueller announced the roll-out of the free tier model for SAP BTP to individual developers, including <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/integration-suite.html">SAP Integration Suite</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hana/cloud.html">SAP HANA Cloud</a>. He was joined by Steffen Pietsch, head of Product Management for SAP BTP, who shared how developers can find available SAP BTP services, as well as use case examples to help build proofs of concept, on <a href="https://discovery-center.cloud.sap/">SAP Discovery Center</a>.</p>
  <p>Pietsch explained how a free tier makes it much easier to gain experience and start to innovate with SAP BTP. Developers can now build their proofs of concept on SAP BTP without any commitment; if they decide to move their applications toward productive usage, they can do so by changing from the free to the productive service plan without rebuilding the entire application in a different account.</p>
  <h2 id="low-codeno-code-speeds-up-development-on-sap-btp">Low-Code/No-Code Speeds Up Development on SAP BTP</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-sap-teched-news-guide">Read the SAP TechEd News Guide</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://sap.com/teched-news-guide">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Acknowledging the tech talent gap and the growing importance of citizen developers, Mueller said that SAP has doubled down on investments in low-code/no-code tools, announcing the launch of a unified <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/events/teched-news-guide/low-code-no-code-pro-code.html#top">low-code/no-code development experience</a> on SAP BTP. He said that SAP was introducing SAP AppGyver for no-code development, and making the <a href="https://www.sapstore.com/solutions/45318/SAP-Business-Application-Studio---the-evolution-of-SAP-Web-IDE">SAP Business Application Studio</a> available for low-code development. He also previewed <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/events/teched-news-guide/low-code-no-code-pro-code.html#article2">SAP Process Automation</a>, a no-code automation solution, showing the audience how non-technical business people, along with designers and experienced developers, can extend SAP Service Cloud with machine learning to quickly resolve customer service issues and speed up order approvals.</p>
  <p>Mueller said that low-code/no-code means both citizen and professional developers can increase productivity and innovate at scale, reflecting how business and IT work together. He saw this unlocking a new order of magnitude of value creation for individuals and society at-large.</p>
  <h2 id="gain-sap-specific-knowledge-free-of-charge">Gain SAP-Specific Knowledge Free of Charge</h2>
  <p>Reinforcing SAP’s commitment to developer learning, Mueller outlined the company’s newly-launched learning experience, <a href="https://learning.sap.com/">SAP Learning now available for free</a>. The centerpiece consisted of seven SAP BTP-specific learning journeys, with more to come.</p>
  <p>He said that the new learner experience was designed for all developer skill levels, including pro-code developers, IT professionals, academic students, and technology thought leaders. Noting that becoming a trusted SAP expert with certified skills has never been easier, Mueller saw all “makers” learning comprehensive skills by taking <a href="https://learning.sap.com/learning-journey">free-of-charge learning journeys</a> to qualify for <a href="https://learning.sap.com/certification">SAP certifications</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-btp-foundation-of-the-intelligent-enterprise">SAP BTP: Foundation of the Intelligent Enterprise</h2>
  <p>Mueller capped his keynote off with an example from Porsche, which uses SAP Business Warehouse on SAP HANA and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/cloud-analytics.html">SAP Analytics Cloud</a> for accurate finance and investment planning across approximately 70 subsidiaries worldwide. Mueller held up Porsche as an example of the many companies worldwide using SAP solutions to simplify business processes and reporting with connected data. He announced the new SAP Data Warehouse Cloud, SAP BW bridge, allowing organizations to innovate faster by moving data from their existing SAP BW application to the SAP Data Warehouse Cloud solution.</p>
  <p>Mueller concluded with a heartfelt message to developers that as demand for SAP grows, the company’s ecosystem is an exciting place to be, nothing less than a true movement. Emphasizing that SAP BTP is the foundation of the intelligent enterprise, he encouraged developers to join in, using SAP’s tools for their success in supporting their companies and customers throughout their digital transformation journey.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me: @smgaler</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bring SAP S/4HANA Cloud to Your Data Center]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/bring-sap-s-4hana-cloud-to-your-data-center</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/bring-sap-s-4hana-cloud-to-your-data-center</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition, customer data center option is now part of RISE with SAP and includes support for Dell Technologies APEX.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ce9ab97a849e34f37f1e1fd43e11e90cba7948f4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ce9ab97a849e34f37f1e1fd43e11e90cba7948f4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ce9ab97a849e34f37f1e1fd43e11e90cba7948f4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Bring SAP S/4HANA Cloud to Your Data Center" src="./media_1ce9ab97a849e34f37f1e1fd43e11e90cba7948f4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="bring-sap-s4hana-cloud-to-your-data-center">Bring SAP S/4HANA Cloud to Your Data Center</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="rise-with-sap-simplify-the-transformation-of-your-business-for-the-digital-age">RISE with SAP: Simplify the transformation of your business for the digital age</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/rise.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Today, SAP is announcing the expansion of the customer data center option for RISE with SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This SAP ERP cloud offering provides license subscriptions to customers that want to gain cloud-like economies yet keep their SAP software landscape and data within their own data center, for geopolitical or data sovereignty concerns, for latency or application entanglement reasons, or for those customers who simply lack access to market-leading hyperscalers. <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/10/444af00c-057e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition, customer data center option</a> is now part of the RISE with SAP offering and includes support for Dell Technologies APEX.</p>
  <p>SAP S/4HANA enables customers to reinvent business and drive new revenue and profits, as well as provides access to amazing technologies that can:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Bring real-time decisions closer to the edge for increased agility</li>
    <li>Enable transformation of data into meaningful business insight</li>
    <li>Increase automation of business processes though artificial intelligence (AI)</li>
    <li>Develop deeper understanding of experiences across employees, products, and customers</li>
  </ul>
  <p>This and more is possible, all while working to reduce your data footprint and lower your overall total cost of ownership.</p>
  <p>RISE with SAP is a simplified and turnkey SAP ERP, private cloud edition deployment model that can reduce risk of implementation and outages, freeing up precious resources so customers can focus on truly vitalizing, cutting-edge technologies and business processes provided by SAP S/4HANA. You don’t have to go on your transformation journey alone.</p>
  <p>Customers told us that they need cloud-like experiences with SAP S/4HANA deployment flexibility and solutions that work in their own data center. Their reasons included the need to meet stringent compliance, security, or data sovereignty guidelines and limited access to hyperscalers. Some have geopolitical concerns. RISE with SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition, customer data center option delivers as-a-service, private cloud managed services, software, and infrastructure for leading business applications with simplicity and incredible uptime commitment to our customers.</p>
  <p>Dell Technologies APEX for SAP S/4HANA is scalable and secure, providing customers that want to run in their own data centers data sovereignty and the peace of mind in knowing where their data is located throughout its life cycle.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-the-sap-s4hana-cloud-private-edition-overview-video">Watch the SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition overview video</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/10/6e5c667b-2a7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With the availability of Dell Technologies APEX as the underlying infrastructure for the customer data center option – for data center and colocation deployments <em>–</em> our customers now have access to leading SAP solutions in a cloud operating model across more geographies.</p>
  <p>“Our longtime partnership supports thousands of organizations around the world and is critical in their business and IT transformations. By marrying Dell and SAP technologies to create Dell Technologies APEX for SAP S/4HANA, we are providing an agile as-a-service infrastructure that paves the way for on-premise cloud solutions a customer can control without disrupting critical workloads in the data center,” says Travis Vigil, senior vice president, Portfolio and Product Management, Infrastructure Solutions Group at Dell</p>
  <p>Together, SAP and Dell Technologies provide a radically simplified as-a-service and cloud experience under one contract, so you can react quickly to capture new opportunities and work to ensure that your technology stays aligned with business requirements. With SAP leading the engagement, Dell Technologies will supply, install, monitor, and manage the required infrastructure for the customer’s landscape in a secured environment. By expanding our solution to include Dell Technologies APEX offerings, in addition to Lenovo TruScale™ and HPE GreenLake, SAP broadens customer flexibility and choice.</p>
  <p>These ecosystem powerhouses enable an open innovation approach that puts customers’ needs first as they start the journey to become an intelligent enterprise. With SAP and partners like these, how can you fail?</p>
  <p>Free your operations team to do new and exciting initiatives, move from CAPEX to OPEX, increase your agility, resilience, and sustainability, and let us help you securely manage the rest. Talk to your account representative today.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Peter Pluim is president of SAP Enterprise Cloud Services at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-teched">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP TechEd</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sap-teched">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-cloud-application-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-hana-enterprise-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Everyone Can Be a Developer: SAP Introduces Tools for Citizen and Professional Developers, Embedded AI, and a Free Learning Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-teched-news-citizen-professional-developer-tools-embedded-ai-free-learning-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-teched-news-citizen-professional-developer-tools-embedded-ai-free-learning-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get the SAP TechEd news for 2021, which includes tools for citizen and professional developers, embedded AI, and a free learning experience.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-appgyver</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fiori</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Now Provides a Unified Low-Code/No-Code Offering]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-now-provides-unified-low-code-no-code-offering</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-now-provides-unified-low-code-no-code-offering</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP BTP allows customers to achieve business agility, specifically with the help of the new unified low-code/no-code offering. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13f25959e37ea308f738565d586dacbd74230cff3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13f25959e37ea308f738565d586dacbd74230cff3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_13f25959e37ea308f738565d586dacbd74230cff3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Now Provides a Unified Low-Code/No-Code Offering" src="./media_13f25959e37ea308f738565d586dacbd74230cff3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-now-provides-a-unified-low-codeno-code-offering">SAP Now Provides a Unified Low-Code/No-Code Offering</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP) allows our customers to achieve business agility, specifically with the help of our new unified low-code/no-code offering. With our low-code and no-code capabilities, we enable everyone to deliver innovation faster and confidently across all lines of business and industries.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP provides:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>An integrated suite of end-to-end business applications</strong> to run your business across all industries and lines of business</li>
    <li><strong>A comprehensive business-centric platform</strong>, with a unified programming model and unified design system, bringing IT and business together to modernize processes and enable rapid innovation – now</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The low-code/no-code offering services in SAP BTP empower IT and citizen developers alike to quickly build enterprise-ready apps, automations, workflows, and chatbots no matter their skill level or coding expertise. Our customers can build enterprise apps fast with SAP’s unified development experience and an ever-growing array of pre-built business content for any line of business, all natively integrated with your SAP applications.</p>
  <p>Examples include <a href="https://store.irpa.cfapps.eu10.hana.ondemand.com/#/explore/order=last-updated%2Cdesc">more than 260 pre-built robotic processing automation (RPA) bots</a> to automate tasks in any line of business – be it finance, sourcing and procurement, manufacturing, sales, and services – and almost <a href="https://api.sap.com/content-type/Workflow/workflowmanagement/packages">40 live process content packages</a> for the SAP Workflow Management service.</p>
  <p>Another example is SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone, which offers a prepackaged experience specifically to address the needs of HR organizations based on SAP Work Zone, with additional functionality such as workflow and mobile services. It has been <a href="/2021/09/hr-executive-top-product-sap-successfactors-work-zone">recognized recently as a Top HR Product</a> by <a href="https://hrexecutive.com/">Human Resource Executive</a> and the <a href="https://www.hrtechnologyconference.com/">HR Technology Conference</a>. Additionally, SAP Business Application Studio comes with pre-built components, wizards, and sample apps.</p>
  <p>SAP unifies the developer experience with low-code and no-code enhancements on SAP BTP to help:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Maximize speed and agility</strong> and <strong>reduce total cost of ownership (TCO)</strong> through accelerated delivery</li>
    <li><strong>Bridge the gap</strong> and <strong>increase adoption</strong> through co-development between business and IT</li>
    <li><strong>Enhance return on investment (ROI)</strong> by leveraging existing investments through seamless integrations</li>
    <li><strong>Accelerate time to value</strong> by implementing best practices with pre-built content packages</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Our low-code/no-code offering covers three areas:</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ba9fc49787f0db173238260324e73caf06eb2b55.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ba9fc49787f0db173238260324e73caf06eb2b55.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ba9fc49787f0db173238260324e73caf06eb2b55.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Diagram explaining the new low-code/no-code offering" src="./media_1ba9fc49787f0db173238260324e73caf06eb2b55.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1696" height="762">
    </picture>For <strong>process automation</strong>, we offer SAP Workflow Management and SAP Intelligent RPA, enabling citizen developers to easily build workflows and to automate tasks. On top of that, SAP Process Automation can bring no-code process automation to the next level. SAP Process Automation is currently available for co-innovation partners, with general availability planned for the first quarter of 2022.
  </p>
  <p>For <strong>low-code/no-code application composition</strong>, we launched SAP AppGyver and new functionalities in SAP Business Application Studio to enable the entire developer continuum to accelerate application development. SAP AppGyver allows citizen developers to build highly sophisticated standalone applications or extensions without writing a single line of code. With SAP Business Application Studio, we also deliver a simplified application development journey to the professional developer with a low-code perspective.</p>
  <p>In the area of <strong>digital experience</strong>, we are offering SAP Work Zone, SAP Launchpad, and SAP Mobile Start to help drive employee productivity and make newly built apps available to everyone in the company.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-btp-accelerate-business-outcomes-with-integration-data-to-value-and-extensibility">SAP BTP: Accelerate business outcomes with integration, data to value, and extensibility</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="what-else-is-new-at-sap-teched">What Else Is New at SAP TechEd?</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-acquires-no-code-development-pioneer-appgyver">SAP Acquires No-Code Development Pioneer AppGyver</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/02/sap-acquire-appgyver">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Let’s go into some specifics for each of the areas in our new unified low-code/no-code offering:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>SAP Business Application Studio has seen a dramatic improvement in development productivity through the low-code/no-code experience now available.</li>
    <li>We’ve also fully integrated the acquisition in the no-code space. SAP AppGyver is now part of CPEA, available to all our customers as well as planned through the free tier model in the first quarter of 2022.</li>
    <li>We’ve made significant improvements in our SAPUI5 technology performance, which can be of immediate benefit to SAP S/4HANA and any other SAP product built on top of the technology within SAP BTP.</li>
    <li>Launching SAP Process Automation brings an elevated user experience for citizen automation in a no-code development environment. To make citizen developers fully productive, the new solution provides end-to-end automation capabilities leveraging advanced workflow management and embedded RPA functionality in a simple drag-and-drop user interface.</li>
    <li>Last but not least, we’ve delivered artificial intelligence (AI) into our workflow engine, so that the AI system monitors the context with which you approve or not on a given workflow, building up the relevant models of your approval process flow. Your workflow becomes more and more intelligent over time, out of the box.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>I invite you to attend SAP TechEd sessions to learn more about our low-code/no-code offering and how SAP BTP is now accessible to anyone. You’ll find a selection of personally recommended sessions below. Let’s explore together how SAP BTP can help you rapidly integrate, automate, and extend business processes for security and performance at scale across your organization.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Recommended Sessions</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><em>Michael Weingartner is president of SAP Business Technology Platform Core at SAP.</em></p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-news-and-coverage-from-sap-teched">Read more news and coverage from SAP TechEd</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sap-teched">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/rpa</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-intelligent-rpa</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
            <category>product/sap-workflow-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A New Chapter for SAP Learning: Empowering Careers and Cultivating Skills for the Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-learning-site-empowering-careers-cultivating-skills</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-learning-site-empowering-careers-cultivating-skills</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The new SAP Learning site takes a new approach to delivering a digitally native and learner-focused experience. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1eb3d5dcede4d7060d6b549750fd52d6f37f7ecb4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1eb3d5dcede4d7060d6b549750fd52d6f37f7ecb4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1eb3d5dcede4d7060d6b549750fd52d6f37f7ecb4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="A New Chapter for SAP Learning: Empowering Careers and Cultivating Skills for the Future" src="./media_1eb3d5dcede4d7060d6b549750fd52d6f37f7ecb4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="a-new-chapter-for-sap-learning-empowering-careers-and-cultivating-skills-for-the-future">A New Chapter for SAP Learning: Empowering Careers and Cultivating Skills for the Future</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>We talk about it regularly: in the next decade, more than a billion workers will require reskilling. At the core of this tectonic shift in work is the integration of software-enabled innovation into every business process. SAP is the backbone of this change – it’s why we see massive demand for SAP skills across our customer environments and partner ecosystem. Those who can leverage SAP to deliver flexibility and harness opportunity are the instigators of innovation.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At SAP, we know that it’s a big responsibility to ensure that this knowledge is pervasive. That’s why we also recognize the need to simplify the act of reskilling. Our increasingly busy schedules and the fast pace of our day-to-day work often pull us away from learning. It’s not easy to find time to sharpen our skills and learn new ones.</p>
  <p>So, when you do make time to focus on your learning, the process of finding the right material should be simple and streamlined – and the content comprehensive. At SAP Learning, we’ve reinforced our commitment to removing barriers to learning by making it simpler to discover our content and easier to navigate our platforms.</p>
  <p>Because success is rooted in learning, it’s critical to have all the support you need right at your fingertips to move forward easily and consistently.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="turn-learning-into-achieving-with-sap-learning">Turn learning into achieving with SAP Learning</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://www.sap.com/training">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="empowering-the-individual-learner">Empowering the Individual Learner</h2>
  <p>Today’s learners demand a personalized experience to cultivate their skills. Almost every individual with an Internet connection has been introduced to the ease of consumer-grade applications – and we know that learning content competes with every distraction. To that end, it is critical to create engaging content and offer enjoyable experiences that empower individuals at every stage of their career and learning journey. Therefore, SAP Learning is taking a new approach to delivering a digitally native and learner-focused experience.</p>
  <p>As part of our ongoing and reimagined commitment to enhancing learning opportunities, we’ve launched an all-new <a href="https://learning.sap.com/">SAP Learning site</a> that includes a comprehensive array of learning content available in various formats – from expert-led sessions and hands-on training to microlearning videos. By opening the door to accessible opportunities for everyone to upskill, reskill, and validate SAP skills, we are focusing squarely on the success of <a href="/2021/10/preparing-partners-for-their-future-with-sap-learning">our ecosystem</a> and meeting our learners where they are. After all, learning should make your life easier, not more complicated.
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c5eff5fc2c74c83179837e7d0dbeefd83957434d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c5eff5fc2c74c83179837e7d0dbeefd83957434d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c5eff5fc2c74c83179837e7d0dbeefd83957434d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="New SAP Learning site" src="./media_1c5eff5fc2c74c83179837e7d0dbeefd83957434d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="733">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>We’re proud of the progress we’re making. We also look forward to hearing more feedback from our community so we can bring continuous improvement to our operations.</p>
  <h2 id="equipping-for-the-needs-of-tomorrow">Equipping for the Needs of Tomorrow</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-launches-free-student-offering-sap-learning-hub-edition-for-sap-next-gen">SAP Launches Free Student Offering: SAP Learning Hub, Edition for SAP Next-Gen</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/05/launch-sap-learning-hub-edition-for-sap-next-gen">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Designed to be simple and intuitive to navigate, the <a href="https://learning.sap.com/">SAP Learning site</a> will become the one-stop-shop that brings together the expansive portfolio of well-established SAP learning offerings. With <a href="/topics/sap-teched">our SAP TechEd releases</a>, learners in development roles as well as future developers can quickly start and gain SAP skills in core innovation areas and prepare for an <a href="https://learning.sap.com/certification?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-Certification">SAP Certification</a> at no cost. The site features access to various free content for upskilling with <a href="https://learning.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-BTP">SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP)</a>, including a brand-new learning journey focused on <a href="https://learning.sap.com/learning-journey/utilize-sap-build-for-low-code-no-code-applications-and-automations-for-citizen-developers?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-LCNC">how to develop low-code/no-code applications</a>.</p>
  <p>We’re also partnering with <a href="https://www.placement.com/">Placement</a>, a career coaching service provider, so that the first 1,000 developers who complete a certification exam on SAP BTP through the new site will receive a voucher for services like résumé review, LinkedIn screening, and career coaching. And now through November 2022, all registered learners on the SAP Learning site can utilize select services from Placement as well as enjoy access to Placement’s Job Board at a discounted price.</p>
  <p>Looking to the future, the site will continue to support all learners’ career development and accelerate broader organizational transformations by extending the scope to include all free SAP Learning content. For more details, watch the <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/11/8008e636-047e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">video</a> or check out the <a href="https://learning.sap.com/">new site</a> on your own.</p>
  <p>It’s never been easier to get started building and achieving SAP skills – and it’s only the beginning for this new chapter of SAP Learning.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Max Wessel is EVP and chief learning officer at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-news-and-coverage-from-sap-teched">Read more news and coverage from SAP TechEd</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sap-teched">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Join Experts Who Live and Breathe Innovation at SAP TechEd]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/innovation-at-sap-teched-join-experts</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/innovation-at-sap-teched-join-experts</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In 2021, join the experts who live and breathe innovation at SAP TechEd. Learn more about the event's packed itinerary.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10721d47f45f641339803a1b91af08b8c6a41dad7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10721d47f45f641339803a1b91af08b8c6a41dad7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10721d47f45f641339803a1b91af08b8c6a41dad7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Join Experts Who Live and Breathe Innovation at SAP TechEd" src="./media_10721d47f45f641339803a1b91af08b8c6a41dad7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="join-experts-who-live-and-breathe-innovation-at-sap-teched">Join Experts Who Live and Breathe Innovation at SAP TechEd</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>This year’s <a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapteched2021/portal/page/overview?source=social-glo-sap-newsblog1">SAP TechEd in 2021</a> event gathers the <a href="https://community.sap.com/">SAP community</a> under one virtual roof for 48 hours of nonstop learning and tons of fun with experts doing cool stuff with the latest SAP technologies.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/2021/10/register-for-sap-teched-learn-innovate-together">Earlier, I explained</a> how customers and partners are front and center this year, sharing their real-world experiences innovating with the latest and greatest SAP solutions across <a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapteched2021/portal/page/tracks">eight topic tracks.</a> Here’s the lowdown on a sampling of sessions from the can’t-miss agenda being broadcast November 16-18.</p>
  <h2 id="channel-1-rethink-the-status-quo-with-up-and-coming-disruptors">Channel 1: Rethink the Status Quo with Up-and-Coming Disruptors</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-news-and-coverage-from-sap-teched">Read more news and coverage from SAP TechEd</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sap-teched">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Design your learning adventure your way on <a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapteched2021/portal/page/channel1">Channel 1</a>, your always-on home for SAP TechEd in 2021. Built around the comfy places you know and love — kitchen, living room, developer lab, and rooftop, plus a brand new space to innovate — each Channel 1 hour-long broadcast is dedicated to a specific intelligent enterprise topic. These include enterprise artificial intelligence (AI), business process integration, emerging tech — think blockchain, the Internet of Things (IoT), robotic process automation (RPA) — and more.</p>
  <p>There is a slew of broadcasts covering how to <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/10/27/sap-teched-2021-use-cases-for-the-sap-business-technology-platform/">extend innovation</a> on major SAP cloud solutions such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a>, employee experience, customer experience, and intelligent spend management.</p>
  <p>Most important, you will see how leading-edge customers and partners are well into their digital transformation journey applying SAP intelligence, data, analytics, and other solutions and tools to extend innovation on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP)</a>.</p>
  <p>Check out the Channel 1 schedule beforehand to select which sessions are most important to you. Or go with the flow and tune in anytime during the 48-hour streaming broadcast to see what is going on. Either way, you will on get the inside story on strategic innovation from candid interviews and community roundtables featuring conversations with customers, partners, and other industry influencers.</p>
  <p>You can gain insights from big-picture perspectives and learn how to make your ideas come to life by watching product demonstrations that deliver real-life results. Expect the unexpected from scheduled and surprise guests that include tutorials with recognized social influencers, lessons learned from well-known customers, and SAP solution updates.</p>
  <p>Experts, including speakers and developer advocates, will answer your live chat questions in the moment, and moderators will consider your submitted tweets for sharing to the entire SAP community.</p>
  <h2 id="get-answers-from-sap-executives">Get Answers from SAP Executives</h2>
  <p>On day one, join the <a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapteched2021/portal/page/sessions/session/1632238246234001c9Hx">executive keynote</a> with Juergen Mueller, chief technology officer and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE, to learn how SAP’s passionate community has been instrumental in powering business resilience in the face of ongoing disruption. Mueller will provide a look back at how SAP has kept its promises to the developer community, plus a leap ahead showing how developers have even more pathways to co-innovate for business results using the latest tools extending SAP BTP. Mueller and special guests will explore what it takes for success, showcasing lessons learned from the growing SAP community of makers that are helping organizations worldwide become intelligent enterprises. Wherever you are in your career, you’ll learn how you can immediately get involved with SAP and build the sustainable world you want to live in.</p>
  <p>Be sure to catch the <a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapteched2021/portal/page/sessions/session/1632238356956001k8N5">executive Q&#x26;A</a> with Mueller and his fellow Executive Board members, Julia White, chief marketing and solutions officer, and Thomas Saueressig, SAP Product Engineering. After industry experts share their reactions to the keynotes, these SAP Executive Board members will answer your questions, live and unscripted.</p>
  <p>On day two, check out the <a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapteched2021/portal/page/sessions/session/1632238684525001QKhY">developer keynote</a> when developer advocates and friends will freely share their knowledge about the simple yet powerful tools behind SAP’s cloud-first strategy that put services and platforms at every developer’s fingertips. From CLI tools for SAP BTP to UI technologies, data federation, low-code/no-code wizards, and more you’ll find out how easy it is to get started and innovate fast. Whether you are creating end-to-end solutions or extending existing applications, these demonstrations will build your understanding of SAP technologies and how you can use them to address your organization’s major challenges.</p>
  <p>Before you go, don’t miss the <a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapteched2021/portal/page/sessions/session/1632238899470001cAnt">closing show and celebration</a>, your opportunity to ask any last questions and hear the winners of <a href="https://developers.sap.com/devtoberfest.html">Devtoberfest</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="register-for-sap-teched-today">Register for SAP TechEd today</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapteched2021/portal/page/overview?source=social-glo-sap-newsblog1">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="registration-is-open-now-visit-the-sap-teched-website-for-the-complete-agenda-and-sign-up-details">Registration is open now. Visit the <a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapteched2021/portal/page/overview?source=social-glo-sap-newsblog1">SAP TechEd website</a> for the complete agenda and sign-up details.</h3>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me: @smgaler</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Reasons to Register for SAP TechEd in 2021: Learn. Innovate. Together.]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/register-for-sap-teched-learn-innovate-together</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/register-for-sap-teched-learn-innovate-together</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn why you should register for SAP TechEd today and join the SAP community for this entirely free and virtual signature event.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f44156f1927489bcdd7ff0eb7af713091234d57b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f44156f1927489bcdd7ff0eb7af713091234d57b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f44156f1927489bcdd7ff0eb7af713091234d57b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Three Reasons to Register for SAP TechEd in 2021: Learn. Innovate. Together." src="./media_1f44156f1927489bcdd7ff0eb7af713091234d57b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="three-reasons-to-register-for-sap-teched-in-2021-learn-innovate-together">Three Reasons to Register for SAP TechEd in 2021: Learn. Innovate. Together.</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapteched2021/portal/page/overview?source=social-glo-sap-newsblog1">SAP TechEd in 2021</a> is shaping up to be among the most memorably valuable experiences for developers this year and beyond.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Registration just kicked off for this entirely free virtual event, being held November 16-18, revealing a thoughtfully curated agenda where SAP and industry experts, along with an unprecedented number of customers and partners, will share strategic insights, the latest innovations, and best practices. Above all, this year’s event puts customers and partners in the spotlight.</p>
  <p>“More than ever, this year’s SAP TechEd reflects our commitment to deliver a continuous, personalized learning journey that inspires and engages our 2.8 million strong <a href="https://community.sap.com/">SAP Community</a>,” said Juergen Mueller, chief technology officer and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “We designed the complete agenda around greater opportunities to network with like-minded innovators in real-world, fun experiences. Half of our hands-on workshop sessions have unlimited seating, so that any number of attendees can join live and watch experts perform and explain exercises, which can then be done by anyone at their own pace. You’ll also learn directly from customers and partners on how to apply the latest SAP technologies to innovate for your professional career development and help your organization become an intelligent enterprise.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="register-for-sap-teched-now">Register for SAP TechEd now</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapteched2021/portal/page/overview?source=social-glo-sap-newsblog1">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="innovate-with-sap-where-it-matters-for-you">Innovate with SAP Where It Matters for You</h2>
  <p>The entire SAP TechEd line-up of expert sessions, dynamic hands-on workshops, and live Channel 1 broadcasts is structured around <a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapteched2021/portal/page/tracks">eight topic tracks</a>:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Database and Data Management</li>
    <li>Analytics</li>
    <li>Application Development and Integration</li>
    <li>Intelligent Technologies</li>
    <li>Intelligent Suite Solutions and Processes</li>
    <li>Integrated Intelligent Suite</li>
    <li>Digital Transformation with Intelligent ERP</li>
    <li>Partner Innovation with SAP</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Select the learning experience most valuable for you, given your career and company objectives and specific technology interests. Join expert sessions for a strategic view of how developers and other technologists are using the SAP platform to help their organizations become intelligent enterprises. Jump into hands-on workshops to watch solution demos and try out creating extensions on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP)</a> of innovations extending the SAP intelligent suite of applications – no pre-booking required.</p>
  <p>Tune in anytime to Channel 1 for live, quick takes with world-class guests who will share their unique perspectives on game-changing topics.</p>
  <h2 id="immerse-yourself-in-real-world-innovations-with-customers-and-sap-experts">Immerse Yourself in Real-World Innovations with Customers and SAP Experts</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-technology-platform-accelerate-business-outcomes-with-integration-data-to-value-and-extensibility">SAP Business Technology Platform: Accelerate business outcomes with integration, data to value, and extensibility</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This year, customers and partners will be front and center, directly sharing how they are using SAP BTP to solve their biggest business challenges. They’re bringing what we call their “use case factory,” so you can learn from their experiences, by industry and SAP solution. You can get answers to your burning questions in live Q&#x26;As or watch the replays at your convenience. They’ll be backed up by sessions with SAP experts sharing the latest product road maps and best practices curated from across the SAP community.</p>
  <h2 id="build-your-community-to-win-together">Build Your Community to Win Together</h2>
  <p>SAP TechEd is much more than two days of nonstop education. It’s part of a continuous learning experience that brings together the entire SAP ecosystem during this signature event, as well as enablement opportunities throughout the year.</p>
  <p>Sessions and workshops will feature recommended resources to expand your knowledge such as accessing code on <a href="https://github.com/">GitHub</a> and exploring proven use cases on <a href="https://discovery-center.cloud.sap/missiondetail/3501/3542/">SAP Discovery Center</a>. Expand your learning, productivity, and performance with tailored learning from SAP, including certification opportunities in the <a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapteched2021/portal/page/learningzone">SAP Learning Zone.</a></p>
  <p>SAP TechEd registration is open now. Visit the <a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapteched2021/portal/page/overview?source=social-glo-sap-newsblog1">SAP TechEd in 2021 website</a> for full details about the agenda and sign-up details.</p>
  <p><em>Follow me: @smgaler</em></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>