<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/industry/chemicals/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Chemicals Supplier BYK Harmonized Supply Chain Planning Processes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/byk-harmonized-supply-chain-planning-processes</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/byk-harmonized-supply-chain-planning-processes</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[BYK, a global supplier of specialty chemicals, has implemented a new supply chain demand planning system using SAP solutions. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-supply-chain-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kemira Leaps Forward with SAP and cbs Corporate Business Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/kemira-leaps-forward-with-sap-and-cbs</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/kemira-leaps-forward-with-sap-and-cbs</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Industrial enterprise Kemira launched its digital business process platform based on SAP with help from cbs Corporate Business Solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Can the Chemicals Industry Capitalize On Carbon Reduction Opportunities?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/chemicals-industry-sustainability-carbon-reduction-opportunities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/chemicals-industry-sustainability-carbon-reduction-opportunities</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Companies in the chemicals industry that look to sustainability and carbon reduction will be able to future-proof their business.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10349c35f3512c6fdd74903bfb6f42dba5cc51705.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10349c35f3512c6fdd74903bfb6f42dba5cc51705.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10349c35f3512c6fdd74903bfb6f42dba5cc51705.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How Can the Chemicals Industry Capitalize On Carbon Reduction Opportunities?" src="./media_10349c35f3512c6fdd74903bfb6f42dba5cc51705.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-can-the-chemicals-industry-capitalize-on-carbon-reduction-opportunities">How Can the Chemicals Industry Capitalize On Carbon Reduction Opportunities?</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The chemicals industry is a $4 trillion business employing upwards of 20 million people. While a consumer of high volumes of energy and resources, it is also at the forefront of developing energy efficiencies, low carbon and renewable raw materials and fuels, chemical energy storage, and materials from CO2 capture. It is also uniquely positioned to pioneer and promote circular economy models by innovating for the easier reuse and recycling of materials.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It is simultaneously the third highest contributor to carbon emissions in the industrial sector and the best placed industry to decarbonize products across a multitude of industries.</p>
  <p>As a result of its position high upstream in the supply chain, the chemicals industry can often seem invisible. Its products sit in the value chain of key industries including agriculture, pharmaceuticals, and consumer goods, making up a significant proportion of their Scope 3 emissions. But change is coming that will make companies more accountable for these previously hidden emissions. New legislation such as the European Corporate Sustainability Reporting Directive (CSRD) will reveal the carbon footprint of the chemicals industry as companies with more than 250 employees will be required to report their GHG emissions, including those that lie in Scope 3.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="create-innovative-new-products-increase-agility-and-drive-greener-growth">Create innovative new products, increase agility, and drive greener growth</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/chemicals.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="a-vision-for-the-chemicals-industry">A Vision for the Chemicals Industry</h2>
  <p>In order to meet new legal requirements and identify opportunities for emissions reduction, the chemicals industry needs to look beyond its current tools and collaborations to upgrade the quality of data — based on primary information rather than averages and estimates — and share access to it. Aligning data structures and using the same semantics will encourage competition among suppliers, galvanizing them to manufacture chemical products with ever lower carbon footprints, benefiting all downstream customers as well as the climate. To realize this vision, the solution will receive actual data from suppliers upstream, using a standardized methodology, allowing companies to calculate their own product carbon footprint so it can then be shared with downstream customers. For broad adoption, this carbon data exchange tool needs to be relatively simple while allowing for secure data exchange.</p>
  <p>The automotive industry already has a blueprint that the chemicals industry can adopt. It tracks material flows digitally throughout the entire supply chain. Catena-X allows companies to share standardized emissions data from their supply chain with confidence based on technology that provides an auditable chain of custody. This offers car manufacturers the information they need to make strategic decisions to reduce the carbon footprint of their products, embrace circularity, and increase the adoption of circular business models such as battery recycling. Some of the chemical companies that supply the automotive industry are already involved, such as BASF.</p>
  <p>“As an energy-intensive industry at the beginning of nearly all value chains, the chemical sector plays a key role in reducing global carbon footprint in manufacturing and beyond. Carbon footprint transparency at product level is a fundamental step to achieve this,” said Alessandro Pistillo, director of Digital Strategic Projects at BASF. “BASF is a founding member and very active contributor in global initiatives focused on Scope 3 transparency and product carbon footprint standardization such as Together for Sustainability in the chemical sector, as well as Catena-X and the Global Battery Alliance in the automotive and battery value chain respectively. At the same time, BASF is also a leading member of WBCSD-PACT, whose framework is geared toward ensuring cross-sectoral interoperability.”</p>
  <h2 id="improved-accuracy">Improved Accuracy</h2>
  <p>Historically, industry averages and secondary data have been used to estimate carbon footprints. The cornerstone of the vision for the chemicals industry involves a significant improvement in GHG emissions data, a step that will provide much greater emissions transparency for the industry itself and for its customers. SAP has been working with the World Business Council for Sustainable Development (WBCSD) since 2021 as an innovation partner and has been involved in the Partnership for Carbon Transparency (PACT) initiative, helping to develop the global standards, methodology, and technological infrastructure needed for product-level emission accounting and exchange.</p>
  <h2 id="collaborative-data-exchange">Collaborative Data Exchange</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="record-report-and-act-on-your-sustainability-goals-with-sap">Record, report, and act on your sustainability goals with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The desire and the frameworks for the chemicals industry to collaborate already exist. They date back to 1985, with the establishment of the Responsible Care program and the 2011 formation of industry body Together for Sustainability, a worldwide initiative to raise sustainability standards in the chemicals industry’s supply chain. Its members include some of the world’s largest chemical groups, represented by their chief procurement officers. Despite the industry’s ability and willingness to cooperate, and its current pilot IT system for sharing upstream product carbon footprint information, it is still on the cusp of data exchange.</p>
  <p>“Footprint data is there,” said Michael Sambeth, global enterprise architect at SAP. “It can be calculated using out-of-the-box solutions from SAP; now it needs to flow across the supply chain.”</p>
  <p><a href="/topics/catena-x">Catena-X</a> led to the launch of the SAP Sustainability Data Exchange application, which was designed specifically with security in mind, to exchange standardized carbon footprint data along the value chain. SAP Sustainability Data Exchange uses the carbon data standards established by WBCSD PACT. With a high proportion of Together for Sustainability members already using SAP ERP systems, they are well placed to be able to leverage SAP Sustainability Data Exchange to exchange this data with their suppliers and customers while adhering to global standards.</p>
  <h2 id="moving-to-a-green-ledger-approach">Moving to a Green Ledger Approach</h2>
  <p>The chemicals industry is a product of its established supply chains, high-volume activities, cost efficiencies, and scalability. It is highly organized and well versed in creating and following methodologies, but it needs to see the value in primary standardized data — and data sharing — for decarbonization.</p>
  <p>A <a href="/topics/green-ledger">green ledger approach</a> will allow businesses to treat their emissions in the same way as their financials. Carbon accounting makes emission “bookings” part of every business transaction in the same way as financial information. This means that a level of detail and confidence is achieved, allowing companies to look at emissions from any angle — by product, organization, profit center, site, factory, equipment, etc. This granularity is the foundation for planning and steering, which cannot be done using averages or highly aggregated figures.</p>
  <p>The decarbonization of a multitude of industries hinges on the ability of the chemicals industry to successfully standardize and exchange carbon footprint data. Only those chemical companies with sustainability at the core of their strategy and the right tools for high-quality emissions accounting will be able to future-proof their business to remain competitive in the face of the ever-evolving legislative changes created to combat the effects of global warming.</p>
  <p>For more information on how SAP helps companies record, report, and act on their sustainability goals, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">www.sap.com/sustainability</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/green-ledger</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Conversations about Leadership with Women in the Chemical and Steel Industries]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/women-leadership-in-chemical-and-steel-industries</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/women-leadership-in-chemical-and-steel-industries</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Women leaders discuss taking career risks, rising above gender stereotypes, and forging new paths in historically male-dominated industries.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-womens-network</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>industry/mining: industry/mill-products</category>
            <category>news-tag/women-in-leadership</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Road to Regeneration: Turning Toxic Mine Waste into Art]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/road-to-regeneration-beautiful-poison</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/road-to-regeneration-beautiful-poison</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how artists, citizens, business, and government are collaborating to restore waterways in Ohio in this Q&A from SAP Insights.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Road to Regeneration: Waste to Life]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/road-to-regeneration-waste-to-life</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/road-to-regeneration-waste-to-life</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how Rita Idehai helps Nigerian communities turn plastic waste into products, jobs, and revenue in this Q&A.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable Salmon Farming and the Future of Digital Procurement]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/evonik-industries-digital-procurement</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/evonik-industries-digital-procurement</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Digitalization frees up procurement to stay on top of fast-changing market conditions, including finding suppliers in unexpected disruptions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Upward Momentum Builds with Digitalization in the Chemicals Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/upward-momentum-digitalization-chemicals-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/upward-momentum-digitalization-chemicals-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the right approach to digitalization and the help of SAP Advisory Services, the chemicals industry can innovate across the value chain.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Upward Momentum Builds with Digitalization in the Chemicals Industry" src="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="upward-momentum-builds-with-digitalization-in-the-chemicals-industry">Upward Momentum Builds with Digitalization in the Chemicals Industry</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Chemical companies are on a nonstop roller coaster of market shocks and digital transformation. Sandwiched between feedstock and energy companies and downstream processing industries, they’re predestined to play a vital role in fulfilling business-to-business (B2B) and consumer expectations for sustainable, reliable, innovative, and trusted products and services.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But rising to the challenge of today’s marketplace – especially increasing raw material and energy prices, margin pressure, supply chain complexity, and regulatory requirements – requires much more than Industry 4.0 initiatives focused on efficiency and price reduction. From operational performance to customer experience, companies must integrate data from across the enterprise into a single source to form sound decisions that make sustainability profitable and profitability sustainable.</p>
  <p>Such a transformation is undoubtedly technology intensive, but the key enablers are also unassailably human. Understanding this reality, many chemical companies rely on the <a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/business-transformation.html">SAP Advisory Services</a> portfolio, provided by the Business Transformation Services group at SAP, to help transform their operations and gain a competitive edge amid fast global changes.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="transform-your-business-and-unlock-digital-innovation-with-help-from-sap-advisory-services">Transform your business and unlock digital innovation with help from SAP Advisory Services</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/business-transformation.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="turning-challenges-into-great-opportunities">Turning Challenges into Great Opportunities</h2>
  <p>Competitively addressing turbulence depends on the ability to view transformation through the lens of six fundamental challenges:</p>
  <p><strong>R&#x26;D Pressure across the Product Portfolio</strong> The imperative to resist margin shrinkage, mitigate risks, increase ROI, and boost growth calls for innovative products and services that offer business value and foster close partnerships with customers. By pushing forward the adoption of advanced technologies to drive global R&#x26;D, supplier, and customer collaborations and joint ventures, businesses can prevent commoditization.</p>
  <p><strong>The Need for Vertical Integration</strong> Evolving production facilities with a balance of high efficiency, global scale, flexibility, and intelligent responsiveness allows supply chains to weigh the synergistic benefits of integrated manufacturing plants or industrial parks against the flexibility of smaller plants. As a result, businesses can leverage new opportunities with disruptive business models, such as making raw materials instead of buying them and producing semi-finished or even finished goods.</p>
  <p><strong>Global Supply Chain Complexity</strong> Global supply chains must be secure enough to mitigate volatile market conditions, such as global health emergencies, rising prices for raw materials and energy, and other factors that impact economic conditions. Companies can gain this advantage by establishing commercial and logistical transparency to support optimization and global planning of demand, sales, and operations.</p>
  <p><strong>Hidden Advantages of Business Networks</strong> Business cannot stay competitive in a complex ecosystem alone. They must also scale and optimize their supply chain globally with business networks, such as the <a href="/2021/03/catena-x-automotive-alliance-picks-up-speed">Catena-X Automotive Network</a>. Doing so empowers suppliers, contract and toll manufacturers, joint ventures, and customers to collaborate openly and create new prospects for co-innovating better products and services, improving value chain efficiency, and fueling long-term growth.</p>
  <p><strong>Compliance and Sustainability Urgency</strong> A primary objective for any chemical business is ensuring compliance with industry regulations. Yet, B2B customers also favor suppliers that help meet their own environmental, social, and governance (ESG) mandates. Sustainable businesses and innovations provide balance between these two expectations, creating a highly sought-after competitive edge by gearing products and services towards a circular economy.</p>
  <p><strong>Business Agility</strong> The industry’s dynamic and fast-changing environment of mergers, acquisitions, and divestitures is creating tremendous complexity and pressure for permanent change and adaptation. Chemical companies need to balance industry-wide globalization and centralization while increasing business agility.</p>
  <p>Chemical companies with a digital strategy encompassing all these topics can address industry challenges and seize on market trends in a disruptive manner. Through <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2016/03/d2238cd0-627c-0010-82c7-eda71af511fa.html">digital innovation</a>, businesses can gain new opportunities and capabilities never previously considered possible – including increased speed and efficiency, process automation, and data transparency.</p>
  <h2 id="seizing-the-moment-with-advisory-expertise">Seizing the Moment with Advisory Expertise</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="at-sap-your-success-is-our-goal">At SAP, your success is our goal</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/support.html#services-support-offerings">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>From the perspective of SAP Advisory Services, digitalization is not just another IT term but also a critical business priority. The more intelligent and sustainable a company becomes, the more agile, flexible, and integrated its value chain becomes.</p>
  <p>Advisory experts from SAP can enable chemical companies to turn their fundamental challenges into opportunities with a well-structured, business-driven design. This approach elaborates on the steps of the digital transformation journey – leading to a road map for future architecture design. Each phase of the road map follows an ideal sequence of digital innovation, technology adoption, and industry best practices and leverages the highest value for the company in the short term.</p>
  <p>SAP Advisory Services help organizations evaluate and act on the sentiments of their customers, partners, and employees and improve their environmental impact. Chemical companies can then be well positioned to keep their workforce engaged, increase organizational agility, and deliver the products and services customers need and trust. Furthermore, they can control their varied sources and categories of spending with outstanding finance and operational efficiency and real-time enterprise insight.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13184d5b5d29ebbc4d371c407a9c86acc71402ad2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13184d5b5d29ebbc4d371c407a9c86acc71402ad2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_13184d5b5d29ebbc4d371c407a9c86acc71402ad2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_13184d5b5d29ebbc4d371c407a9c86acc71402ad2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="300" height="283">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Intelligent enterprise framework</em></p>
  <p>Essentially, chemical companies that work with SAP advisory experts can realize their potential as <a href="https://www.sap.com/intelligent-enterprise.html">intelligent enterprises</a>. They can make confident decisions and drive continuous innovation to adapt, innovate, and overcome challenges while making responsible choices that help reduce waste and emissions and drive long-term growth.</p>
  <p>This business model is accomplished with intelligent technologies, including business networks, a business technology platform, cloud-based infrastructures, and solutions for business process management, experience management, industry cloud, and sustainability management. Additionally, artificial intelligence (AI), blockchain, data platforms, the Internet of Things (IoT), machine learning, predictive analytics, and virtual as well as augmented realities (VR/AR) are embedded in the intelligent technologies to drive end-to-end business processes and decision-making across enterprise domains.</p>
  <h2 id="bringing-to-life-an-intelligent-and-sustainable-network">Bringing to Life an Intelligent and Sustainable Network</h2>
  <p>The pressures on the chemicals industry may be relentless, with shocks coming in from all directions. However, this doesn’t mean businesses cannot find great opportunities in this volatile environment. With the right approach to digitalization, they can transform, innovate, and collaborate across the value chain to build upward momentum and better serve customers as an intelligent and sustainable network.</p>
  <p>Learn more about the <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2022/09/29/business-and-digital-trends-in-the-chemical-industry/">market trends and business priorities shaping various lines of businesses in the chemical industry</a> and how SAP can help guide the innovation needed to overcome them. Read the series <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/tag/business-digital-trends-in-the-chemical-industry/">“Business and Digital Trends in the Chemical Industry</a>” on SAP Community.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Ornulf Rexin is chief business consultant of Chemicals and Life Sciences for Business Transformation Services at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advisory-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Top Five Renewable Energy Challenges for the Utilities Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/renewable-energy-challenges</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/renewable-energy-challenges</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Explore the top five renewable energy challenges for the energy sector – and how the utilities industry is meeting and beating them.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Road to Regeneration | SAP Insights]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/the-road-to-regeneration</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/the-road-to-regeneration</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The road to regeneration is a journey, not a destination. Learn how to build a sustainable business that benefits both your bottom line and the planet.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_155b97388a0a99e34fe0e0f2ad532c25038b28e02.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_155b97388a0a99e34fe0e0f2ad532c25038b28e02.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_155b97388a0a99e34fe0e0f2ad532c25038b28e02.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Garbage plastic with island floating in the ocean" src="./media_155b97388a0a99e34fe0e0f2ad532c25038b28e02.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-road-to-regeneration">The Road to Regeneration</h1>
        <p>Humanity now needs more than one Earth to satisfy its demands for resources – but sustainable, regenerative materials can reverse our overextension of the planet’s capacity.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By Dan Wellers, Emily Acton, Fawn Fitter</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_118362ee0d6e63ddb6f60f9f5122e3f6f41307792.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_118362ee0d6e63ddb6f60f9f5122e3f6f41307792.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_118362ee0d6e63ddb6f60f9f5122e3f6f41307792.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_118362ee0d6e63ddb6f60f9f5122e3f6f41307792.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="320" height="180">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/m/gEHkW4D/hls.m3u8">SAP Digital Futures: How Regenerative Materials Will Heal an Overextended Planet</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>From plastic bottles to the bricks and concrete that make up our buildings and roads, <a href="/blogs/the-super-materials-revolution">materials</a> determine the form and function of everything we experience in the world around us and every product we use to fulfill our needs.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="want-a-quick-overview">Want a quick overview?</h3>
        <p>Read “How Regenerative Materials Will Heal an Overextended Planet.”</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/12/6a233be3-0c7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Download the PDF</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>However, the way we currently produce and use materials is so wasteful and toxic that we’re degrading the planet beyond its ability to repair itself, with all that implies for humanity’s survival. In 2023, “Earth Overshoot Day,” the day on which humans use more natural resources than the planet can regenerate in a year, arrived on August 2. In other words, humanity now needs <a href="https://www.overshootday.org/how-many-earths-or-countries-do-we-need/">1.7 Earths</a> just to satisfy its demands.</p>
  <p>This situation is not just unsustainable; it’s permanently altering our environment. The weight of every human-made thing that exists, from the biggest ocean vessels to the smallest electronic components, now equals all living <a href="https://singularityhub.com/2020/12/24/anthropocene-human-made-materials-now-weigh-as-much-as-all-living-biomass-say-scientists/">biomass</a> combined. If current trends continue, this “<a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-020-3010-5">anthropogenic mass</a>” will outweigh the natural world threefold by 2040. And the output of all this human activity has a negative environmental impact disproportionate to its size: we produce more than <a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.chempr.2020.12.006">350 million metric tons</a> of synthetic polymers (plastics) each year, but 76% of all plastic ever <a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/B978-0-12-817880-5.00002-5">produced</a> is lying unused in landfills, floating in the oceans, and defiling the natural environment.</p>
  <p>But there’s hope for a more sustainable future. Researchers and innovative companies are rethinking the materials that businesses use throughout their operations. They understand that we can no longer separate how materials are used from how they’re sourced and disposed of – so they’re creating better alternatives for existing needs, designing materials to do more than is currently possible, and inventing materials that are less harmful to the planet and even actively help <em>regenerate</em> natural ecosystems.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e276eaacf60fb51bc80bf9a0d3253813bf489cc2.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e276eaacf60fb51bc80bf9a0d3253813bf489cc2.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1e276eaacf60fb51bc80bf9a0d3253813bf489cc2.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Workers in a lab" src="./media_1e276eaacf60fb51bc80bf9a0d3253813bf489cc2.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="finding-alternatives-for-plastics-and-textiles--and-harvesting-carbon-emissions-for-new-uses">Finding alternatives for plastics and textiles – and harvesting carbon emissions for new uses</h2>
  <p>To remove conventional materials from supply chains, we need to find sustainable alternatives that perform at least as well, if not better. After all, so much plastic exists because it is lightweight, durable, relatively low-cost, and can be used in a multitude of ways.</p>
  <p>In fact, the <strong>plastics</strong> problem is a leading target for improving materials use. Many possibilities are emerging for developing durable but biodegradable bioplastics. One approach involves diverting food waste, with promising experiments involving <a href="https://www.innovationnewsnetwork.com/creating-high-performance-plastic-foam-from-whey-protein/12521/">whey protein</a>, <a href="http://innovationnewsnetwork.com/citrus-peel-pef-plastics/10743/">citrus peels</a>, <a href="https://www.innovationnewsnetwork.com/enhancing-food-preservation-mango-based-bioplastic/13572/">mango leaves</a>, <a href="https://www.designweek.co.uk/issues/26-october-1-november-2020/bioplastic-made-from-lobster-shells-leads-wave-of-material-innovation/">lobster shells</a>, <a href="https://scitechdaily.com/making-cleaner-greener-biodegradable-plastics-from-waste-fish-parts/">fish oil</a> from salmon processing scraps, and <a href="https://scitechdaily.com/plant-based-vegan-spider-silk-provides-sustainable-alternative-to-single-use-plastics/">soybean oil</a> byproducts. Other sources of biopolymers come from beyond the plate and pantry, like <a href="https://news.uchicago.edu/story/sustainable-future-scientists-rethink-plastics-and-devices">cellulose</a>, which makes up the cell walls of plants, and <a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/science/mycelium-fungi-green-materials-1.5954664">mycelium</a>, the root network of fungi. There’s even a company that crushes stone to extract <a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90600241/manufacturing-most-innovative-companies-2021">calcium carbonate</a>, one of the most common minerals in the world, and uses it to replace up to 80% of the plastic in chip bags, candy wrappers, and other packaging so it degrades in months instead of centuries.</p>
  <p>Another material that needs to be made more sustainably is <strong>concrete</strong>. Traditionally, concrete is made by binding gravel and fine sand with a paste of cement (made of limestone and ash that have been burned together and ground up) and water. Its strength and durability make concrete the most widely used human-made material on the planet, but <a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2071-1050/13/1/204">making it</a> consumes about 10% of the water used worldwide for industrial and commercial activities and emits about 8% of global CO<sub>2</sub> emissions. But researchers have discovered that replacing up to half of the sand, which is expensive and carbon-intensive to produce, with waste clay dug up during <a href="https://www.innovationnewsnetwork.com/producing-sustainable-concrete-repurposing-excavation-waste/10977/">excavation work</a>, makes a super-concrete that’s both stronger and diverts construction material from landfills. Another new approach to concrete involves combining lime binder with fast-growing hemp plants to create a renewable, carbon-sequestering “<a href="https://sustainablebrands.com/read/product-service-design-innovation/3-advances-in-sequestering-carbon-in-the-built-environment">hempcrete</a>” that weighs eight times less than standard concrete and is ideal for non-structural uses like borders or sidewalks.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bcfad6dd2be61da24aa4f4ea99646054e06ff4c9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bcfad6dd2be61da24aa4f4ea99646054e06ff4c9.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1bcfad6dd2be61da24aa4f4ea99646054e06ff4c9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Oil drops on a water surface" src="./media_1bcfad6dd2be61da24aa4f4ea99646054e06ff4c9.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>There’s ample room to rethink <strong>other construction materials</strong>, too, as well as how to use them to design buildings with smaller ecological footprints. Renewable bio-based alternatives to standard building materials might include nanocellulose <a href="https://revolutionized.com/7-amazing-ways-we-use-nanocellulose/">insulation</a> that’s stronger and more effective than Styrofoam, <a href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/05/210504154557.htm">transparent, heat-retaining wood</a> made with citrus peel waste, and <a href="https://www.startus-insights.com/innovators-guide/top-10-construction-industry-trends-innovations-in-2021/">engineered wood products</a> that are as strong, stable, safe, and as versatile as concrete and steel. There’s also lightweight, flexible, emissions-free construction board made from cellulose extracted from <a href="https://www.dezeen.com/2020/11/26/honext-recyclable-construction-material-cellulose-paper/">paper recycling waste</a> that would otherwise be discarded, and <a href="https://www.buildwithrise.com/stories/hempwood-the-sustainable-new-building-material">wood made from hemp</a> that’s been bioengineered to be as durable as oak, but to grow 100 times faster. And nanotechnology has enabled <a href="https://www.graphenglass.com/">graphene-based</a> construction materials that enhance solar protection, deflect wind, kill germs, and more, actively improving the buildings’ immediate environments.</p>
  <p>In addition to shelter, we need clothing, furniture, and bedding. But <strong>textiles and fabrics</strong> are often unsustainable. If the fashion industry continues its current practices, it will create an <a href="https://www.thefashionlaw.com/home/can-the-fashion-industry-ever-really-be-sustainable">estimated</a> 148 million tons of waste by 2030, or 38.5 pounds (17.5 kilograms) of waste for every person on the planet. We’ll need eco-friendly alternatives that create less waste during production, like fast-growing <a href="https://sourcingjournal.com/denim/denim-mills/us-national-hemp-association-fiber-kontoor-panda-biotech-agi-xinjiang-cotton-276485/">hemp</a> as a cotton substitute or artificial leather made of <a href="https://utenvironment.org/2020/11/05/mycelium-the-future-of-leather/">mycelium</a> fibers.</p>
  <p><strong>Other industries</strong> are also rethinking materials use. Take <strong>aerospace</strong>, for example. Researchers recently announced they had developed a new <a href="https://www.innovationnewsnetwork.com/optimising-future-aircraft-with-the-worlds-lightest-aerogel-material/12625/">aerogel</a> that, while not made from particularly green materials itself, is so lightweight that it would significantly cut fuel consumption in the next generation of aircraft – while also reducing noise pollution from the engine, both inside and outside the cabin. Another recent development in <strong>construction</strong> involves ultra-white <a href="https://www.purdue.edu/newsroom/releases/2021/Q2/the-whitest-paint-is-here-and-its-the-coolest.-literally..html">paint</a> so effective at reflecting sunlight and infrared heat that it actually makes surfaces cooler than their surroundings. The scientists who developed it speculate that giving buildings a lightweight, hyper-white coat of paint could be enough to significantly reduce the need for electricity-hungry air conditioning.</p>
  <p>We’ll also turn more <strong>waste</strong> into value by capturing carbon belched from smokestacks. By turning it into black <a href="https://reflowproject.eu/best-practices/air-ink/">inks</a>, paints, and coatings, or embedding it in <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2021/06/23/magazine/interface-carpet-carbon.html">carpet tiles</a> that also use recycled vinyl, waste vegetation, and salvaged nylon, we can create durable products that move greenhouse gases out of the atmosphere for years, if not decades.</p>
  <p>Finding more sustainable materials for our present-day needs is just the beginning. Materials scientists are going further by creating and using materials that expand on what’s possible.</p>
  <h2 id="materials-with-future-potential">Materials with future potential</h2>
  <p>As we investigate the properties of more renewable materials, we will find uses for them that aren’t possible with materials we’re familiar with today.</p>
  <p>For example, when certain common ocean bacteria eat a combination of gelatin and sand, they turn into a mass of <a href="https://www.discovermagazine.com/the-sciences/this-regenerative-building-material-is-made-from-sand-and-bacteria">living concrete</a> that can repair and reproduce itself. This material has promise for rebuilding after disasters and providing shelter quickly in challenging conditions. Scientists think they could even teach it to make oxygen and water, which would be useful in harsh environments – not just on Earth, but on other planets, should NASA realize plans to send crews to settle Mars, for example. Similarly, researchers are working on making building materials and tools by combining chitin, a <a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/14610026/">biopolymer</a> produced by fungi and insects, with <a href="https://physicsworld.com/a/martian-buildings-could-be-made-of-chitin-based-material/">other materials</a> that are readily available.</p>
  <p>Plants will also inspire new material properties. A lightweight, breathable textile made of cellulose fibers and <a href="https://reflowproject.eu/best-practices/seacell-fiber/">seaweed</a> could be able to infuse nutrients through skin contact, for clothing that nourishes the person wearing it. A genetically tailored <a href="https://arstechnica.com/science/2021/02/kombucha-tea-inspires-new-living-material-for-biosensing-applications/">kombucha tea</a> starter that can sense pollutants and produce glow-in-the-dark enzymes could potentially be an eco-friendly biosensor indicating a package has been tampered with. Plants infused with nanoparticles that <a href="https://news.mit.edu/2019/ambient-plant-illumination-could-light-way-greener-buildings-0510">turn energy from photosynthesis</a> into light could replace lighting fixtures with ambient off-grid lighting that also freshens the air.</p>
  <p>In addition, researchers are creating partly organic and non-organic <a href="https://royalsociety.org/-/media/policy/projects/animate-materials/animate-materials-report.pdf">animate materials</a> that are capable of sensing and adapting to their environments. Buildings made from these materials would be able to harvest light, water, heat, bacteria, greenhouse gases, and biowaste from their surroundings and inhabitants, then use those resources to maintain and repair themselves while generating useful outputs like power, oxygen, heat, and drinkable water. Equipment in industrial facilities could be made from self-repairing plastics and self-diagnostic coatings that simplify maintenance. Products could be programmed to disassemble themselves at end-of-life so their basic components can be recycled or repurposed. Even <a href="/blogs/fashion-the-future-interface-between-mind-body-and-planet">clothing</a> could be made with animate materials that respond to people’s vital signs to keep them comfortable or detect possible illness.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16375f25aab6a15164645fc95037a5291d5fa8909.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16375f25aab6a15164645fc95037a5291d5fa8909.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_16375f25aab6a15164645fc95037a5291d5fa8909.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Streams of light" src="./media_16375f25aab6a15164645fc95037a5291d5fa8909.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="regeneration-the-next-frontier">Regeneration: The next frontier</h2>
  <p>In the search for a sustainable materials future, the ultimate outcome could be a broad shift to materials that aren’t just lower-impact, but that actively regenerate the environment and systems they are part of. That could mean designing materials that sustain themselves, restore nutrients to the environment as they break down, or actively remove <em>existing</em> waste from the environment as they’re created. Researchers in the Netherlands recently mixed microalgae with bacterial cellulose to create a “<a href="https://www.tudelft.nl/en/2021/tnw/researchers-create-living-material-based-on-algae">living material</a>” that can be 3D printed into sturdy, biodegradable objects that sustain and regenerate themselves through photosynthesis. One potential application is artificial leaves that, given water and CO<sub>2</sub>, emit oxygen and store energy as sugars that can be harvested for fuel.</p>
  <p>Living materials like this could also be formed into artificial skin that speeds healing by flooding a wound site with oxygen before dissolving – or <a href="https://www.tudelft.nl/en/2021/tnw/researchers-create-living-material-based-on-algae">fabric</a> that requires less water than cotton to produce, purifies the air through photosynthesis, and returns nutrients to the environment when it biodegrades.</p>
  <p>People who prefer less literal active wear may choose instead to wear textiles made from repurposed agricultural waste, and that break down at end of life to return nutrients to the environment. According to the EU’s Reflow Project, these garments could come from <a href="https://reflowproject.eu/best-practices/pinatex/">pineapple leaves</a>, <a href="https://reflowproject.eu/best-practices/malai-plant-base-leather/">coconut water</a>, or crustacean shells combined with <a href="https://reflowproject.eu/best-practices/orange-fibre/">citrus byproducts</a> or <a href="https://reflowproject.eu/best-practices/tomtex/">coffee grounds</a>.</p>
  <p>When it comes time to package all of these products, we can feed sewage <a href="https://www.futurity.org/bioplastics-mangrove-bacteria-wastewater-2487542-2/?utm_source=rss&#x26;utm_medium=rss&#x26;utm_campaign=bioplastics-mangrove-bacteria-wastewater-2487542-2">sludge</a> and agriculture wastewater to hungry bacteria who excrete it as biopolymers that can be made into biodegradable plastics. Sourcing plastics this way could remove a sizable amount of sewage sludge from landfills – 2,500 Olympic-sized swimming pools’ worth is produced annually in the United States alone – and when those bioplastics dissolve or are recycled into their individual components, we can reuse, recycle, and reform those components into more sustainable materials.</p>
  <p>The future of materials isn’t just about making man-made items more durable or designing them so that they can be upcycled or retired with less harm to the environment. It’s a fundamentally different paradigm. Ultimately, the future of materials requires us to leave behind our unsustainable system of resource extraction, processing, consumption, and disposal in favor of one where our materials restore and/or repair the damage we have done to the planet.</p>
  <p>In other words, it’s not enough to travel down the wrong path more slowly. We need to take a different path – one that actually improves the quality of life for humanity and all other living things.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-supply-chain</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>content-type/trends-predictions</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[EY Unlocks Innovation and Opportunity in the Chemical Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/ey-unlocks-innovation-opportunity-chemical-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/ey-unlocks-innovation-opportunity-chemical-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The chemical industry is undergoing a structural transformation due to post-COVID-19 business impacts. Kevin Jinks from EY discusses.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/chemical-industry-partner-series</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/ey</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transforming SAP Solutions into Value: NTT DATA Business Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/ntt-data-business-solutions-sap-solutions-value</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/ntt-data-business-solutions-sap-solutions-value</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[NTT DATA Business Solutions designs, implements, manages, and continuously enhances SAP solutions to make them work for companies.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10fbd03aeede6e2279147cab16d30abc93b46da68.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10fbd03aeede6e2279147cab16d30abc93b46da68.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10fbd03aeede6e2279147cab16d30abc93b46da68.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Transforming SAP Solutions into Value: NTT DATA Business Solutions" src="./media_10fbd03aeede6e2279147cab16d30abc93b46da68.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="transforming-sap-solutions-into-value-ntt-data-business-solutions">Transforming SAP Solutions into Value: NTT DATA Business Solutions</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="whitepaper-the-intelligent-enterprise-for-the-chemical-industry">Whitepaper: The Intelligent Enterprise for the Chemical Industry</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2016/03/d2238cd0-627c-0010-82c7-eda71af511fa.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Digital transformation helps companies reach their full potential – if the underlying technologies work for the people using them. NTT DATA Business Solutions designs, implements, manages, and continuously enhances SAP solutions to make them work for companies – and for their people.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>With deep industry knowledge and a commitment to value realization, the SAP partner ecosystem is critical to the success of the chemical industry. SAP partners help customers of all sizes, in countries worldwide take advantage of SAP’s innovative solutions, simplify their business processes, and orchestrate the Intelligent Enterprise. To bring this perspective to the SAP community in the chemical industry, we are continuing with the fourth edition of the <a href="/topics/chemical-industry-partner-series">Chemical Industry Partner Stage series</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1baac8d47aea63b9508352427f0026d1c7d9a8449.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1baac8d47aea63b9508352427f0026d1c7d9a8449.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1baac8d47aea63b9508352427f0026d1c7d9a8449.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="NTT Data logo" src="./media_1baac8d47aea63b9508352427f0026d1c7d9a8449.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="475" height="163">
    </picture>Here, we talk with Brandon Evans, vice president of Customer Transformation at NTT DATA Business Solutions.
  </p>
  <p><strong>Q: When you talk to chemical customers, what are some of the challenges and opportunities you see in the industry?</strong></p>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> When we look at the chemical industry holistically, given an SAP context, we see a lot of change happening in the ecosystem. In 2020, we saw a lot of mergers and acquisitions put on hold due to market uncertainty, which we feel will result in increased activity in 2021 and 2022.</p>
  <p>In the same period, we’ve been shown how a strong or fragile supply chain can affect the chemical industry in terms of supply and order fulfillment. Building stronger supply chains to protect the business has never been more pertinent. It’s important to apply agility in the face of industry or societal disruption to service customers and deliver outcomes.</p>
  <p>Lastly, we continue to see organizations focusing on environmental issues, energy sourcing, and volatility. Sustainability and becoming carbon neutral are beginning to take hold, through leveraging technology to begin carbon tracking for example. Alternative sources of fuel are being investigated further, such as hydrogen, partially driven by the volatility in oil pricing for petrochemical companies looking to take advantage of the upswing in oil pricing.</p>
  <p>In summary, we see a lot of change in the chemical space, which presents opportunities for fast movers to resolve challenges and take advantage of chemical industry market dynamics.</p>
  <p><strong>Looking to the second half of 2021 and beyond, what do you see as the top priorities for chemical customers?</strong></p>
  <p>We see the following four major trends when dealing with our chemical clients:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Improving customer experience (CX):</strong> Customers are requiring digital collaboration for faster product introductions, self-service ordering, and B2B/B2C e-commerce platforms.</li>
    <li><strong>Moving from selling products to selling business outcomes:</strong> Clients are looking to serve customers based on insights, using data such as product sales volume and product adoption to create faster new product introduction with assurance.</li>
    <li><strong>Strengthening supply chains:</strong> Customers are asking themselves questions such as “How can we be more insightful with demand planning and forecasting using statistical modeling, prediction, and outside factors to adjust and become more agile?” and “How can we use business networks to allow for multi-sourcing if global competition for raw materials or feedstock becomes too rife?”</li>
    <li><strong>Focusing on factories:</strong> There is interest in connected machines to synergize pipeline flow, with costing metrics of process or phases, as well as the maintenance and servicing of aging facilities, coupled with governmental compliance and sustainability initiatives.</li>
  </ul>
  <p><strong>How has digital enabled these priorities from your perspective?</strong></p>
  <p>Digital can mean a lot of things in today’s age, but for us digital in the context of these priorities means the ability to provide solutions to business issues now, in a relatively short amount of time.</p>
  <p>SAP has made a great deal of investment in tools for industries to improve customer experience and supply chain via cloud deployment solutions. The days of infrastructure, lengthy implementations, and design from scratch are gone. Now, chemical and process industries can adopt SAP Commerce and SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain and deploy these solutions in a matter of weeks, not months.</p>
  <p><strong>What have been the key elements of success when working with chemical customers?</strong></p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="drive-higher-value-outcomes-and-new-customer-experiences-through-innovative-products-services-and-business-models-with-sap-solutions-for-chemicals">Drive higher value outcomes and new customer experiences through innovative products, services, and business models with SAP solutions for chemicals</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/chemicals.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>When we look at some of our recent chemical success stories, many of them point back to a few major tenets that we reinforce within our client engagements. For example, with a recent specialty chemical SAP S/4HANA implementation, the following aspects helped achieve faster time to value and organizational adoption:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Executive buy-in and involvement:</strong> Having stakeholders that are invested in and championing the project initiative is critical.</li>
    <li><strong>Adopting best practices versus design:</strong> In order to move with agility, it is key to ensure the scope is managed appropriately and that the organization challenges <em>why</em> standard best practices cannot be leveraged. If change requests from the business do not increase revenue, decrease costs, or provide competitive advantage, then full stop.</li>
    <li><strong>Recognize change, plan for people to be impacted:</strong> Change is difficult, but progress is never made by adhering to the status quo. Equally important when implementing software, the return on investment is achieved much faster if users are engaged and leveraging the system. In short, plan for change, plan for impact, and ensure users understand how their job responsibilities will change moving forward.</li>
  </ul>
  <p><strong>When we talk to customers, big or small, change management is a key pillar of digital transformation. How are companies embracing these changes and setting up their teams for success?</strong></p>
  <p>Organizational change management is a large topic with any software implementation to ensure value is realized from the implementation. Given the remote nature of working today, we are finding it even more essential to plan for additional avenues to ensure end users accept, adopt, and understand change. We share a few of the best practices we are deploying with our customers in small and large engagements:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Leveraging collaboration platforms for virtual learning</li>
    <li>Preparing just-in-time course content for team enablement</li>
    <li>Building quick-reference guides that are shared physically and electronically</li>
    <li>Using augmented reality (virtual reality glasses) to visualize processes and collaborate on issues</li>
    <li>Communicating with numerous quick touchpoints on virtual platforms daily and augmenting that with various collaboration tools, like SharePoint, Google Docs, Slack, and Microsoft Teams</li>
    <li>Prescriptively ramping up in-person opportunities for knowledge sharing and other forms of support</li>
  </ul>
  <p><strong>What differentiates you in the chemical industry?</strong></p>
  <p>At NTT DATA Business Solutions, we focus solely on implementing SAP software products – SAP is in our DNA. Over the years, we have spent a great amount of time working with our customers to understand their business challenges and problems, so we can help them realize solutions, obtain benefits, and meet corporate objectives.</p>
  <p>Having these experiences and focusing only on SAP products has allowed us to create global practices, or competency centers, which share in the development of business content (pre-configured best practices) and our own <a href="https://addstore.nttdata-solutions.com/us-en/">software solutions</a> (software extension solutions to solve common chemical gaps).</p>
  <p>Finally, we have scaled our ability to cover nearly all SAP solutions with strategic acquisitions in supply chain, such as <a href="https://nttdata-solutions.com/us/localprsrlss/ntt-data-significantly-expanding-presence-in-us-market/">My Supply Chain Group</a>, and have long-standing partnerships with niche competencies to fulfill all of your SAP needs through one service integrator.</p>
  <p><strong>How can people connect with NTT DATA Business Solutions?</strong></p>
  <p>We have a variety of assets available on our Website for chemical companies that are evaluating SAP solutions or current customers planning their business transformations. Please follow us on <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/ndbs-us/">LinkedIn</a> and visit our channels for more background on how we help businesses thrive and transform in the chemical industry.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://nttdata-solutions.com/us/">NTT Business Solutions</a></li>
    <li><a href="https://nttdata-solutions.com/us/industries/chemical-industry/">NTT Business Solutions – Chemical Industry</a></li>
    <li><a href="https://nttdata-solutions.com/us/services/digital-transformation-as-a-service/">NTT Business Solutions – Business Transformation</a></li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Looking to stay connected with the chemical Industry? Please join the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/2152/">SAP Chemical Industry community on LinkedIn</a>, follow us on Twitter <a href="https://twitter.com/sapchemicals">@SAPChemicals</a>, and check out our <a href="https://community.sap.com/topics/chemicals">SAP Community page</a>.</p>
        <p>SAP is a leader in the chemical industry and is committed to continuous innovation. We encourage you to collaborate with us and discuss how the SAP solution portfolio can enable the Intelligent Enterprise in the chemical industry.</p>
        <p><em>David Dunn is director of Global Industries Marketing at SAP.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/chemical-industry-partner-series</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Linx-AS: Digital Innovation with Core Industry Roots]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/linx-as-digital-innovation-industry-roots</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/linx-as-digital-innovation-industry-roots</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In a truly a dynamic chemicals industry, Linx-AS helps businesses be more of what they aspire to be with SAP. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e37267cb03a5d51edeb3c4145ca07ef6336c240e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e37267cb03a5d51edeb3c4145ca07ef6336c240e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e37267cb03a5d51edeb3c4145ca07ef6336c240e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Linx-AS: Digital Innovation with Core Industry Roots" src="./media_1e37267cb03a5d51edeb3c4145ca07ef6336c240e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="linx-as-digital-innovation-with-core-industry-roots">Linx-AS: Digital Innovation with Core Industry Roots</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Established in 2000, <a href="https://linxas.com/">Linx-AS</a> has core consulting practices in product lifecycle management (PLM), environment, health, and safety (EHS), and enterprise user experience (UEx). The business helps large companies implement more profitable product development processes, ensure operations are within regulated environment, health, and safety standards, and, overall, make SAP easier for people to access and use. Additionally, its Innovations Division focuses on designing SAP-certified solutions and accelerators that provide faster time to value for customers.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e27c708fb8081993b743596eee642ba26df883d8.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e27c708fb8081993b743596eee642ba26df883d8.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1e27c708fb8081993b743596eee642ba26df883d8.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1e27c708fb8081993b743596eee642ba26df883d8.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="425" height="145">
    </picture>Linx-AS helps businesses be more of what they aspire to be with SAP—strategic, innovative, sustainable, productive, and profitable. In doing so, it brings the highest level of expertise to its customers, delivering thoughtfully designed and meticulously implemented solutions.
  </p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>With deep industry knowledge and a commitment to value realization, the SAP partner ecosystem is critical to the success of the chemical industry. SAP partners help customers of all sizes, in countries worldwide take advantage of SAP’s innovative solutions, simplify their business processes, and orchestrate the Intelligent Enterprise. To bring this perspective to the SAP community in the chemical industry, we are continuing with our third edition of the <a href="/topics/chemical-industry-partner-series">Chemical Industry Partner Stage series</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Here, we talk with Jeff Frye, president and CEO of Linx-AS.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="whitepaper-the-intelligent-enterprise-for-the-chemical-industry">Whitepaper: The Intelligent Enterprise for the Chemical Industry</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2016/03/d2238cd0-627c-0010-82c7-eda71af511fa.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="q-when-you-talk-to-chemical-customers-what-excites-you-about-the-chemical-industry">Q: When you talk to chemical customers, what excites you about the chemical industry?</h3>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> First off, the chemical industry is where Linx-AS got its start in 2000 with our environment, health, and safety consulting practice, so our chemical roots run deep. Since that time, the many changes and challenges chemical companies have faced—whether internal or external—have been met with innovation. It’s truly a dynamic industry, and that’s what makes working in chemicals exciting for us. We have earned insight on how chemical manufacturers operate and the business processes that drive success. It’s a natural fit for us to innovate with SAP technologies to deliver inspired customer solutions.</p>
  <h3 id="was-quite-the-year-what-do-you-see-as-the-top-priorities-for-chemical-customers-in-2021">2020 was quite the year. What do you see as the top priorities for chemical customers in 2021?</h3>
  <p>Everyone was blindsided by the <strong><a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a></strong> and the disruptions to life and business as we knew it. If there was a bright spot to 2020, it’s that the market and operational stresses were a catalyst for transformation trends that will continue as priorities through 2021.</p>
  <p>Across industries, a predictable focus on worker health and safety emerged. I believe companies will continue to shore up foundational data and processes while exploring innovative ways, like mobile, the Internet of Things (IoT), and sensors, to extend the enterprise into the workplace.</p>
  <p>Another priority will be research and development (R&#x26;D). Confronted with disrupted supply chains, the need for R&#x26;D agility became painfully apparent. Whether it’s reformulating products with substitute raw materials or developing for alternative markets, streamlining upstream definitely makes the list.</p>
  <p>And then for chemicals especially, sustainability is key moving forward—not only taking care of what you produce now but driving sustainable product development for the future, which ties into R&#x26;D agility.</p>
  <h3 id="how-has-digital-enabled-these-priorities-from-your-perspective">How has digital enabled these priorities from your perspective?</h3>
  <p>Digital is critical. I think there are a lot of definitions and expectations—or maybe aspirations—of digital floating around. For our customers, foundational work often needs to be done before realizing or even recognizing transformational opportunities. Reflecting on the priorities, simply centralizing data and digitalizing current processes in these areas is step one.</p>
  <p>For instance, I mentioned health and safety initiatives. We’ve engaged in pilots and proofs of concept for mobile and IoT in this space to increase data collection and accuracy to ultimately drive decision-making and safety performance. The key takeaway is that you can collect all the data you want with sensors and apps. However, if your foundation isn’t solid, you can’t process the data in a meaningful way. To make digital effective, you must put data to work to deliver insights and drive workflow across the enterprise. My advice to customers is to definitely explore innovative solutions, but make sure you’re innovating on solid ground. That approach will lead to true transformation.</p>
  <h3 id="you-just-mentioned-mobile-how-do-you-see-the-mobile-landscape-in-sap-and-do-you-have-any-advice-for-chemical-customers-embarking-on-mobile-initiatives">You just mentioned mobile. How do you see the mobile landscape in SAP, and do you have any advice for chemical customers embarking on mobile initiatives?</h3>
  <p>That’s a rich topic. There are so many factors to consider when looking at mobile, ranging from the technical to corporate policy to user personas to security. Are you running SAP S/4HANA or still on SAP ERP? Do you have a bring-your-own-device (BYOD) policy? Do your users require offline capabilities? It goes on and on. It’s an exercise we help clients with all the time. To sum up, the landscape is difficult. But the mobile landscape, particularly with cloud solutions from SAP, has a lot of potential for customers.</p>
  <p>What I will say is that mobile is beyond exploratory; it’s expected now. It’s part of everyday life outside of work, so users demand it on the job with the same user experience (UX) performance. For some areas of SAP, you’ll require custom development to extend core capabilities. For instance, we’ve built a suite of risk management apps to augment SAP Environment, Health, and Safety Management by supporting additional use cases. For a customer in a development situation, I’d say pay attention to your users, use standard technologies, and choose an easily deployable architecture.</p>
  <h3 id="when-we-talk-to-chemical-industry-customers-big-or-small-change-management-is-a-key-pillar-of-digital-transformation-how-do-you-see-this-topic-in-the-industry">When we talk to chemical industry customers, big or small, change management is a key pillar of digital transformation. How do you see this topic in the industry?</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="drive-higher-value-outcomes-and-new-customer-experiences-through-innovative-products-services-and-business-models-with-sap-solutions-for-chemicals">Drive higher value outcomes and new customer experiences through innovative products, services, and business models with SAP solutions for chemicals</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/chemicals.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It all comes down to communication. If you assess and understand the risks going into a transformation project, you’ll be prepared to navigate the challenges—and there are always challenges. If everyone impacted, from the top to shop, is engaged early, you’re on solid footing when you encounter bumps. It sounds simple, but it’s often difficult because of things that you can’t necessarily control. You need champions for your solution in impacted areas. Sometimes they’re not there or as vocal as needed. You need executive buy-in. Again, it’s another variable.</p>
  <p>One thing we do at Linx-AS, a thing we can control, is constantly thinking of the end user in the solution—from design through implementation and support. Most failures can be attributed to breakdowns in user adoption. It’s critical to get user feedback and involve users in prototyping, so there are no surprises, or at least fewer, when you roll out and train your teams.</p>
  <h3 id="why-partner-with-linx-as">Why partner with Linx-AS?</h3>
  <p>What we hear most from our customers is usually one or all of three things: you understand our business, you really know SAP, and you give it to us straight. Because our focus in PLM and EHS is so specialized, we’ve invested heavily in our people, drawing from talent who have worked in industry and keeping them up to speed on the latest technology. It’s not commodity consulting that you can contract out. You need people who know the complexities of the chemical industry and have the business acumen to apply technology smartly. And, to the last of the three, that’s just how we do business. When you partner with Linx-AS, you get honest assessments of what will bring the most value to your business.</p>
  <h3 id="what-makes-linx-as-different-from-other-implementation-partners-in-the-chemical-industry">What makes Linx-AS different from other implementation partners in the chemical industry?</h3>
  <p>Echoing my last comments, our expertise in PLM and EHS, coupled with our understanding of the chemical industry, is unmatched. But, to expand on this, I’d say that our Innovations Division is truly a differentiator. We have a dedicated team that is churning out solutions that extend SAP. Whether it’s workflow solutions in recipe development or our <a href="https://linxas.com/worksafe-cloud/">WorkSafe Cloud</a> offering for SAP Environment, Health, and Safety Management, we continually have an eye toward bringing added value to customers and designing solutions that engage end users.</p>
  <h3 id="how-does-linx-as-create-value-for-the-chemical-industry-and-how-can-people-connect-with-you">How does Linx-AS create value for the chemical industry and how can people connect with you?</h3>
  <p>I’d go back to part of the Linx-AS vision statement that says, “We help businesses be more of what they aspire to be with SAP.” We understand chemical manufacturers have significant investment in SAP technology to realize benefits across the enterprise, but sometimes the path to value, particularly in the specialized areas of PLM and EHS, isn’t always clear cut. We simplify that path, provide focus for customers, and bring additional innovation to the platform that engages users and improves business performance.</p>
  <p>As far as getting in touch, you can reach me at <a href="mailto:jfrye@linxas.com">jfrye@linxas.com</a>. For the latest on Linx-AS, you can go to our <strong><a href="https://linxas.com/">website</a></strong> or follow us at @LinxASLLC.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Looking to stay connected with the chemical Industry? Join the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/2152/">SAP Chemical Industry community on LinkedIn</a>, follow us on Twitter <a href="https://twitter.com/sapchemicals">@SAPChemicals</a>, and check out our <a href="https://community.sap.com/topics/chemicals">SAP Community page</a>.</p>
        <p>SAP is a leader in the chemical industry, and we are committed to continuous innovation. We encourage you to collaborate with us and discuss how the SAP solution portfolio can enable the intelligent enterprise in the chemical industry.</p>
        <p><em>Mark Carlson is an chemicals solution expert at SAP.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/chemical-industry-partner-series</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enowa: Driving Business Transformation in Chemicals]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/enowa-business-transformation-chemicals</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/enowa-business-transformation-chemicals</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP partner Enowa is active in the chemical industry, leading multiple business and SAP S/4HANA transformations. Hear more from the company.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Enowa: Driving Business Transformation in Chemicals" src="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="enowa-driving-business-transformation-in-chemicals">Enowa: Driving Business Transformation in Chemicals</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Established in 2002, <a href="https://www.enowa.com/about-us/about-us">Enowa</a> is a global midsize SAP partner with a dedicated focus on business process and SAP consulting. Enowa’s nearly 20-year foundation started in the chemical industry, supporting business process optimization and SAP engagements delivered with functional and technical experts, driving value in small teams for our mutual clients.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d89d2c117f1c6a5b20b218e28357088f29c2404e.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d89d2c117f1c6a5b20b218e28357088f29c2404e.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1d89d2c117f1c6a5b20b218e28357088f29c2404e.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1d89d2c117f1c6a5b20b218e28357088f29c2404e.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="225" height="100">
    </picture>Enowa is active in the chemical industry, leading multiple business and SAP S/4HANA transformations as well as sponsoring the recent ASUG Best Practices for Chemicals event. During this event, Enowa’s client, Jayhawk Chemical, spoke about its five-month SAP S/4HANA business transformation, and Lubrizol shared how Celonis was leveraged to support its SAP S/4HANA journey.
  </p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>With deep industry knowledge and a commitment to value realization, the SAP partner ecosystem is critical to the success of the chemical industry. SAP partners help customers of all sizes in countries worldwide take advantage of SAP’s innovative solutions, simplify their business processes, and orchestrate the Intelligent Enterprise. To bring this perspective to the SAP community in the chemical industry, we are continuing with the second edition of the <strong><a href="/topics/chemical-industry-partner-series">Chemical Industry Partner Stage series</a></strong>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Here, we talk with Rick Place, partner and vice president of Marketing and Client Development at Enowa Consulting.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="whitepaper-the-intelligent-enterprise-for-the-chemical-industry">Whitepaper: The Intelligent Enterprise for the Chemical Industry</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2016/03/d2238cd0-627c-0010-82c7-eda71af511fa.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="q-when-you-talk-to-chemical-customers-what-excites-you-about-the-industry">Q: When you talk to chemical customers, what excites you about the industry?</h3>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> The chemical industry is SAP’s foundation; it is the base of why SAP ERP came to life. Similarly, Enowa started with most of its clients in the chemical industry, and now its client base spans across all sectors of manufacturing (mill to food, repetitive to discrete) and other industry sectors.</p>
  <p>Our excitement of and alignment with the SAP community in the chemical industry is firmly rooted in our start. I think, like everyone, we get excited when we talk about our roots. The roots establish the tenure of our experts. We have SAP configurations that are more than 20 years old deployed at various divisions of companies that have been bought and sold for decades – and Enowa’s configuration footprint is still running at those clients!</p>
  <p>What excites me is the drive for efficiency and change. In 2021, we expect to see many mergers, acquisitions, divestitures, and spin-offs. These transactions are always prevalent in the chemical space, but the frequency is increasing and the speed requirements to complete these projects increases for shorter timelines. This results in a landscape complexity reduction in the divesting company and a lower cost of TSA for the acquiring entity. We are excited because our competence in both scenarios is our core.</p>
  <p>In addition, over the more than 20 years I’ve been leading Enowa’s alignment for new projects, I’ve been able to lean heavily on our successful delivery team. I cannot think of a better compliment than trust and partnership between Enowa and our clients. In sum, trust is what excites me to make a difference every day with clients.</p>
  <h3 id="looking-forward-into-2021-what-do-you-see-as-the-top-priorities-for-chemical-customers">Looking forward into 2021, what do you see as the top priorities for chemical customers?</h3>
  <p>Speed. We see two needs for speed. The first is with clients who need real data in real time, or close to it. They are calling on Enowa experts to drive transformation projects both in SAP ERP and SAP S/4HANA landscapes. Most commonly, we are driving results on these topics:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Financial optimization projects leveraging group reporting and SAP Analytics Cloud for planning</li>
    <li>Analytics based on having data governance and data accessibility to visualize and analyze data</li>
    <li>Reviewing process execution with Celonis</li>
    <li>SAP S/4HANA transformations through a mutually agreed upon approach:
      <ul>
        <li>Selective data transition to limit business disruption and leverage existing parts while leaving behind undesired areas</li>
        <li>Greenfield to move away from years of unnecessary customization</li>
        <li>Brownfield to leverage previous releases in good condition</li>
      </ul>
    </li>
  </ul>
  <p>The second need for speed is around mergers, acquisitions, and divestitures, largely driven by private equity. For these clients, our consultants run these complex projects. They will expect a fully functioning system in short order.</p>
  <p>Overall, the chemical industry is continuing to leverage advancing technologies. We see more activity around these topics:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Process excellence such as rapid financial closing; refined and optimized planning and scenario-based planning; shop floor integration with SAP Manufacturing Integration and Intelligence; and customer experience focused on enabling sales teams with SAP Sales Cloud and backend customer satisfaction with SAP Commerce Cloud</li>
    <li>Digitalization such as supply chain integration of data from shop floor, lab, and sales with actionable insights; and robotic process analysis (RPA) analysis, assessment, and results projection, leveraging available RPA technology</li>
  </ul>
  <h3 id="how-has-digital-enabled-these-priorities-from-your-perspective">How has digital enabled these priorities from your perspective?</h3>
  <p>We no longer only talk to IT about business system transformation. We talk to the business in their terms so they can understand how SAP products improve productivity for their department. In the chemical industry, we do not see wide corporate adoption of digital transformation, but adoption in pointed areas. For instance, our Connect Lab combines real-time data with actionable insights to keep products moving, with temperature range and with notification of any supply chain disruptions.</p>
  <h3 id="we-had-a-chance-to-hear-about-enowas-sap-s4hana-implementation-at-jayhawk-fine-chemical-corporation-during-various-asug-events-at-jayhawk-sap-s4hana-was-deployed-in-five-months-what-made-this-project-successful">We had a chance to hear about Enowa’s SAP S/4HANA implementation at Jayhawk Fine Chemical Corporation during various ASUG events. At Jayhawk, SAP S/4HANA was deployed in five months. What made this project successful?</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="drive-higher-value-outcomes-and-new-customer-experiences-through-innovative-products-services-and-business-models-with-sap-solutions-for-chemicals">Drive higher value outcomes and new customer experiences through innovative products, services, and business models with SAP solutions for chemicals</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/chemicals.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The foundation is always the excitement for change. Enowa’s business process experts were able to demonstrate foundational changes that would help every department drive efficiency, and now fast forward to the past year where every person is essential and process efficiency is key. Once we established the C-suite’s commitment to change, we kept them visible while navigating around the other departments, from finance, to production, to warehouse, and to customer service.</p>
  <p>The ability for our experts to create excitement about change is key. Jayhawk’s team was as equally committed and motivated as we were, which is the key for accomplishing a project together. We always explain this to clients: The software works, but we cannot just do this project <em>to you</em>, we need to do it <em>with you</em>.</p>
  <h3 id="when-we-talk-to-customers-big-or-small-change-management-is-a-key-pillar-of-digital-transformation-how-are-companies-embracing-these-changes-and-equipping-their-teams-for-success">When we talk to customers, big or small, change management is a key pillar of digital transformation. How are companies embracing these changes and equipping their teams for success?</h3>
  <p>I see two things here. Readiness and change management.</p>
  <p>Our clients understand that SAP S/4HANA works; the end-to-end technology supports the majority of business processes, especially in the chemical industry. What is often confused is the business changes necessary in a readiness phase. These include the story build, the vision, and many benefit statements needed to bring the business into a lead or co-lead position for foundational change. Given Enowa’s business consulting experts, we build the storyboard to ensure the business drives projects and participates in key decisions. Simultaneously, Enowa is working with IT to build the platform, including systems, applications, and technology components as preparation for a successful adoption of SAP S/4HANA.</p>
  <p>Recently, organizational change management is a regular topic. In the past, Enowa had always executed a “train the trainer” approach via our consultants who performed the project and were most intimate with configuration and supporting documentation. As change is now occurring with remote work and more disparate operations, we approach each client with a rich program to understand what it means to do their job after go-live. These programs contain knowledge portals for managing and tracking training, documentation, help guides, and other key elements. We also promote a non-live system that is close to what a productive solution would look like for larger programs, so users can touch and feel a system in a day-in-the-life scenario.</p>
  <h3 id="enowa-is-a-close-partner-to-sap-and-continues-to-execute-successful-projects-what-advice-can-you-offer-to-our-chemical-clients-to-enable-success">Enowa is a close partner to SAP and continues to execute successful projects. What advice can you offer to our chemical clients to enable success?</h3>
  <p>We have a few pillars of success, which have been recent changes to the current delivery capacity. These foundational delivery components, in a remote setting, can be leveraged by SAP clients as well.</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Execute in small teams. Only engage meeting or project participation with those that are critical. Wide project teams take longer to move and communication is more challenging.</li>
    <li>Look at the pieces of a process that are most complex and tackle them succinctly in small groups and consumable portions. Engage an internal or external expert to validate the overall process before digging in deeper.</li>
    <li>Encourage and equip every participant with good audio, visual, and remote working means.</li>
    <li>Spend the time and effort to build a robust training plan and execute it thoroughly.</li>
  </ul>
  <h3 id="how-does-enowa-create-value-for-the-chemical-industry-and-how-can-people-connect-with-you">How does Enowa create value for the chemical Industry and how can people connect with you?</h3>
  <p>Recognizing the Enowa logo is getting easier given the depth of our projects in the chemical industry. We are growing our activity in many areas of SAP, like chemical and other manufacturing industries such as food, consumer packaged goods, and pharmaceuticals.</p>
  <p>While our logo appears up with the large system integrators, we are still intimate in what we do – our clients appreciate and realize having the right dedicated expert, not necessarily a whole swath of resources in a different country, is needed. When we deliver our projects with a smaller team of experts, communication is streamlined, clutter is lost, and the overall number of delivery hours is a fraction of when trying to execute with too many consultants.</p>
  <p>As many of our clients will tell you, I am available when you need me, and this is true of our team. I’m routinely getting text messages from the executives at our clients and responding to calls and e-mails at all times of the day. We can be followed on social media, contacted through an expert on our website chat, called at 610-296-3640, or e-mailed at <a href="mailto:info@enowa.com">info@enowa.com</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Looking to stay connected with the chemical industry? Join the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/2152/">SAP Chemical Industry community on LinkedIn</a>, follow us on Twitter <a href="https://twitter.com/sapchemicals">@SAPChemicals</a>, and check out our <a href="https://community.sap.com/topics/chemicals">SAP Community page</a>.</p>
        <p>SAP is a leader in the chemical industry and is committed to continuous innovation. We encourage you to collaborate with us and discuss how the SAP solution portfolio can enable the intelligent enterprise in the chemical industry.</p>
        <p><em>Matthew Reymann is a chemicals solution specialist at SAP.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/chemical-industry-partner-series</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hitachi Vantara: Maximizing Business Value in the Chemical Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/hitachi-vantara-business-value-chemical-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/hitachi-vantara-business-value-chemical-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The SAP partner ecosystem is critical to the success of the chemical industry. Learn how Hitachi Vantara creates value.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b0a0eb14b04e62e8b1d2fd0ce35b6a175876b052.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b0a0eb14b04e62e8b1d2fd0ce35b6a175876b052.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b0a0eb14b04e62e8b1d2fd0ce35b6a175876b052.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Hitachi Vantara: Maximizing Business Value in the Chemical Industry" src="./media_1b0a0eb14b04e62e8b1d2fd0ce35b6a175876b052.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="hitachi-vantara-maximizing-business-value-in-the-chemical-industry">Hitachi Vantara: Maximizing Business Value in the Chemical Industry</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>With deep industry knowledge and a commitment to value realization, the SAP partner ecosystem is critical to the success of the chemical industry. SAP partners help customers of all sizes in countries worldwide take advantage of SAP’s innovative solutions, simplify their business processes, and orchestrate the Intelligent Enterprise.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To bring this perspective to the SAP community in the chemical industry, we are kicking off 2021 with our Chemical Industry Partner Stage Series.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.hitachivantara.com/en-us/home.html">Hitachi Vantara</a>, a wholly-owned subsidiary of Hitachi, Ltd., announced it has come together with Hitachi Consulting as one company to create a new digital infrastructure and solutions powerhouse. The new Hitachi Vantara combines consulting-led digital solutions and vertical industry expertise of Hitachi Consulting with Hitachi Vantara’s IT and Internet of Things (IoT) domain expertise. Going forward, the integrated company will help customers develop practical, scalable digital strategies and solutions that transform operational processes, improve customer experiences, and create new business models to drive innovation and growth.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c3965f60225a5a61acf34b810893c34dc222084a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c3965f60225a5a61acf34b810893c34dc222084a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c3965f60225a5a61acf34b810893c34dc222084a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1c3965f60225a5a61acf34b810893c34dc222084a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="313" height="91">
    </picture>Hitachi Vantara has evolved since its founding in 1989 from a manufacturer of mainframes, to enterprise storage systems, to complete cloud computing solutions, to complete digital transformation services. Today, Hitachi Vantara provides hardware, software, content platforms, storage arrays, and professional services globally.
  </p>
  <p>Hitachi was founded over 100 years ago and is one of the largest manufacturing conglomerates in the world with over 200 manufacturing facilities that produce automotive parts and systems, robotics, military vehicles, construction machinery, locomotives, consumer products, steel, wire and cable, telecommunications equipment, IT infrastructure, wind generation systems, nuclear power plants, hydroelectric power plants, elevators and escalators, aerospace components, power grid equipment, chemicals, and infrastructure components.</p>
  <p>Here, we talk with Jack Roman, vice president of Americas, and Kimberly Reid, vice president of U.S., SAP Solutions, from Hitachi Vantara.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="whitepaper-the-intelligent-enterprise-for-the-chemical-industry">Whitepaper: The Intelligent Enterprise for the Chemical Industry</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2016/03/d2238cd0-627c-0010-82c7-eda71af511fa.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="q-when-you-talk-to-chemical-customers-what-excites-you-about-the-chemical-industry">Q: When you talk to chemical customers, what excites you about the chemical industry?</h3>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> Our company was founded as a manufacturing company and both of us have backgrounds in manufacturing. Kimberley came out of the chemical industry, Jack came out of the glass manufacturing industry, and both of us have spent over 25 years consulting for primarily manufacturing firms. Close to 20 years ago we decided to focus on the chemical industry and have worked with many chemical companies over the years.</p>
  <p>We both have a passion for manufacturing, helping process manufacturing companies improve and compete, and, for a lack of a better term, working with old school heavy industrial manufacturing firms. We both still get excited to walk into a chemical plant and learn about its business, challenges, history, and evolution as a firm. Some people get excited about Silicon Valley or fancy consumer products; we get excited about chemicals!</p>
  <h3 id="was-a-crazy-year-looking-forward-what-do-you-see-as-the-top-priorities-for-chemical-customers-in-2021">2020 was a crazy year. Looking forward, what do you see as the top priorities for chemical customers in 2021?</h3>
  <p>Yes, 2020 was a crazy year. We saw chemical companies having economic challenges for probably 12 months or more before the coronavirus hit. <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> obviously added greatly to these challenges. We saw a lot of companies in crisis management throughout 2020, but now we are starting to see management refocusing on longer term priorities.</p>
  <p>I think the top themes we hear from chemical company executives are the reevaluation of supply chains caused by both COVID-19 and trade disputes, new technologies and consumer demands impacting the bottom line and the ability to forecast the future, sustainability and risk management, and the volatility of commodity prices. Besides managing the impact of COVID-19 and trying to determine how work life will change in the future, if we had to prioritize what challenges we hear chemical companies addressing and investing in to address in 2021, number one would be sustainability and the circular economy, then alternative material sources (renewable, bio-based), and finally digitization (IoT, sensors, automation).</p>
  <h3 id="how-has-digital-enabled-these-priorities-from-your-perspective">How has digital enabled these priorities from your perspective?</h3>
  <p>Digital is all about capturing data, storing data, and analyzing data. Digital has enabled the ability to capture huge amounts of data that weren’t available in the past. Capturing it is one thing, but the value comes from having the tools and ability to analyze the data and use it to make decisions, change, and react. Whether its customer preferences, supply chain track and trace, manufacturing efficiencies, product quality, or employee and environmental safety – whatever the priority – we see companies investing to build the capability to capture data and use the results of analysis to improve their business.</p>
  <h3 id="when-we-talk-to-chemical-industry-customers-big-or-small-change-management-is-a-key-pillar-of-digital-transformation-how-are-companies-embracing-these-changes-and-equipping-their-teams-for-success">When we talk to chemical industry customers, big or small, change management is a key pillar of digital transformation. How are companies embracing these changes and equipping their teams for success?</h3>
  <p>From our perspective as a professional services firm focused on process manufacturing for the past 25 years, we have seen a significant shift in our projects. At one time it was very technical, a very technology-centric approach to implementing solutions. Then it became all about speed: how can customers reduce three- to five-year implementations to a year or under a year—pre-configured industry solutions, methodologies, code libraries, and templates.</p>
  <p>But, even the most efficient implementations were not always totally successful because one piece was missing: change management. About 10 years ago we realized that change management was as important or perhaps more important than any other component of a transformation. We started placing much more emphasis on it in our projects, training our consultants, and eventually incorporating it as a key part of our methodology. Our chemical customers today are much more aware of the importance of change management, and they don’t need to be convinced to invest the money and resources in this part of a project.</p>
  <p>Companies recognize that there is a lot of change involved and recognize the importance of planning for this and addressing it. It’s one of our primary conversation topics with customers when we are planning digital transformations. When it comes to equipping their teams, it’s recognized that key customer resources that hold credibility in the organization should be tasked with change management. It is recognized that consulting resources, in some cases a significant amount, should be retained as part of the project. Whether our project manager pushes it or the customer realizes it and wants it, there is an emphasis on change management tasks and deliverables. These include training, communication, executive sponsorship and involvement, job function change evaluation, and all of the tools that help with these.</p>
  <h3 id="we-had-a-chance-to-hear-about-hitachi-vantaras-sap-s4hana-implementation-at-tokyo-chemicals-during-the-2019-best-practices-for-chemicals-event-what-made-this-project-successful">We had a chance to hear about Hitachi Vantara’s SAP S/4HANA implementation at Tokyo Chemicals during the 2019 Best Practices for Chemicals event. What made this project successful?</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="drive-higher-value-outcomes-and-new-customer-experiences-through-innovative-products-services-and-business-models-with-sap-solutions-for-chemicals">Drive higher value outcomes and new customer experiences through innovative products, services, and business models with SAP solutions for chemicals</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/chemicals.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This project was successful because of our desire to be fully aligned with their strategic goals and business vision. We understood the need to partner, collaborate, and think creatively in the midst of a global pandemic where our entire global team worked virtually. Our SAP S/4HANA go-live occurred in May 2020 and the global big bang deployment to transform operations was quite remarkable.</p>
  <h3 id="what-does-hitachi-vantara-deliver-in-your-chemical-industry-best-practices-business-scenarios-template">What does Hitachi Vantara deliver in your Chemical Industry Best Practices business scenarios template?</h3>
  <p>We leverage the pre-configured content at the core of SAP S/4HANA and focus on bringing to light the value of specific SAP Fiori apps, embedded analytics, and embedded capabilities in transportation management and warehouse management to provide an end-to-end solution capability. In addition, we deliver simplified integrated business planning scenarios to enable consensus-based planning processes, inventory optimization, and the development of constrained supply plans. Our focus is on delivering value in a meaningful way that will drive higher user adoption rates and sustainable business value.</p>
  <h3 id="what-makes-hitachi-vantara-different-from-other-implementation-partners-in-the-chemical-industry">What makes Hitachi Vantara different from other implementation partners in the chemical industry?</h3>
  <p>We believe that our understanding of the pain points, challenges, and trends facing our customers is one of our greatest strengths. We recognize that when we help our clients learn their new business processes in conjunction with SAP products, end users will adhere to the new ways of executing tasks. This supports maximizing business value attainment and helps our customers see value in the SAP investment.</p>
  <p>We stay connected to the latest innovations that are planned in our areas of focus and we assist in determining the relevancy of these capabilities for the clients we serve. We define implementation strategies and approaches that support the customer throughout their entire journey. We enjoy sharing our lessons learned and helping our clients to grow and develop a passion for SAP solution capabilities.</p>
  <h3 id="why-partner-with-hitachi-vantara">Why partner with Hitachi Vantara?</h3>
  <p>Hitachi isn’t just a top SAP partner and a leader in the chemical industry; we are also a large, global manufacturing organization that happens to be one of the largest users of SAP in the world. We focus on manufacturing companies with a heavy emphasis on process manufacturing. We have been delivering SAP solutions utilizing the Chemical Industry Best Practices template for over 15 years. Change management is a key component of our methodology and all our projects. Our teams consist of experienced consultants, many of whom have worked in the chemical industry and understand manufacturing.</p>
  <h3 id="how-does-hitachi-vantara-create-value-for-the-chemical-industry-and-how-can-people-connect-with-you">How does Hitachi Vantara create value for the chemical industry and how can people connect with you?</h3>
  <p>We create value by helping to demystify the SAP value proposition for mid-size chemical manufacturing companies and allow them to streamline their software portfolio while lowering operational costs associated with using SAP. We help to provide the foundation for growth and further innovation through the SAP platform. We help our clients adopt new business models by leveraging the tools and accelerators available through our Hitachi manufacturing heritage. You can reach us at <a href="mailto:Jack.Roman@hitachivantara.com">Jack.Roman@hitachivantara.com</a> and <a href="mailto:Kimberley.Reid@hitachivantara.com">Kimberley.Reid@hitachivantara.com</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Looking to stay connected with the chemical industry? Join the SAP Chemical Industry Community on LinkedIn, follow us on Twitter @SAPChemicals, and check out our <a href="https://community.sap.com/topics/chemicals">SAP Community page</a>.</p>
        <p>SAP is a leader in the chemical industry, and we are committed to continuous innovation. We encourage you to collaborate with us and discuss how the SAP solution portfolio can enable the intelligent chemical enterprise.</p>
        <p><em>Mark Carlson is a chemicals solution expert at SAP</em>.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/chemical-industry-partner-series</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>