<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-topic/ecosystem/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Elevating the RISE with SAP Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/06/elevating-rise-with-sap-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/06/elevating-rise-with-sap-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn more about the elevated RISE with SAP experience that is improving services and delivery for customers end-to-end.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16f71bd27ee4db299c2fe36e929f4108d8ce4d936.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16f71bd27ee4db299c2fe36e929f4108d8ce4d936.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16f71bd27ee4db299c2fe36e929f4108d8ce4d936.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Elevating the RISE with SAP Experience" src="./media_16f71bd27ee4db299c2fe36e929f4108d8ce4d936.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="elevating-the-rise-with-sap-experience">Elevating the RISE with SAP Experience</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>According to Albert Einstein, “Life is like a bicycle. To keep your balance, you must keep moving.” He had a point! The same is true of business.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-sapphire-taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">SAP Sapphire: Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Successful businesses keep moving and evolving, especially in times of rapid change and macroeconomic uncertainty. And given the current volatility, business transformation is no longer optional; it’s imperative.</p>
  <p>Knowing this, we launched RISE with SAP in 2021 not as a technical IT migration approach, but as a comprehensive solution designed to drive broad business transformation. With 6,000 customers having selected RISE with SAP, we know we cannot stop moving either. And I was <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZZ1yFoALzAs">thrilled to share at SAP Sapphire this year</a> how we are taking the RISE with SAP experience to the next level and improving services and delivery for customers end-to-end.</p>
  <p>Here are some key takeaways.</p>
  <h2 id="evolving-how-we-engage-with-customers">Evolving How We Engage with Customers</h2>
  <p>Navigating the transformation of today’s complex system landscapes and business processes is like orchestrating a symphony with countless instruments and moving parts. To succeed, we need to keep refining our engagement approach to better manage the intricacies of our customers’ complex architecture at an unprecedented level of detail.</p>
  <p>To this end, we’re making a lot of changes in how we engage with customers, including strengthening the role of the enterprise architect (EA). The EA harmonizes all elements and guides the customer throughout their cloud journey.</p>
  <h2 id="enhancing-methodologies">Enhancing Methodologies</h2>
  <p>We know the biggest challenge for any cloud transformation is to make the system landscape more agile and enable innovation — quickly. We’ve been listening and have introduced solutions. For example, our <strong><a href="/2024/04/transform-confidence-rise-with-sap-methodology">RISE with SAP Methodology</a></strong> is a significant step forward in creating a consistent experience for all RISE with SAP customers, independent of their individual cloud journeys. Now, a dedicated enterprise architect guides customers through the RISE with SAP Methodology to enhance onboarding and provides transparency throughout the project with key milestone checks, q-gates, and checklists that ensure consistent quality and more predictable timelines throughout the implementation process.</p>
  <p>This new offering is included in our <strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/rise.html#migration">SAP RISE Migration and Modernization</a></strong> program, which is designed to give customers the confidence to migrate even the most complex ERP systems to the cloud. By enabling our customers to integrate and extend SAP S/4HANA with a clean core approach, we ensure our customers experience better maintainability and lower total cost of ownership.​ Because legacy ERP systems often carry technical debt and, let’s face it, code is also a liability not just an asset. The more code you have, the more you have to optimize, debug, and modernize. And this is something we all need to actively work against.</p>
  <h2 id="introducing-partner-training-and-validation">Introducing Partner Training and Validation</h2>
  <p>We are also making it easier for RISE with SAP customers to identify partners to help with complex SAP S/4HANA Cloud transformations. It is essential for our partner ecosystem to follow the RISE with SAP Methodology as well. For customers to onboard successfully, there needs to be a close alignment between SAP, the customer, and implementation partner. This is why we are training and validating partners to use the RISE with SAP Methodology and will collaborate closely with partners to provide consistency and quality.</p>
  <p>We are also introducing the <strong>RISE with SAP Validated Partner</strong> recognition, which verifies a partner’s adherence to the RISE with SAP Methodology and our q-gates, giving businesses the confidence to know that they are fully leveraging the potential of cloud-based innovations from SAP. Almost 90% of all SAP implementations are overseen by partners, so training and validating them is a key part of our strategy to ensure consistency and quality for customers.</p>
  <h2 id="building-a-seamless-end-to-end-tool-chain">Building a Seamless End-to-End Tool Chain</h2>
  <p>As a former SAP CIO, I’ve felt the challenges (and pain) of large-scale transformation. I know the pressure CIOs are under to show tangible business outcomes quickly. It’s why true business transformation requires a holistic approach, not a simple technology lift and shift.</p>
  <p>We deliver the most complete business transformation suite in the industry. With the range of capabilities on offer today — including SAP Signavio, SAP LeanIX, and SAP Cloud ALM solutions as well as SAP Business Technology Platform — we have an amazing set of tools to bring out the best in businesses. Now, we are bringing them more closely together as one end-to-end seamless tool chain to make it easier to manage the process, system, and data landscape holistically.</p>
  <p>With our recently announced <a href="/2024/06/sap-enters-agreement-to-acquire-walkme">agreement to acquire <strong>WalkMe</strong></a>, we plan to further strengthen our ability to deliver successful business transformation across applications, processes, systems, and people. ​WalkMe will help us incorporate user-centric adoption, enablement, and productivity capabilities alongside our Business Transformation Management portfolio of SAP Signavio and SAP LeanIX solutions. And WalkMe’s AI capabilities will complement our process AI with user intelligence, improving the capabilities of our <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">generative AI copilot Joule</a> to help people get work done faster.​</p>
  <h2 id="sap-business-ai-new-frontier-for-business-transformation">SAP Business AI: New Frontier for Business Transformation</h2>
  <p>In 2024, SAP Sapphire has been an opportunity for us to showcase how we are introducing in a new era of optimized business operations, with all the IT complexity concealed behind intuitive, AI-powered user experiences.</p>
  <p>We highlighted the progress we are making embedding Joule throughout our enterprise portfolio and the enormous potential we see for AI to support both customers and partners in their RISE with SAP journey. I was thrilled to announce that starting in Q4 of 2024, customers and partners can leverage generative AI-powered assistance for their RISE with SAP clean core success plan.</p>
  <p>We are also bringing new consulting capabilities to Joule, aimed at simplifying SAP implementations for partners. The new consulting capability draws insights from SAP product documentation and the SAP community to provide consultants with vital information and is planned to be available in the second half of this year.</p>
  <h2 id="business-transformation-more-than-an-it-project">Business Transformation: More Than an IT Project</h2>
  <p>At SAP, we understand that true business transformation is more than an IT project. It requires a holistic approach and not a simple technological lift and shift. That’s why we are putting the people, methodologies, financial incentives, tools, partner practices, and SAP Business AI in place to ensure our customers not only have compelling reasons to move to the cloud, but also a compelling experience.</p>
  <p><strong>Learn more:</strong></p>
  <ul>
    <li>Watch the replay of the <strong><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZZ1yFoALzAs">Customer Keynote at SAP Sapphire</a></strong></li>
    <li>Read all the announcements in the <strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">SAP Sapphire News Guide</a></strong></li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Thomas Saueressig is a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE leading Customer Services &#x26; Delivery.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-leanix</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Game On: Business Builders Prepares Future Business Leaders for a Data-Driven World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/business-builders-sap-university-alliances</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/business-builders-sap-university-alliances</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Business Builders, built from a partnership between SAP University Alliances and HEC Montréal, is where education meets real-world needs.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Introduces a New Validation Recognition for Service Partners]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/new-rise-with-sap-validated-partner-recognition</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/new-rise-with-sap-validated-partner-recognition</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The new RISE with SAP Validated Partner SAP recognition helps customers with complex SAP ERP landscapes starting their journey.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a157e78734853652179498700d8b366ba88f70cd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a157e78734853652179498700d8b366ba88f70cd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a157e78734853652179498700d8b366ba88f70cd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Introduces a New Validation Recognition for Service Partners" src="./media_1a157e78734853652179498700d8b366ba88f70cd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-introduces-a-new-validation-recognition-for-service-partners">SAP Introduces a New Validation Recognition for Service Partners</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Customers Can More Easily Identify Partners with Deep Expertise and Experience in Large and Complex RISE with SAP Implementations</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>The <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/rise.html#migration">RISE with SAP Migration and Modernization program</a> helps bring renewed focus on the cloud transformation journey by enabling smooth, secure migration of on-premise SAP ERP Central Component (SAP ECC) and SAP S/4HANA customers to the cloud.</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-sapphire-taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">SAP Sapphire: Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>One of the key pillars of the program is RISE with SAP Methodology. The methodology is designed to provide a consistent approach — from planning to go-live to ongoing operations and evolution — that can meet customers’ business transformation goals leveraging specific implementation stages and success KPIs.</p>
  <p>To support customers’ RISE with SAP transformations, SAP is <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide/erp.html#sap-validated-partner-designation">training and validating partners to use RISE with SAP Methodology</a> and collaborating closely with these partners on quality and consistency. By following the methodology, customers can drive predictable timelines for implementations and provide progress transparency with key milestone assessments.</p>
  <p>SAP customers with complex SAP ERP landscapes starting their journey to RISE with SAP can now identify their ideal cloud transformation partner through the new <strong>RISE with SAP Validated Partner</strong> recognition.</p>
  <p>These select partners meet elevated capability and experience criteria for the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/rise.html">RISE with SAP offering</a>, have proven experience in large enterprise engagements, and demonstrate their implementation approach is aligned with <a href="/2024/04/transform-confidence-rise-with-sap-methodology">RISE with SAP Methodology</a>. Using this methodology, the validated partners can ensure customers are cloud compliant and innovation ready, with an accelerated time to value.</p>
  <p>Partners that have been validated as part of this program include Accenture, Capgemini, Deloitte, EY, IBM, Infosys, NTT DATA, and PwC.</p>
  <p>In addition to adhering to the principles of RISE with SAP Methodology, these validated partners complement it in several ways, such as by leveraging specialized tools, templates, architecture patterns, and pre-configured solutions that speed up transformation of our enterprise customers. Additional eligible partners will be validated in the second half of 2024.</p>
  <p>“Empowering our partners with RISE with SAP Methodology isn’t just about alignment; it’s about forging a standardized path to success,” said SAP Chief Partner Officer Karl Fahrbach. “By formalizing our engagement model, we reinforce a commitment to excellence, ensuring every project delivers with precision and consistency, driving unparalleled results for our most valued customers. Our partners can lead the way with our support, igniting a paradigm shift in how we approach innovation and collaboration.”</p>
  <p>Companies also have the option to leverage <a href="https://partnerfinder.sap.com/partnerNavigator?designation=rise&#x26;q=&#x26;queryType=partner">SAP Partner Finder</a> and the <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2022/06/426a3ea2-3f7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Competency Framework</a> to find the expertise they need, no matter their business challenges, company size, industry, or location. Partners that have attained the essential level have met the minimum training and delivery requirements for delivering RISE with SAP implementations. This gives customers confidence that the partner has the necessary level of maturity and has demonstrated customer success through effective project delivery.</p>
  <p>RISE with SAP Validated partners are required to attain the expert level of multiple competencies, including RISE with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition, SAP Business Technology Platform, and SAP Business Process Transformation. These designated partners must also maintain bi-annual performance requirements and eligibility checks with a focus on clean core quality gates.</p>
  <p>For additional information regarding the <a href="/2024/01/rise-with-sap-migration-and-modernization-cloud-first-business-strategy">RISE with SAP Migration and Modernization program</a> and the importance of partners, read “<a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/enterprise-resource-planning-blogs-by-sap/partners-are-vital-to-your-company-s-success-when-transitioning-to-cloud/ba-p/13616168">Partners Are Vital to Your Company’s Success When Transitioning to Cloud ERP</a>.”</p>
  <p>Eric van Rossum is chief marketing officer for Cloud ERP at SAP.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's New AI Innovations and Partnerships Deliver Real-World Results]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/ai-innovations-partnerships-sap-sapphire</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/ai-innovations-partnerships-sap-sapphire</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Explore the AI capabilities and ecosystem innovations presented at SAP Sapphire in 2024, all aimed at delivering real-world results.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/abap-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>news-tag/ai-ethics</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/aws</category>
            <category>news-tag/bcg</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Generative AI Innovations Take Center Stage at SAP Sapphire in 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-generative-ai-center-stage</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-generative-ai-center-stage</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A series of generative AI innovations and partnerships announced at SAP Sapphire showcase how SAP is taking business to the next level.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183c39d6e19efd7774c87954a8bbf7838320ef779.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183c39d6e19efd7774c87954a8bbf7838320ef779.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_183c39d6e19efd7774c87954a8bbf7838320ef779.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Generative AI Innovations Take Center Stage at SAP Sapphire in 2024" src="./media_183c39d6e19efd7774c87954a8bbf7838320ef779.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="generative-ai-innovations-take-center-stage-at-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Generative AI Innovations Take Center Stage at SAP Sapphire in 2024</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP CEO Christian Klein kicked off SAP Sapphire this week with an upbeat keynote that highlighted the company’s latest business AI innovations, products, and partnerships, which he said will change how people work.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“This year is a very special Sapphire,” Klein said. “We are entering a new phase of AI, with endless possibilities for us all.”</p>
  <p>Klein and Chief Marketing and Solutions Officer Julia White used the keynote to outline how AI will deliver real business benefits for different corporate functions and “Bring Out Your Best,” this year’s event theme.</p>
  <h2 id="delivering-on-an-ai-promise">Delivering on an AI Promise</h2>
  <p>Klein emphasized how SAP has delivered on its promise to infuse generative AI throughout its business portfolio, has enabled customers to exploit the potential of business AI, and has positioned the Joule copilot as the new front end for SAP applications.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a9e312c5b8efe848ea7622ac6bcc8c38c9e5913.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a9e312c5b8efe848ea7622ac6bcc8c38c9e5913.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11a9e312c5b8efe848ea7622ac6bcc8c38c9e5913.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Sapphire Opening Keynote: Bring Out the Best in Your Business | 2024" src="./media_11a9e312c5b8efe848ea7622ac6bcc8c38c9e5913.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/gOVQhhm5yO0?si=wkpDopYq0gPK6kWn">SAP Sapphire Opening Keynote: Bring Out the Best in Your Business | 2024</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Together, the two also announced the next evolution and new capabilities in both RISE with SAP and GROW with SAP. Since it was launched over three years ago, more than 6,000 customers have selected RISE with SAP. During his keynote, Klein announced that RISE with SAP will now include a dedicated enterprise architect to guide customers through the RISE with SAP Methodology as well as an integrated tool chain to help manage the process, system, and data landscape holistically across the RISE with SAP life cycle.</p>
  <p>Meanwhile White, broadcasting live from the central showcase on the SAP Sapphire show floor, announced that cloud ERP offering GROW with SAP will now include SAP Sales Cloud and Concur Expense at no additional charge. Whether its managing your finances or managing your expenses, GROW with SAP has you covered, she said.</p>
  <h2 id="ai-momentum">AI Momentum</h2>
  <p>Building on SAP’s business AI momentum, Klein and White also announced a series of expanded partnerships to help companies make the most out of this decisive AI moment. The expanded partnerships include deals with Amazon Web Services (AWS) and Google Cloud. Klein also announced the integration of Microsoft 365 Copilot with Joule, delivering what he described as a “truly differentiated employee experience.”</p>
  <p>Together onstage with customers and SAP Chief AI Officer Philipp Herzig, they showcased how SAP is infusing generative AI throughout the application portfolio and enabling customers to thrive in the AI era.</p>
  <p>“The business AI innovations we’re announcing will not only change how people work with SAP solutions, but how people work overall,” said Klein ahead of his keynote address.</p>
  <h2 id="new-joule-capabilities">New Joule Capabilities</h2>
  <p>Klein announced Joule for consulting capabilities and Joule for ABAP developer capabilities, which will help SAP’s 6-million-strong consultant and developer community to accelerate projects by 30% and implement SAP solutions faster than ever before.</p>
  <p>During his keynote he described business AI as being “an inflection point” and added, “Today’s AI announcements and partnerships build on our commitment to deliver revolutionary technology that drives real-world results, helping customers unleash the agility and ingenuity they need to succeed in today’s fast-moving business landscape.”</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16cdfc9fd1fdbbf5cdc9cd5193401b9dfcafd1805.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16cdfc9fd1fdbbf5cdc9cd5193401b9dfcafd1805.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16cdfc9fd1fdbbf5cdc9cd5193401b9dfcafd1805.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Why Joule Will Change the Way You Work" src="./media_16cdfc9fd1fdbbf5cdc9cd5193401b9dfcafd1805.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/a9j2Q6VVCfM?si=9cdzuqQ27TZ_J3uj">Why Joule Will Change the Way You Work</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“SAP is the only tech company who can infuse AI capabilities right into your business processes and workflows,” he said, saluting the achievements of the 40,000 SAP employees in the Product Development organization.</p>
  <h2 id="shout-out-to-sap-developers">Shout Out to SAP Developers</h2>
  <p>“No other tech company can offer a more powerful platform to transform enterprises to rewrite how business is run.” SAP developers have transformed SAP’s portfolio “from an ERP system that enabled transactions in real time, to a system with modular applications and embedded AI so that you can run intelligent, connected, and sustainable enterprises.”</p>
  <p>“We promised this to you, and we delivered,” Klein told audiences online and the 14,000 customers and partners attending SAP Sapphire in person this week in Orlando. “Now we are using the power of generative AI across our stack to once again revolutionize how businesses run and end users will work in the future.”</p>
  <p>After announcing generative AI copilot Joule in September 2023, Klein confirmed that it will become the new front-end and UX for SAP applications and “will turn your words into action.” Joule is ready for prime time, he declared, “and going forward, it will be embedded out of the box for all our cloud customers.”</p>
  <h2 id="joule-key-to-higher-productivity">Joule: Key to Higher Productivity</h2>
  <p>He predicted that Joule will also become the biggest productivity engine for every SAP end user, and that by the end of the year, 80% of the most used tasks will be managed via Joule and the 300 million end users of SAP products will be 20% more productive.</p>
  <p>While AI is a powerful technology facilitating huge opportunities for business and employees, the SAP CEO emphasized that it is also crucial to offer responsible AI. To that end, he announced that SAP is among the first tech companies to adhere to UNESCO’s AI principles.</p>
  <p>Klein wrapped up the keynote by emphasizing that SAP does not view AI as an end in itself, but rather as a tool to help the world run better and improve people’s lives. “You have my commitment that we will continue to listen to your needs, we will continue to deliver great innovations and we will continue to deliver great outcomes for your company.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Joule to Integrate with Microsoft Copilot for a Unified Work Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/joule-microsoft-copilot-unified-work-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/joule-microsoft-copilot-unified-work-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is bringing its generative AI copilot Joule together with Microsoft Copilot for Microsoft 365 for deep bi-directional integration.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/microsoft</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Expands Business AI Portfolio with Meta Open-Source Models]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-business-ai-meta-open-source-models</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-business-ai-meta-open-source-models</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is integrating Meta Llama 2 and Meta Llama 3 models into generative AI hub to enable customers to create dashboards based on rich content.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP’s Partnership with Mistral AI, One of the Leading LLM Makers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-mistral-ai-leading-llm-maker-partnership</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-mistral-ai-leading-llm-maker-partnership</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The collaboration between SAP and Mistral AI is a symbiotic combination of AI expertise and technology. Learn about the partnership.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Accenture Collaborate on Getting to Value Faster with SAP Business AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/accenture-sap-sapphire-business-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/accenture-sap-sapphire-business-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Accenture are working together to help their customers make SAP Business AI and data their No. 1 competitive advantage.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-leanix</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-news-business-ai-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-cutting-edge-partnerships</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-news-business-ai-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-cutting-edge-partnerships</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New SAP Business AI innovations and collaborations with partners are igniting ingenuity. Read the news from SAP Sapphire Orlando in 2024.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best" src="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-infuses-business-ai-throughout-its-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-and-partners-with-cutting-edge-ai-leaders-to-bring-out-customers-best">SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP Business AI Innovations and Collaborations with Partners including Google Cloud, Meta, Microsoft, Mistral AI and NVIDIA Ignite Ingenuity</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td><strong><em>ORLANDO</em></strong> — At its annual SAP Sapphire conference, SAP unveiled generative AI innovations and partnerships that showcase how the company is taking business to the next level in the era of AI.</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By infusing Business AI across an enterprise cloud portfolio that powers the world’s most mission-critical processes and partnering with companies pushing the edge of what’s possible with AI, SAP is igniting a new wave of insight and ingenuity in global business.</p>
  <p>“The Business AI innovations we’re announcing at SAP Sapphire in 2024 will redefine the way businesses run,” says Christian Klein, CEO and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “Today’s AI announcements and partnerships build on our commitment to deliver revolutionary technology that drives real-world results, helping customers unleash the agility and ingenuity they need to succeed in today’s fast-moving business landscape.”</p>
  <h2 id="ai-that-means-business">AI That Means Business</h2>
  <p>As SAP embeds Business AI across its enterprise solutions, it puts rich insights at users’ fingertips, empowering them to deliver better outcomes and elevate the creative problem-solving humans do best. Examples include AI-generated reports in SAP SuccessFactors solutions that give people managers responsibly sourced insights for compensation-related discussions as well as forecasting capabilities in SAP Sales Cloud solutions that predict combinations of salespeople and products most likely to drive sales. Meanwhile, the SAP Business Technology Platform is adding large language models from Amazon Web Services, Meta and Mistral AI to its generative AI hub. This capability in the SAP AI Core infrastructure makes it easier to build generative AI use cases for SAP applications.</p>
  <p>SAP’s generative AI copilot Joule, which quickly sorts and contextualizes data from multiple systems to advance automation and improve decision-making, is expanding throughout the company’s solution portfolio. Joule launched in <a href="/2023/09/joule-new-generative-ai-assistant">SAP SuccessFactors solutions last fall</a> and is now embedded into SAP S/4HANA Cloud solutions and others including SAP Build and SAP Integration Suite. Further expansion by year-end will include SAP Ariba and SAP Analytics Cloud solutions. At Sapphire, SAP also announced <a href="/">plans to further broaden Joule’s scope</a> by integrating it with Microsoft Copilot to surface even richer insights. This deep, bi-directional integration gives users a unified experience built right into the flow of work, enabling seamless access to information from interactions with business applications in SAP and Microsoft 365.</p>
  <p>Reflecting Business AI’s increasing importance, SAP is redoubling its commitment to the principles of relevant, reliable, and responsible AI it pioneered. At Sapphire, SAP is adopting the 10 guiding principles of the UNESCO Recommendation on the Ethics of Artificial Intelligence, which aim to ensure that AI technologies are developed and used in ways that respect human rights, promote fairness and contribute to sustainable development.</p>
  <h2 id="partnerships-that-scale-innovation">Partnerships That Scale Innovation</h2>
  <p>SAP is partnering with best-in-class technology leaders to push the limits of what generative AI can do at an enterprise level. In addition to our expanded collaborations with <a href="/2024/05/aws-sap-generative-ai-new-innovation">AWS</a> and Microsoft, partnerships with Google Cloud, Meta, Mistral AI and NVIDIA ensure SAP can harness the power of AI-ready technology to innovate at speed and deliver richer real-world results.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Google Cloud</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP and Google Cloud are expanding their partnership, using Business AI to help enterprises better predict and mitigate supply-chain risks to minimize disruptions and maintain optimal inventory levels. The companies will integrate Joule and the SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain solution with Google Cloud’s Gemini models AI assistant and Google Cloud Cortex Framework’s data foundation.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Meta</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP will leverage Meta Llama 3 to generate scripts that render highly customized analytics applications in SAP Analytics Cloud. Meta’s next-generation AI model excels at language nuances and contextual understanding, making it an ideal candidate for translating enterprise business requirements into tangible outcomes.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Mistral AI</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP will also add <a href="/">new large language models from Mistral AI</a>, a global company headquartered in Paris specializing in generative AI, to the generative AI hub capability in SAP AI Core.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>NVIDIA</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP and NVIDIA Corporation advance a <a href="https://blogs.nvidia.com/blog/sap-sapphire-ai-omniverse/">cross-product partnership</a> to embed cutting-edge technologies into enterprise-ready business applications:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>As SAP trains Joule to serve as an AI assistant for the RISE with SAP solution implementations, NVIDIA’s state-of-the-art AI models sift through SAP consulting assets to provide relevant and precise answers to implementation-related questions;</li>
    <li>As SAP embeds Joule in the ABAP Cloud model to generate ABAP code for SAP developers, NVIDIA’s accelerated infrastructure will run, scale, and manage SAP’s generative AI model for ABAP code generation;</li>
    <li>As SAP infuses generative AI into the SAP Intelligent Product Recommendation solution, NVIDIA Omniverse Cloud APIs enable the simulation of complex manufacturing products and configurations as industrial digital twins.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="cloud-technology-that-drives-agility-and-sustainability">Cloud Technology That Drives Agility and Sustainability</h2>
  <p>Business success in the era of AI means being in the cloud. SAP is making the move easier than ever with initiatives that help customers find partners with the expertise needed for complex SAP S/4HANA Cloud transformations. Further cloud innovations at SAP Sapphire include features that help the world’s organizations measure, manage and execute their sustainability strategies. SAP Sustainability Control Tower and SAP Sustainability Footprint Management solutions now track carbon footprints at scale and help businesses meet regulatory standards.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Learn more in the 2024 SAP Sapphire News Guide</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE:SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 (650) 445-6780, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a> PT<br>Marcus Winkler, +49 6227-767497, <a href="mailto:marcus.winkler@sap.com">marcus.winkler@sap.com</a> CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you receive this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/abap-cloud</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AWS and SAP Unlock New Innovation with Generative AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/aws-sap-generative-ai-new-innovation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/aws-sap-generative-ai-new-innovation</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and AWS are making it easier for customers to embed generative AI into their entire portfolio of business-critical applications.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_104d1ffe68c31e9f2e51bfd7af2878774eaaff54a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_104d1ffe68c31e9f2e51bfd7af2878774eaaff54a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_104d1ffe68c31e9f2e51bfd7af2878774eaaff54a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="AWS and SAP Unlock New Innovation with Generative AI" src="./media_104d1ffe68c31e9f2e51bfd7af2878774eaaff54a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="aws-and-sap-unlock-new-innovation-with-generative-ai">AWS and SAP Unlock New Innovation with Generative AI</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Generative AI hub in SAP AI Core integrates with foundation models in Amazon Bedrock to deliver generative AI-driven insights and streamline manual processes for enterprise customers</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td><strong><em>SEATTLE and WALLDORF</em></strong> — Amazon Web Services (AWS), an Amazon.com company (NASDAQ: AMZN), and <a href="https://www.sap.com/index.html">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced an expanded, strategic collaboration to transform modern cloud enterprise resource planning (ERP) experiences and help enterprises drive new capabilities and efficiencies with generative artificial intelligence (AI).</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>Together, AWS and SAP are striving to make it easier for customers to adopt the RISE with SAP solution on AWS, to improve the performance and efficiency of SAP workloads running in the cloud and to embed generative AI into an enterprise’s entire portfolio of business-critical applications.</p>
        <p>“AWS was the first cloud provider certified to support the SAP portfolio and today, thousands of enterprise companies run SAP solutions on AWS to get the most out of their mission-critical applications,” said Matt Garman incoming CEO at AWS. “Now, AWS and SAP are making it faster and easier for companies to apply generative AI to their core business data to become more efficient, responsive and sustainable.”</p>
        <p>“Partnerships like this collaboration with AWS are critical as we embed generative AI solutions across our ERP applications so that customers can drive innovation at an accelerated pace,” said Christian Klein, Chief Executive Officer of SAP SE. “In addition to delivering modern cloud ERP to our joint customers, we are excited to support Amazon on their own transformation journey as they adopt RISE with SAP for pioneering areas such as Project Kuiper, Amazon’s satellite initiative intended to increase global broadband access.”</p>
        <h2 id="generative-ai-models-from-amazon-bedrock-available-on-the-generative-ai-hub-in-sap-ai-core">Generative AI Models from Amazon Bedrock Available on the Generative AI Hub in SAP AI Core</h2>
        <p>The generative AI hub in SAP AI Core infrastructure provides customers with secure access to a broad range of large language models (LLMs) that can easily be integrated into SAP business applications. With the integration of generative AI models from Amazon Bedrock such as the Anthropic Claude 3 model family and Amazon Titan, SAP customers will be able to access high-performing LLMs and other foundation models (FMs) to build applications customized with their own data. Tens of thousands of customers use Amazon Bedrock to easily, quickly and securely build and scale generative AI applications using FMs from leading AI companies such as AI21 Labs, Anthropic, Cohere, Meta, Mistral AI, Stability AI and Amazon.</p>
        <p>With this integration, SAP customers may accelerate the adoption of generative AI and modernize key business processes built on SAP solutions. These innovations can be used in embedded use cases within RISE with SAP and the intelligent scenario lifecycle management functionality as an integration component or side-by-side directly on SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP). SAP and AWS plan to expand the use of Bedrock capabilities in the generative AI hub to further enable embedded AI functionality within SAP’s portfolio of cloud solutions and applications. This includes additional use cases across finance and product lifecycle management.</p>
        <h2 id="sap-to-use-aws-chips-to-train-and-deploy-future-sap-business-ai-offerings">SAP to Use AWS Chips to Train and Deploy Future SAP Business AI Offerings</h2>
        <p>SAP’s use of <a href="/2023/11/sap-hana-cloud-now-supports-aws-graviton">AWS Graviton3 chips to support SAP HANA Cloud</a> helps to deliver performance gains, cost savings and energy efficiency to SAP. By using Graviton3-based Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2) instances, SAP has realized up to 30% better compute for analytical workloads and an estimated 45% reduction in carbon footprint for SAP HANA Cloud. Now SAP and AWS are collaborating on the next generation of Graviton4 for SAP HANA Cloud and additional SAP applications to continue to improve performance and efficiency. Based on the success of running SAP HANA Cloud on AWS Graviton, SAP plans to use AWS Graviton to support SAP solutions and applications such as SAP BTP, SAP Datasphere, SAP Analytics Cloud and the SAP Cloud ALM solution.</p>
        <p>SAP plans to use <a href="https://aws.amazon.com/machine-learning/inferentia/">AWS Trainium</a> and <a href="https://aws.amazon.com/machine-learning/inferentia/">AWS Inferentia</a> chips, purpose built for AI and machine learning (ML) workloads, for training and deploying future SAP Business AI offerings. Using Trainium and Inferentia2-based instances in a proof of concept, SAP engineers trained and fine-tuned generative AI LLMs in two days versus 23 days with comparable Amazon EC2 instances. By leveraging Trainium’s specialized architecture designed for efficient ML model training, SAP can accelerate the development process while maintaining high levels of accuracy and reliability.</p>
        <h2 id="increased-performance-for-rise-with-sap-on-aws">Increased Performance for RISE with SAP on AWS</h2>
        <p>Thousands of customers have selected RISE with SAP on AWS to run their largest, most complex, global SAP solution implementations. Now generally available, the next-generation Amazon EC2 High Memory U7i instances offer up to 32TiB of memory in a single instance and provide customers the memory and flexibility they need to support expanding SAP HANA database requirements. Amazon EC2 High Memory U7i instances are the first DDR5 memory-based 8-socket offering by a leading cloud provider to improve the performance of memory-intensive applications such as SAP S/4HANA Cloud as part of RISE with SAP.</p>
        <h2 id="amazons-project-kuiper-selects-rise-with-sap">Amazon’s Project Kuiper Selects RISE with SAP</h2>
        <p>Amazon companies, including Twitch, Zappos.com and Zoox Inc., already use SAP software on AWS to support their operations. And now Project Kuiper—Amazon’s satellite broadband network—is deploying RISE with SAP to support its complex supply chain and manufacturing operations and get the best performance and most value out of its mission-critical SAP software. Running SAP solutions on AWS allows Kuiper to take advantage of the latest SAP capabilities embedded in RISE with SAP to help drive impactful transformation, accelerating company decisions and enhancing overall performance and productivity.</p>
        <p>Hundreds of millions of people lack adequate internet access and Project Kuiper’s goal is to help close the digital divide by delivering fast, affordable broadband to a wide variety of customers operating in places without reliable internet connections. Delivering on that vision requires Kuiper to build satellites at an unprecedented rate. RISE with SAP allows the Project Kuiper team to leverage the most reliable and scalable infrastructure to run a modern, cloud ERP as a managed service, so they can focus on innovation instead of IT management.</p>
        <p>To learn more about the SAP and AWS partnership, tune in to the <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire.html">SAP Sapphire conference</a>, June 3-5, in Orlando.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="join-experts-speakers-and-peers-at-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Join experts, speakers and peers at SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="https://x.com/sapnews">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About Amazon Web Services</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Since 2006, Amazon Web Services has been the world’s most comprehensive and broadly adopted cloud. AWS has been continually expanding its services to support virtually any workload, and it now has more than 240 fully featured services for compute, storage, databases, networking, analytics, machine learning and artificial intelligence (AI), Internet of Things (IoT), mobile, security, hybrid, media, and application development, deployment, and management from 105 Availability Zones within 33 geographic regions, with announced plans for 18 more Availability Zones and six more AWS Regions in Malaysia, Mexico, New Zealand, the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia, Thailand, and the AWS European Sovereign Cloud. Millions of customers—including the fastest-growing startups, largest enterprises, and leading government agencies—trust AWS to power their infrastructure, become more agile, and lower costs. To learn more about AWS, visit <a href="https://cts.businesswire.com/ct/CT?id=smartlink&#x26;url=https%3A%2F%2Faws.amazon.com%2F&#x26;esheet=53904515&#x26;newsitemid=20240304438993&#x26;lan=en-US&#x26;anchor=aws.amazon.com&#x26;index=12&#x26;md5=74b48ab611b237d4b1c4af457e844e2a">aws.amazon.com</a>.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About Amazon</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Amazon is guided by four principles: customer obsession rather than competitor focus, passion for invention, commitment to operational excellence, and long-term thinking. Amazon strives to be Earth’s Most Customer-Centric Company, Earth’s Best Employer, and Earth’s Safest Place to Work. Customer reviews, 1-Click shopping, personalized recommendations, Prime, Fulfillment by Amazon, AWS, Kindle Direct Publishing, Kindle, Career Choice, Fire tablets, Fire TV, Amazon Echo, Alexa, Just Walk Out technology, Amazon Studios, and The Climate Pledge are some of the things pioneered by Amazon. For more information, visit <a href="https://cts.businesswire.com/ct/CT?id=smartlink&#x26;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.aboutamazon.com%2F&#x26;esheet=53552459&#x26;newsitemid=20230913559977&#x26;lan=en-US&#x26;anchor=amazon.com%2Fabout&#x26;index=4&#x26;md5=a9213abaf1405cdcf6f92fbf73419565">amazon.com/about</a> and follow @AmazonNews.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE: SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Scott Malinowski, +1 (781) 852-3822, <a href="mailto:scott.malinowski@sap.com">scott.malinowski@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a><br>Amazon.com, Inc. Media Hotline<br><a href="mailto:Amazon-pr@amazon.com">Amazon-pr@amazon.com</a><br><a href="https://cts.businesswire.com/ct/CT?id=smartlink&#x26;url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fpr&#x26;esheet=52838073&#x26;newsitemid=20220829005779&#x26;lan=en-US&#x26;anchor=www.amazon.com%2Fpr&#x26;index=11&#x26;md5=f7f322f746ba4e16da9b2e92d74e349a">www.amazon.com/pr</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you receive this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-ai-revolutionary-technology-real-world-results">SAP Business AI: Revolutionary technology, real-world results</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/aws</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Partners Recognized for Outstanding Achievements]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-successfactors-partners-recognized-for-achievements</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-successfactors-partners-recognized-for-achievements</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors partners received SAP Global Line of Business Partner Excellence Awards for 2024. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-global-lob-partner-excellence-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IBM and SAP Plan to Expand Collaboration to Help Clients Become Next-Generation Enterprises with Generative AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/ibm-and-sap-generative-ai-new-value-generation-partnership</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/ibm-and-sap-generative-ai-new-value-generation-partnership</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New Value Generation partnership from SAP and IBM includes new generative AI capabilities and industry-specific cloud solutions. Read the news]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aeeb46bbfcb4f664eb2a3c5eaebfbd24570cce9b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aeeb46bbfcb4f664eb2a3c5eaebfbd24570cce9b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1aeeb46bbfcb4f664eb2a3c5eaebfbd24570cce9b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="IBM and SAP Plan to Expand Collaboration to Help Clients Become Next-Generation Enterprises with Generative AI" src="./media_1aeeb46bbfcb4f664eb2a3c5eaebfbd24570cce9b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="ibm-and-sap-plan-to-expand-collaboration-to-help-clients-become-next-generation-enterprises-with-generative-ai">IBM and SAP Plan to Expand Collaboration to Help Clients Become Next-Generation Enterprises with Generative AI</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>New Value Generation partnership initiative focused on delivering greater client productivity and innovation with new generative AI capabilities and industry-specific cloud solutions</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <p><strong><em>WALLDORF and ARMONK</em></strong></p>
                <hr>
                <p>IBM (NYSE: <a href="http://www.ibm.com/investor">IBM</a>) and <a href="http://sap.com">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced their vision for the next era of their collaboration, which includes new <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/generative-ai.html">generative AI</a> capabilities and industry-specific cloud solutions that can help clients unlock business value.</p>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="unlock-new-capabilities-with-generative-ai">Unlock new capabilities with generative AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/generative-ai.html">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“IBM and SAP’s shared approach to generative AI, built on an open ecosystem, trust and purpose-built models, will help empower clients to optimize business outcomes,” said John Granger, Senior Vice President, IBM Consulting. “Our new Value Generation partnership initiative will enable clients to accelerate the path to innovation, competitive advantage and become a next generation enterprise through generative AI.”</p>
  <p>“It makes perfect sense to expand our partnership with IBM to help more customers accelerate their cloud journey leveraging RISE with SAP and realize the transformative benefits of generative AI for business in the cloud,” said Scott Russell, Chief Revenue Officer &#x26; Executive Board Member, Customer Success of SAP SE. “This expanded partnership will help more of our joint customers reach new heights by innovating through the cloud, data and business AI to grow and transform their businesses.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.ibm.com/consulting">IBM Consulting</a> and SAP aim to accelerate transformation enabled by RISE with SAP by supporting clients in the following key areas:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Next-Generation AI Business Processes</strong>: Together, the companies are exploring opportunities to build new generative AI capabilities for RISE with SAP and infuse AI into SAP business processes across industry-specific cloud solutions and line of business applications. Initially, IBM plans to extend AI capabilities across SAP’s portfolio of cloud solutions and applications, all of which are underpinned by SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP). This includes RISE with SAP, the GROW with SAP solution, financial solutions for the office of the CFO, supply chain management solutions, solutions for human capital management, SAP Customer Experience solutions and intelligent spend management solutions. IBM also plans to leverage SAP Signavio and SAP Business AI solutions to help define next-generation business processes through a proof-of-concept adoption program.</li>
    <li><strong>Next-Generation Industry Innovation</strong>: IBM and SAP plan to build intelligent industry use cases, enabled by data-driven insights, into end-to-end business processes to fuel next-generation industry innovation. These use cases will initially focus on the industrial manufacturing, consumer packaged goods (CPG), retail, defense, automotive and utilities industries. This includes IBM’s recent work with SAP to develop new AI solutions for the CPG and retail industries. As part of this initiative, IBM has begun the development of an extensive portfolio of over 100 AI solutions across industry, line-of-business and product delivery. In addition, IBM plans to develop prescriptive industry value maps that define next-generation business processes and opportunities for impact with AI. Clients will be able to access all of these new AI solutions through the global <a href="https://www.ibm.com/about/innovation-studio">IBM Innovation Studios</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation.html">SAP Experience Center</a> sites.</li>
    <li><strong>Next-Generation Platform Architecture and Customer Adoption Approach</strong>: Next-generation enterprises require next-generation platform architectures and a modernized approach to customer adoption. Through the Value Generation partnership initiative, IBM intends to provide next-generation reference architectures that enable a clean core approach. To do this, IBM plans to leverage SAP BTP, SAP Signavio and LeanIX solutions. These new reference architectures will help define standards across data, process, systems and device integration, process orchestration and automation. IBM consultants supporting clients on SAP projects can also leverage IBM Consulting Advantage, IBM’s AI services platform, and its portfolio of proprietary methods, assets and Assistants to bring more repeatability and consistency to client delivery. With IBM Consulting Advantage, IBM consultants can transform the way they deliver SAP solutions to boost productivity and mitigate risk by leveraging generative AI to help complete tasks like generation of user stories, test scripts, training and change management content and code creation.</li>
    <li><strong>Next-Generation Ecosystem Expansion</strong>: IBM and SAP plan to partner around their respective employee network groups and “next-gen” communities, such as the business women’s networks at IBM and SAP, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/next-gen-innovation-platform/university-alliances.html">SAP University Alliances</a> program and the <a href="https://jobs.sap.com/content/Military-Veterans/?locale=en_US">Veterans to Work</a> program of SAP and Veterans at IBM to increase the SAP solutions experience in the consulting workforce and develop the next generation of talent. The companies also plan to explore new ways to collaborate on social impact programs, such as training at- risk youth in the IT sector and accelerating the integration of social businesses into global supply chains.</li>
    <li><strong>watsonx Planned Availability on the Generative AI Hub</strong>: IBM Granite Model Series are expected to be accessible for use across SAP’s portfolio of cloud solutions and applications – which is underpinned by the generative AI hub in SAP AI Core. The generative AI hub facilitates relevant, reliable and responsible business AI and provides instant access to a broad range of large language models (LLMs). This expands on IBM and SAP’s collaboration around <a href="https://newsroom.ibm.com/2023-05-02-SAP-to-Embed-IBM-Watson-Artificial-Intelligence-into-SAP-R-Solutions">embedding IBM Watson AI technology into SAP solutions</a>. To further highlight watsonx.ai Granite capabilities, IBM Consulting plans to build extensions using the model on the generative AI hub for select customers.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>This initiative will build on the companies’ over 50-year collaboration based on deep technology, industry and domain expertise and demonstrates the two organizations’ joint commitment to continue to evolve to put clients first and meet market demand.</p>
  <p>IBM Consulting accelerates business transformation for our clients through hybrid cloud and AI technologies, leveraging our open ecosystem of partners. With deep industry and business expertise spanning strategy, experience design, technology, and operations, we have become the trusted partner to the world’s most innovative and valuable companies, helping modernize and secure their most complex systems. Our 160,000 consultants embrace an open way of working and apply our proven, collaborative engagement model, IBM Garage, to scale ideas into outcomes. As the only major global systems integrator inside a technology company, we don’t just advise – we invent and build what’s next together with our clients. Find out more at <a href="http://ibm.com/consulting">IBM.com/consulting</a>.</p>
  <p>To learn more about the Value Generation partnership initiative, visit <a href="https://www.ibm.com/info/sap-value-generation">ibm.com/info/sap-value-generation</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About IBM</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>IBM is a leading provider of global hybrid cloud and AI, and consulting expertise. We help clients in more than 175 countries capitalize on insights from their data, streamline business processes, reduce costs and gain the competitive edge in their industries. More than 4,000 government and corporate entities in critical infrastructure areas such as financial services, telecommunications and healthcare rely on IBM’s hybrid cloud platform and Red Hat OpenShift to effect their digital transformations quickly, efficiently and securely. IBM’s breakthrough innovations in AI, quantum computing, industry-specific cloud solutions and consulting deliver open and flexible options to our clients. All of this is backed by IBM’s commitment to trust, transparency, responsibility, inclusivity and service.</p>
  <p>Visit <a href="http://www.ibm.com/">www.ibm.com</a> for more information.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE:SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Scott Malinowski, SAP, +1 (781) 852-3822, <a href="mailto:scott.malinowski@sap.com">scott.malinowski@sap.com</a><br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a><br>Jamee Nelson, IBM, <a href="mailto:jamee.nelson@ibm.com">jamee.nelson@ibm.com</a></p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-power-of-sap-partners-who-drive-customer-success-delivering-trusted-advice-and-deep-product-knowledge">Learn more about the power of SAP partners, who drive customer success, delivering trusted advice and deep product knowledge</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/partners.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/ibm</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Defining the AI Opportunity for SAP and Our Partners]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-partners-ai-opportunity</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-partners-ai-opportunity</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and partners are seizing the AI opportunity, providing new solutions backed by expertise, business process knowledge, and SAP system data.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a591bef8055a8ff0903470a566a95b31994c8267.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a591bef8055a8ff0903470a566a95b31994c8267.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a591bef8055a8ff0903470a566a95b31994c8267.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Defining the AI Opportunity for SAP and Our Partners" src="./media_1a591bef8055a8ff0903470a566a95b31994c8267.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="defining-the-ai-opportunity-for-sap-and-our-partners">Defining the AI Opportunity for SAP and Our Partners</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Artificial intelligence is by far the disruptor of the decade. It can search, summarize, and analyze vast data stores, putting data-driven insights at employees’ fingertips in a matter of minutes. It can also generate content, anything from text to software code, streamlining workflows and saving precious time and money.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>And that’s just the surface. We are still learning just how far reaching the implications could be in the workplace.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-ai-revolutionary-technology-real-world-results">SAP Business AI: Revolutionary technology. Real-world results.</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As we explore this new realm and AI’s vast potential, SAP has adjusted its strategy with the goal of becoming not only the leading enterprise application provider but also the No. 1 business AI company. The foundation is now available with SAP Business AI that offers SAP customers a reliable, relevant, and responsible AI solution portfolio.</p>
  <p>A key element of that strategy is leveraging SAP partners’ expertise. The trusted relationships our partners have developed with our joint customers are essential to communicating the value of AI solutions from SAP and finding the best SAP products to meet their business objectives. It also poses a great opportunity for partners to expand their business.</p>
  <p>But first, let’s take a step back and explore why SAP is best positioned to deliver on the business AI opportunity.</p>
  <h2 id="saps-ai-advantage">SAP’s AI Advantage</h2>
  <p><strong>Deep Business Process Knowledge</strong><br>Before AI can make operations faster, data-driven, and more effective, organizations must optimize business processes. SAP brings a deep understanding of business processes to AI applications, enabling solutions that orchestrate workflows, data sharing, and automation for the greatest efficiency and productivity.</p>
  <p><strong>SAP Data</strong> AI solutions require data to train their algorithms to provide accurate, relevant, real-world outputs. SAP can draw on business data from thousands of customer systems across the value chain, helping to address our customers’ challenges and drive their digital transformation.</p>
  <p><strong>Focus on Application Creation</strong> SAP is partnering with technology providers to make the most of the AI opportunity by creating value with new applications. For example, large language models (LLMs) will become solution differentiators. LLMs perform a range of natural language processing tasks. Combining LLMs with AI solutions automates insight delivery, freeing users from the need to wait for help from their IT or data science departments. It allows companies to focus on data insights, rather than devoting focus to the technology that produces them.</p>
  <p><strong>Strong Partner Ecosystem</strong><br>SAP recognizes that it cannot reach the full addressable market alone. That is why our more than 25,500 partner ecosystem is a huge advantage when offering business AI solutions. Working together, we can drive innovation, accelerate AI road maps, and expand AI capabilities beyond its own limitations.</p>
  <p>I cannot underscore enough how important that fourth component is to our AI strategy. It is a linchpin to our success. That’s why we must ensure we are creating win-win scenarios for our partners that benefit us both for the long term.</p>
  <h2 id="partner-opportunities">Partner Opportunities</h2>
  <p>While AI offers a range of benefits to SAP customers, it also represents a significant business opportunity for SAP partners. As a part of the SAP ecosystem, partners can provide advanced functionality out of the box with embedded AI capabilities within SAP applications. They must also take advantage of the virtually endless opportunities that AI offers regardless of the chosen SAP partner business model:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Sell:</strong> Partners that resell SAP solutions can leverage the embedded AI portfolio from SAP to accelerate RISE with SAP and GROW with SAP deals. Sell partners can also enhance the appeal of the cloud with AI capabilities exclusive to SAP cloud solutions and enlarge deals with AI units from SAP required for premium AI capabilities.</li>
    <li><strong>Service:</strong> Service partners can drive adoption of SAP’s AI portfolio and custom AI capabilities built on SAP by bundling them with services and support. This approach enables customers to gain value through customized generative AI use cases built on the foundation of SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP), including the generative AI hub, and accelerate their cloud migrations and business transformation, backed by partners’ expertise.</li>
    <li><strong>Innovate:</strong> Partners also have the opportunity to develop innovative AI solutions and extensions to enhance the SAP portfolio. Partners can build customer-specific and repeatable use cases with AI services from SAP on SAP BTP and augment customer business processes.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="take-the-next-step">Take the Next Step</h2>
  <p>Ready to expand your partnership with SAP to build on the AI opportunity? <a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/products/aic/about.html">Explore our AI portfolio</a> and visit <a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/partnership/manage/expand.html">SAP Partner Portal site to learn more</a>. If you’re not currently an SAP partner, there’s never been a better time to explore the benefits of becoming a part of the SAP ecosystem.</p>
  <p>If you’re ready to start your SAP partnership journey and provide businesses in your market with reliable, effective AI solutions, <a href="https://www.sap.com/partners/partner-program.html">get started here today</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Karl Fahrbach is chief partner officer at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="win-more-customers-and-grow-revenue-with-the-help-of-saps-award-winning-partner-program-and-portfolio-of-industry-leading-solutions">Win more customers and grow revenue with the help of SAP’s award-winning partner program and portfolio of industry-leading solutions</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/partners/partner-program.html">Explore how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Global Line of Business Partner Excellence Awards: 2024 Winners and Finalists]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-global-lob-partner-excellence-awards-2024-winners-finalists</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-global-lob-partner-excellence-awards-2024-winners-finalists</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Global LoB Partner Excellence Awards celebrate partners' contributions to our cloud ambitions. Here are the 2024 finalists and winners.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-global-lob-partner-excellence-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Smart Manufacturing Creates Opportunity for Partner-Driven, AI-Infused Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-partner-ai-innovation-smart-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-partner-ai-innovation-smart-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In the age of business AI, SAP partners are developing and delivering industry innovations across discrete manufacturing.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_149e02fca5b080a1038dfae06eb31000b8cc98754.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_149e02fca5b080a1038dfae06eb31000b8cc98754.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_149e02fca5b080a1038dfae06eb31000b8cc98754.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Smart Manufacturing Creates Opportunity for Partner-Driven, AI-Infused Innovation" src="./media_149e02fca5b080a1038dfae06eb31000b8cc98754.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="smart-manufacturing-creates-opportunity-for-partner-driven-ai-infused-innovation">Smart Manufacturing Creates Opportunity for Partner-Driven, AI-Infused Innovation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>One of the perks of my job is that I get to spend a considerable amount of time with our industry partners. Whether I’m talking with a startup software company or an established global service partner, two words — two letters actually — are the hot topic of almost every engagement lately: artificial intelligence, specifically <strong>business AI</strong>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-at-hannover-messe-bring-out-new-manufacturing-excellence">SAP at Hannover Messe: Bring out new manufacturing excellence</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://events.sap.com/hannovermesse/en/home">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As we navigate this brave new world of business AI, SAP partners are playing an essential role as equal parts technology disrupters, trusted advisors, and innovation multipliers. They work and live at the edge, breaking technology rules with every new solution and innovation they bring to the table. These companies are passionate about their AI-driven solutions, which will provide what SAP manufacturing customers want most for their businesses nowadays: more efficiency, accuracy, and agility in their production operations and supply chains. Their energy and passion are positioning them to redefine the rules of engagement regarding how partner ecosystems work.</p>
  <p>It doesn’t matter what kind of partner you are — you could be on the build, implement/service, or sell sides of the SAP partner ecosystem, the opportunities to innovate, and co-innovate with SAP and other partners, solutions that bring value to customers in discrete manufacturing industries are as limitless as our imaginations. It’s an exciting time to be an SAP industry partner.</p>
  <h2 id="innovative-solutions-from-sap-and-partners-give-our-manufacturing-customers-a-competitive-edge">Innovative Solutions from SAP and Partners Give Our Manufacturing Customers a Competitive Edge</h2>
  <p>Giving our manufacturing customers the business AI solutions they need to thrive in highly competitive and often volatile markets is an absolute must. Whether those solutions are developed by an SAP partner, SAP itself, or collaboratively is secondary.</p>
  <p>This new drive to co-innovate on our customers’ behalf is creating opportunities for partners to develop and deliver industry innovations in three areas of discrete manufacturing:</p>
  <ol>
    <li><strong>Solutions that enable efficient, accurate, and agile manufacturing and supply chains</strong> by integrating processes, removing data silos, and seamlessly connecting manufacturing and supply chain applications with the whole of the business.</li>
    <li><strong>Solutions that improve decision-making</strong> by using AI to analyze data from internal and external sources in context and produce insights that increase manufacturing operations’ resilience and help customers strike the right balance among cost, sustainability, and customer satisfaction.</li>
    <li><strong>Solutions that promote collaboration within a business ecosystem</strong>. Many of the company executives I’ve spoken with recently wanted to talk about Manufacturing-X, the growing cross-industry initiative in which companies across various manufacturing value chains come together within a global business ecosystem to define a standard that enables them to share production and supply chain data across platforms and technology to further increase resilience, sustainability, and competitiveness.</li>
  </ol>
  <p>We are bringing this customer-focused, partner-driven approach to life this week at Hannover Messe, bringing center stage the latest, most compelling innovations to emerge from SAP and our partner ecosystem, across both discrete and process manufacturing — many embedded with business AI.</p>
  <p>Some of the showcases that have been developed collaboratively in action include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Modular manufacturing that orchestrates production cells with a hard independent fleet manager</li>
    <li>High-speed bottling that captures traceability data and in-line quality assurance</li>
    <li>A centralized operations control center that manages an offsite process production line</li>
    <li>AI-enhanced visual inspection and guided instructions during component assembly</li>
    <li>A quick guided journey through an Industrial Metaverse, showing how assets inside a power plant can be intelligently and remotely managed</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP partners are playing an integral part in our presence at Hannover Messe, just as they are in our overarching industry vision. Partners including Accenture, Camelot ITLab, Cideon Software &#x26; Services, FORCAM, Kinexon, Systema, and TeamViewer are all exhibiting their solutions alongside their SAP counterparts, demonstrating the true power of partnership and innovation at every turn.</p>
  <p>By leveraging resources like the new SAP AI Launchpad and generative AI hub, our partners will introduce industry innovations that will add immediate value for customers in the discrete and process manufacturing space. Hence, they have the intelligent digital tools they need to be future-ready.</p>
  <p>Kinexon’s OS extension to the SAP Digital Manufacturing solution is one example. Kinexon OS orchestrates the shop floor and automates previously manual processes, improving production speed, quality, and asset utilization. It is providing customers with an essential pathway to modular production and autonomous manufacturing.</p>
  <p>For those of you at the event, stop by the SAP space and experience innovation and partnership in perfect harmony firsthand. An electric injection molding machine developed by Fanuc with support from partner Syntax will be cranking out made-to-order drinking vessels.</p>
  <p>Come enjoy a cup of inspiration on us. It’s a small but meaningful taste of what’s possible for partners in our collaborative, customer-focused, and business AI-driven cloud ecosystem.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Sven Denecken is senior vice president and chief marketing and solutions officer for Industries &#x26; CX at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-power-of-partnership-drive-customer-success-with-solutions-from-sap-delivering-trusted-advice-and-deep-product-knowledge">The power of partnership: drive customer success with solutions from SAP, delivering trusted advice and deep product knowledge</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/partners.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/hannover-messe</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Solutions from SAP and Icertis Empower Enterprises with Contract Intelligence Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-icertis-contract-intelligence-innovation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-icertis-contract-intelligence-innovation</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Icertis are working to improve contract intelligence for enterprises, reducing revenue leakage and increasing efficiency. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/icertis</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Partnerships Help Customers Successfully Navigate a Data-Driven World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/partnerships-help-customers-navigate-data-driven-world</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/partnerships-help-customers-navigate-data-driven-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP partners can deploy SAP Datasphere and SAP Analytics Cloud to provide data access, effective planning, and trusted AI across operations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16fa40a8c4f0c1be7eb9eaf1afe27075d1230ec25.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16fa40a8c4f0c1be7eb9eaf1afe27075d1230ec25.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16fa40a8c4f0c1be7eb9eaf1afe27075d1230ec25.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Partnerships Help Customers Successfully Navigate a Data-Driven World" src="./media_16fa40a8c4f0c1be7eb9eaf1afe27075d1230ec25.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="partnerships-help-customers-successfully-navigate-a-data-driven-world">Partnerships Help Customers Successfully Navigate a Data-Driven World</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In the modern business environment, the critical need to effectively harness data is undeniable. Companies that fail to become data-driven risk falling behind in a world where agility and informed decision-making are paramount. In the recent <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/data-unleashed.html">SAP Data Unleashed</a> event we explored strategies to help organizations access data from any source, transform planning and analysis with a business data fabric, and foster trusted artificial intelligence (AI) across their businesses. Central to this transformation are <a href="/topics/ecosystem">SAP partners</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For decades, our partners have leveraged their industry expertise and technological know-how to bring immense value to companies of all sizes. They possess a rare fusion of deep industry insights and technological expertise, which they leverage to guide businesses through the delicate process of modernization while ensuring that the essence of their identity remains intact.</p>
  <p>We recently <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/partners.html#trending">asked several of our strategic SAP partners</a> how they’re helping customers take better advantage of their organization’s data. Our partners have observed a significant shift in the way data is perceived and utilized. It’s no longer just a byproduct of business operations but a core asset that, when effectively distributed and made accessible, can revolutionize customer experiences and enable a more strategic, company-wide approach to decision-making.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11f5934a69f41fbb435d136fc80e11b26ab8eb2f5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11f5934a69f41fbb435d136fc80e11b26ab8eb2f5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11f5934a69f41fbb435d136fc80e11b26ab8eb2f5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Partners Bring Out Your Best as a Data-Driven Organization" src="./media_11f5934a69f41fbb435d136fc80e11b26ab8eb2f5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/Cj3BF9-9I30">SAP Partners Bring Out Your Best as a Data-Driven Organization</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>However, the mere availability of data is not a panacea. The crux of the matter is transforming data into actionable insights. This is where our partners excel, mapping out advanced use cases and facilitating the transition to cutting-edge platforms like SAP Datasphere and SAP Analytics Cloud. These solutions can empower organizations to evolve into entities where data is not just present but central to every action and decision.</p>
  <p>The practical implications of data are vast and deeply rooted in the operational successes of our clients. AI, for instance, is a frontier rich with potential, but its success is inextricably linked to the quality and accessibility of data. Recognizing this, SAP partners are investing in building AI capabilities that can not only propel new business functions but also deliver substantial value.</p>
  <p>Another key area of focus for our partners is the concept of a business data fabric, which is critical in developing a flexible enterprise architecture. Such an architecture allows for co-innovation and customization of solutions, ensuring that data is not just an afterthought but a driving force in business operations.</p>
  <p>The journey toward a data- and AI-centric business model is an ongoing one, marked by evolving needs, emerging challenges, and a relentless pursuit of innovation. The ultimate aim is to convert potential into lasting business success.</p>
  <p>The essence of our relationship with our partners is rooted in a shared vision. We are united in our pursuit of discovery, innovation, and improvement as we navigate the future together. Be sure to <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/partners.html#trending">watch the videos</a> with our seven strategic partners and discover how the <a href="https://www.sap.com/partners.html">SAP partner ecosystem</a> can help your company become a data-driven organization.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Karl Fahrbach is chief partner officer at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-partners-are-helping-their-clients-solve-critical-business-challenges">SAP partners are helping their clients solve critical business challenges</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/partners.html#trending">Discover how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Pinnacle Awards: 2024 Finalists and Winners Announced]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-pinnacle-awards-2024-finalists-and-winners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-pinnacle-awards-2024-finalists-and-winners</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Pinnacle Awards recognize top-performing and innovative partners. Learn more about the SAP Pinnacle Awards 2024 finalists and winners.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11764e94c92ed4681b4c79ee2e132a07bdde6ab9c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11764e94c92ed4681b4c79ee2e132a07bdde6ab9c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11764e94c92ed4681b4c79ee2e132a07bdde6ab9c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Pinnacle Awards: 2024 Finalists and Winners Announced" src="./media_11764e94c92ed4681b4c79ee2e132a07bdde6ab9c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-pinnacle-awards-2024-finalists-and-winners-announced">SAP Pinnacle Awards: 2024 Finalists and Winners Announced</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The SAP Pinnacle Awards, our most prestigious global partner recognition program, shine a spotlight on our top-performing partners that demonstrate excellence in unlocking innovative new ways for customers to run their businesses.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP’s ecosystem plays a key role in our vision to enable every organization and every industry to become a network of intelligent, sustainable enterprises. Through their unique industry expertise, implementation methodologies, complementary solutions, and commitment throughout the Customer Value Journey, partners help customers thrive and succeed with SAP.</p>
  <p>Across 26 categories in the areas of Customer Success, Intelligent Enterprise Realization, Sustainability, and Social Impact, partners are recognized for their outstanding contributions, exponential growth, and simplification. Through delivering cloud innovations that help customers achieve their goals, these partners exemplify dedication to teamwork and embody our vision for partnering excellence.</p>
  <p>Twenty-five of the 2024 winners and finalists were selected from <a href="/topics/ecosystem">SAP’s wide-ranging partner base</a>, using system-generated data on core metrics and key performance indicators. A steering committee of global SAP representatives reviewed, vetted, and ranked the achievements according to our internal criteria, which aligned with SAP’s communicated business strategies.</p>
  <p>The only exception is the Social Impact category, which recognized a partner’s lasting societal impact by leveraging SAP innovation with concrete results. Partner nominations were evaluated and ranked by a panel of jurors consisting of SAP internal and third-party representatives.</p>
  <p>Winners and finalists for all categories will receive a communication package to help them promote their success to their customers, prospects, and the media, including logos for online and physical marketing vehicles. To increase their global exposure, SAP will list the winners and finalists on its Web site for an entire year, in addition to running a comprehensive campaign that promotes these winners and finalists to joint prospects and customers.</p>
  <p>Congratulations to the <a href="https://www.sap.com/partners/pinnacle-awards.html">winners and finalists</a>! We look forward to celebrating your success at SAP Partner Connect and SAP Sapphire.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Karl Fahrbach is chief partner officer at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-pinnacle-awards-showcase-partners-that-have-excelled-in-helping-customers-become-best-run-businesses">SAP Pinnacle Awards showcase partners that have excelled in helping customers become best-run businesses</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/partners/pinnacle-awards.html">Check out this year’s winners and finalists</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-pinnacle-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and NVIDIA to Accelerate Generative AI Adoption Across Enterprise Applications Powering Global Industries]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-and-nvidia-to-accelerate-generative-ai-adoption</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-and-nvidia-to-accelerate-generative-ai-adoption</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Together, SAP and NVIDIA will bring custom generative AI to thousands of enterprises around the world. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b3fcf19084a91c9721f2b9169c59bd16f3f8e1b6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b3fcf19084a91c9721f2b9169c59bd16f3f8e1b6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b3fcf19084a91c9721f2b9169c59bd16f3f8e1b6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP and NVIDIA to Accelerate Generative AI Adoption Across Enterprise Applications Powering Global Industries" src="./media_1b3fcf19084a91c9721f2b9169c59bd16f3f8e1b6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-and-nvidia-to-accelerate-generative-ai-adoption-across-enterprise-applications-powering-global-industries">SAP and NVIDIA to Accelerate Generative AI Adoption Across Enterprise Applications Powering Global Industries</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Customers Can Harness Their Business Data in Cloud Solutions from SAP Using Customized LLMs Deployed with NVIDIA AI Foundry Services and New NVIDIA NIM Microservices</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <p><strong><em>WALLDORF and SANTA CLARA, Calif.</em></strong></p>
                <hr>
                <p><a href="http://www.nvidia.com">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) and <a href="http://www.nvidia.com">NVIDIA</a> (NASDAQ: NVDA) today announced a partnership expansion focused on accelerating enterprise customers’ ability to harness the transformative power of data and generative AI across SAP’s portfolio of cloud solutions and applications.</p>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>The companies are collaborating to build and deliver SAP Business AI, including scalable, business-specific generative AI capabilities inside the Joule copilot from SAP and across SAP’s portfolio of cloud solutions and applications – all of which are underpinned by the SAP generative AI hub. The generative AI hub facilitates relevant, reliable and responsible business AI and provides instant access to a broad range of large language models (LLMs).</p>
        <p>As part of SAP’s ongoing initiative to build generative AI directly into the applications that power the world’s businesses, the partnership aims to help customers adopt generative AI capabilities at scale across their organizations. SAP will use <a href="https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/ai-data-science/generative-ai/">NVIDIA’s generative AI foundry service</a> to fine-tune LLMs for domain-specific scenarios and deploy applications with new <a href="https://nvidianews.nvidia.com/news/generative-ai-microservices-for-developers">NVIDIA NIM</a>™ microservices. SAP and NVIDIA plan to make the new integrated capabilities available by the end of 2024.</p>
        <p>“Enterprise customers want to leverage state-of-the-art technology that delivers real business value,” said Christian Klein, CEO and Member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “Strategic technology partnerships, like the one between SAP and NVIDIA, are at the core of our strategy to invest in technology that maximizes the potential and opportunity of AI for business. NVIDIA’s expertise in delivering AI capabilities at scale will help SAP accelerate the pace of transformation and better serve our customers in the cloud.”</p>
        <p>“SAP is sitting on a gold mine of enterprise data that can be transformed into custom generative AI agents to help customers automate their businesses,” said Jensen Huang, founder and CEO of NVIDIA. “Together, NVIDIA and SAP will bring custom generative AI to the thousands of enterprises around the world that rely on SAP to power their operations.”</p>
        <h2 id="harnessing-business-data-and-generative-ai-to-advance-customer-insights">Harnessing Business Data and Generative AI to Advance Customer Insights</h2>
        <p>SAP and NVIDIA plan to collaborate to integrate generative AI into cloud solutions from SAP, which include the latest release of the SAP Datasphere solution, SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP) and RISE with SAP.</p>
        <p>SAP plans to build additional generative AI capabilities within SAP BTP using NVIDIA’s generative AI foundry service, featuring <a href="https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/data-center/dgx-cloud/">NVIDIA DGX™ Cloud</a> AI supercomputing, <a href="https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/data-center/products/ai-enterprise/">NVIDIA AI Enterprise</a> software and NVIDIA AI Foundation models. These new capabilities are designed to be the basis of SAP’s development and deployment of generative AI for customers and is expected to be accessible in the generative AI hub in SAP AI Core and SAP Datasphere.</p>
        <p>Additional generative AI initiatives include:</p>
        <ul>
          <li><strong>New capabilities for the Joule copilot</strong>: Joule can leverage <a href="https://blogs.nvidia.com/blog/2023/11/15/what-is-retrieval-augmented-generation/">retrieval-augmented generation</a> (RAG) capabilities built by NVIDIA and SAP, which can be deployed on leading hyperscalers or SAP’s own cloud environments. As a natural-language, generative AI copilot, Joule helps customers unlock the potential in their business by automating time-consuming tasks and quickly analyzing business-critical data to deliver more intelligent, personalized experiences.</li>
          <li><strong>Innovative use cases leveraging SAP S/4HANA Cloud, SAP SuccessFactors and SAP Signavio</strong>: SAP and NVIDIA are exploring more than 20 generative AI use cases where the companies can combine assets to simplify and enhance digital transformation. Among these are generative AI features that can automate enterprise resource planning with intelligent invoice matching in SAP S/4HANA Cloud; improve human resources use cases leveraging SAP SuccessFactors; and accelerate new generative AI insights from SAP Signavio to better process business recommendations and optimize SAP’s customer support processes.</li>
          <li><strong>Unifying AI data sources with SAP Datasphere</strong>: Built on SAP BTP, SAP Datasphere enables integration and a unified view of semantically rich SAP data with third-party data across the enterprise landscape to help customers adapt faster to market changes and make more efficient and better informed decisions. With SAP Datasphere, customers can confidently access a high-quality data fabric using AI and machine learning (ML) models. To accelerate SAP’s federated machine learning (FedML) capabilities for SAP Datasphere, NVIDIA and SAP are facilitating easier access to data for data scientists and enhancing ML workload performance with the support of NVIDIA accelerated computing platforms and NVIDIA AI Enterprise data science software such as <a href="https://developer.nvidia.com/rapids">NVIDIA RAPIDS</a>™.</li>
          <li><strong>Using LLMs for the ABAP programming language</strong>: To aid developers in creating domain-specific language code, SAP plans to use NVIDIA AI foundry services to assist in fine-tuning LLMs. This will build on SAP’s use of generative AI models to assist developers who use ABAP through the company’s ABAP Cloud model and SAP Cloud Application Programming model.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2 id="nvidia-ai-enterprise-powers-production-grade-generative-ai-across-cloud-solutions-from-sap">NVIDIA AI Enterprise Powers Production-Grade Generative AI Across Cloud Solutions from SAP</h2>
        <p>Once models are ready for deployment in cloud solutions from SAP, SAP plans to use NVIDIA AI Enterprise software, including NVIDIA NIM inference microservices and NVIDIA NeMo Retriever™ microservices. NVIDIA NIM can be used to accelerate and maximize inference performance across the accelerated infrastructure from SAP. Using NVIDIA NeMo Retriever microservices, SAP plans to add RAG capabilities that enable generative AI applications to more securely access data running on SAP software to improve accuracy and insights. Customers can plan to use RAG on both SAP and third-party data.</p>
        <p>To learn more about the SAP and NVIDIA partnership, <a href="https://www.nvidia.com/gtc/keynote/">watch the replay of Huang’s GTC keynote address</a>.</p>
        <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
        <h2 id="about-nvidia">About NVIDIA</h2>
        <p>Since its founding in 1993, <a href="https://www.nvidia.com/">NVIDIA</a> (NASDAQ: NVDA) has been a pioneer in accelerated computing. The company’s invention of the GPU in 1999 sparked the growth of the PC gaming market, redefined computer graphics, ignited the era of modern AI and is fueling industrial digitalization across markets. NVIDIA is now a full-stack computing infrastructure company with data-center-scale offerings that are reshaping industry. More information at <a href="https://nvidianews.nvidia.com/">https://nvidianews.nvidia.com/</a>.</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td><strong>About SAP</strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent, sustainable enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 26 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="revolutionize-how-you-interact-with-sap-business-system-while-simplifying-your-day-to-day-with-faster-work-smarter-insights-and-better-outcomes">Revolutionize how you interact with SAP business system while simplifying your day-to-day with faster work, smarter insights and better outcomes</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">Meet Joule</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high-resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong> Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For further information, contact:</strong><br>SAP: Scott Malinowski, +1 (617) 538-6297, <a href="mailto:scott.malinowski@sap.com">scott.malinowski@sap.com</a><br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a><br>NVIDIA: Shannon McPhee, +1 (310) 920-9642, <a href="mailto:smcphee@nvidia.com">smcphee@nvidia.com</a></p>
  <p>Certain statements in this press release including, but not limited to, statements as to: the benefits, impact, performance, features, and availability of NVIDIA’s products and technologies, including NVIDIA’s generative AI foundry service, NVIDIA NIM microservices, NVIDIA DGX Cloud AI supercomputing, NVIDIA AI Enterprise software, and NVIDIA AI Foundation models, NVIDIA accelerated computing platforms, NVIDIA AI Enterprise data science software such as NVIDIA RAPIDS, RAPIDS cuDF and cuML, NVIDIA NeMo Retriever microservices; NVIDIA’s partnership with SAP, the benefits and impact of such partnership, and the features and availability of its services and offerings; SAP sitting on a gold mine of enterprise data that can be transformed into custom generative AI agents to help customers automate their businesses; and NVIDIA and SAP bringing custom generative AI to the thousands of enterprises around the world that rely on SAP to power their operations are forward-looking statements that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause results to be materially different than expectations. Important factors that could cause actual results to differ materially include: global economic conditions; our reliance on third parties to manufacture, assemble, package and test our products; the impact of technological development and competition; development of new products and technologies or enhancements to our existing product and technologies; market acceptance of our products or our partners’ products; design, manufacturing or software defects; changes in consumer preferences or demands; changes in industry standards and interfaces; unexpected loss of performance of our products or technologies when integrated into systems; as well as other factors detailed from time to time in the most recent reports NVIDIA files with the Securities and Exchange Commission, or SEC, including, but not limited to, its annual report on Form 10-K and quarterly reports on Form 10-Q. Copies of reports filed with the SEC are posted on the company’s website and are available from NVIDIA without charge. These forward-looking statements are not guarantees of future performance and speak only as of the date hereof, and, except as required by law, NVIDIA disclaims any obligation to update these forward-looking statements to reflect future events or circumstances.</p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.</p>
  <p>© 2024 SAP SE and NVIDIA Corporation. All rights reserved.</p>
  <p>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p>NVIDIA, the NVIDIA logo, DGX, NVIDIA NeMo Retriever, NVIDIA NIM, and RAPIDS are trademarks and/or registered trademarks of NVIDIA Corporation in the U.S. and/or other countries. Other company and product names may be trademarks of the respective companies with which they are associated. Features, pricing, availability, and specifications are subject to change without notice.</p>
  <p>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Quantum-Inspired Solution for Enterprise Optimization]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/quantum-inspired-computing-enterprise-optimization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/quantum-inspired-computing-enterprise-optimization</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Fujitsu collaborated to test out Fujitsu’s new quantum-inspired computing solution for optimization. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/quantum-computing</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Wait Is Over: Here Are the 2024 SAP Innovation Award Finalists]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/2024-sap-innovation-award-finalists</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/2024-sap-innovation-award-finalists</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The 2024 SAP Innovation Award finalists have utilized cloud solutions from SAP and AI to achieve remarkable results. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP AppHaus Network to Onboard New Partners in North America]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-apphaus-network-new-partners-in-north-america</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-apphaus-network-new-partners-in-north-america</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP AppHaus Network announced its plans to establish additional partner-driven locations in North America. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/human-centered-innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital Eco-Farming: How SAP Japan Helps Revitalize Rural Communities]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/minano-digital-eco-farm-sap-japan-revitalize-rural-communities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/minano-digital-eco-farm-sap-japan-revitalize-rural-communities</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Minano Digital Eco Farm, launched by PSI and SAP Co-Innovation Lab in Japan, is helping the town of Minano revitalize its community.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/agribusiness</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitization</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/internet-of-things</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-co-innovation-lab</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Goes the Distance with EV Fleet Digitalization]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-goes-the-distance-ev-fleet-digitalization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-goes-the-distance-ev-fleet-digitalization</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Longtime partners SAP and Mercedes-Benz are transforming the sustainable EV experience with digitalized corporate fleet management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1300ce8d341537d322ce2ddfe25ec1e05ce2fbf64.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1300ce8d341537d322ce2ddfe25ec1e05ce2fbf64.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1300ce8d341537d322ce2ddfe25ec1e05ce2fbf64.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Goes the Distance with EV Fleet Digitalization" src="./media_1300ce8d341537d322ce2ddfe25ec1e05ce2fbf64.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-goes-the-distance-with-ev-fleet-digitalization">SAP Goes the Distance with EV Fleet Digitalization</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Electric vehicles (<a href="/topics/electric-vehicles">EVs</a>) are transforming the mobility experience in corporate fleet management. A great example is the partnership between <a href="https://www.mercedes-benz.com/en/">Mercedes-Benz</a> and SAP where the companies are both customers and vendors to each other. Mercedes-Benz is using SAP solutions to digitalize its omnichannel buying experience, and SAP is the first customer using its own technology to manage the company’s vehicle fleet in Germany.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As longtime partners, SAP and Mercedes-Benz have a history of shared knowledge for mutual competitive advantage. The fleet management program is grounded in the companies’ similar business philosophies and product road maps.</p>
  <p>Mercedes-Benz has committed to move the company’s B2B business to 100% digital and plans to sell 25% of all new cars online by 2025. The company selected <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/commerce-cloud.html">SAP Commerce Cloud</a> to help support this mission. It will create a future-proof composable commerce portfolio designed to reliably power the company’s digital strategy, including a standardized offering across different markets. It will also simplify processes and reduce time-to-market.</p>
  <h2 id="benefits-of-digitalized-fleet-management">Benefits of Digitalized Fleet Management</h2>
  <p>From the SAP employee’s perspective, ordering a company EV couldn’t be simpler. Instead of time-consuming manual research and back and forth communication with the car dealer, employees can use <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/solutions.html">the guided buying capability in SAP Ariba solutions</a> to order the EV they want directly from the Mercedes-Benz online catalog. They can choose the features they want, such as car make and model, color, and equipment packages, within SAP’s pre-set guidelines.</p>
  <p>“The car configurator automates the EV selection process end-to-end, eliminating manual steps and saving time while providing the employee with a highly personalized experience,” said Steffen Krautwasser, head of SAP’s global car fleet. “Automating the approval process assures data consistency and eliminates the need for manual quality checks.”</p>
  <p>There’s a tremendous convenience factor in captured EV data as well. In one pilot program for select EVs in SAP’s fleet, the digital twin will automatically track mileage. Drivers will no longer need to manually enter mileage every time they recharge, and SAP can use this data to better manage the fleet.</p>
  <h2 id="connected-data-drives-sustainable-business">Connected Data Drives Sustainable Business</h2>
  <p>Once ordered, EVs are tracked as assets in SAP’s financial system. After delivery, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/digital-vehicle-suite.html">SAP Digital Vehicle Suite</a> creates a digital twin that can capture relevant, secure data across the EV’s lifetime. SAP’s fleet management team can track CO2 emissions based on green energy usage, mileage, and the number of vehicles on the road. Krautwasser envisioned reporting this data to support the company’s global sustainability commitments.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-digital-vehicle-suite-delivers-a-holistic-approach-to-vehicle-sales-and-data-management">SAP Digital Vehicle Suite delivers a holistic approach to vehicle, sales, and data management</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/digital-vehicle-suite.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Performance data from the EV digital twin can help corporate fleet managers guide employees in choosing the best vehicle for their driving needs,” said Krautwasser. “Over time, drivers can better understand travel ranges between charges.”</p>
  <p>Data is expected to help address so-called range anxiety, alerting EV drivers when their vehicle needs a charge and, most important, where to recharge. Mercedes-Benz is investing in charging infrastructure to create an ecosystem that would be integrated with public and private charge point providers in the U.S., China, and Europe.</p>
  <p>The partnership also reflects a shared commitment to sustainability. Mercedes-Benz has committed to become carbon neutral by 2038, and transition to 100% electric vehicles by 2030 wherever possible. SAP is transitioning the company’s vehicle fleet for employees in Germany to all EVs by 2025 as part of its corporate commitment to be carbon neutral by 2030.</p>
  <h2 id="omnichannel-is-fastest-path-to-customer-love">Omnichannel Is Fastest Path to Customer Love</h2>
  <p>The digital experience is extremely important for customers who expect convenience and quality. Organizations in many industries have shifted to an omnichannel strategy that offers people their preferred experience, whether online or in-person, building brand loyalty and repeat business.</p>
  <p>“We want to provide a seamless journey for employees as they research, select, purchase, and enjoy their vehicle,” said Krautwasser. “The most exciting part of our EV fleet management strategy is how we can use our knowledge to enhance the employee experience. Through data and digital services, we can get closer to our employees and act quickly based on their feedback, making improvements and introducing new offerings that keep us on top of trends and support SAP’s sustainability commitment.”</p>
  <p>EVs represent a profound business model shift for the entire automotive supply chain as automakers sell direct to customers, provide digital services from vehicle data, and explore new revenue opportunities. It’s clear that Mercedes-Benz and SAP are going the distance for a sustainable and satisfying driving experience.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Susan Galer is a communications director at SAP. Follow her @smgaler.<br>Top photo courtesy of SAP employee Jude Calvin Parong.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-twin</category>
            <category>news-tag/e-mobility</category>
            <category>news-tag/electric-vehicles</category>
            <category>news-tag/mercedes</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Announces Winners of Regional Partner Excellence Awards]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-regional-partner-excellence-awards-2024-winners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-regional-partner-excellence-awards-2024-winners</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Regional Awards for Partner Excellence recognize partner success in sales, innovation, tech, services, and solution areas in each region.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-global-lob-partner-excellence-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CEV Technologies and SAP Fuel E-Mobility Revolution in Croatia’s Retail Sector]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/cev-technologies-e-mobility-croatia-retail-sector</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/cev-technologies-e-mobility-croatia-retail-sector</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To realize the potential of convenient charging within the customer experience, CEV Technologies implemented SAP E-Mobility in Croatia.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/electric-vehicles</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-e-mobility</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Collaborates with UC Berkeley to Advance AI Research]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-uc-berkeley-to-advance-ai-research</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-uc-berkeley-to-advance-ai-research</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP will collaborate with the Sky Computing Lab at UC Berkeley to support cutting-edge research on AI and cloud technology.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1342ba2098b330e0ff6c9b8ee63f66f6254cc1550.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1342ba2098b330e0ff6c9b8ee63f66f6254cc1550.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1342ba2098b330e0ff6c9b8ee63f66f6254cc1550.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Collaborates with UC Berkeley to Advance AI Research" src="./media_1342ba2098b330e0ff6c9b8ee63f66f6254cc1550.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-collaborates-with-uc-berkeley-to-advance-ai-research">SAP Collaborates with UC Berkeley to Advance AI Research</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>BERKELEY, Calif.</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced it will collaborate with the Sky Computing Lab at the University of California (UC), Berkeley to support the university’s cutting-edge research on interconnected cloud technology in the context of artificial intelligence (AI).</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>UC Berkeley’s insights will help accelerate SAP’s AI strategy aiming to build hundreds of applications.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-how-you-can-benefit-from-ai-built-into-your-core-business-processes">Learn how you can benefit from AI built into your core business processes</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">Explore now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“There’s no technology advancing faster than AI,” SAP Chief AI Officer Philipp Herzig said. “While the progress on foundation models is impressive, there is a lot to learn and shape on the AI stack on top, in particular for designing and scaling distributed cloud applications in multi-cloud environments or to build AI agents in combination with large language models. The Sky Computing Lab at UC Berkeley conducts very relevant research in this field, and the frameworks that are being built look very promising.”</p>
  <p>Generative AI is a transformative force that is changing how people work, communicate and learn. As AI applications become increasingly sophisticated, efficient handling of large workloads becomes critical.</p>
  <p>UC Berkeley’s research activities focus on enabling users to run large language model applications and general AI workloads seamlessly on any cloud, substantially reducing cloud costs, tapping into best-in-class hardware on different clouds and enjoying higher resource availability, according to Ion Stoica, director of the Sky Computing Lab at UC Berkeley.</p>
  <p>The interconnection of clouds aims to create a distributed network, giving users access to a vast pool of computing power. This agility is crucial for dynamically allocating and scaling computational capabilities based on specific AI task requirements, ensuring optimal efficiency and cost-effectiveness for users. As the computational demands of AI continue to evolve, this approach ensures not only the scalability and efficiency of AI tasks but also lays the groundwork for an innovative and interoperable future in artificial intelligence.</p>
  <p>Through this collaboration with the Sky Computing Lab at UC Berkeley, SAP aims to advance knowledge in artificial intelligence. Besides AI-specific expertise, SAP will support graduate students through scholarships and internships.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong><br>Samantha Finnegan, +1 (415) 377-0475, <a href="mailto:samantha.finnegan@sap.com">samantha.finnegan@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2022 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modernize SAP Business Warehouse with SAP Datasphere and Its Open Data Ecosystem]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/modernize-sap-bw-with-sap-datasphere-open-data-ecosystem</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/modernize-sap-bw-with-sap-datasphere-open-data-ecosystem</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is now offering a limited-time, complimentary SAP BW system assessment to help you optimize your transition to SAP Datasphere.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16bae8ef497f5c9c6bdf1b5fdaf69f1f911aad108.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16bae8ef497f5c9c6bdf1b5fdaf69f1f911aad108.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16bae8ef497f5c9c6bdf1b5fdaf69f1f911aad108.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Modernize SAP Business Warehouse with SAP Datasphere and Its Open Data Ecosystem" src="./media_16bae8ef497f5c9c6bdf1b5fdaf69f1f911aad108.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="modernize-sap-business-warehouse-with-sap-datasphere-and-its-open-data-ecosystem">Modernize SAP Business Warehouse with SAP Datasphere and Its Open Data Ecosystem</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Many SAP Business Warehouse (SAP BW) customers are seeking to leverage cloud-based solutions but want to ensure that their previous investments are safeguarded. While the benefits of modernizing to the cloud are clear, customers need a flexible path that builds upon their existing technology and talent.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP Datasphere can offer that path. Its native connectivity to SAP BW means customers can reuse up to 80% of existing SAP BW content, retaining value while adding cloud speed, scale, and interoperability and avoiding costly and unnecessary rework.</p>
  <p>Delivering meaningful data to every data professional requires a comprehensive cloud data service. With SAP Datasphere, organizations can:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Access authoritative data, accelerating time-to-value by automatically reusing the semantical definitions and associations from SAP applications.</li>
    <li>Enrich all data projects, harmonizing heterogeneous data into a business semantic model of their diverse data landscapes.</li>
    <li>Simplify the data landscape, accessing all their data across hybrid and cloud environments no matter where it resides.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP has also partnered with an open data ecosystem of leading technology vendors to provide tailored integration between SAP Datasphere and their solutions. The first set of industry-leading data and AI vendors includes Collibra, Confluent, Databricks, DataRobot, and Google Cloud. By closely integrating their data and AI platforms with SAP Datasphere, organizations can access their mission-critical business data across any cloud infrastructure.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="transition-to-a-modern-business-data-fabric-at-your-pace-with-sap-datasphere">Transition to a modern business data fabric at your pace with SAP Datasphere</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/migration.html#migration">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="flexible-paths-to-the-cloud">Flexible Paths to the Cloud</h2>
  <p>Many SAP BW users have always-on projects that depend on SAP BW data and objects, which requires flexibility in modernizing to the cloud.</p>
  <p>SAP offers flexible paths. Whether you’re moving directly or integrating SAP Datasphere as part of your data landscape to enhance your SAP BW deployment, there’s a strategy:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Gradually transition functionality over time using <a href="https://community.sap.com/topics/datasphere/bw-bridge">SAP Datasphere, SAP BW bridge</a> to reuse and integrate SAP BW objects.</li>
    <li>Leverage SAP BW data ingestion and staging to accelerate the move or, for SAP Business Suite customers without SAP BW, move directly to SAP Datasphere.</li>
    <li>In some cases, migrate SAP BW systems to SAP Datasphere for a complete transition.</li>
    <li>Modernize with a combination of SAP Datasphere and SAP HANA Cloud to benefit from the capabilities of both solutions. SAP Datasphere can provide the foundation for a business data fabric, while SAP HANA Cloud enables the development of intelligent data applications.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The goal is to provide options to fit each customer’s unique environment and timeline. With the right approach, the move to SAP Datasphere can be straightforward while optimizing previous investments.</p>
  <p>Our experienced SAP partners understand the importance of flexible paths. They work with our customers to outline customized modernization paths that can safeguard their technology and fit their goals.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>We are excited to help SAP BW customers experience the power of SAP Datasphere. We’ve already seen multiple customers take this modernization approach and it’s the ideal modernization path to protect the customer’s existing SAP BW investments.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Deepu Sasidharan, Vice President, Analytics, Applexus</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>No matter which path a customer takes, they can always progress to SAP Datasphere. Technically, this can be achieved with the support of SAP Datasphere, SAP BW bridge and modernization tools. That’s why customers like <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2022/7/cd349586-5fc8-4a25-8486-4204460ca03d.html">Nipro</a> chose SAP Datasphere.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>SAP Datasphere, SAP BW bridge is a complete game changer. The cloud architecture allows us to simplify our landscape. We are also seeing significant improvements in our performance.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Iaroslav Korzh, SAP Technology Manager, Nipro Europe Group Companies</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="new-professional-readiness-assessment">New Professional Readiness Assessment</h2>
  <p>Whether you’re starting fresh or modernizing an existing system, having a solid plan is key for a successful move to the cloud.</p>
  <p>SAP is now offering a limited-time, complimentary SAP BW system assessment to help you optimize your transition to SAP Datasphere. Through this assessment, you can gain insight into your SAP BW environment and learn which objects are active and frequently used and whether they can be migrated.</p>
  <p>This assessment helps deliver a reliable basis for an actionable modernization plan. With the right information, you can modernize on your terms. Get started today by applying for your complimentary <a href="https://www.sap.com/registration/free-assessment-offer-for-bw-customers.html">assessment</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="get-started">Get Started</h2>
  <p>Visit our <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/migration.html#migration">Web site</a> for the latest modernization tools, including our <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/10/96cfbee0-8f7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">getting started guide</a>, <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/technology-blogs-by-sap/watch-the-sap-bw-modernization-webinar-series/ba-p/13699559">technical deep dive webinar series</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/registration/free-assessment-offer-for-bw-customers.html">professional readiness assessment</a>.</p>
  <p>SAP BW customers moving to SAP Datasphere may also qualify for exclusive incentives. Contact your SAP representative before this limited-time opportunity expires.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Daniel Yu is senior vice president of Solution Management and Product Marketing for SAP Data and Analytics.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/data-fabric</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-warehouse</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Invests in Partner Learning to Boost Availability of SAP Experts]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-invests-in-partner-learning</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-invests-in-partner-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Learning is reimagining partner enablement with SAP Learning Journeys, subject matter experts, and opportunities to earn credentials.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>