<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/opentext/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intelligent Document Processing: Unlocking Hidden Insights with AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/intelligent-document-processing-unlocking-hidden-insights-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/intelligent-document-processing-unlocking-hidden-insights-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Intelligent document processing is becoming a vital ally for process optimization, innovation, and delivering exceptional user experiences.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/opentext</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why the Reinvention of the Oil and Gas Industry Begins with Intelligent Enterprise Content Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/reinvention-of-oil-and-gas-enterprise-content-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/reinvention-of-oil-and-gas-enterprise-content-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[More than 65% of oil and gas companies are increasing their investment in enterprise software solutions and cloud migrations. Find out why.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>news-tag/greenhouse-gas-emissions</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>news-tag/opentext</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Wholesale Distributors Can Stand Out in a Direct-to-Consumer World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/wholesale-distributors-stand-out-direct-to-consumer-world</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/wholesale-distributors-stand-out-direct-to-consumer-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the help of SAP ECM solutions by OpenText, wholesale distributors can close the gap in their e-commerce strategies. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/opentext</category>
            <category>industry/wholesale-distribution</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why Retail Has to Adapt with Digitalization]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/why-retail-has-to-adapt-digitalization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/why-retail-has-to-adapt-digitalization</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Retailers must leverage customer and operational content with enterprise content management technology that is complete and personalized.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/opentext</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Information Sharing Can Ease the Consumer Goods Supply Strain]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/information-sharing-ease-consumer-goods-supply-strain</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/information-sharing-ease-consumer-goods-supply-strain</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Standardized information sharing is a critical first step toward strengthening much-needed resiliency, efficiency, and control. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16acfad5b667087aba74dcf54df81132861712462.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16acfad5b667087aba74dcf54df81132861712462.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16acfad5b667087aba74dcf54df81132861712462.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Information Sharing Can Ease the Consumer Goods Supply Strain" src="./media_16acfad5b667087aba74dcf54df81132861712462.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="information-sharing-can-ease-the-consumer-goods-supply-strain">Information Sharing Can Ease the Consumer Goods Supply Strain</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Consumer products companies are dealing with an entirely new set of challenges that are driving up costs and increasing supply chain fragility – making them more susceptible to losing consumers. Could it be that quick-fix digitalization efforts during the <a href="/topics/covid-19">pandemic</a> are exacerbating these challenges?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Every business involved in the consumer products value chain – including raw material suppliers, ingredient producers, manufacturers, logistics providers, retailers, and wholesale distributors – has made great strides in digitalizing its internal operations. Yet, a lack of data exchange across the entire network could intensify delays and inefficiencies as resources or products move from one part of the supply chain to the other.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="how-can-enterprise-content-management-drive-differentiation-in-consumer-products-operations">How can enterprise content management drive differentiation in consumer products operations?</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/09/a01dc772-f87d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="moving-supplies-with-better-transparency-and-insight">Moving Supplies with Better Transparency and Insight</h2>
  <p>According to <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/09/a01dc772-f87d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">IDC</a>, consumer products companies are beginning to get the message: 39% of surveyed industry players expect to increase spending on integrated enterprise content management (ECM) applications in 2021. Moreover, nearly half of them expect this digital investment to be a key contributor to operational performance (43%) and employee productivity (44%) – two factors that can significantly ease today’s consumer goods supply strain.</p>
  <p>During the pandemic, most consumer products companies adopted point solutions while maintaining a preexisting infrastructure of isolated legacy systems and spreadsheets for critical functions. However, this setup – which, at the time, was a response to changing consumer behaviors and employee needs – is missing the connectedness, intelligence, and transparency necessary to align operational capacity with surging demand.</p>
  <p>Many businesses now realize that standardized information sharing is a critical first step toward strengthening much-needed resiliency, efficiency, and control. It allows internal and external supply chain participants to exchange consumer expectations insight, communicate actionable next steps, and scale operations as one ecosystem.</p>
  <p>With cloud-based SAP enterprise content management solutions by OpenText, the entire supply chain can connect all this information so stakeholders can access curated content anytime, anywhere, and across the business. Plus, the inclusion of embedded artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning enables the technology to automatically capture, organize, and analyze massive amounts of data to support higher productivity.</p>
  <p>Along with supply chain operations, SAP ECM solutions by OpenText can improve adjacent departments – such as accounts payable, accounts receivable, inventory, and trade promotion management – that directly impact overall customer satisfaction. These back-office functions can use real-time supply chain information, coupled with insights into emerging customer demand and financial constraints, to reduce the pressure of supply challenges. For example, they can shape product allocation to minimize waste and optimize existing production capacity by adjusting consumer segmentation, evolving product portfolios, and innovating business models – all while offering a consistent brand experience.</p>
  <h2 id="satisfying-consumers-better-despite-shortages">Satisfying Consumers Better Despite Shortages</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="discover-sap-ecm-solutions-by-opentext-to-help-transform-your-business-into-an-intelligent-enterprise">Discover SAP ECM solutions by OpenText to help transform your business into an intelligent enterprise</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/oth/enterprise-content-management/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While conditions on the supply side may not ease until ports add capacity and companies can keep up with growing demand, it’s never too soon to unify the business network with smooth information sharing and workflows. Otherwise, brands risk ignoring revenue growth opportunities while wrestling with supply chain disruptions.</p>
  <p>SAP ECM solutions by OpenText can help relieve consumer products companies from making that trade-off. Now, their employees and stakeholders can make highly informed, data-driven decisions that help satisfy consumer demand – even as the stakes increase during peak buying seasons.</p>
  <p>Find out how personalized communications and a complete understanding of your sellers and consumers can lead to unique and differentiating brand value. Read the info sheet, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/11/c2adb0fe-027e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Drive Differentiation with Intelligent Enterprise Content Management</a>.”</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/opentext</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enterprise Content Management: A Pivotal Step to End-to-End Digitalization]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/enterprise-content-management-ecm-digitalization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/enterprise-content-management-ecm-digitalization</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[According to an IDC whitepaper, SAP ECM solutions by OpenText can help businesses go paperless, resulting in greater efficiency. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_184c064ceef0464e02871782164bc5c9529c8989b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_184c064ceef0464e02871782164bc5c9529c8989b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_184c064ceef0464e02871782164bc5c9529c8989b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Enterprise Content Management: A Pivotal Step to End-to-End Digitalization" src="./media_184c064ceef0464e02871782164bc5c9529c8989b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="enterprise-content-management-a-pivotal-step-to-end-to-end-digitalization">Enterprise Content Management: A Pivotal Step to End-to-End Digitalization</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Work patterns may have changed over the years, but surprisingly most workplaces have yet to make any meaningful progress toward becoming paperless. Is this resistance to content digitalization and integration holding businesses back from becoming resilient and sustainable enough to stay competitive?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While the concept of the paperless workplace is nothing new, the opportunity to achieve this vision is quickly approaching as businesses advance their transformation strategies. Over the past year, companies have invested in software-as-a-service (SaaS) and cloud-enabled systems, new methodologies such as process automation, and network-wide collaboration to keep employees productive, update suppliers, and deliver on customer expectations.</p>
  <p>Now, some organizations are looking to go even further in their business transformation journey by digitalizing and integrating content with a comprehensive enterprise platform.</p>
  <p>According to an IDC whitepaper sponsored by SAP and OpenText, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2022/01/629d79f0-127e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">The Business Value of SAP Enterprise Content Management Solutions by OpenText in the Digital-First World</a>,” implementing solutions ‒ such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/enterprise-content-management.html">SAP enterprise content management (ECM) solutions by OpenText</a> ‒ can quickly yield a 288% three-year ROI. And at the center of this effective transformation is fast and efficient document migration, intake, processing, and auditing with fewer errors and higher productivity.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="discover-enterprise-content-management-solutions-to-help-your-business-become-an-intelligent-enterprise">Discover enterprise content management solutions to help your business become an intelligent enterprise</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/oth/enterprise-content-management/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="capturing-us7-million-in-revenue-growth">Capturing US$7 Million in Revenue Growth</h2>
  <p>The benefits of content digitalization, integration, and automation with <a href="/2020/05/study-ecm-and-mdg-solution-extensions-opentext-utopia">enterprise content management can be combined to increase revenue</a> by more than $7 million per year. By increasing efficiency, reducing errors, and accelerating processes, organizations surveyed by IDC reported an average gain of 4,794 productive hours each ‒ a 21% increase in gross user productivity.</p>
  <p>This improvement allowed respondents to avoid the hiring of 2.6 full-time employees to accomplish equivalent workloads, resulting in approximately $178,000 in enhanced user productivity value per organization. Additionally, enhanced interdepartmental document sharing and the automation of manual processes boosted profitability even further by driving $3.82 million in savings per one million documents.</p>
  <h2 id="migrating-documents-with-more-efficiency">Migrating Documents with More Efficiency</h2>
  <p>Migrating millions of documents that have been created, managed, and stored on paper to digital is a daunting task during any change initiative, especially when moving to a modern enterprise resource planning (ERP) system, such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a>. However, document-related migration is not just a one-time effort; it’s a project that can happen as regularly as organizations continue to evolve throughout their digital transformation.</p>
  <p>Interviewed organizations that use solutions for enterprise content management cited considerable migration efficiencies and cost reductions. For example, some respondents required 24% fewer full-time employees to complete migration projects, from 128.6 to 97.3 on average. The duration of the migration was also shortened from 12.2 months to only seven months, a 43% improvement. As a result of these efficiencies gain, the cost of document-related migration became 24% more affordable.</p>
  <p>As one manufacturing executive noted, “Doing data migration is easier if you minimize the number of applications. SAP ECM solutions by OpenText helped us put building blocks in place. Our knowledge has increased, and the learning curve is less steep. We know more about what is required country to country.”</p>
  <h2 id="decreasing-invoice-errors">Decreasing Invoice Errors</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-a-snapshot-of-the-idc-whitepaper">Get a snapshot of the IDC whitepaper</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/10/3ede3947-027e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>When the volume of paper invoices increases, manual processes become too time-consuming and risk-prone to maintain. For one of the survey participants, the lack of history tracking, trend analysis, and currency distinction led to €300,000 lost on paying invoices because the organization missed out on receiving discounts upwards of two percent. And in some cases, IDC reported that many respondents also paid interest and penalties on late payments that they could have avoided.</p>
  <p>After automating invoicing tasks with enterprise content management, organizations realized a 35% drop in delayed payments and paid 36% less on penalties and interest. The system immediately validates and approves incoming invoices, improving overall invoice performance and decreasing errors by 43% on average.</p>
  <p>A participating executive from an industrial chemicals company remarked on the tremendous value of digitalizing invoice management: “From the moment the organization moved toward less touching, it saw a 70% improvement over paper.”</p>
  <h2 id="boosting-organizational-efficiency">Boosting Organizational Efficiency</h2>
  <p>As digital transformation becomes synonymous with business growth, executives must consistently consider new capabilities and enhancements to improve their operations, employees’ lives, desired outcomes, and customer experiences. In fact, this mindset is bringing forth a new focus on business efficiency and resiliency.</p>
  <p>From invoice intake and processing, accounts payable, and auditing teams to areas outside of finance, solutions for enterprise content management can have an impressive impact on organizational efficiency, ranging from 24% to 41%. This outcome is largely due to allowing multiple users to obtain documents with greater ease. Organizations can work independently of an office location and still have secure access to content from a single centralized environment.</p>
  <p>In return, users who work from remote locations can work more effectively, which is a tremendous benefit for businesses with most of their workforce still working from home and in the field. Companies can support employees from more geographic regions and across all process streams and operational areas ‒ all without shuttling physical documents back and forth in e-mail.</p>
  <p>In addition, since their content is archived and stored in a centralized process and database, organizations can stay compliant with regulatory and business requirements with minimal or no effort. A surveyed healthcare executive noted this advantage’s value: “We can see content now, whereas the older way we had to search. We can now look at transactional records, so compliance is handled on the schedule.”</p>
  <h2 id="gaining-the-full-potential-of-content-management">Gaining the Full Potential of Content Management</h2>
  <p>The deeper companies transform into digital-first enterprises, the closer they get to operate at a level of efficiency, intelligence, and speed that rivals their competitors. And the first place to gain that edge is best found in digitalization through enterprise content management that removes the complexity of siloed information, spreadsheets, data extractions, and manipulations.</p>
  <p>Explore the calculated cost savings and business benefits of SAP enterprise content management solutions by OpenText, which support enterprise content management. Read the IDC whitepaper, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2022/01/629d79f0-127e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">The Business Value of SAP Enterprise Content Management Solutions by OpenText in the Digital-First World</a>,” commissioned by SAP and Open Text.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/opentext</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>