<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/manufacturing-2/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hannover Messe: What Can AI Do for Manufacturing?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/hannover-messe-ai-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/hannover-messe-ai-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At Hannover Messe 2024, SAP and its partners showed how they are embedding AI to help companies achieve excellence in manufacturing.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>news-tag/hannover-messe</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-x</category>
            <category>product/sap-digital-manufacturing</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Smart Manufacturing Creates Opportunity for Partner-Driven, AI-Infused Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-partner-ai-innovation-smart-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-partner-ai-innovation-smart-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In the age of business AI, SAP partners are developing and delivering industry innovations across discrete manufacturing.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_149e02fca5b080a1038dfae06eb31000b8cc98754.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_149e02fca5b080a1038dfae06eb31000b8cc98754.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_149e02fca5b080a1038dfae06eb31000b8cc98754.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Smart Manufacturing Creates Opportunity for Partner-Driven, AI-Infused Innovation" src="./media_149e02fca5b080a1038dfae06eb31000b8cc98754.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="smart-manufacturing-creates-opportunity-for-partner-driven-ai-infused-innovation">Smart Manufacturing Creates Opportunity for Partner-Driven, AI-Infused Innovation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>One of the perks of my job is that I get to spend a considerable amount of time with our industry partners. Whether I’m talking with a startup software company or an established global service partner, two words — two letters actually — are the hot topic of almost every engagement lately: artificial intelligence, specifically <strong>business AI</strong>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-at-hannover-messe-bring-out-new-manufacturing-excellence">SAP at Hannover Messe: Bring out new manufacturing excellence</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://events.sap.com/hannovermesse/en/home">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As we navigate this brave new world of business AI, SAP partners are playing an essential role as equal parts technology disrupters, trusted advisors, and innovation multipliers. They work and live at the edge, breaking technology rules with every new solution and innovation they bring to the table. These companies are passionate about their AI-driven solutions, which will provide what SAP manufacturing customers want most for their businesses nowadays: more efficiency, accuracy, and agility in their production operations and supply chains. Their energy and passion are positioning them to redefine the rules of engagement regarding how partner ecosystems work.</p>
  <p>It doesn’t matter what kind of partner you are — you could be on the build, implement/service, or sell sides of the SAP partner ecosystem, the opportunities to innovate, and co-innovate with SAP and other partners, solutions that bring value to customers in discrete manufacturing industries are as limitless as our imaginations. It’s an exciting time to be an SAP industry partner.</p>
  <h2 id="innovative-solutions-from-sap-and-partners-give-our-manufacturing-customers-a-competitive-edge">Innovative Solutions from SAP and Partners Give Our Manufacturing Customers a Competitive Edge</h2>
  <p>Giving our manufacturing customers the business AI solutions they need to thrive in highly competitive and often volatile markets is an absolute must. Whether those solutions are developed by an SAP partner, SAP itself, or collaboratively is secondary.</p>
  <p>This new drive to co-innovate on our customers’ behalf is creating opportunities for partners to develop and deliver industry innovations in three areas of discrete manufacturing:</p>
  <ol>
    <li><strong>Solutions that enable efficient, accurate, and agile manufacturing and supply chains</strong> by integrating processes, removing data silos, and seamlessly connecting manufacturing and supply chain applications with the whole of the business.</li>
    <li><strong>Solutions that improve decision-making</strong> by using AI to analyze data from internal and external sources in context and produce insights that increase manufacturing operations’ resilience and help customers strike the right balance among cost, sustainability, and customer satisfaction.</li>
    <li><strong>Solutions that promote collaboration within a business ecosystem</strong>. Many of the company executives I’ve spoken with recently wanted to talk about Manufacturing-X, the growing cross-industry initiative in which companies across various manufacturing value chains come together within a global business ecosystem to define a standard that enables them to share production and supply chain data across platforms and technology to further increase resilience, sustainability, and competitiveness.</li>
  </ol>
  <p>We are bringing this customer-focused, partner-driven approach to life this week at Hannover Messe, bringing center stage the latest, most compelling innovations to emerge from SAP and our partner ecosystem, across both discrete and process manufacturing — many embedded with business AI.</p>
  <p>Some of the showcases that have been developed collaboratively in action include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Modular manufacturing that orchestrates production cells with a hard independent fleet manager</li>
    <li>High-speed bottling that captures traceability data and in-line quality assurance</li>
    <li>A centralized operations control center that manages an offsite process production line</li>
    <li>AI-enhanced visual inspection and guided instructions during component assembly</li>
    <li>A quick guided journey through an Industrial Metaverse, showing how assets inside a power plant can be intelligently and remotely managed</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP partners are playing an integral part in our presence at Hannover Messe, just as they are in our overarching industry vision. Partners including Accenture, Camelot ITLab, Cideon Software &#x26; Services, FORCAM, Kinexon, Systema, and TeamViewer are all exhibiting their solutions alongside their SAP counterparts, demonstrating the true power of partnership and innovation at every turn.</p>
  <p>By leveraging resources like the new SAP AI Launchpad and generative AI hub, our partners will introduce industry innovations that will add immediate value for customers in the discrete and process manufacturing space. Hence, they have the intelligent digital tools they need to be future-ready.</p>
  <p>Kinexon’s OS extension to the SAP Digital Manufacturing solution is one example. Kinexon OS orchestrates the shop floor and automates previously manual processes, improving production speed, quality, and asset utilization. It is providing customers with an essential pathway to modular production and autonomous manufacturing.</p>
  <p>For those of you at the event, stop by the SAP space and experience innovation and partnership in perfect harmony firsthand. An electric injection molding machine developed by Fanuc with support from partner Syntax will be cranking out made-to-order drinking vessels.</p>
  <p>Come enjoy a cup of inspiration on us. It’s a small but meaningful taste of what’s possible for partners in our collaborative, customer-focused, and business AI-driven cloud ecosystem.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Sven Denecken is senior vice president and chief marketing and solutions officer for Industries &#x26; CX at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-power-of-partnership-drive-customer-success-with-solutions-from-sap-delivering-trusted-advice-and-deep-product-knowledge">The power of partnership: drive customer success with solutions from SAP, delivering trusted advice and deep product knowledge</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/partners.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/hannover-messe</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Unveils AI-Driven Supply-Chain Innovations to Transform Manufacturing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-hannover-messe-ai-supply-chain-innovations-transform-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-hannover-messe-ai-supply-chain-innovations-transform-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New AI supply chain advancements from SAP will unleash a transformative wave of productivity, efficiency and precision in manufacturing.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_139d76aac37abd129378ce3f34ce615947934235d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_139d76aac37abd129378ce3f34ce615947934235d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_139d76aac37abd129378ce3f34ce615947934235d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Unveils AI-Driven Supply-Chain Innovations to Transform Manufacturing" src="./media_139d76aac37abd129378ce3f34ce615947934235d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-unveils-ai-driven-supply-chain-innovations-to-transform-manufacturing">SAP Unveils AI-Driven Supply-Chain Innovations to Transform Manufacturing</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>HANNOVER</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced AI advancements in its supply chain solutions that will unleash a transformative wave of productivity, efficiency and precision in manufacturing. AI-driven insights from real-time data will help companies use their own data to make better decisions across supply chains, streamline product development and improve manufacturing efficiency.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-at-hannover-messe-bring-out-new-manufacturing-excellence">SAP at Hannover Messe: Bring out new manufacturing excellence</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://events.sap.com/hannovermesse/en/home">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Businesses today are confronted with challenges ranging from supply chain disruptions and labor shortages to geopolitical uncertainties,” said Muhammad Alam, member of the Executive Board of SAP SE, SAP Product Engineering. “SAP recognizes the imperative for agility and intelligence, driving innovation with AI-powered solutions to streamline supply chain and manufacturing processes. Companies can enhance operational efficiency and improve supply chain resiliency while delighting customers with superior service, paving the way for sustained growth and market competitiveness.”</p>
  <p>Accurate and relevant real-time information helps mitigate the impact that supply-chain disruptions have on suppliers, manufacturers and distributors worldwide. SMA Solar Technology AG and other customers have already witnessed the benefits of SAP’s solutions, including an approximately 15% increase in supply chain workforce productivity, a 10% decrease in overall supply chain planning costs and a 10% reduction in inventory carrying costs and stock turnover rate.</p>
  <p>“SMA Solar modernizes its manufacturing execution systems to support sustainable, risk-resilient manufacturing operations with the power of AI-enabled visual inspection in the SAP Digital Manufacturing solution,” said Heiko Kehm, SMA Solar head of IT Order to Cash.</p>
  <p>Sixty-three percent of supply chain executives and 52% of operations executives have an AI strategy linked to business objectives, according to “<a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2024/04/2214aa25-b77e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">The Importance of AI in Supply Chain and Operations</a>,” a global 2024 IDC InfoBrief sponsored by SAP*. Fifty-one percent of the 2,000 survey respondents are embedding AI into supply chain planning business processes and key applications for real-time decision-making. Another 58% are using AI to increase operational efficiency and employee productivity.</p>
  <p><a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/supply-chain-management-blogs-by-sap/ai-powered-supply-chain-solutions-better-decisions-better-outcomes/ba-p/13675845">Key improvements</a> to SAP’s supply chain solutions to support customers’ AI-centric strategy include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Optimizing decisions across the supply chain with AI-driven insights:</strong> Companies can now leverage higher volumes of machine data and integrate AI-driven visual inspection by computer into their production processes, enabling a remarkable increase in quality through automation.</li>
    <li><strong>Streamlining product development:</strong> Product developers can now use SAP’s AI copilot Joule to gather and enhance new product ideas quickly and effectively using natural language queries. Joule also helps tag product designs with business data, so they visually contextualize business-critical information.</li>
    <li><strong>Detecting equipment anomalies</strong>: Using AI, asset operators can proactively address potential breakdowns based on sensor data collected from smart devices and edge gateways. This new capacity utilizes the cutting-edge Cumulocity IoT platform from Software AG, which is planned to be embedded in the SAP Asset Performance Management application in Q3.</li>
    <li><strong>Improving field response:</strong> Customers can optimize driving routes and allocate job assignments efficiently with integrated real-time traffic data and machine-learning-trained models, which enable the right field service technicians to reach their destinations on time.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Find more details about the innovations SAP will show at Hannover Messe <a href="https://events.sap.com/hannovermesse/en/home">here</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p>*IDC InfoBrief, sponsored by SAP, The Importance of AI in Supply Chain and Operations, document #US52042224, April 2024.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE: SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Dana Roesiger, +49 6227 7 63900, <a href="mailto:dana.roesiger@sap.com">dana.roesiger@sap.com</a>, CET<br>Julie Schneider, +1 (650) 687-2788, <a href="mailto:julie.schneider@sap.com">julie.schneider@sap.com</a>, PT<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/hannover-messe</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jowat Creates Seamless, Just-in-Time Operations with SAP Digital Manufacturing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/jowat-creates-seamless-operations-sap-digital-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/jowat-creates-seamless-operations-sap-digital-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP Digital Manufacturing, Jowat is on its way to having transparent factories with a reduction in risks, errors, and process costs.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1751a2980ab4eaba557c46a3624a271a2fe09bc21.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1751a2980ab4eaba557c46a3624a271a2fe09bc21.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1751a2980ab4eaba557c46a3624a271a2fe09bc21.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Jowat Creates Seamless, Just-in-Time Operations with SAP Digital Manufacturing" src="./media_1751a2980ab4eaba557c46a3624a271a2fe09bc21.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="jowat-creates-seamless-just-in-time-operations-with-sap-digital-manufacturing">Jowat Creates Seamless, Just-in-Time Operations with SAP Digital Manufacturing</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.jowat.com/en/">Jowat Group</a> is one of the world’s top adhesive manufacturers for industrial use. Tradition and experience from 100 years of corporate development and experience allow it to act as a leading company in technology and innovation in numerous markets and application areas.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Jowat SE’s annual production amounts to 100,000 tons of industrial adhesives. Production is complex and requires high volumes of specialized chemicals and a tremendous amount of power. With raw materials and energy costs skyrocketing, premium manufacturer Jowat looked to get a tighter grip on its inventory management and production processes.</p>
  <p>To ensure maximum efficiency, Jowat requires enough raw materials to fulfill orders while minimizing waste and inventory costs. Moreover, the company needs smooth workflows, as any delay in order placement, production, or the delivery of raw materials can have huge cost implications for the company. As a result, Jowat works hard to ensure that its 24/7 manufacturing processes always run like clockwork.</p>
  <p>With demand for industrial adhesives surging, the company was eager to ensure that its production processes could scale to meet increasing order numbers and still deliver optimum efficiency.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="deliver-individualized-sustainable-and-smart-equipment-products-and-components-in-industrial-manufacturing">Deliver individualized, sustainable, and smart equipment, products, and components in industrial manufacturing</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/industrial-manufacturing.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="targeting-seamless-digital-workflows">Targeting Seamless Digital Workflows</h2>
  <p>Originally established in 1919, Jowat is no stranger to innovation. Leaders at Jowat identified that the next stage of the company’s evolution would require a radical digital transformation of its production and inventory management processes.</p>
  <p>“Our factory workers relied heavily on paper-based processes,” explained Dirk-Alexander Segger, Detmold plant manager at Jowat. “For instance, when employees had finished mixing and decanting adhesives, they handwrote notes to track the volume and type of raw materials that they used during the process. Shortly after decanting, workers would then input the information from their notes into our inventory management and manufacturing execution systems, adding to their workload and increasing the risk of errors.”</p>
  <p>Tracking materials usage manually created time delays, potential for human errors, and discrepancies between the stock numbers recorded in Jowat’s inventory system and the actual volume of raw materials available on the factory floor. Moreover, with information stored across multiple systems and in different formats, plant managers had no clarity to identify process bottlenecks or potential enhancements.</p>
  <p>Annette Podleschny-Borchardt, project lead at Jowat, commented: “To enhance efficiency, improve transparency, and prepare for growth, we decided it was time to go entirely paperless. Building digital processes would give us a more detailed, up-to-date picture of our stock position, which would help drive smarter raw materials purchasing decisions and production improvements.”</p>
  <p>“We aimed to take a more proactive approach to our manufacturing processes. Developing robust, reliable, end-to-end digital workflows was the perfect way to achieve this goal,” explained Christine Künne, head of IT and Business Process Services at Jowat SE.</p>
  <h2 id="embracing-digital-transformation">Embracing Digital Transformation</h2>
  <p>To find the best solution to support its digital transformation initiative, Jowat invited multiple technology vendors to outline the strengths of their solutions. To keep customization low, Jowat targeted a solution that it could easily adapt to meet the highly specialized nature of just-in-time chemicals manufacturing.</p>
  <p>After reviewing 15 different solutions, Jowat selected <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/digital-manufacturing-cloud.html">SAP Digital Manufacturing</a>. In addition to providing a solid foundation for digitalization, SAP Digital Manufacturing can also integrate seamlessly with Jowat’s existing SAP solutions, including <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/extended-warehouse-management.html">SAP Extended Warehouse Management</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP).</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sustainable-risk-resilient-manufacturing-is-here">Sustainable, risk-resilient manufacturing is here</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/digital-manufacturing-cloud.html">Learn more about SAP Digital Manufacturing</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“We were immediately interested in SAP Digital Manufacturing because it is a cloud-native solution,” commented Segger. “Previously, we used on-premise solutions that required us to carry out extensive and disruptive updates. With SAP Digital Manufacturing, we get instant access to the latest features thanks to the quarterly release schedule.”</p>
  <p>Jowat also valued SAP’s proactive engagement with the chemicals manufacturing industry. “We really appreciate that SAP is eager to co-innovate with industry leaders like Jowat to develop next-generation manufacturing solutions,” said Podleschny-Borchardt. “Through the SAP Customer Engagement Initiative, we can help expert developers at SAP build smart factory solutions that meet the needs of our sector down to the finest detail.”</p>
  <h2 id="sticking-with-the-experts">Sticking with the Experts</h2>
  <p>To ensure a smooth implementation of SAP Digital Manufacturing, Jowat relied on support from SAP Services and Support.</p>
  <p>“Whenever we hit a stumbling block, the experts helped us work through the issues. For instance, we wanted to develop a dedicated production operation dashboard, which would give plant managers fast access to key production metrics. As this was uncharted territory, it naturally took a lot of time and energy to work through and SAP was behind us every step of the way,” said Segger.</p>
  <p>Currently, Jowat is completing the first phase of the SAP Digital Manufacturing implementation at its Detmold factory before expanding the solution across all plants. Künne explained: “With a phased implementation, we can ensure that the processes we build at our Detmold plant are tried and tested to deliver maximum efficiency. This will give us the best chance of success when we roll out these processes across all our facilities.”</p>
  <p>“Consultants from SAP Services and Support brought not only their expertise to the project, but also the willingness to listen to the needs and the challenges of our industry. Because of this, we were able to collaborate extremely effectively,” added Podleschny-Borchardt.</p>
  <h2 id="driving-efficient-manufacturing-with-high-quality-data">Driving Efficient Manufacturing with High-Quality Data</h2>
  <p>With SAP Digital Manufacturing, Jowat left error-prone, manual processes behind and now benefits from seamless digital workflows with end-to-end transparency. This helps increase quality and ease work for shop floor operators. The activity confirmation is automatically done in the SAP system, enabling real-time inventory insight.</p>
  <p>Consequently, Jowat gained the following benefits:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>100% digitalized manufacturing process</li>
    <li>One source of truth for detailed production information</li>
    <li>Time savings of three person days per week through automated raw material consumption updates allowing employees focus on higher value activities</li>
    <li>100% accurate inventory</li>
  </ul>
  <p>“Today workers feed consumption information at the point of production. Previously, it would take one full-time employee three days a week to track raw materials consumption,” said Segger. “With SAP Digital Manufacturing, we have a real-time, accurate picture of our raw materials usage and needs. This is helping us optimize usage and reduce costs.”</p>
  <p>Podleschny-Borchardt added: “Production processes are so much faster now that we have built streamlined digital processes. Before, our paper-based ways of working could add up to five days to production timelines. With SAP Digital Manufacturing, we’ve shaved off this time, allowing us to produce and distribute products to our customers much faster, boosting satisfaction.”</p>
  <h2 id="planning-ahead-for-an-ai-driven-future">Planning Ahead for an AI-Driven Future</h2>
  <p>With reliable, up-to-date information in SAP Digital Manufacturing, plant managers and leaders at Jowat can have full visibility across the entire manufacturing cycle. “SAP Digital Manufacturing has helped improve the traceability of our products and given us a much more detailed understanding of our manufacturing operations. Ultimately, that helps to enhance planning and provides new insights into potential process improvements,” said Künne.</p>
  <p>Jowat’s plans for SAP Digital Manufacturing go far beyond a global rollout. The company is already exploring the potential to scale and streamline manufacturing processes further with artificial intelligence (AI) and Internet of Things (IoT) technologies.</p>
  <p>“AI holds tremendous potential for us,” reflected Podleschny-Borchardt. “We’re excited to explore how it can help us to ensure consistently excellent quality across heavily customized product lines and how we can enhance production uptime with IoT-driven predictive maintenance. Having an AI-ready solution like SAP Digital Manufacturing at the heart of our operations makes taking these next steps in our innovation journey much easier.”</p>
  <p>Summarizing the overall benefits, Künne concluded: “With the implementation of SAP Digital Manufacturing through SAP Services and Support, we see ourselves on the way to becoming a transparent factory with a reduction in risks, errors, and process costs thanks to optimized processes.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/smart-press-shop.html">Discover benefits other companies have gained</a>, including improved quality with AI-assisted visual inspection. Be sure to listen to the <a href="https://event.on24.com/eventRegistration/console/apollox/mainEvent?&#x26;eventid=4294893&#x26;sessionid=1&#x26;username=&#x26;partnerref=web&#x26;format=fhvideo1&#x26;mobile=&#x26;flashsupportedmobiledevice=&#x26;helpcenter=&#x26;key=2A85021F45D14DF9C657C622AA74D180&#x26;newConsole=true&#x26;nxChe=true&#x26;newTabCon=true&#x26;consoleEarEventConsole=false&#x26;text_language_id=en&#x26;playerwidth=748&#x26;playerheight=526&#x26;eventuserid=626283838&#x26;contenttype=A&#x26;mediametricsessionid=550094581&#x26;mediametricid=6052808&#x26;usercd=626283838&#x26;mode=launch">webinar</a> about how a renowned manufacturer revolutionizes manufacturing with Industry 4.0. Also, read this <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/risk-resilient-supply-chain-manufacturing/typ.html">report</a> from Oxford Economics about making supply chains more resilient and sustainable.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Karin Fent is senior director of Global Customer Success for Digital Supply Chain at SAP.</p>
        <p>Top image courtesy of Jowat.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>industry/mining: industry/mill-products</category>
            <category>product/sap-digital-manufacturing</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jowat Doubles Productivity with Smarter Maintenance and Strategic Insight into Asset Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/jowat-smarter-maintenance-strategic-insight-asset-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/jowat-smarter-maintenance-strategic-insight-asset-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP solutions, Jowat empowered its technicians to prioritize work more effectively and make smarter decisions about asset investments.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/asset-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP S/4HANA Cloud Is a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud ERP for Product-Centric Enterprises]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/gartner-magic-quadrant-cloud-erp-product-centric-enterprises-sap-s-4-hana</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/gartner-magic-quadrant-cloud-erp-product-centric-enterprises-sap-s-4-hana</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[As enterprises transition mission-critical ERP processes to the cloud, they look to SAP to help them realize business value.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Nine ERP Systems to One: KWC Simplifies App Landscape with SAP S/4HANA Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/kwc-simplifies-app-landscape-sap-s-4hana-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/kwc-simplifies-app-landscape-sap-s-4hana-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Manufacturer KWC Group Ltd. has made significant steps in its digital transformation by implementing SAP S/4HANA Cloud, public edition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Gibson Makes Beautiful Music with High Tech and Strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/gibson-makes-music-high-tech-strategy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/gibson-makes-music-high-tech-strategy</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Technology helps Gibson connect with customers easily and in the ways that they want. Learn more about the company's strategy and tech duet.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/e-commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-emarsys</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>industry/media: industry/sports-entertainment</category>
            <category>news-tag/nrf</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shinhwa Auto Drives North American Expansion with Public Cloud ERP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/shinhwa-auto-drives-expansion-public-cloud-erp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/shinhwa-auto-drives-expansion-public-cloud-erp</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Shinhwa Auto chose GROW with SAP so the company can operate in a more streamlined manner on a global, standardized scale. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-digital-manufacturing</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How PILLER Increased Customer Service with SAP Customer Experience Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/piller-increased-customer-service-sap-cx</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/piller-increased-customer-service-sap-cx</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the help of SAP, PILLER was able to share information and optimize business processes across sales, service, and marketing.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183ba6c7acd6d09f1a49eb03d61c336ed1830707f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183ba6c7acd6d09f1a49eb03d61c336ed1830707f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_183ba6c7acd6d09f1a49eb03d61c336ed1830707f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How PILLER Increased Customer Service with SAP Customer Experience Solutions" src="./media_183ba6c7acd6d09f1a49eb03d61c336ed1830707f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-piller-increased-customer-service-with-sap-customer-experience-solutions">How PILLER Increased Customer Service with SAP Customer Experience Solutions</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.piller.de/">PILLER Blowers &#x26; Compressors</a> produces high-performance blowers and compressors and customized solutions to meet specific requirements of various industries. Its global network of wholly owned subsidiaries and joint ventures enables it to serve an international customer base.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To increase customer service quality, the company wanted to share information and optimize business processes across its sales, service, and marketing activities.</p>
  <h2 id="moving-from-manual-processes-to-integrated-activities">Moving from Manual Processes to Integrated Activities</h2>
  <p>At PILLER, different departments were using their own IT solutions.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-customer-experience-solutions-help-connect-customer-data-improve-loyalty-and-grow-your-business">SAP Customer Experience solutions help connect customer data, improve loyalty, and grow your business</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The service department had manual processes, such as Microsoft Excel spreadsheets, to dispatch service technicians. The technicians were logging into a central server to retrieve data and recording customer support by e-mails and conversations. The sales department had a basic access environment due to custom-made products with individual serial numbers. There was no master data; tailored sales quotes were done on paper, posing challenges for data updating and quality. The marketing department was conducting its business, like capturing trade-fair leads or planning and executing campaigns, by hand and with spreadsheets. All these manual activities were time intensive and prone to human error.</p>
  <p>To enable the marketing, sales, and service teams to perform to the best of their abilities, PILLER wanted solutions that allowed it to share important information. It wished to harmonize all customer-related processes, from initial contact and order management to delivery of spare parts and follow-up.</p>
  <p>“For new products or customers, it’s important that real-time master data in our core software is mirrored in our sales, service, and marketing systems. We can do this by integrating SAP Customer Experience solutions and SAP Field Service Management with SAP S/4HANA,” said Frank Münzner, in-house SAP consultant for Lead to Cash at PILLER Blowers &#x26; Compressors GmbH.</p>
  <h2 id="adopting-cloud-solutions-to-achieve-innovative-customer-service">Adopting Cloud Solutions to Achieve Innovative Customer Service</h2>
  <p>PILLER employed the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/sales-cloud.html">SAP Sales Cloud</a> solution to help address the needs of its sales team and integrate functionalities, such as managing quotes and orders, in one place. The solution offers a search capability and a modern, intuitive user interface.</p>
  <p>The company is using the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/field-service-management.html">SAP Field Service Management mobile app</a> to help create service tickets, which are the single point of customer contact, with product serial numbers and metadata. Integrating this mobile app with the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/service-cloud.html">SAP Service Cloud</a> solution can enable technicians to receive service ticket information on an Apple iPad, so they can have everything they need to carry out their work. This can also translate to good customer support.</p>
  <p>By deploying the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/marketing.html">SAP Marketing Cloud</a> solution and integrating it with SAP Sales Cloud, PILLER now proactively shares data, such as service tickets, lead opportunities, and customer contacts, between the sales and marketing teams. This lets the company contact a customer with a warranty option or service cost reduction, for example.</p>
  <p>PILLER has now integrated the three SAP Customer Experience solutions for sales, service, and marketing and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/field-service-management.html">SAP Field Service Management</a> with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA</a>, the company’s enterprise resource planning (ERP) software.</p>
  <p>PILLER partnered with <a href="https://www.fis-gmbh.de/en/">FIS Global</a> to gain advice about new functionalities and implementation support, while <a href="https://www.ibsolution.com/en/">IBsolution</a> provided guidance around leveraging the potential in terms of business transformation and digitization.</p>
  <h2 id="gaining-comprehensive-customer-visibility-with-integrated-solutions">Gaining Comprehensive Customer Visibility with Integrated Solutions</h2>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="resolve-customer-issues-faster-with-proactive-ai-enabled-field-service-management-software-from-sap">Resolve customer issues faster with proactive, AI-enabled field service management software from SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/field-service-management.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The major advantage in connecting the SAP Customer Experience portfolio, SAP Field Service Management, and SAP S/4HANA is that real-time data can be available across all these solutions. While master data, such as for a new product, customer, or material, is entered and kept in SAP S/4HANA as the core software, it’s automatically pushed into the other integrated solutions.</p>
  <p>This is helping PILLER deliver highly efficient and innovative customer service and business models. The company gains a comprehensive view of worldwide customers in real time while interacting with them at each stage of their journey in a targeted manner.</p>
  <p>There are now customer-related processes across departments, sites, and systems as well as consistent communication throughout the company, thanks to standardized forms and templates. The business is achieving agile sales with faster response times and better allocation of target groups. It’s also making decisions for customer management based on facts and analyses.</p>
  <p>Other benefits the company achieved were:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>360-degree view of customers worldwide in real time</li>
    <li>90% less paper with digital processes</li>
    <li>30% reduction in effort by using digital processes</li>
  </ul>
  <p>“We’ve always combined tradition with innovation when manufacturing our blowers. With SAP Customer Experience solutions, our customer management operations are superior to those of our competitors. We’re able to keep a close eye on processes and respond quickly and accordingly,” said Thomas Henzler, CIO at PILLER Blowers &#x26; Compressors GmbH.</p>
  <h2 id="rolling-out-customer-centric-solutions">Rolling Out Customer-Centric Solutions</h2>
  <p>Combining <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">SAP Customer Experience solutions</a> and the SAP Field Service Management mobile app with SAP S/4HANA is helping deliver real-time data for integrated processes.</p>
  <p>The integration of the SAP Field Service Management mobile app with SAP Service Cloud is being piloted with three service technicians and garnering positive feedback so far.</p>
  <p>Watch an <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/sales-cloud.html?video=189daad3-437e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">overview video</a> of SAP Sales Cloud to help build lasting customer relationships and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/service-cloud.html?pdf-asset=983be5bb-b27d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff&#x26;page=1">learn more about SAP Service Cloud</a> to maximize customer lifetime value with connected service. Read about the benefits companies achieved with <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/topcon.html">SAP Customer Experience solutions</a>. View a <a href="https://www.sap.com/sea/products/scm/field-service-management/features.html?video=66ec8033-617e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">solution demo</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/field-service-management/features.html?video=f83398c5-247e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">overview video</a> to learn how to maximize productivity and asset uptime with SAP Field Service Management. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/field-service-management.html?video=14f5efa9-427e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">Learn what benefits other enterprises achieved</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Karin Fent is senior director of Global Customer Success Digital Supply Chain at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign Up</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/field-service-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-marketing-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-service-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Manufacturers Monetize Beyond Products: As-a-Service Builds Customer Relationships]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/as-a-service-builds-customer-relationships-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/as-a-service-builds-customer-relationships-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[As-a-service business models have helped manufacturers turn services into ongoing revenue streams and build relationships. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/quote-to-cash</category>
            <category>news-tag/recurring-revenue-models</category>
            <category>product/sap-billing-and-revenue-innovation-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/xaas</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Creating an Agile, Resilient, and Sustainable Logistics Network]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/creating-agile-resilient-sustainable-logistics-network</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/creating-agile-resilient-sustainable-logistics-network</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's Till Dengel shares how industrial manufacturing businesses can drive an agile, resilient, and sustainable logistics network.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-network-for-logistics</category>
            <category>product/sap-warehouse-robotics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Leveraging SAP’s Industry Cloud, Going from Concept to Commercialization Can Be Fast and Fulfilling]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/cogniac-sap-syntax-industry-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/cogniac-sap-syntax-industry-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The industry cloud partnership between Cogniac, Syntax, and SAP illustrates how combining forces can deliver more value to customers.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-digital-manufacturing</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-io</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global Manufacturer Jabil Transforms and Innovates with SAP S/4HANA Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/jabil-transforms-innovates-sap-s-4hana-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/jabil-transforms-innovates-sap-s-4hana-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP customer Jabil shares how organizations can prepare today for their SAP S/4HANA Cloud journey so they’ll be future-ready for tomorrow.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>industry/mining: industry/mill-products</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Ways One of Europe’s Largest Steel Producers Is Decarbonizing the Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/salzgitter-decarbonizing-steel-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/salzgitter-decarbonizing-steel-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[German steel giant Salzgitter AG relaunched its brand to reflect its strategic vision to become the leader in circular economy solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Business Network for Industry Helps Meet Unique Business Needs]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-business-network-for-industry-meet-unique-business-needs</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-business-network-for-industry-meet-unique-business-needs</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Every industry faces challenges that a one-size-fits-all approach can't address. That's where SAP Business Network for Industry can help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1859392f911d9814db661b8bac76fdce9ce2568e6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1859392f911d9814db661b8bac76fdce9ce2568e6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1859392f911d9814db661b8bac76fdce9ce2568e6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Business Network for Industry Helps Meet Unique Business Needs" src="./media_1859392f911d9814db661b8bac76fdce9ce2568e6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-business-network-for-industry-helps-meet-unique-business-needs">SAP Business Network for Industry Helps Meet Unique Business Needs</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Companies have been forced to reevaluate the fundamentals of their supply chains over the past several years, often completely overhauling their processes to meet shifting demands. Some of the most significant challenges businesses are facing include skilled labor shortages, shipping and logistics issues, and evolving environmental, social, and governance (ESG) regulations.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The reactive, ad-hoc approach that companies have taken to tackle disruption has resulted in mismatched supply chain processes that offer little visibility and don’t keep up with the speed of change. Companies rely on convoluted, manual communication methods between suppliers and buyers. E-mails and calls get lost in the shuffle of vacations and holidays, making critical collaboration untraceable and delayed.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-sap-sapphire-news-guide-tackle-the-future-with-confidence">Read the SAP Sapphire News Guide: Tackle the Future with Confidence</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="sap-business-network-is-an-industry-ready-digital-network-of-suppliers-and-buyers">SAP Business Network Is an Industry-Ready Digital Network of Suppliers and Buyers</h2>
  <p>Businesses need a collaborative, many-to-many platform to drive transparent, resilient, and sustainable supply chains. That’s where <a href="/topics/business-network">SAP Business Network</a> comes in: a multi-enterprise collaboration network, built for industry, that helps companies execute their vision and meet growth targets by connecting with trading partners seamlessly.</p>
  <p>Only SAP Business Network provides collaboration across a broad range of processes, including indirect and direct procurement, supply chain, logistics, asset collaboration, finance, and talent.</p>
  <p>But each industry faces unique challenges that can’t always be addressed with a one-size-fits-all approach. For this reason, we are introducing SAP Business Network for Industry with an initial focus on the <strong>consumer products</strong>, <strong>life sciences</strong>, <strong>high tech</strong>, and <strong>industrial manufacturing</strong> industries. This includes:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>A portfolio of SAP Business Network capabilities that address industry needs</li>
    <li>A new SAP Business Network Industry Advisory Board to guide our product and road map strategy</li>
    <li>New SAP Business Network for Supply Chain industry services accelerators for select industries to help customers fast-track their implementation and post go-live success</li>
  </ul>
  <p>With SAP’s more than 50 years of industry expertise and industry process excellence embedded in our technology, we know better than anyone how to help customers tackle their specific challenges.</p>
  <h2 id="capabilities-designed-to-meet-industry-needs">Capabilities Designed to Meet Industry Needs</h2>
  <p>As we work to help companies tackle challenges with supply chain transparency, resiliency, and sustainability, we’ve engaged directly with customers to improve existing functionalities and develop new capabilities for SAP Business Network.</p>
  <p>We developed capabilities including contract manufacturing, planning and forecasting, quality collaboration, stock transfers, support for supplier-managed inventory, material traceability, and track and trace. Several of these capabilities were developed alongside customers to answer unique industry challenges in a variety of industries, including consumer products, high tech, industrial manufacturing, and life sciences. While these and other innovations were originally created to address a specific industry need, many of them can be applied cross-industry to help businesses increase visibility, mitigate risks, and operate more efficiently.</p>
  <p>Working with our customers has helped evolve SAP Business Network into the well-rounded, comprehensive solution it is today. It has been amazing to see the innovations that have come out of these relationships with customers, and their stories and successes have truly inspired me. To build on what we’ve accomplished so far, we’re strengthening the way we collaborate with customers and helping accelerate implementation with new industry-specific use cases.</p>
  <h2 id="continuing-the-tradition-of-customer-collaboration">Continuing the Tradition of Customer Collaboration</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="press-release-saps-vision-for-future-proofed-business-in-the-age-of-ai-comes-to-life">Press Release: SAP’s Vision for Future-Proofed Business in the Age of AI Comes to Life</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2023/05/sap-sapphire-future-proofed-business-age-of-ai">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To continue the tradition of working with our customers to enhance and extend our product capabilities, we’re introducing the SAP Business Network Industry Advisory Board. This select group of industry leaders will provide strategic direction for our product and road map, making sure we’re meeting the needs of our customers and helping their businesses grow. I’m eager to see the exciting new ideas and developments that will come out of this collaborative forum of industry experts.</p>
  <h2 id="expedite-time-to-value-with-industry-services-accelerators-for-sap-business-network-for-supply-chain">Expedite Time to Value with Industry Services Accelerators for SAP Business Network for Supply Chain</h2>
  <p>For customers beginning their journey with SAP Business Network for Supply Chain in particular, we’re introducing new industry services accelerators from our SAP Business Network Services team to help expedite time to value and achieve success.</p>
  <p>These industry services accelerators support critical supply chain business processes in the consumer products, high tech, industrial manufacturing, and life sciences industries. With prepackaged industry use cases and capabilities, implementation best practices, and dedicated post go-live support, industry services accelerators are based on SAP’s knowledge and expertise with SAP Business Network for Supply Chain. Industry services accelerators can be delivered in collaboration with partners.</p>
  <h2 id="stay-tuned-for-more">Stay Tuned for More</h2>
  <p>Other additions to SAP Business Network include new supplier innovations that will help support supplier adoption, focusing on creating an easier integration process to reduce friction and help grow your business to achieve maximum value.</p>
  <p>To learn more, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-ISM-1982254&#x26;source=blog-glo-blog">SAP Business Network for Industry on sap.com</a>. Here, we’ll keep you up-to-date on all of the exciting innovations happening and share resources to help you tailor your SAP Business Network experience.</p>
  <p>And, don’t miss learning more about SAP Business Network and how SAP can help solve the unique business challenges of your industry at <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/spend-connect-live.html">SAP Spend Connect Live in Vienna</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Val Blatt is global head for SAP Business Network Customer Success &#x26; Go-to-Market at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire">Read more news and coverage from SAP Sapphire</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>industry/high-tech</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network-for-industry</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HANNOVER MESSE: Making Manufacturing More Resilient]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/hannover-messe-making-manufacturing-more-resilient</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/hannover-messe-making-manufacturing-more-resilient</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At the 2023 Hannover Messe trade show, SAP showed visitors how it enables resilient, sustainable production and supply chain operations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/hannover-messe</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-4-0</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-x</category>
            <category>product/sap-digital-manufacturing</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-Time Support from SAP Is Essential to the Digital Transformation of Jinlong]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/real-time-support-essential-to-digital-transformation-jinlong</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/real-time-support-essential-to-digital-transformation-jinlong</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Real-Time Support from SAP helps customers, like Jinlong, quickly resolve issues and accelerate their digital transformations. Learn how!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/real-time-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Partners Drive a Wave of Industry Cloud Innovation in Discrete Manufacturing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-partners-industry-cloud-innovation-discrete-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-partners-industry-cloud-innovation-discrete-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and its partners are capitalizing on industry cloud opportunities in the discrete manufacturing industries. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unleashing Automation for a Resilient Aerospace & Defense Sector]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/unleashing-automation-resilient-aerospace-defense-sector</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/unleashing-automation-resilient-aerospace-defense-sector</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The aerospace and defense industry needs ways to overcome labor shortage-driven production challenges. Automation solutions and SAP can help]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/aerospace-defense</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-twin</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-4-0</category>
            <category>news-tag/rpa</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
            <category>product/sap-warehouse-robotics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Milliken & Company Transforms HR in the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/milliken-company-transforms-hr-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/milliken-company-transforms-hr-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Milliken & Company leveraged cloud HR solutions to create a sustainable workforce. Read to learn more about its transformation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[This Bathroom and Wellness Business Is Growing Strong Thanks to Top Tech and Design]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/eczacibasi-growing-strong-top-tech-and-design</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/eczacibasi-growing-strong-top-tech-and-design</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Eczacibaşi, a Turkish building materials company and industry leader, is digitalizing to drive efficiency and reduce waste. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Can Remanufacturing Build the Industrial-Sized Circular Economy?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/remanufacturing-build-industrial-circular-economy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/remanufacturing-build-industrial-circular-economy</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Remanufacturing tightens the loop between first-time usage and reuse to reduce waste and increase profits, powering the circular economy.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>industry/mining: industry/mill-products</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical Manufacturers Fight Fake Drugs with Intelligent Supply Chains]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/pharmaceutical-manufacturers-drug-supply-chains</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/pharmaceutical-manufacturers-drug-supply-chains</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Investing in intelligent supply chain solutions can enable resilience and prevent counterfeit drugs in the life sciences industry. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>product/sap-information-collaboration-hub-for-life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Industry 4.0 Attracts Workers Whose Entire Lives Are on Their Mobile Device]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/industry-4-0-attracts-workers-whose-entire-lives-are-on-their-mobile-device</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/industry-4-0-attracts-workers-whose-entire-lives-are-on-their-mobile-device</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Manufacturers are transforming factories, hoping next-generation workers come for the cool factor and stay for career-building innovations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-4-0</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/mobile</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Solutions Live in Action at Industry 4.0 Pop-Up Factory]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/industry-4-0-pop-up-factory</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/industry-4-0-pop-up-factory</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP launched the Industry 4.0 Pop-Up Factory, where customers and partners can experience SAP solutions, technologies, and innovations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-4-0</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-experience-center</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Digital Innovations Behind the Booming Life Sciences Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/digital-innovations-life-sciences-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/digital-innovations-life-sciences-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The pandemic has irrevocably disrupted the life sciences industry, revealing a new vision for innovation from cloud-based collaboration.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[California’s Low-Cost Insulin Is Symptom of Lifesaving Innovations to Come]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/life-sciences-innovations-to-come</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/life-sciences-innovations-to-come</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Life sciences leaders are connecting data and people to find for more cost-effective disease prevention innovations and lifesaving cures.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainability Takes Flight across Aviation Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sustainability-aviation-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sustainability-aviation-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Airplane manufacturers are moving towards a holistic strategy for sustainable design throughout an airplane’s entire life cycle. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/aerospace-defense</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-neutrality</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-enterprise-product-development</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Principles of Resilient Supply Chains for CPG Manufacturing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/three-principles-resilient-cpg-supply-chains</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/three-principles-resilient-cpg-supply-chains</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Supply chain resilience can lead directly to business resilience, especially for consumer packaged goods (CPG) manufacturers. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>