<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/non-sap-event/earth-overshoot-day/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Earth Overshoot Day 2023: Reversing the Clock for a Sustainable Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/earth-overshoot-day-2023-sustainable-future</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/earth-overshoot-day-2023-sustainable-future</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Earth Overshoot Day 2023 falls five days later than last year, but it's no cause for celebration. Read how to drive more change and impact.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>news-tag/decarbonization</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/earth-overshoot-day</category>
            <category>news-tag/net-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/renewable-energy</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sustainability-solutions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Earth Overshoot Day 2022: Can We Live in Balance with the Earth?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/earth-overshoot-day-2022-live-balance</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/earth-overshoot-day-2022-live-balance</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[On Earth Overshoot Dat 2022, we focus on what can and has to be done to turn the human economy around to be more sustainable.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/earth-overshoot-day</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why Doing Business As Usual Can Cost Us Dearly]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/07/earth-overshoot-day-business-as-usual-can-cost-us-dearly</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/07/earth-overshoot-day-business-as-usual-can-cost-us-dearly</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[On Earth Overshoot Day, SAP CEO Christian Klein discusses how SAP can help protect our planet and create a better future for our children.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12a8d26c316039df7af71f2f7c159ffbf8a65b64f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12a8d26c316039df7af71f2f7c159ffbf8a65b64f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12a8d26c316039df7af71f2f7c159ffbf8a65b64f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Why Doing Business As Usual Can Cost Us Dearly" src="./media_12a8d26c316039df7af71f2f7c159ffbf8a65b64f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="why-doing-business-as-usual-can-cost-us-dearly">Why Doing Business As Usual Can Cost Us Dearly</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>I am a proud dad of two young kids. Since they were born, the world has experienced a global <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, increasing social unrest, numerous political conflicts, and countless natural disasters from heat waves and wildfires to record flooding.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Oftentimes, when we talk about sustainability, we think about it in terms of the distant future. But looking at the past few years alone, it becomes clear that we don’t need solutions in, say, five years. We need them now.</p>
  <p>It’s not about what we are doing to make the world better by the time our children are grown up, but about what can we do to make things better right now. What are we doing to make an impact by the time they learn to ride a bike, have their first day in kindergarten, leave school, and enter their first job?</p>
  <p><strong>We need to act now to ensure that our children have a sustainable future.</strong></p>
  <p>We might think that our individual actions don’t matter. But changes – both big and small –in the way we live our lives can help reduce our own personal carbon footprint, and also encourage other individuals, businesses, and policy makers to act for the good of the planet. Because at the end of the day, everything counts. Every day we act, every step we take, every decision we make can help move the needle. And vice versa: Every step we don’t take today will take us three steps back in the future.</p>
  <p>Today is <a href="/2021/07/earth-overshoot-day-2021">Earth Overshoot Day 2021</a>. It marks the date when humanity has exhausted nature’s budget for the year. From this day forward, we are using an unsustainable amount of the world’s resources. The exact date each year is calculated based on 3 million statistical data points from 200 countries, and the team at Global Footprint Network <a href="https://www.overshootday.org/about-earth-overshoot-day/">explains the process here</a> in more detail.</p>
  <p>This year’s date is almost as early as in 2019, when it fell on July 26, after being momentarily pushed back in 2020 by lockdowns due to the coronavirus pandemic. So for more than 40 years, we have been using up our planet’s resources in excess. Our desire for every aspect of our lives to become better, faster, and newer is not only stealing from a planet that cannot keep up with the demands of almost 8 billion people, but also costing our future generations an Earth on which they can live and prosper.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="chasing-zero-aspire-to-a-world-with-zero-emissions-zero-waste-and-zero-inequality">Chasing Zero: Aspire to a world with zero emissions, zero waste, and zero inequality</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="covid-19-reset">COVID-19 Reset</h2>
  <p>The graphic above shows what is possible in extreme situations such as with the numerous lockdowns and restrictions due to the COVID-19 pandemic.</p>
  <p>Just a few examples: Due to beach closures in Florida, female turtles laid more eggs. In Japan — one of my favorite countries to visit — the Nara deer left the park to find food because the tourists that would normally feed them were no longer there. Air and water quality improved as tourism ground to a halt. For the first time in 30 years, Indians in the city of Jalandhar and the surrounding area could see the Himalayas.</p>
  <p>These examples show that our planet could recover relatively quickly if given the chance. However, life in many parts of the world is returning to a new version of normal with more and more people receiving vaccinations. While this is good for humanity, it also has an impact on nature.</p>
  <h2 id="our-responsibility">Our Responsibility</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-from-saps-chief-sustainability-officer-about-earth-overshoot-day-2021">Read more from SAP's Chief Sustainability Officer about Earth Overshoot Day 2021</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/07/earth-overshoot-day-2021">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The private sector for sure has its part to play if we are to combat climate change. Businesses should not focus exclusively on profit maximization, but at turning things around, in the here and now, for current and future generations.</p>
  <p>Without any doubt, sustainability is about more than protecting our environment. It is about ensuring the balance between economic growth, environmental care, and social welfare. That said, carbon neutrality is a major driver and key indicator of sustainability.</p>
  <p>At SAP, we set our goal to become carbon-neutral in our own operations by the end of 2023, two years earlier than previously stated. The SAP approach is of first avoiding, second reducing, and third compensating for emissions. You can read more about <a href="/2021/03/sap-carbon-neutrality-goal-2023">our goal for 2023 here</a>.</p>
  <p>But in addition to pursuing our own targets, we also want to help our customers become more sustainable. Because we are convinced: It’s time to build sustainability into the fabric of how we do business. We need to make it a standard dimension of corporate management just like productivity or growth.</p>
  <p>We’ve <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability.html">developed various solutions</a> to help businesses embed operational, experiential, and financial data and insights to drive sustainability at scale. With our sustainability portfolio, we support companies on their entire journey across the full spectrum of sustainability – from carbon neutrality to social impact and economic progress.</p>
  <p>Additionally, we will drive multi-year innovation roadmaps to ultimately provide our customers with end-to-end visibility around sustainability, integrated into their core business processes. To get to our vision of <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html">Chasing Zero</a>, we must act now with the goal of zero waste, zero emissions, and zero inequality.</p>
  <p>Given the significance of global supply chains in tackling sustainability, the SAP community truly has the power to protect our planet and create a future our children want to be part of. So, let’s give our planet the chance to recover and #MoveTheDate together.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Christian Klein is CEO of SAP SE.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/why-doing-business-usual-can-cost-us-dearly-christian-klein/">This piece was originally published on LinkedIn</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/earth-overshoot-day</category>
            <category>news-tag/economics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Earth Overshoot Day: Closing the Loop and Moving the Date Together]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/earth-overshoot-day-2021</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/earth-overshoot-day-2021</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[On Earth Overshoot Day 2021, SAP Chief Sustainability Officer Daniel Schmid reflects on why climate action and circular economy is needed.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_197917d99f8e792f5e97bcad63870d842ef7e0799.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_197917d99f8e792f5e97bcad63870d842ef7e0799.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_197917d99f8e792f5e97bcad63870d842ef7e0799.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Earth Overshoot Day: Closing the Loop and Moving the Date Together" src="./media_197917d99f8e792f5e97bcad63870d842ef7e0799.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="earth-overshoot-day-closing-the-loop-and-moving-the-date-together">Earth Overshoot Day: Closing the Loop and Moving the Date Together</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="build-sustainability-into-your-core-business-processes-with-sap-software">Build sustainability into your core business processes with SAP software</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><em>“In less than eight months, humanity has exhausted Earth’s budget for the year.”</em> I was concerned to read this on the <a href="https://www.footprintnetwork.org/our-work/earth-overshoot-day/">Global Footprint Network’s homepage</a> few weeks ago, when the global Earth Overshoot Day 2021 was <a href="https://www.overshootday.org/">announced to land on July 29</a>. This means that for the rest of the year, we are running on a deficit: our demand for ecological resources and services is exceeding what Earth can regenerate.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>What unsettles me most is that we have completely re-bounced to the pre-pandemic overshoot. When I was <a href="/2020/08/earth-overshoot-day-moving-back-on-budget">reflecting on Earth Overshoot Day on August 22 last year</a>, I was hopeful that we had turned around the <a href="https://www.overshootday.org/newsroom/past-earth-overshoot-days/">devastating trend</a> of reaching our planet’s natural limits earlier and earlier since 1970. It had been the first time in years that we had pushed Earth Overshoot Day to a later date. But now we have almost returned to the level of 2019, with an <a href="https://www.overshootday.org/2021-calculation/">estimated 6.6% increase of our global ecological footprint in 2021</a> compared to 2020.</p>
  <p>Have we not learned our lessons? Are we not managing to leverage the small window of opportunity to ensure a sustainable recovery?</p>
  <p>The conversation around sustainability did actually accelerate in the last 18 months, quite drastically even. Political will has been converging with true economic business cases. <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/dishashetty/2021/03/24/a-fifth-of-worlds-largest-companies-committed-to-net-zero-target/?sh=62cc3a83662f">Ambitious sustainability commitments were abundantly announced</a>. For businesses it is no longer a question of “if,” but of “how” and “how fast” — and the latter seem to be the issue. The many bold targets from diversity to net-zero remain to be executed.</p>
  <p>It’s clear that we need to move from goal setting to action and do so faster.</p>
  <p>Being a stubborn optimist, I never give up taking note of examples that prove progress in the right direction. I was intrigued when reading about <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/25/amsterdam-brussels-bet-on-doughnut-economics-amid-covid-crisis.html">Amsterdam</a> and <a href="https://doughnuteconomics.org/news/10">Brussels</a> being among the first cities to implement Doughnut Economics amid the <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> crisis. The model was introduced by <a href="https://www.kateraworth.com/doughnut/">economist Kate Raworth, who describes it as follows</a>:</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>Humanity’s 21st century challenge is to meet the needs of all within the means of the planet. In other words, to ensure that no one falls short on life’s essential needs (from food and housing to health care and political voice), while ensuring that collectively we do not overshoot our pressure on Earth’s life-supporting systems, on which we fundamentally depend. The Doughnut of social and planetary boundaries is a playfully serious approach to framing that challenge, and it acts as a compass for human progress this century.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Having been inspired by Raworth’s doughnut, as well as by related frameworks such as Johan Rockström’s concept of the <a href="https://stockholmresilience.org/research/planetary-boundaries.html">planetary boundaries</a>, we have also evolved SAP’s objective over time to “creating positive economic, social, and environmental impact within the planetary boundaries.” We know it’s still directional, but are passionately working together with our employees, partners, suppliers, governments, and NGOs toward bringing this to life.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="catch-up-on-the-virtual-sap-sustainability-summit">Catch up on the virtual SAP Sustainability Summit</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At our first <a href="https://vshow.on24.com/vshow/SustainabilitySummit/#exhibits/L1">SAP Sustainability Summit</a> in April this year, we heard inspiring examples of how this has already been put into practice along with future solutions yet to be implemented. While the focus was on holistic steering and reporting, climate action,and circular economy, it is the circular economy that especially comes to mind today.</p>
  <p>Earth Overshoot Day painfully visualizes that our current economy is largely based on a “take-make-waste” model — the linear economy, or as Raworth puts it so vividly the “industrial caterpillar, ingesting food at one end, chewing it through, and excreting the waste out of the other end.” The key is to move away from this degenerative approach toward a regenerative one based on continual (re)use of resources in a closed-loop system, minimized use of resource inputs, and reduction of waste, pollution, and carbon emissions. This only works through collaboration across networks, which is a key motivation for SAP to <a href="/2021/06/sapphire-now-business-network-sustainable-performance">create new business communities</a> able to improve business outcomes, better navigate changing economic and geopolitical conditions, and enhance sustainability contributions.</p>
  <p>The experiences, advancements, and challenges shared during the SAP Sustainability Summit by both large corporations — including Mitsubishi, adidas, H&#x26;M, Nestle, Dow, Eastman, Audi, and BASF — as well as startups such as Queen of Raw, Topolytics, Rheaply, Greentoken, and Re-loop, make me hopeful that we have the foundation on which to build. Partnerships that were equally discussed at the event — as with Accenture, the World Business Council for Sustainable Development, the Ellen MacArthur Foundation, or the World Economic Forum’s Global Plastics Action Partnership — should provide the springboard to accelerate and scale.</p>
  <p>SAP is committed to play its part in driving the transition toward an <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability/economy.html">inclusive, circular, and zero-waste economy</a> — be it through the <a href="/2021/06/sapphire-now-sustainability-management-by-sap">launch of new sustainability solutions</a>, supporting alliances and pledges like the WWF’s OneSource <a href="https://www.onesourcecoalition.org/">coalition</a> and Ellen MacArthur Foundation’s <a href="https://plastics.ellenmacarthurfoundation.org/epr">Call to Action</a> encouraging government actions against plastic wast,e or by offering a <a href="https://open.sap.com/courses/ce1">free online course</a> to increase the awareness of benefits and best practices.</p>
  <p>I invite everyone to join in and act now. The Global Footprint Network has a <a href="https://www.overshootday.org/portfolio/i-join-the-solutions-to-movethedate-movement/">#MoveTheDate movement</a> to chip away at our own ecological footprint, both collectively and individually. Let’s make it happen together!</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Daniel Schmid is chief sustainability officer at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/earth-overshoot-day</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>