<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/redefining-youth/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Empowering Anthems: A Playlist for International Youth Day]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/international-youth-day-2023-anthems</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/international-youth-day-2023-anthems</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For International Youth Day 2023, get the playlist you need to inspire us all to work better together to protect people and planet.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Small Step in Space Exploration, a Giant Leap for Youth]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/flynn-doherty-redefining-youth-space-exploration-leap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/flynn-doherty-redefining-youth-space-exploration-leap</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Flynn Doherty is among the thousands of inspiring participants from the Young ICT Explorers program, run by SAP. Read his story.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Code Unnati: Inspiring Bright Futures through Digital Inclusion]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/code-unnati-digital-inclusion</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/code-unnati-digital-inclusion</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Code Unnati aims to impart digital literacy among adolescents, citizens, and children as well as employable IT skills among youth. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-education</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meet and Code: Closing Europe’s Digital Skills Gap One Student at a Time]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/meet-and-code-closing-digital-skills-gap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/meet-and-code-closing-digital-skills-gap</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP’s Meet and Code initiative has helped non-profits introduce young people to the exciting world of technology and coding. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Redefining (YOU)th: Nurturing Potential to Accelerate Change]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/redefining-youth-nurture-potential-accelerate-change</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/redefining-youth-nurture-potential-accelerate-change</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Kicking off the Redefining (YOU)th 2022 campaign, learn more about the exceptional young people driven by a shared purpose.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[To the Young People Who Move Us Forward]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/international-youth-day-young-people-move-us-forward</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/international-youth-day-young-people-move-us-forward</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[On International Youth Day, SAP thanks the future of business who are shaping the business of future. Learn more about our gratitude.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_105fe4b2ea2df77b44006256013330a86b5c479a0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_105fe4b2ea2df77b44006256013330a86b5c479a0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_105fe4b2ea2df77b44006256013330a86b5c479a0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="To the Young People Who Move Us Forward" src="./media_105fe4b2ea2df77b44006256013330a86b5c479a0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="to-the-young-people-who-move-us-forward">To the Young People Who Move Us Forward</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>To young people worldwide, on International Youth Day, I offer my gratitude to you on behalf of our 103,000 colleagues at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To the doers, the dreamers, and those like <a href="https://vimeo.com/446987417">Teevyah</a> and <a href="https://vimeo.com/431802348">Veenadhari</a> who are <a href="https://www.un.org/en/observances/youth-day">transforming food systems</a>, we honor you. To all The Possibilists who dare businesses to do things differently, we hear you. We see you. You are not just the future of business; you are shaping the business of future!</p>
  <p>For every Greta, Malala, or Simone making global headlines, there are thousands of young changemakers like you, <a href="/2021/08/african-refugee-camps-youth-inspire-change">Avina</a>, <a href="/2021/07/possibilists-study-youth-lead-post-pandemic-world">Ryan</a>, and <a href="/2021/08/the-world-within-us-passion-travel-purpose">Anina</a>, who are making a world of difference in communities and countries alike. The successes and struggles documented in <a href="https://thepossibilists.org/">The Possibilists</a>, a recent report by an alliance of 16 of the world’s leading youth social innovation networks, is a reminder to all of us that you can’t be stopped. And if we can unite business, government, and the social sector around your work, we will succeed in accelerating (your) solutions to the world’s most challenging problems.</p>
  <p>While traditional business has much to learn from social innovators, we also have a lot to offer you.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="in-a-post-pandemic-world-youth-take-center-stage-and-lead">In a Post-Pandemic World, Youth Take Center Stage and Lead</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/07/possibilists-study-youth-lead-post-pandemic-world">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="accessing-networks-build-bridges-not-silos">1. Accessing Networks: Build Bridges, Not Silos</h2>
  <p>Many of the solutions the world needs already exist, but gaining access to the right people and organizations to share those solutions with is not as easy. More than 94% of Possibilists shared that they lack the personal or business access needed to move their organization forward. And yet, combined with financial and mental hardships, they forge on with their work because they are intrinsically motivated to do the right thing for the world. So how can corporations create space for leaders like you to bring game changing ideas to the table? It might be easier than you think.</p>
  <p>In 2020, SAP formally launched “Youth To The Table” in partnership with <a href="https://www.wearefamilyfoundation.org/">We Are Family Foundation</a>, giving skilled experts like Riddhima Yadav, a young climate and sustainability finance expert, a seat at c-suite level decision making tables at SAP. Riddhima joined SAP’s External Sustainability Advisory Council this year, joining the ranks of tenured sustainability leaders. Together, the council members provide formal outside-in guidance on SAP’s sustainability journey. Like many of The Possibilists, Riddhima formed her first organization as a teenager. Although still “early” in her career, she is an outstanding representative for both her field of expertise and her generation.</p>
  <p>A program like Youth To The Table should not only exist within one company, and perhaps we can help change that. I challenge you to approach the business leaders and companies operating in your field of interest or expertise. Reach out to their sustainability or corporate social responsibility leaders on social media as a place to start. If that doesn’t work, connect with intermediaries like <a href="https://changemakerxchange.org/">ChangemakerXChange</a> or We Are Family Foundation, which have formal youth-to-corporate programs. This is an opportunity for all of us if we focus more on building bridges, and a little less on our erecting own silos.</p>
  <h2 id="accelerating-business-keep-the-promise">2. Accelerating Business: Keep the Promise</h2>
  <p>Once you know who is (or could be) in your extended network, be sure you know how you can partner with them. During the <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vx5O0ECmr2g">presentation of The Possibilists results</a>, we heard innovators request support like, “We need help. We’re looking for an expert who can help us do the work.” Rest assured, there is help out there.</p>
  <p>Helping businesses run better is what we do, but SAP is not alone in that work when it comes to supporting the work of social entrepreneurs. Unilever, EY, and Ikea are a few awesome corporations that come to mind. We all have programs that will provide you with skilled business experts or financial support, usually in partnership with social sector organizations like <a href="https://movingworlds.org/organization">MovingWorlds</a>, <a href="https://acumen.org/covid-19-response/">Acumen</a>, <a href="https://www.pyxeraglobal.org/">PYXERA Global</a>, and <a href="https://www.yunussb.com/">Yunus Social Business</a>. We are constantly innovating together through initiatives like the <a href="https://www.weforum.org/covid-alliance-for-social-entrepreneurs">COVID Response Alliance for Social Entrepreneurs</a> to help improve the way we connect you with valuable resources.</p>
  <p>So you’re probably asking yourself, “Why would companies share their resources with you?” It’s a win-win for us, too. As employees connect with topics that matter to them, they also flex their leadership skills, build empathy and cross-cultural understanding, and gain exposure to ‘what’s next’ from leaders like you.</p>
  <p>If you are looking for skilled support, know that you don’t have to go it alone. SAP and MovingWorlds are inviting social innovators ages 18 to 30 to <a href="https://movingworlds.org/partner/sap/acceleration-collective-organizations">join the Acceleration Collective</a>, a new pro bono consulting experience launching in September. Beyond pro bono consulting, the Acceleration Collective includes access to certified business coaching, and bridges access to other SAP partners’ service offerings like <a href="https://acumenacademy.org/">Acumen Academy</a>. Unilever and EY, with the support of the COVID Response Alliance, are also offering resources through their market-leading program <a href="https://www.transform.global/resources/">TRANSFORM</a>.</p>
  <p>Keeping the promise to organizations of all kinds is just another day at the office for many of us. Do your research to see who is willing to help. (Hint: we are!) If you are not sure where to begin, join Social Shifters and SAP at <a href="https://sewfonline.com/events/2021-events/youth-forum/">Social Enterprise World Forum’s Youth Forum on September 27</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="recognizing-your-value-tell-it-like-it-is">3. Recognizing Your Value: Tell It Like It is</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-sap4good-stories">Read more SAP4Good stories</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sap4good">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It is true that with age comes wisdom, but age is not synonymous with the value you bring forward as a leader. Innovation starts with all of us! Last year, I was working on a speaker series, and I approached a young social entrepreneur to speak at the event on SAP’s behalf. Her response was one you should take note of. “I’d gladly speak to your audience, but preparing and speaking for you comes at an opportunity cost for my organization. Will you compensate me for my time?” I was momentarily speechless. She further explained to me, “The moderator is likely getting paid, along with the caterer and the venue. They are all providing a service to you, and so am I.” This young person was respectfully challenging my originally unpaid request. She was right to do so — and you are too!</p>
  <p>My ask was not one of ill intention, rather ignorance, though it’s still no excuse. Throughout a decade working in marketing for SAP, I often asked business leaders to speak on our company’s behalf. The difference? They were all being paid by their organization for their time. Young innovators can be exploited and showcased on both virtual and physical stages globally, but you can change that.</p>
  <p>If you are being asked for something, know your worth and how to leverage it. Be bold and ask for the support you need in return. It may not always be financial compensation, rather it might be access to people or networks or could also include personal skill-building or revenue generation opportunities for your organization.</p>
  <p>Lastly, I want to revisit a topic I touched on briefly above. The Possibilists shared that many of you sacrifice your mental and financial well-being in the pursuit of a better world. While I’m grateful for your efforts, I’m also here to remind you that you will never be able to successfully deliver on your goals if you don’t also prioritize your own well-being. Breathe, find a coach, join a peer support group, pay yourself: whatever it is, invest in your own well-being. You are worth it!</p>
  <h2 id="so-what">So What?</h2>
  <p>Am I asking you to start your own youth movement within the corporate world? No. Am I trying to do that? Perhaps. Do I expect that every organization has the same support structure as SAP to embrace young leaders like you? Probably not. But I hope I’m giving you the courage to connect, learn, and lead with people and organizations like mine.</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Reach out and connect with those who can help you. I promise there are more of us who want to help!</li>
    <li>Learn from the experts and teach them a few things along the way. We don’t know it all, I assure you.</li>
    <li>Speak up! Keep leading the way doing exactly what you are doing. You are creating the change we all need to see in the world, and I can’t wait to see more of you in board rooms around the world.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Thank you for all that you do to keep moving us forward. We owe you one.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Jennifer Beason is global program director of Social Entrepreneurship for Corporate Social Responsibility at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
            <category>news-tag/social-entrepreneurship</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Turning a Passion for Travel into an Obsession with Purpose]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/the-world-within-us-passion-travel-purpose</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/the-world-within-us-passion-travel-purpose</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP employee Anina Monteforte combined her passions to found the social enterprise The World Within Us. Learn her story.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inspiring the Next Generation of Women in STEM at SAP Labs China]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/girls-power-tech-next-generation-women-stem</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/girls-power-tech-next-generation-women-stem</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Last year, the Girls Power Tech program at SAP Labs China brought together 25 passionate young women. Learn more about the project.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bd7f9b31b1114c48be77e06ff4e18c285c18dd80.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bd7f9b31b1114c48be77e06ff4e18c285c18dd80.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1bd7f9b31b1114c48be77e06ff4e18c285c18dd80.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Inspiring the Next Generation of Women in STEM at SAP Labs China" src="./media_1bd7f9b31b1114c48be77e06ff4e18c285c18dd80.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="inspiring-the-next-generation-of-women-in-stem-at-sap-labs-china">Inspiring the Next Generation of Women in STEM at SAP Labs China</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Last year, SAP launched a Girls Power Tech program in China and India to encourage financially disadvantaged young women from remote areas in the world’s most populous countries by making technology accessible.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Its objective was to empower changemakers of today and of tomorrow in the largely marginalized rural populations of China and India, which make up 38% and 68% of the country’s total populations respectively.</p>
  <p>In these largely patriarchal societies, access to technology is scarce and if available is often a luxury enjoyed by men. The program therefore aims to help these women pursue their dreams, make a difference, and find their way to success.</p>
  <p>“At SAP, we believe in not only creating a culture of inclusion within the organization, but also in extending it externally to those who are not as fortunate as us,” SAP CEO <a href="https://www.sap.com/investors/de/governance/executive-board/christian-klein.html">Christian Klein</a> shared. “Through Girls Power Tech, our effort is to go beyond the STEM initiatives in school and colleges and bring world-class technology experiences and career opportunities at the doorstep of these girls. That, in the true sense, would be completing the circle of inclusion.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="in-a-post-pandemic-world-youth-take-center-stage-and-lead">In a Post-Pandemic World, Youth Take Center Stage and Lead</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/07/possibilists-study-youth-lead-post-pandemic-world">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="teamwork-during-a-pandemic">Teamwork During a Pandemic</h2>
  <p>SAP Labs China conducted the program throughout 2020, amid the <a href="/covid-19">global pandemic</a> that crippled economic and social activities around the world. Schools in China were locked down and students were not allowed to do internships onsite.</p>
  <p>Despite this, after four months of screening, 25 young women were selected to join the internship specifically for this program. Some participants came from the far regions of Tibet and Xinjiang, with most of them remotely onboarding with a welcome package and a computer. It was not easy for the students to begin the internship virtually, but their eagerness to learn, an undying spirit, and sheer perseverance made this possible. COVID-19 brought unprecedented challenges, but strong support from sponsors, the recruiting team, and volunteers, helped the program run smoothly.</p>
  <h2 id="young-women-begin-the-change">25 Young Women Begin the Change</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-sap4good-stories">Read more SAP4Good stories</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sap4good">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The internship began in June and a two-day Girls Power Tech bootcamp was held in Shanghai September 11-12. The young changemakers convened in Shanghai to meet their peers and share learnings from the three months of the internship. Most of them had to work remotely due to COVID-19 but were able to complete the assigned tasks with their creativity coming to the fore. After the presentation, the judges awarded “Shining Team” and “Shining Girl” prizes. The sessions also served as an introduction of the powerful concepts of teamwork and collaboration.</p>
  <p>On day two, two panels titled “Search Inside Yourself” and “Gender Equality, Technology Trend, and Career” were held and gave the young women access to new information from the vast experiences of the sharp minds of the panelists. The interactions encouraged them to follow their hearts, believe in themselves, embrace change, and dare to try. Not only a wonderful learning experience, the panels also helped participants identify the areas for improvement, such as communication skills, and offered them new directions for future career development.</p>
  <h2 id="strong-impact-and-feedback">Strong Impact and Feedback</h2>
  <p>Students provided heartfelt farewell quotes on their experience, describing their challenges and many learnings. The 25 girls from 10 provinces and 19 colleges joined 19 R&#x26;D teams in Shanghai, Chengdu, Xi’an, Beijing, and Dalian. They learned product knowledge, programming language, and methodology; participated in product development and testing; and experienced the culture and active community activities across SAP Labs offices. More than 28 volunteers supported this program in different capacities. Seven enablement sessions and a bootcamp were sucessfully delivered. Finally, five of the students received an offer to join SAP full time in 2021.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>SAP is committed to helping the world run better and improve people’s lives, with youth playing a critical role. Join us in sharing good news by tagging stories of inspirational youth or your actions inspiring youth with SAP4Good on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/sap4good/">Instagram</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/sap4good">Twitter</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/sap4good">Facebook</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Youth Are Inspiring Change in Refugee Camps Across Africa]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/african-refugee-camps-youth-inspire-change</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/african-refugee-camps-youth-inspire-change</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Avina has dedicated herself to supporting refugees who arrive in Ghana from Liberia, Sierra Leone, Togo, Ivory Coast, Democratic Republic of the Congo, Libya, and ...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dfd4407e976b465eef32fd914a558935b857855b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dfd4407e976b465eef32fd914a558935b857855b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1dfd4407e976b465eef32fd914a558935b857855b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How Youth Are Inspiring Change in Refugee Camps Across Africa" src="./media_1dfd4407e976b465eef32fd914a558935b857855b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-youth-are-inspiring-change-in-refugee-camps-across-africa">How Youth Are Inspiring Change in Refugee Camps Across Africa</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>There are over 1.2 billion youth in the world today. Among them is one young leader, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/avina-ajit-a153b742/?originalSubdomain=in">Avina Ajith</a>, who at 24 years of age traveled halfway across the globe to help make a difference in the lives of refugees whose plight went largely unnoticed by much of the world.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16d30c0529fd1447dba10eb9f35f18303379136bb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16d30c0529fd1447dba10eb9f35f18303379136bb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16d30c0529fd1447dba10eb9f35f18303379136bb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Avina Ajith" src="./media_16d30c0529fd1447dba10eb9f35f18303379136bb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1250" height="1425">
    </picture>Avina has dedicated herself to supporting refugees who arrive in Ghana from Liberia, Sierra Leone, Togo, Ivory Coast, Democratic Republic of the Congo, Libya, and Sudan, among others. In Ghana alone, more than 16,000 refugees live in camps with little to no geographical or financial access, and of course no social contacts..
  </p>
  <p>In many ways, Avina is like most 24-year-olds around the world. She loves to eat and cook, and is discovering new hobbies to get through the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, including experimenting with baking. She is a cat and plant mother, a love that is reflected throughout her home. The pandemic has affected everyone, and it certainly was not kind to a social startup leader like her.</p>
  <p>Like many of her <a href="/2021/07/possibilists-study-youth-lead-post-pandemic-world">Possibilist peers</a>, Avina works seven days a week, often putting in 12-hour days. She knows that every minute she puts into her organization brings hope to some of the most neglected people in the world. That was her motivation when she launched the <a href="https://refugeeintegration.org/who-we-are/">Refugee Integration Organization</a> (RIO).</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="in-a-post-pandemic-world-youth-take-center-stage-and-lead">In a Post-Pandemic World, Youth Take Center Stage and Lead</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/07/possibilists-study-youth-lead-post-pandemic-world">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="the-journey-of-a-changemaker">The Journey of a Changemaker</h2>
  <p>Avina’s journey began when she secured a highly coveted job as a journalist with Reuters. For two years she focused on reporting about social exclusion of refugees, especially those in Africa. After saving up money, she then quit her job to visit Ghana and learn more about the realities of the place she reported on during her journalist days.</p>
  <p>By her own admission, nothing could have prepared her for the life-altering experiences there that gave her direction and a true sense of purpose.</p>
  <p>During her stay at the Krisan refugee camp in Ghana, she was chaperoned by Abraham Davies, who fled to the refugee camp at age 16 after witnessing terrible ordeals committed against his family. Now a father of three girls, he shares his story to demonstrate how life for him — and thousands of others like him — remains a struggle after leaving their homes and seeking shelter in refugee camps. He explained that there are those who had and would live out their entire lives in such camps.</p>
  <p>Avina relayed stories she witnessed of single fathers who handed over their children to neighboring families to head out and seek work, often never returning. She met women who walked through the desert for days and months, facing terrible atrocities during their journeys to just find a safe place to call home.</p>
  <p>What brings stories like these together are two things. First, that people like Abraham are all seeking safety, and second, they want to earn a living to change their circumstances. Some begin in small ways, like selling homemade food or setting up a poultry farm, but the opportunities for education and workforce inclusion in camps like Krisan are limited.</p>
  <h2 id="bringing-about-change">Bringing About Change</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-sap4good-stories">Read more SAP4Good stories</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sap4good">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Visiting the Krisan refugee camp and getting to know those who lived there inspired Avina, along with co-founder Rya G. Kuewor, to set up RIO in Accra, Ghana. The organization aspires to change the way people look at refugee camps — often as a burden on the country — and instead inspires them to see a microcosm full of potential. Many living within the confines of the camps are skilled workers. They are willing and ready to integrate into any system that will allow them to earn a living wage and establish a future for them and their families. “They just need a little support,” Avina offered. “A chance to earn a better life.”</p>
  <p>RIO is influenced by the idea that the more money circulating in the refugee camp community the better. The more that refugees can offer to the local community, the greater the chances are for integration into regular society. This will ultimately have a positive impact on the larger economy of the country.</p>
  <p>In 2019, RIO successfully provided <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Wxc7CjMFrSc&#x26;t=1s">microfinancing to 23 women</a> at very low interest rates, which was used to build small home-based businesses. The money was unrestricted and spent on very basic things, such as transportation, allowing borrowers the opportunity to buy essentials from the open market and sell it within the camps. The organization provided support to the women throughout the entire process, helping them to build out sustainable businesses processes, such as understanding supply and demand, financial management, and more.</p>
  <p>What began as a small initiative with the 23 women pumped life into the camp. For the first time in 25 years, people engaged in forms of business, even those as small as selling home-cooked food. It provided a way for refugees to contribute to their community, despite it being a non-conducive environment, with major paucity of funds.</p>
  <h2 id="redefining-youth">Redefining (YOU)th</h2>
  <p>Per the Possibilist study, 66% of young changemakers said that they cannot cover their financial needs solely through the work on their initiative alone, meaning they have to look elsewhere for financial compensation and security. Yet they continue to do what they can to make the world a better place.</p>
  <p>Avina pursues the opportunity to improve people’s lives despite the barriers that she — and the women she is trying to help — face. As she continues to work toward making the world a better place, Avina is redefining what many think youth are capable of and inspiring current and future young leaders like herself.</p>
  <p>She also has a message for youth today who do have access to opportunities like higher education: “College may not lead you to where you need to be, but it teaches you things that you can apply in different spaces. Be more cognizant of situations in all kinds of struggles and align yourself with that in some way. With education and the resources youth have today, we’re capable of bringing about great change.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>To learn more about young leaders like Avina, follow SAP4Good on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/sap4good/">Instagram</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/sap4good">Twitter</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/sap4good">Facebook</a>. We also encourage you to share stories of inspirational youth or your actions inspiring youth on social media with the hashtag #SAP4Good.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[De-Coding the Classroom]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/science-on-stage-de-code-the-classroom</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/science-on-stage-de-code-the-classroom</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Supported by SAP, the European Code Leaguge and Science on Stage enable more students to gain digital skills needed for a challenging future.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10ef344527722252b1347bd697f9b1d41b88e24d6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10ef344527722252b1347bd697f9b1d41b88e24d6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10ef344527722252b1347bd697f9b1d41b88e24d6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="De-Coding the Classroom" src="./media_10ef344527722252b1347bd697f9b1d41b88e24d6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="de-coding-the-classroom">De-Coding the Classroom</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Teachers, along with their students, are shaping the future of education with Science on Stage’s European Code League. Meet this year’s inspiring 2021 winner.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the 1940s, Nobel Prize-winning Hungarian biochemist Albert Szent-Gyoergyi wrote: “The future will be like the schools are today.” In 2021, these words still ring true, even more so for the winners of the European Code League competition, Dr. Corina Toma and Mihaela Giurgea, along with their students from Tiberiu Popoviciu High School of Computer Science in Romania. Second and third place went to teams from Turkey and Greece.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="in-a-post-pandemic-world-youth-take-center-stage-and-lead">In a Post-Pandemic World, Youth Take Center Stage and Lead</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/07/possibilists-study-youth-lead-post-pandemic-world">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="change-is-the-only-constant-but-changemakers-are-ever-changing">Change Is the Only Constant, but Changemakers Are Ever Changing</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-sap4good-stories">Read more SAP4Good stories</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sap4good">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> has been quite a revelation in this aspect, with unexpected and seemingly limitless opportunities presenting themselves and youth grabbing them with both hands.</p>
  <p>According to a report by the World Economic Forum, around 65% of children who start primary school today will work in professions that do not even exist yet: their future lies in the hands of educators. To date, Science on Stage reaches about 100,000 teachers and teacher trainers in over 30 countries, providing a necessary network to exchange ideas and to scale them across Europe. And with 79% of participating teachers implementing the teaching ideas they’ve seen at Science on Stage festivals over the years, European Code League has proven that it’s possible for teachers and students to work together — even in the midst of a pandemic — to create inspiring, real-world science, technology, engineering, and mathematics (STEM) projects.</p>
  <p>Organized by Science on Stage with the support of the SAP Corporate Social Responsibility (SAP CSR) team in Middle Eastern Europe, the European Code League is a competition to which teacher-student teams with innovative coding projects can apply. It was launched in 2020 as a follow up to Science on Stage’s <a href="https://www.science-on-stage.eu/project/coding-stem-education">successful coding project for STEM education</a>.</p>
  <p>“Science on Stage gave me the opportunity to find new ways to motivate my students to learn physics using ICT,” says Dr. Toma, who became a teacher after 10 years working as a physicist. “Physics is everywhere and happens at any time. In the classroom, I am at home. I like to talk with my students and explain all kinds of topics.”</p>
  <p>Science on Stage Europe is a network for STEM teachers focusing on the exchange of best practice teaching ideas. The ultimate goal is to improve STEM teaching by supporting educators in their professional development and growth.</p>
  <p>“Teachers are often the ideas, the starting point. Students who finish high school do not know what their role in the world will be,” Dr Toma adds. “These projects show how important it is to code, and also to learn STEM subjects like mathematics, physics, chemistry, and biology.”</p>
  <p>CaeliBox, the winning coding project, used sensors to measure different air parameters such as concentration of CO2, humidity, pressure, temperature, noise, and other noxious substances in the studennts’ town. The data was transferred to a server so the students could access and work with it at any time.</p>
  <p>“My town in Romania used to be small but now it is very big. As a result, the air is polluted because we have so many cars. CaeliBox is a useful device for STEM education and our students were happy to combine coding with physics and technology,” explains Dr. Toma, who adds that she faced many challenges trying to complete the project, from broken sensors to realizing they needed more space and swapping out their Arduino Uno for an Arduino Mega.</p>
  <p>For Dr. Toma, Science on Stage is far more than a networking opportunity for teachers, it’s a community of like-minded educators: “At first, I saw that the education in Romania is very different from other countries, but then I realized that as teachers we have the same goals and can make the same activities. Science on Stage is a community to challenge our ideas and to understand that we are in the same place. SAP can be very proud for supporting STEM teaching training in Europe.”</p>
  <p>There is no one way to make the world a better place. By helping discover and promote innovative teaching concepts among Europe’s science teachers, Science on Stage and the European Code League enable more students to gain the digital skills they need for a challenging future and encourage them to consider a career in science, ICT or engineering to help the positively change the world.</p>
  <p>In a world shaped increasingly by technology and digitalization, teachers make the difference and the youth of today have so many more opportunities to learn and be the change.</p>
  <p>The 12th European Science on Stage festival takes place March 24-27, 2022, in Prague, Czech Republic. Stay tuned to see amazing youth in action, redefining how a career in science, ICT, or engineering can help make a positive change in the world.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>SAP is committed to helping the world run better and improve people’s lives, with youth playing a critical role. Join us in sharing good news by tagging your stories of inspirational youth or your actions inspiring youth with @SAP4Good on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/sap4good/">Instagram</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/sap4good">Twitter</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/sap4good">Facebook</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Empowering Equity in Education with Virtual Reality and Immersive Learning]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/skill-immersion-lab-education-equity</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/skill-immersion-lab-education-equity</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To support equity in education, SAP and JFFLabs have rolled out a Skill Immersion Lab program with high school-aged learners at three sites.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1af0df9b9b6da496f33f3d94554e2892a50ad3aaf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1af0df9b9b6da496f33f3d94554e2892a50ad3aaf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1af0df9b9b6da496f33f3d94554e2892a50ad3aaf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Empowering Equity in Education with Virtual Reality and Immersive Learning" src="./media_1af0df9b9b6da496f33f3d94554e2892a50ad3aaf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="empowering-equity-in-education-with-virtual-reality-and-immersive-learning">Empowering Equity in Education with Virtual Reality and Immersive Learning</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> has dramatically disrupted traditional learning. While that disruption has widened gaps in access to education that existed along racial, ethnic, and socioeconomic lines, it has also accelerated advances in innovation that could help close those gaps.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>More than a year after schools and training providers pivoted to remote learning, two trends have emerged. First, finding innovative ways to teach and learn is here to stay. Second, many educators who have gained a new appreciation for how technology can help students learn will forever be on the lookout for technical tools that support unique approaches to education. These tools will create pathways to new educational and career opportunities with students from under-resourced communities.</p>
  <p>JFFLabs is the <a href="http://www.jff.org/labs">innovative unit of JFF</a>, a national nonprofit that drives transformation in the American workforce and education systems. Kristina Francis, executive director of JFFLabs, believes that immersive learning currently represents one of the most promising options for changing traditional approaches to education and closing achievement gaps.</p>
  <p>Together, JFFLabs and SAP are piloting an effort to introduce immersive learning to classrooms across the country.</p>
  <p>“This time in history requires expanded access and new entry points for learning, education experiences, and innovation,” Francis said. “It requires corporations and school districts to partner to put resources and technology in the hands of our most marginalized and disadvantaged learners and, frankly, future leaders and innovators.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="in-a-post-pandemic-world-youth-take-center-stage-and-lead">In a Post-Pandemic World, Youth Take Center Stage and Lead</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/07/possibilists-study-youth-lead-post-pandemic-world">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="a-need-for-new-entry-points">A Need for “New Entry Points”</h2>
  <p>The program is called the Skill Immersion Lab. SAP and JFFLabs have rolled it out at three sites working with high school-aged learners: a high school in Queens, New York; a community center in St. Paul, Minnesota; and a workforce development center serving a rural area of Louisiana, which offers instruction to young people ages 16-24 who are unemployed and not in school.</p>
  <p>The importance of finding new ways to engage and motivate students became clear during the pandemic. A June 2020 <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/industries/public-and-social-sector/our-insights/covid-19-and-student-learning-in-the-united-states-the-hurt-could-last-a-lifetime">McKinsey report</a>, citing data from Curriculum Associates, revealed that student engagement rates at schools that serve low-income populations lagged behind those serving high-income students. The data suggested that 60% of students from low-income families were regularly logging on to online instruction, compared to 90% of high-income students.</p>
  <p>Students in the Skill Immersion Lab program are engaging in immersive experiences using desktop and virtual reality (VR) platforms to strengthen human skills, also called employability or “soft” skills, such as effective communication and leadership capabilities. The four-to-six-week courses feature curriculum from Talespin, a developer of a VR platform that learners can use to take part in interactive role-playing exercises, allowing them to practice interpersonal skills in virtual settings.</p>
  <p>Research has shown that immersive technology is a powerful educational tool. According to <a href="https://www.pwc.com/us/en/services/consulting/technology/emerging-technology/vr-study-2020.html#:~:text=In%20our%20study%2C%20VR%2Dtrained,training%20and%20have%20better%20outcomes.">PwC</a>, people who are taught using virtual reality tech are 3.75 times more emotionally connected to the content, four times more focused than their e-learning peers, and 275% more confident about applying the skills they learn after training. It’s also possible to train people more quickly and cost-effectively using VR.</p>
  <p>Educators at the Skill Immersion Lab sites, who have been working with learners in their communities for years, say they welcome the opportunity to offer immersive learning experiences with students.</p>
  <p>“A gap that we notice as mentors is the need for students to apply the skills they learn from seminar sessions into a real-world setting,” said a career readiness advisor at the Queens site. “Students learn a lot about the ‘what’ to communicate in a professional environment, but getting students to learn the ‘how’ and ‘why’ as they maneuver through multilevel relationships in the workplace is crucial to ensuring that they are prepared for the many types of communication scenarios they would experience in the workforce. Allowing students to engage in virtual reality experiences early on gives them a head start into building awareness through verbal and non-verbal communication, not only for themselves but also for others.”</p>
  <p>The Skill Immersion Lab is also a critical opportunity to listen to learners who bring important lessons and skills from past experiences. Their feedback and engagement will push the program to be more relevant and effective for their own education and career goals.</p>
  <h2 id="an-effective-tool-for-tough-topics">An Effective Tool for Tough Topics</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-student-and-graduate-programs-at-sap">Learn more about student and graduate programs at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/students-graduates.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“It’s all about giving learners access to technology that is proven to be an effective teaching tool for tough topics,” says Katie Booth, who leads the SAP Corporate Social Responsibility team in North America. “We want to give them the language to think about things differently — and understand that they have a place within any environment, whether it’s a corporate setting or a community one. These deep communication skills will help them succeed.”</p>
  <p>The Skill Immersion Lab holds significant promise, particularly with young learners located outside of wealthy, suburban, or urban areas. Young people are receiving early access to some of the most innovative and effective immersive learning tools on the market, and they’re using those tools to advance their communication skills and further the pursuit of their education and career goals.</p>
  <p>As chief customer innovation officer for SAP North America, I’ve seen firsthand how innovative technology can help transform our customers’ businesses. The potential impact of this initiative is tremendous. Not only can it help educators build a deeper understanding of how new technology can empower young people, it can teach young learners some of the most important skills they need to succeed in life — and not just young learners in well-to-do communities, but any student, anywhere in the country.</p>
  <p>It’s possible. As one of the nation’s first programs focused squarely on immersive learning experiences for this age group, the Skill Immersion Lab is paving the way.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Stephanie Nashawaty is chief customer innovation officer at SAP North America.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/05/25/empowering-equity-in-education-with-virtual-reality-and-immersive-learning/">This article originally appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Skilling Up Young Disruptors, Dreamers, and Doers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/world-youth-skills-day-2021-disruptors-dreamers-doers</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/world-youth-skills-day-2021-disruptors-dreamers-doers</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[World Youth Skills Day 2021 focuses on the creativity and resilience of youth throughout the pandemic. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In a Post-Pandemic World, Youth Take Center Stage and Lead]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/possibilists-study-youth-lead-post-pandemic-world</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/possibilists-study-youth-lead-post-pandemic-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is proud to support the Possibilists, youth working to solve the issues of the world and striving to maximize their agency and potential.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Teaming Up to Make Data Science a Priority]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/data-science-for-everyone-coalition-sap-49ers</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/data-science-for-everyone-coalition-sap-49ers</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A Data Science For Everyone panel covered how education strengthens communities and workforces, and how SAP and the 49ers are making change.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18eaa0ffb768dab870dc015fb7a7a513d8799b857.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18eaa0ffb768dab870dc015fb7a7a513d8799b857.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18eaa0ffb768dab870dc015fb7a7a513d8799b857.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Teaming Up to Make Data Science a Priority" src="./media_18eaa0ffb768dab870dc015fb7a7a513d8799b857.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="teaming-up-to-make-data-science-a-priority">Teaming Up to Make Data Science a Priority</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-how-sap-university-alliances-is-building-the-talent-of-the-future">Learn how SAP University Alliances is building the talent of the future</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/next-gen-innovation-platform/university-alliances.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The math curriculum taught to today’s high school students is out of sync with the current landscape and our everyday use of technology. A <a href="https://freakonomics.com/podcast/math-curriculum/">podcast by <em>Freakonomics</em> author Steven Levitt</a> discusses the current “geometry sandwich” of Algebra I/Geometry/Algebra II, which was designed to prepare students for the Space Race of the 1950s, not where we are today.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Data Science for Everyone found that 90% of the world’s data was created in the last two years. However, only 11% of high school students take a statistics course. Data science jobs have seen a 650% growth since 2012 and reports show that seven of 10 careers with the fastest growth are data-centric. In order to prepare students for the future, a change needs to be made with their relationship with data.</p>
  <p>Data Science for Everyone is a <a href="https://www.datascience4everyone.org/about">national movement for advancing data literacy in the U.S.</a> among students, comprised of a coalition of more than 160 educators, policymakers, and industry leaders. Earlier this year, Data Science for Everyone submitted a letter to the Biden administration urging to make data literacy a national priority. They have created actionable steps and gathered resources for educators to implement into their curriculum.</p>
  <p>To date, states including California, Oregon, and Ohio are working to update their current curriculum to meet the growing demand. Additionally, UCLA’s Introduction to Data Science course is taught in 26 school districts nationwide. This is still not enough; additional advocacy is needed to help ensure that the issue of data literacy remains part of the conversation surrounding education.</p>
  <p>Last month, Data Science for Everyone held a virtual Commitments Campaign event to bring together all stakeholders who are working to make a change in data literacy. The event garnered 272 commitments from companies, education leaders, and policymakers that impact more than 3 million students, 25,000 teachers, and 500 school districts.</p>
  <p>Dr. Karina Edmonds, senior vice president and head of Academies and <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/next-gen-innovation-platform/university-alliances.html">SAP University Alliances</a> for SAP, spoke to how data science education strengthens our communities and workforce: “We absolutely have to get everyone at the table as the growth of data science jobs continues to skyrocket. We can’t afford to leave a great part of our society behind.”</p>
  <p>The <a href="https://www.datascience4everyone.org/commitments-event-2021?wix-vod-video-id=5f4d3c8871784f06a4d86981aab2c1ac&#x26;wix-vod-comp-id=comp-kqjzhw47">49ers and SAP have committed to offer rich educational data science resources</a> for K-12 students over the next year. SAP and the 49ers Foundation plan to launch a new data science course by next year that will include data modules focused on using football data to make data science more relevant to students. The two phased program will be comprised of virtual lessons for middle school students, along with a high school curriculum and field trips for grades 9-12.</p>
  <p>We can each play a role with bringing this movement to life. Individuals can make their own personal commitment to help ensure that students have access to data literacy skills. Simple things like the following:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Parents and adults must encourage children’s curiosity around data science and math. Projecting negative past experiences with math and science can influence children’s relationship with data science in the future. Remove negative self-talk — things like “I hate math” or “I’m not good with numbers” — that are only hurting the curiosity we want youth to have.</li>
    <li>Contact decision-makers and initiate conversations in your community to find support for modern standards that reflect the data-centric world. This can include contacting the Department of Education, state legislators, or the local school board and district superintendent. These policymakers influence curriculum, course offerings, and teachers’ professional development, so engaging these leaders and getting them excited about data science can unlock the potential of new courses and better trained teachers.</li>
    <li>Get personally involved as a volunteer. Not all programs rely on volunteer support, but there is great importance in students hearing from experts in the topic being discussed. The SAP Corporate Social Responsibility team has partners across North America that can host employees for speaking opportunities. Check out organizations like <a href="https://www.csforallteachers.org/">Computer Science for All Teachers</a> and <a href="https://www.techgirlz.org/volunteer/">Tech Girlz</a>.</li>
  </ul>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/education</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>