<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/external-workforce-management/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Supply Chain and External Workforce Innovations Reduce Organizational Inefficiencies]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/supply-chain-external-workforce-innovations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/supply-chain-external-workforce-innovations</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP Sapphire, we introduced supply chain and external workforce innovations to help reduce inefficiency and improve decision-making.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ardent Partners Positions SAP Fieldglass as a Market Leader for Vendor Management Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/ardent-partners-sap-fieldglass-vms-market-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/ardent-partners-sap-fieldglass-vms-market-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Ardent Partners positioned SAP Fieldglass as a Market Leader for vendor management systems (VMS). Read to learn more about the recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Standard Chartered Gains Agility with Total Workforce Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/standard-chartered-total-workforce-solution</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/standard-chartered-total-workforce-solution</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Standard Chartered uses total workforce management with SAP SuccessFactors and SAP Fieldglass for one view of permanent and external workers.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/banking</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Talent Strategies Procurement Leaders Can Employ to Lead Through the Polycrisis]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/talent-strategies-procurement-polycrisis</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/talent-strategies-procurement-polycrisis</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read about three key actions procurement leaders can take to address talent strategies in turbulent times, like a polycrisis.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Fieldglass: Cloud Innovation for Commercial Regulated Industries]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sap-fieldglass-sap-ns2-cloud-innovation-commercial-regulated-industries</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sap-fieldglass-sap-ns2-cloud-innovation-commercial-regulated-industries</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP Fieldglass at SAP NS2, government agencies and highly regulated industries in the U.S. can adopt market-leading cloud applications.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ns2</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[To Improve Business Results, Insurers Must Modernize External Workforce Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/insurers-modernize-external-workforce-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/insurers-modernize-external-workforce-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The external workforce is a key lever in enabling business performance. Learn why insurers must prioritize external workforce management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/contingent-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>industry/insurance</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-insurance</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[If The Pandemic Was Their Wake-Up Call, This Is How Employers Are Reacting]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/pandemic-wake-up-call-workforce-resiliency</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/pandemic-wake-up-call-workforce-resiliency</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Organizations are devising new strategies to increase workforce resiliency in the wake of the pandemic and the Great Resignation. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/contingent-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Once-in-a-Generation Opportunity for Workforce Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/once-in-a-generation-opportunity-workforce-innovation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/once-in-a-generation-opportunity-workforce-innovation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A new report by Harvard Business Review Analytic Services sponsored by SAP explores workforce planning in a time of labor shortages.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/contingent-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Great Adaptation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/great-adaptation-not-resignation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/great-adaptation-not-resignation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To overcome the challenges posed by the Great Resignation, business are tapping into the Great Adaptation and reimagining their workforces.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Will the Disruption Ever End? 2022 Predictions for Intelligent Spend Management and Business Network]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/2022-predictions-intelligent-spend-management-business-network</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/2022-predictions-intelligent-spend-management-business-network</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For 2022 predictions in the intelligent spend management and business network space, get perspectiiv from SAP leaders on what to watch for.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14ceca97504cb15542a527fbb238f048af3f48195.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14ceca97504cb15542a527fbb238f048af3f48195.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14ceca97504cb15542a527fbb238f048af3f48195.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Will the Disruption Ever End? 2022 Predictions for Intelligent Spend Management and Business Network" src="./media_14ceca97504cb15542a527fbb238f048af3f48195.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="will-the-disruption-ever-end-2022-predictions-for-intelligent-spend-management-and-business-network">Will the Disruption Ever End? 2022 Predictions for Intelligent Spend Management and Business Network</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="automate-spending-processes-and-actively-manage-more-spend-for-better-control-greater-value-and-more-savings">Automate spending processes and actively manage more spend for better control, greater value, and more savings</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As eventful as 2020 was, 2021 has certainly been full of surprises too. This time last year we were anxiously awaiting the vaccine rollout and the return to life as we knew it before COVID-19.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Fast-forward to today and we are still witnessing the ongoing effect of the pandemic wreaking havoc worldwide with widespread supply chain disruption, the “Great Resignation,” and variants continuing to cause uncertainty.</p>
  <p>In 2020 we saw panic buying leading to toilet paper shortages; this year we’re grappling with the impact of the microchip shortage in the automotive and high tech industries. And for those of us who didn’t start holiday shopping before Halloween, we may not see our gifts arrive until the new year. On top of this, every industry from restaurants and retail to manufacturing and logistics are struggling to fill vacant jobs to meet growing business demand as COVID-19 restrictions continue to evolve.</p>
  <p>On the bright side, companies are continuing to rebound and are looking for solutions to manage their ongoing sourcing, supply chain and labor challenges. We asked our global leaders for their perspective on what to watch for in 2022. Here’s what they had to say.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>“The impact of the pandemic-driven lockdowns underscores how the global economy is a networked economy. Companies know that no business does business alone — success depends not only on one company’s ability to deliver, but the abilities of all companies in its entire supply chain. To adapt to ever-changing business challenges, procurement and supply chain leaders will increasingly look to cloud-based and network-aware solutions to deliver the innovation they need to continually align their spend strategy to their business strategy.”</p>
        <p><em><strong>–</strong> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/john-wookey-786360b/">John Wookey</a>, president, Intelligent Spend and Business Network, SAP</em></p>
        <p>“Clogged cargo ports, backlogged rail yards, microchip and gas shortages: 18 months later and we are still feeling the economic aftershocks of the disruption brought on by COVID-19. We had hoped that business would get back to ‘normal’ in 2021. As we enter a new year, we realize that ‘disruption is the new normal’ and resilience is a top priority. In 2022, companies need to formalize resilience, building sustainable supply chain execution that supports business growth. Despite the volatility, organizations must take a step back and look at spend holistically. An integrated spend management approach spanning procurement, external workforce and travel and expense management, will provide customers with the visibility and agility they need to adapt to changes in their markets while continuing to drive their business objectives.”</p>
        <p><em><strong>–</strong> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/etoshathurman/">Etosha Thurman</a>, chief marketing and solutions officer,</em><br><em>Intelligent Spend and Business Network, SAP</em></p>
        <p>“It has been nearly two years since the pandemic began wreaking havoc on the world’s businesses, exposing the fragility of linear supply chains and the need for a more networked economy. During this time, many businesses have changed their view of procurement from cost watchdog to that of a strategic enabler. As we enter 2022, many procurement leaders are tasked with aligning every spend decision to their overall corporate strategies. To best deliver on this responsibility, these professionals will need an integrated view of total spend across the enterprise and deep into their supply chain. This level of visibility will enable the necessary information sharing and collaboration needed to contribute to stronger business benefits, including better inventory management, more predictable lead times, alternative sources of supply, stronger supplier compliance, and, of course, continued cost savings.”</p>
        <p><em><strong>–</strong> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/jeffcollier/">Jeff Collier</a>, chief revenue officer, Intelligent Spend and Business Network, SAP</em></p>
        <p>“As global markets continue to face unprecedented labor shortages across industries, businesses will see an increased need to master external workforce management and maximize talent utilization. Tapping into contingent workers and service providers will continue to gain momentum beyond the pandemic as businesses are realizing the benefits: improved productivity, agility and resilience, reduced costs, increased access to quality talent, and flexibility. With an estimated 70% of executives anticipating they will hire more temporary workers and freelancers over the next two years, external workforce will remain a top priority across organizations. With this comes the need for leaders to have complete visibility into their usage of external workforce to make more calculated, timely decisions about who is doing the work, at what cost, where, and for how long. Digitalizing and automating external workforce management processes and improving visibility will help companies reduce inefficiencies and gain the most value out of its flexible resources.”</p>
        <p><em><strong>–</strong> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/vishbaliga/">Vish Baliga</a>, chief technology officer, <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/">SAP Fieldglass Solutions</a>, SAP</em></p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th colspan="2">Promo</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <h3 id="what-can-sap-business-network-do-for-your-business">What can SAP Business Network do for your business?</h3>
              </td>
              <td><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">Learn more</a></strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>“This has been the year of supply chain disruption. People who have never heard the term supply chain before are now talking about it as everyone is experiencing stock shortages in stores and lack of availability of the holiday gifts we had planned to buy. Recent events like COVID-19 and Brexit have shown that traditional, linear, fragmented supply chains no longer work, and no business can do business alone. Companies will look to move beyond enterprise-centric systems toward those that are designed for cross-company transparency and collaboration. A digital network approach can transform fragmented supply chains into unified, collaborative, intelligent networks for supply, logistics, asset management, and service. With tighter collaboration between trading partners on a trusted network, companies can better anticipate shifts in supply and demand, deepening their competitive edge in the face of profound disruption.”</p>
        <p><em><strong>–</strong> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/paigeweicox/">Paige Cox</a>, senior vice president and head of Business Network, SAP</em></p>
        <p>“If 2021 has taught us anything, it is that even the best of predictions failed to anticipate some of the challenges the world has seen. What did occur though was that procurement organizations moved away from simply managing and optimizing processes to becoming pivotal in solving critical business problems. In 2022 procurement professionals should be bold in embracing this mandate and propose solutions that help companies navigate troubled, uncertain waters. Creative procurement solutions can address some of the biggest challenges businesses continue to face today: managing supply shortages, rethinking a globalized supply chain, leaning on a vibrant external workforce in the face of the ‘Great Resignation,’ and focusing on working capital at a time of increasing global inflation. Let’s be bold and re-define traditional paradigms to tackle these challenges.”</p>
        <p><em><strong>–</strong> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/bfarooq/">Baber Farooq</a>, head of Market and Solution Strategy, Procurement Solutions, SAP</em></p>
        <p>“By now, it’s fair to assume that all the big gains to make the internal combustion engine more efficient have already taken place. There will always be a place for it in our world, but to make impactful change at this point a bigger pivot is needed, for example, to electric vehicles. I think about automated expense reporting in a similar way. Technology providers can spend increasing amounts of resources to make incremental gains, but a big pivot is needed to usher in the next wave of efficiency and innovation. That big pivot is a shift to settlement. Creating an expense report is never the ultimate goal; the goal is to settle payments for employee-initiated spend. While the expense report isn’t going away any time soon, more innovation will lead to bigger improvements in capturing, processing, and verifying expenses, driven by increasingly sophisticated artificial intelligence. With this pivot, we will shrink and evaporate expense reports, with a subset of expenses moving to automated settlement and skipping the traditional expense report process entirely.”</p>
        <p><em><strong>–</strong> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/michael-koetting-3463315/">Mike Koetting</a>, senior vice president and SAP Concur solution area leader, SAP</em>(<a href="https://www.concur.com/newsroom/article/sap-concur-2022-predictions">Read more 2022 predictions from SAP Concur</a>)</p>
        <p>“Sustainability and social responsibility are some of the most pressing issues we’re dealing with today. The recent <a href="https://ukcop26.org/">UN Climate Change Conference of the Parties</a> (<a href="/topics/cop26">COP26</a>) brought representatives from nearly 200 countries together in the fight against climate change. Individuals and businesses alike must heed the urgent call to make drastic changes to help the environment and to stick to ethical principles. I believe that procurement can play an essential role in leading the charge to create a long-term strategy that embeds sustainable and ethical factors in the process from start to finish. While new and emerging solutions are on the horizon to enable these long-term plans, leaders will look to their digital procurement solutions in use today to support environmental, social, and governance goals like reducing carbon emissions or banning child labor. Over the next few years, we’ll see further investment in core procurement technology to help businesses achieve more than just operational efficiencies and cost savings, but also to drive risk mitigation and increased visibility into the supply base and supply chain processes to achieve ESG goals.”</p>
        <p><em><strong>–</strong> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/salvatore-lombardo-a579662/">Salvatore Lombardo</a>, senior vice president and chief product officer,</em><br><em>Procurement Solutions, SAP</em></p>
        <p>“Listening to understand customers’ business operations, goals, and expectations is the foundation to building a relationship as a trusted advisor. We have moved well beyond traditional inside-out views of a customer’s situation and transactional sales cycles toward outcome-focused experiences. With the lingering disruption and chaos caused by the pandemic, siloed approaches of solving problems reactively are no longer good enough. Especially as companies are embracing the cloud to increase innovation and propel their digital transformation journeys. Next year we will continue to see many more instances of agile customer-led engagements across channels. These will connect all interactions into an end-to-end solution that addresses customers’ holistic spending needs from procurement to managing an external workforce to capturing travel and expense.”</p>
        <hr>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/sws1210/">Steve Seide</a>, Global Procurement Success partner, SAP</em></p>
        <p>To learn more about our 2022 predictions, follow SAP Ariba on Linkedin and join our upcoming Linkedin Live with Etosha Thurman and John Wookey along with Hackett Group Analyst Kurt Albertson on Wednesday, December 15, at 11:00 am ET. <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/events/procurementtrends-lookingbackat6871932870290661376/">Sign up here</a>.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[External Workforce Is Key for Customer Satisfaction in Times of Disruption]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/external-workforce-key-for-customer-satisfaction-times-of-disruption</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/external-workforce-key-for-customer-satisfaction-times-of-disruption</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The external workforce has proved to be crucial to enabling businesses to take steps toward recovery during COVID-19. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Companies Choose SAP to Help with Supply and Demand Volatility]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/companies-choose-sap-to-help-with-supply-and-demand-volatility</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/companies-choose-sap-to-help-with-supply-and-demand-volatility</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To help with supply and demand volatility, hundreds of companies worldwide have chosen SAP Ariba and SAP Fieldglass in Q3 2021.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d415aacc3ac94c9eeb05f9f24e47bd885f1ef09a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d415aacc3ac94c9eeb05f9f24e47bd885f1ef09a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d415aacc3ac94c9eeb05f9f24e47bd885f1ef09a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Companies Choose SAP to Help with Supply and Demand Volatility" src="./media_1d415aacc3ac94c9eeb05f9f24e47bd885f1ef09a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="companies-choose-sap-to-help-with-supply-and-demand-volatility">Companies Choose SAP to Help with Supply and Demand Volatility</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-ariba-digitalize-and-simplify-all-your-processes-end-to-end">SAP Ariba: Digitalize and simplify all your processes end-to-end</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://www.ariba.com/?campaigncode=CRM-IS20-PRL-OOCWA01">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that Palace Resorts and Siemens Energy are among the hundreds of companies worldwide to have chosen <a href="http://www.ariba.com/?campaigncode=CRM-IS20-PRL-OOCWA01">SAP Ariba</a> and <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/?campaigncode=CRM-IS20-PRL-OOCWF02">SAP Fieldglass</a> solutions in the third quarter to help digitalize procurement and external workforce management.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Hundreds more companies also renewed licenses and went live with solutions from SAP to optimize spend management.</p>
  <p>SAP maintains the largest share of the procurement applications software market, according to the recently published “<a href="https://www.ariba.com/resources/library/library-pages/worldwide-procurement-applications-software-market-shares-2020">IDC Worldwide Procurement Applications Software Market Shares, 2020: Digital Became the New Normal</a>” report.* IDC estimates that <strong>SAP’s market share has grown to 32.8%,</strong> maintaining its position of having the largest share of the market — more than the next 11 vendors combined.</p>
  <p>IDC Vice President of Enterprise Applications and Digital Commerce Mickey North Rizza said, “SAP clients have told us collectively that they have chosen SAP Ariba solutions for the extensive benchmarking across industries and spend categories and integration with SAP S/4HANA. They also love the guided buying experience in the SAP Ariba solutions. Many others have told us SAP Fieldglass solutions have helped improve their services procurement processes for engagement with consulting firms, marketing agencies, field services, maintenance and business process outsourcing.” According to the report, IDC estimates that the <a href="https://www.ariba.com/solutions/solutions-overview/procurement">procurement software</a> market has grown 5.4% to $6.2 billion in 2020 alone.</p>
  <p>Ongoing shifts and imbalances in supply and demand have led companies across geographies and industries to recognize how critical digitalizing operations is to procuring goods and services and keeping the global economy running.</p>
  <p>“Right now, business leaders are recognizing the power of procurement and flexible workforces to help them achieve more than just cost savings,” said Etosha Thurman, Chief Marketing and Solutions Officer, Intelligent Spend and Business Network, SAP. “We believe our market leadership is one of the reasons why they are turning to SAP to help increase agility and reduce risk in a world where supply and demand is volatile, disruption is expected and risk in various forms is more pervasive than ever before.”</p>
  <p>Highlights from the third quarter include:</p>
  <p><strong>Grupo KUO</strong>, a Mexican industrial conglomerate, selected SAP Fieldglass solutions for contingent workforce management. By digitalizing and automating its processes for sourcing, hiring and managing external talent, the company aims to comply with Mexico’s recent labor outsourcing regulation while also improving the experience for its workers and talent suppliers.</p>
  <p><strong>Mubadala Investment Company</strong>, a global investment group based in the United Arab Emirates and owner of the <strong>Acelen</strong> oil refinery in Brazil, has chosen SAP to support its growth strategy. Acelen will adopt the RISE with SAP offering, combining SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition, and the SAP Analytics solution to unify operations under one robust platform. In addition, cloud-based SAP Ariba, SAP Concur, SAP Fieldglass and SAP SuccessFactors solutions will help transform spend management and total workforce management so Acelen can maximize savings and deliver a better human experience for all workers.</p>
  <p>The <strong>Palace Resorts</strong> hotel chain in Mexico has selected RISE with SAP to support its IT strategy of digitalizing business processes in the cloud. The hospitality group also chose SAP Ariba solutions to help transform its procurement function and improve the buying experience and collaboration with its suppliers.</p>
  <p><strong>Petrobras</strong>, the Brazilian energy company, is accelerating its digital transformation with SAP. Taking a phased approach following the adoption of SAP S/4HANA, this quarter the company went live with SAP Ariba solutions for guided buying and catalogs to help improve its procurement and supply chain processes and provide a better user experience for employees and suppliers.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-fieldglass-solutions-for-the-modern-external-workforce">SAP Fieldglass: Solutions for the Modern External Workforce</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/?campaigncode=CRM-IS20-PRL-OOCWF02">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Siemens Energy AG</strong>, based in Munich, Germany, is focused on shaping the energy transition worldwide to help protect the climate while meeting growing energy demand with its strong and resilient portfolio. It selected SAP Ariba solutions to help improve, harmonize and automate procurement operations across the organization.</p>
  <p><strong>Waters Corporation</strong>, the Massachusetts-based analytical laboratory instrument and software company, selected SAP Ariba solutions — after a highly competitive evaluation and selection process — to help digitally transform its supply chain and improve its procurement operations with standardized and automated processes. Connecting to a digital network and aligning stakeholders and trading partners to a common plan will help Waters gain real-time visibility to anticipate and respond to changes in demand more quickly and orchestrate its multitier supply chain more effectively, with the goal of improving inventory management, customer service and on-time shipments.</p>
  <p><strong>Zijin Mining</strong> is one of China‘s largest gold mining companies. To support its rapid global expansion, the company selected SAP Ariba solutions to help improve the transparency, intelligence and compliance of its procurement system, strengthen group governance, and meet different procurement requirements around the world.</p>
  <p>For more information, visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong></p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as a sustainable intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into sustainable intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want — without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong> Kelly Sheldon Murray, +1 (978) 708-6821, <a href="mailto:kelly.murray@sap.com">kelly.murray@sap.com</a><u>,</u> ET<br>Geraldine Lim, +1 (415) 418-0945, <a href="mailto:geraldine.lim@sap.com">geraldine.lim@sap.com</a>, PT<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p><em>*“IDC Worldwide Procurement Applications Software Market Shares, 2020: Digital Became the New Normal” report (Doc # US47984421, August 2021).</em><br>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="http://www.sap.com/corporate-en/legal/copyright/index.epx#trademark">http://www.sap.com/corporate-en/legal/copyright/index.epx#trademark</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/contingent-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Australia’s Asset-Intensive Industries Save Millions Managing the External Workforce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/australia-asset-intensive-industries-external-workforce</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/australia-asset-intensive-industries-external-workforce</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Organizations in asset-intensive industries can integrate data to holistically manage contingent workers for safety and savings. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
            <category>product/sap-erp</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Helps Red Hat Advance Contingent Workforce Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/sap-red-hat-contingent-workforce-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/sap-red-hat-contingent-workforce-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Red Hat has streamlined and consolidated its external workforce program with the help of SAP Fieldglass Contingent Workforce Management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/contingent-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-news</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Companies Continue to Digitalize Spend Management with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/companies-digitalize-spend-management-with-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/companies-digitalize-spend-management-with-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Ariba and SAP Fieldglass solutions help companies across industries digitalize spend management and external workforce management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18336490c7900d7c1abeb97d7ba5022908af43cf5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18336490c7900d7c1abeb97d7ba5022908af43cf5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18336490c7900d7c1abeb97d7ba5022908af43cf5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Companies Continue to Digitalize Spend Management with SAP" src="./media_18336490c7900d7c1abeb97d7ba5022908af43cf5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="companies-continue-to-digitalize-spend-management-with-sap">Companies Continue to Digitalize Spend Management with SAP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="achieve-digital-transformation-from-source-to-pay-with-sap-ariba-solutions">Achieve digital transformation from source to pay with SAP Ariba solutions</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.ariba.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that Molson Coors Beverage Co. and the Florida Department of Management Services are among the hundreds of companies across industries and geographies in the second quarter to have chosen <a href="http://www.ariba.com/?campaigncode=CRM-IS20-PRL-OOCWA01">SAP Ariba</a> and <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/?campaigncode=CRM-IS20-PRL-OOCWF02">SAP Fieldglass</a> solutions to digitalize procurement and external workforce management. Hundreds more renewed licenses and still more went live with the solutions to optimize spend management.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“We have seen significant growth this quarter with companies around the world continuing to prioritize improving their spend management operations,” said John Wookey, president of SAP Intelligent Spend and Business Network. “By modernizing and digitalizing critical business processes across procurement and external workforce management, our customers are gaining visibility and insights that enable them to control costs, reduce risk and drive innovation and growth for their businesses.”</p>
  <p>Highlights from the quarter include:</p>
  <p><strong>Alcon Vision</strong>, the Fort Worth, Texas–based company, is a global leader in eye care, specializing in surgical medical devices and nonsurgical vision care products. Alcon selected SAP Ariba solutions for sourcing and procurement for direct and indirect materials. The company also selected the Qualtrics XM for Suppliers solution to help build stronger and more collaborative relationships with suppliers. With a new and improved intuitive source-to-pay experience, Alcon aims to foster simplicity, speed and user-friendly buying services with increased data transparency and compliance.</p>
  <p>Refrigeration and air conditioning technology manufacturer <strong>BITZER SE</strong> has implemented the SAP Ariba Buying solution with guided buying capability to help streamline and digitalize its procurement operations. With the SAP Ariba solution, BITZER, based in Sindelfingen, Germany, aims to drive a more efficient, paperless, transparent process from sourcing to payment as it expands globally.</p>
  <p>The <strong>Florida Department of Management Services (DMS)</strong> selected SAP Ariba solutions for sourcing, contracts, buying and invoicing, and commerce automation to modernize its statewide procurement system with a cloud-based solution. DMS plans to standardize and automate procurement processes across the State of Florida, increase spend visibility and control, and enhance savings statewide.</p>
  <p>Aligned with its innovation and sustainability strategy, <strong>Grupo Financiero Banorte, S.A.B. de C.V.,</strong> one of the largest financial holdings companies in Mexico, continues its procurement transformation with the renewal of SAP Ariba solutions. By further digitalizing its procurement processes and strengthening its supply lifecycle management automation, Banorte will help improve the experience of more than 21,000 suppliers while enhancing process efficiency and spend compliance.</p>
  <p><strong>Molson Coors</strong> made a strategic investment in SAP Ariba solutions to help modernize its global procurement operations, building on its implementation of the SAP Ariba Contracts solution and adding the SAP Ariba Buying and Invoicing solution with commerce automation capabilities. With the new solutions integrated with its multiple ERP infrastructure, the company, headquartered in Golden, Colorado, and Montreal, Canada, intends to standardize on best practices from source to pay, improve efficiency in supplier relationship management and minimize risk.</p>
  <p><strong>Promigas SA ESP</strong>, a leading Colombian provider of natural gas, has selected SAP Ariba solutions for digital procurement as it continued its transformation journey with SAP. Building on its existing transportation management system based on SAP S/4HANA, Promigas will adopt the cloud-based SAP Ariba solutions to help standardize and automate its procurement processes, increase purchasing efficiencies and reduce costs and risks.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-fieldglass-rework-how-work-gets-done">SAP Fieldglass: Rework how work gets done</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Roca Sanitario SA</strong>, a global leader in bathroom equipment, selected SAP Ariba solutions for strategic sourcing, buying, commerce automation and supply chain collaboration. The Spanish company will adopt the digital <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/solutions/services-procurement">procurement solutions</a> to help improve, standardize and automate spend management processes across the organization. The company expects to increase visibility into spend and supplier performance to optimize costs and operational efficiencies.</p>
  <p>For more information, visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong></p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: 77% of the world’s transaction revenue touches an SAP system. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong> Kelly Sheldon Murray, +1 (978) 708-6821, <a href="mailto:kelly.murray@sap.com">kelly.murray@sap.com</a><u>,</u> ET<br>Geraldine Lim, +1 (415) 418-0945, <a href="mailto:geraldine.lim@sap.com">geraldine.lim@sap.com</a>, PT<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="http://www.sap.com/corporate-en/legal/copyright/index.epx#trademark">http://www.sap.com/corporate-en/legal/copyright/index.epx#trademark</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-news</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-buying</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-contracts</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New SAP Fieldglass Assignment Management Solution Simplifies External Workforce Management for Asset-Intensive Industries]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/new-sap-fieldglass-assignment-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/new-sap-fieldglass-assignment-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Fieldglass Assignment Management is now available to help manage contractors performing ad hoc work under existing supplier agreements.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1209b09e702d8143c3a54beabfff6aa6db906e9ee.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1209b09e702d8143c3a54beabfff6aa6db906e9ee.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1209b09e702d8143c3a54beabfff6aa6db906e9ee.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="New SAP Fieldglass Assignment Management Solution Simplifies External Workforce Management for Asset-Intensive Industries" src="./media_1209b09e702d8143c3a54beabfff6aa6db906e9ee.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="new-sap-fieldglass-assignment-management-solution-simplifies-external-workforce-management-for-asset-intensive-industries">New SAP Fieldglass Assignment Management Solution Simplifies External Workforce Management for Asset-Intensive Industries</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="transform-how-you-select-engage-and-manage-your-external-workforce-with-sap">Transform how you select, engage, and manage your external workforce with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/e-procurement/contingent-workforce.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced the general availability of <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/solutions/assignment-management?campaigncode=CRM-PR21-FIP-FGAMLAUPRM">SAP Fieldglass Assignment Management</a>, a new solution to help manage contractors performing ad hoc work under existing supplier agreements.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The solution simplifies assigning and managing work projects across multiple workers and variable pay rates, enabling operations managers to quickly deploy assignments, minimize downtime and maximize return on investment.</p>
  <p>Companies in asset-intensive industries such as oil and gas, chemicals, utilities and mining rely heavily on contractors to perform ad hoc maintenance and project work. These external workers are often assigned simultaneously to multiple projects. But each project may be managed individually under separate contracts, often across disparate systems. This makes it difficult to find and deploy the right resources with the right skills for each job, pay those hourly workers on time while enforcing contract compliance, and track hours and costs against purchase orders, cost centers and work orders.</p>
  <p>“SAP is providing a solution on a single platform on which companies can manage the complexity of multiple projects with several contractors under one supplier agreement,” said Mickey North Rizza, IDC Program Vice President of Enterprise Applications and Digital Commerce. “This solution limits up-front sourcing for every project and reduces overall supply agreements while extending information into the manufacturing operation systems and ERP.”</p>
  <p>External labor accounts for 42% of total workforce spend, according to a <a href="/2021/02/sap-oxford-economics-agile-procurement-insights-research">recent report</a> by SAP and Oxford Economics. Although 55% of the executives surveyed said that their company would be unable to conduct business as usual without an external workforce, many organizations lack visibility and insight into this large, strategic spend category. The SAP Fieldglass Assignment Management solution helps provide transparency, flexibility and control with a single interface to simplify how organizations manage contractors deployed on an as-needed basis within gated facilities.</p>
  <p>“As the portion of business spend on external labor grows, companies need full transparency into their external workforce operations,” said SAP Fieldglass General Manager Arun Srinivasan. “SAP Fieldglass Assignment Management enables organizations to better control their costs with a highly configurable, integrated tool. Businesses in asset-intensive industries can be confident that highly skilled contractors have access to the right facilities to complete the critical maintenance work while ensuring billing is done accurately and labor regulations, including worker safety, are followed.”</p>
  <p>Already an industry leader in external workforce management, SAP is responding to customer demands with the release of SAP Fieldglass Assignment Management to empower organizations with:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Visibility to improve cost control and results.</strong> Pay rules help manage compliance at the contract and location level, and businesses can track standard time and overtime on a daily basis.</li>
    <li><strong>Flexibility to increase speed and productivity.</strong> Integration with gate pass systems and embedded smart logic help ensure more accurate calculation of working time with fewer errors, enabling organizations to help keep their maintenance crews and operations running smoothly to minimize downtime and disruptions.</li>
    <li><strong>Confidence to manage compliance and security risks.</strong> Better tracking and management of work assignments help ensure contractors have access to the proper facilities and that on- and offboarding are standardized across workers. This helps to mitigate risk and increase compliance with local labor regulations.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>To learn more about SAP Fieldglass Assignment Management, visit <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/solutions/assignment-management?campaigncode=CRM-PR21-FIP-FGAMLAUPRM">here</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong></p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: 77% of the world’s transaction revenue touches an SAP system. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT) and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want — without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Geraldine Lim, +1 (415) 418-0945, <a href="mailto:geraldine.lim@sap.com">geraldine.lim@sap.com</a>, PT<br>Kelly Sheldon Murray, +1 (978) 708-6821, <a href="mailto:kelly.murray@sap.com">kelly.murray@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>