<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-responsible-design-and-production/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[UN Plastics Treaty: Good for Business and the Planet]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/un-plastics-treaty-good-for-business-and-planet</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/un-plastics-treaty-good-for-business-and-planet</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is part of the Business Coalition for a Global Plastics Treaty, which supports a legally binding UN treaty to end plastic pollution.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>product/sap-green-token</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sustainability-solutions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[We Can’t Achieve Net Zero Without the Circular Economy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/we-cant-achieve-net-zero-without-the-circular-economy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/we-cant-achieve-net-zero-without-the-circular-economy</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Net zero and the circular economy go hand in hand. Read to learn how businesses, like SAP, and non-corporate bodies can accelerate progress.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/net-zero</category>
            <category>product/sap-green-token</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sustainability-solutions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Zamora Company Is Helping Create a Better World by Reducing Packaging with SAP Responsible Design and Production]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/zamora-company-reducing-packaging-sap-responsible-design-and-production</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/zamora-company-reducing-packaging-sap-responsible-design-and-production</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Responsible Design and Production helped Zamora Company adhere to new packaging taxes in Spain. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18070844b43147c00d535b4fc2b7e284b2b6e0bcf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18070844b43147c00d535b4fc2b7e284b2b6e0bcf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18070844b43147c00d535b4fc2b7e284b2b6e0bcf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Zamora Company Is Helping Create a Better World by Reducing Packaging with SAP Responsible Design and Production" src="./media_18070844b43147c00d535b4fc2b7e284b2b6e0bcf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="zamora-company-is-helping-create-a-better-world-by-reducing-packaging-with-sap-responsible-design-and-production">Zamora Company Is Helping Create a Better World by Reducing Packaging with SAP Responsible Design and Production</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As a consumer you may not have heard of <a href="https://zamoracompany.com/conscious-company/">Zamora Company</a>, but it will surely ring a bell when you hear the names of some of its most popular premium spirit and wine brands, such as Licor 43, Martin Miller’s Gin, Yellow Rose, Ramón Bilbao, Champagne Pommery, and many others.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The international enterprise with headquarters in Spain and operations in more than 80 countries has been including environmental protection and economic growth into its DNA and is constantly working on achieving a sustainable business model that will be its future legacy to society and to the planet. Its commitment to the planet is based on four pillars: climate action, biodiversity protection, circularity, and conscious suppliers.</p>
  <p>The mission of Zamora Company toward its suppliers is to encourage them to be more sustainable by collaborating closely to substitute product and packaging materials with more sustainable alternatives and to use more recyclable packaging materials to support circular economy principles. It’s no wonder that, for Zamora, <a href="/topics/sustainability">sustainability</a> goes hand in hand with innovation without compromising the highest quality standards. <a href="https://zamoracompany.com/conscious-company/">Zamora Company’s strategy</a> as a conscious company is also focused and aligned with the achievement of the <a href="https://www.un.org/sustainabledevelopment/">Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs)</a> set by the United Nations 2030 agenda.</p>
  <h2 id="accelerating-innovation-through-new-packaging-legislation">Accelerating Innovation Through New Packaging Legislation</h2>
  <p>Since the introduction of a <a href="https://sede.agenciatributaria.gob.es/Sede/en_gb/impuestos-especiales-medioambientales/impuesto-especial-sobre-envases-plastico-reutilizables.html">new packaging tax</a> in Spain on January 1, 2023 on non-reusable plastic packaging, companies are required to meet comprehensive reporting requirements.</p>
  <p>The tax is an indirect excise tax with an environmental purpose. It aims to internalize the environmental costs related to the manufacturing and consumption of plastic packaging in the price of final products.</p>
  <p>The taxable event is the manufacturing, import, or intra-community acquisition of non-reusable plastic packaging for its use within the Spanish market. The plastic packaging tax captures a broad concept of “non-reusable plastic packaging” in its scope, which includes:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Non-reusable plastic containers – the law provides definitions of “non-reusable,” “plastic,” and “container” for the purpose of this tax</li>
    <li>Semi-finished plastic products, such as preforms and thermoplastic sheets, intended for production of non-reusable plastic containers</li>
    <li>Plastic products aimed to facilitate the closing, trading, or presentation of non-reusable containers</li>
  </ul>
  <p>“The new legislation required us to respond to governmental requisitions and was an additional driver to accelerate our sustainability efforts,” Enrique Gonzalo Mecández, SAP manager in Operations at Zamora Company, explained. “With a cross-departmental team, we were looking to find the most appropriate and scalable software solution to meet the country’s regulatory requirements and help us with data management, a tax monitor, and reporting and insights.”</p>
  <h2 id="keeping-all-data-in-one-central-place">Keeping All Data in One Central Place</h2>
  <p>As a result, Zamora Company found that <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/responsible-design-and-production.html">SAP Responsible Design and Production</a>, an industry cloud-based solution, would best meet its needs. SAP Responsible Design and Production can support manufacturers and retailers in calculating extended producer responsibility (EPR) obligations and fees, plastic taxes, and corporate commitments to optimize material choices. In addition, it helps improve design decisions based on costs and planetary impact.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="start-acting-on-a-circular-economy-and-eliminate-waste-with-sap">Start acting on a circular economy and eliminate waste with SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/responsible-design-and-production.html">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“From a process standpoint, SAP Responsible Design and Production facilitates the incorporation of everything related to sustainability data linked to the material, so that all relevant information is unified in the material master,” Gonzalo Mecández said. “As all information is kept in one place, purchasing work and master data maintenance required to ensure regulatory compliance is centralized, without the need to manually replicate information in different systems.”</p>
  <p>“Moreover, leveraging a single and integrated platform with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA</a> provides the security of working with up-to-date and correct data. Additionally, the data quality application allows our users to detect any lack of information and correct it,” he added. “With deep knowledge and solution experience, our trusted partner <a href="https://www.indracompany.com/en/minsait">Minsait</a>, an <a href="https://www.indracompany.com/en/">Indra</a> company, closely supported us during the implementation of SAP Responsible Design and Production, as well as the integration with our SAP S/4HANA platform.”</p>
  <p>The benefits Zamora Company achieved include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Ability to rely on 100% correct data, fully aligned with material registration processes</li>
    <li>Cost savings thanks to less administrative work, eased reporting, and a central data repository</li>
    <li>Reduced risk of non-compliance with extended producer responsibility regulations in Spain</li>
    <li>A simple, user-friendly tool to support legal reporting requirements in a timely manner</li>
    <li>Ability to expand solution usage to meet upcoming EPR legislation in other countries, like Italy</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="positive-impact-on-customers-economy-society-and-environment">Positive Impact on Customers, Economy, Society, and Environment</h2>
  <p>“The project helped us learn more about our products and incorporate their packaging details, so that our company knows exactly how much plastic and non-recycled plastic is being used. In a more strategic phase, this will allow us to evaluate alternative materials and compositions, which can create cost savings for the company and positively contribute to the environment by being able to transition to more sustainable elements,” Gonzalo Mecández concluded.</p>
  <p>Watch a solution <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/responsible-design-and-production.html?video=d287b342-047e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">overview video</a> to learn how to start acting on a circular economy, design products sustainably, and eliminate waste with SAP Responsible Design and Production. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/responsible-design-and-production.html?pdf-asset=6e06c630-667e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=1">Read</a> about what benefits other enterprises achieved.</p>
  <p>To explore how the comprehensive, cloud-based sustainability solution portfolio from SAP can support carbon footprint management, reducing material waste, and becoming a socially responsible business, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">here</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Karin Fent is senior director of Global Customer Success, Digital Supply Chain, at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="stay-in-touch-by-following-sap-news-on-linkedin">Stay in touch by following SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Connect with us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gonzalez Byass Tracks Plastics From the Vineyard to Your Wine Glass]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/gonzalez-byass-tracks-plastics-sap-responsible-design-and-production</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/gonzalez-byass-tracks-plastics-sap-responsible-design-and-production</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Gonzalez Byass can monitor, measure, and act on its plastic data using SAP Responsible Design and Production. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/agribusiness</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The SAP Solution Transforming How Businesses Navigate Plastic Regulations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/sap-responsible-design-production-navigate-plastic-regulations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/sap-responsible-design-production-navigate-plastic-regulations</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Responsible Design and Production assists operations, such as Henkel’s, in navigating the labyrinth of product and packaging composition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Supports Plastic Packaging Taxes with SAP Responsible Design and Production]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/plastic-packaging-taxes-sap-responsible-design-and-production</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/plastic-packaging-taxes-sap-responsible-design-and-production</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Responsible Design and Production helps manage plastic packaging taxes and supports transitioning to a sustainable packaging portfolio.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Can Businesses Phase Out Virgin Plastic for Good?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/can-businesses-phase-out-virgin-plastic-for-good</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/can-businesses-phase-out-virgin-plastic-for-good</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In response to the UN Treaty on Plastic Pollution, SAP created a digital solution to enable customers to apply the framework. Learn more!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>product/sap-green-token</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HANNOVER MESSE 2023: SAP Generates New Data-Driven Insights for Resilient Manufacturing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-hannover-messe-2023-data-driven-insights-resilient-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-hannover-messe-2023-data-driven-insights-resilient-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At HANNOVER MESSE 2023, SAP will showcase its unique position to accelerate the journey to resilient manufacturing. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>news-tag/hannover-messe</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-x</category>
            <category>news-tag/oxford-economics</category>
            <category>product/sap-digital-manufacturing</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Responsible Design and Production Helps Companies Manage Plastic Taxes in a Fragmented Environment]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/sap-responsible-design-and-production-manage-plastic-taxes</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/sap-responsible-design-and-production-manage-plastic-taxes</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Responsible Design and Production enables companies to comply with plastic taxes legislation and develop more circular processes.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/wef-davos</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Together Toward a Circular Economy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2022/06/circular-economy-sap-customers-reduce-food-waste</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2022/06/circular-economy-sap-customers-reduce-food-waste</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Collective action to address food waste and global hunger must take many forms. Read how a number of SAP customers are leading the way.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-supply-chain-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Extending the Reach of SAP Cloud for Sustainable Enterprises]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/extending-sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/extending-sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Cloud for Sustainable Enterprises combines a comprehensive portfolio of solutions to holistically manage sustainability performance.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[UK Plastic Tax Reshapes Global Supply Chains to Create Circular Economy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/uk-plastic-tax-circular-economy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/uk-plastic-tax-circular-economy</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The UK Plastic Tax is a milestone sustainability commitment and a significant step in the growth of the worldwide circular economy.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and the Ellen MacArthur Foundation Announce Circular Economy Partnership to Deliver Regenerative Business]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/circular-economy-partnership-regenerative-business-ellen-macarthur-foundation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/circular-economy-partnership-regenerative-business-ellen-macarthur-foundation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has become a partner in the Ellen MacArthur Foundation’s network to deliver circular economy solutions led by regenerative business.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BCG and SAP Join Forces to Transform Companies into Sustainable Enterprises]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/bcg-and-sap-transform-sustainable-enterprises</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/bcg-and-sap-transform-sustainable-enterprises</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Together, BCG and SAP will help companies tackle the generational challenge of climate change. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/bcg</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Disrupting Business Models to Protect Our Most Valuable Asset: The Planet]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/sap-and-bcg-partnership-protect-planet</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/sap-and-bcg-partnership-protect-planet</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The SAP and BCG partnership supports companies in the digital transformation to become intelligent sustainable enterprises.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/bcg</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Enterprise Adoption: Localization Services Power Global Sustainable Business]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/localization-services-power-global-sustainable-business</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/localization-services-power-global-sustainable-business</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In this exclusive Q&A, SAP’s Eva Zauke talks about the powerful localization revolution happening behind every digital-first business.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>product/sap-billing-and-revenue-innovation-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-adoption</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Changing Our Reality for the Better by Moving Toward a Sustainable World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2022/01/moving-toward-sustainable-world</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2022/01/moving-toward-sustainable-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP wants to make 2022 the year an interconnected world transitions toward a more sustainable world. Learn more about how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12de401c221ecaa5cca1ef1e16db0e23766e63072.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12de401c221ecaa5cca1ef1e16db0e23766e63072.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12de401c221ecaa5cca1ef1e16db0e23766e63072.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Changing Our Reality for the Better by Moving Toward a Sustainable World" src="./media_12de401c221ecaa5cca1ef1e16db0e23766e63072.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="changing-our-reality-for-the-better-by-moving-toward-a-sustainable-world">Changing Our Reality for the Better by Moving Toward a Sustainable World</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Gone are the days when companies discussed the <strong>why</strong> of sustainable business practices. Today, it is all about the <strong>how</strong>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>How can businesses take climate action? How can they turn linear processes into circular resources and product flows? How can they ensure socially responsible value chains? And ultimately, how can they integrate economic, environmental, and social performance into strategic decision-making?</p>
  <p>These questions are top of mind for executives. In 2021, sustainability <a href="https://go.alpha-sense.com/wp-sap-sustainability/">became the top trending topic for the C-suite</a>.</p>
  <p>At SAP, we deliver answers to these questions through our products. Our customers can benefit from solutions that help them achieve <strong>zero emissions</strong>, <strong>zero waste</strong>, <strong>zero inequality</strong>, as well as <strong>holistic steering and reporting</strong> of their sustainability efforts.</p>
  <p>Last year, we launched three new solutions: <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/product-footprint-management.html">SAP Product Footprint Management</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/responsible-design-and-production.html">SAP Responsible Design and Production</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability-control-tower.html">SAP Sustainability Control Tower</a>. All are embedded SAP S/4HANA cloud-native applications that are delivered in a modular way and built on top of SAP Business Technology Platform.</p>
  <p>What is more, we are embedding sustainability across SAP’s entire solution portfolio. A recent example is the inclusion of product footprints in SAP Integrated Business Planning, so customers can monitor the greenhouse gas emissions from their production plants. Another example is the integration of SAP Sustainability Control Tower with SAP SuccessFactors solutions, enabling customers to obtain insights into how their organization is faring on crucial aspects such as diversity and inclusion.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="choose-both-profitability-and-sustainability-with-sap">Choose both profitability and sustainability with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="sustainable-business-strategies-sustainable-enterprises">Sustainable Business Strategies, Sustainable Enterprises</h2>
  <p>For the last 50 years, our innovative solutions have helped our customers transform their business processes and stay ahead in rapidly changing business environments. And we will continue to take and enable organizations of any size and in any industry to take a transformative approach to sustainability as well.</p>
  <p>Quick fixes that do not get to the root cause of problems won’t make businesses more sustainable in the long run. Fragmented sustainability strategies won’t help. Sustainable business strategies will. That is why we support companies in integrating sustainability into the heart of their business processes.</p>
  <p>Our approach pays off. Today, the most sustainable companies run our software. According to our analysis of S&#x26;P Trucost Limited data and <a href="https://www.spglobal.com/esg/solutions/data-intelligence-esg-scores">S&#x26;P Global ESG Scores for 2021</a>, SAP customers with high digital maturity — those adopting SAP’s latest technologies — on average have 75% better environmental, social, and governance (ESG) scores compared to their industry peers. They also produce 24% less CO2 emissions than the market average.</p>
  <p>To further facilitate the sustainability transformation for our customers, we recently launched a new offering. <a href="/2022/01/sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises-take-action-together">SAP Cloud for Sustainable Enterprises</a> is a flexible bundle of sustainability-specific applications. It allows businesses to adopt our solutions based on the current stage of their sustainability transformation. Depending on where they stand, they can implement holistic management or start with specific areas of sustainability performance.</p>
  <h2 id="chasing-zero-together">Chasing Zero, Together</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises-taking-action-together">SAP Cloud for Sustainable Enterprises: Taking Action Together</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2022/01/sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises-take-action-together">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The past year has been all about delivering the tools that help businesses transition into sustainable enterprises. So, what’s next? 2022 will be the year to implement these tools <a href="/2022/01/global-sustainability-ecosystem-power-scale">globally in close collaboration with our customers and partners</a>.</p>
  <p>Ultimately, the transition to a more sustainable global economy is not something one company can achieve on its own. In today’s interconnected world, we must rely on our ecosystem to ensure sustainability across the entire value chain. Let’s make 2022 the year we transition toward a more sustainable world, together.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Thomas Saueressig is a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE leading SAP Product Engineering.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Our Planet Cannot Afford Fragmented Reporting – Can You?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/12/planet-cannot-afford-fragmented-reporting-sap-sustainability-control-tower</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/12/planet-cannot-afford-fragmented-reporting-sap-sustainability-control-tower</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The days of fragmented reporting must end. Go further with ESG integration and data transparency using SAP Sustainability Control Tower.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fa4922faa7ff4ba0376ab0f75cc3ace85cd4e944.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fa4922faa7ff4ba0376ab0f75cc3ace85cd4e944.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1fa4922faa7ff4ba0376ab0f75cc3ace85cd4e944.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Our Planet Cannot Afford Fragmented Reporting – Can You?" src="./media_1fa4922faa7ff4ba0376ab0f75cc3ace85cd4e944.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="our-planet-cannot-afford-fragmented-reporting--can-you">Our Planet Cannot Afford Fragmented Reporting – Can You?</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>There is consensus. The recent <a href="https://ukcop26.org/">United Nations Climate Change Conference of the Parties</a> (<a href="/topics/cop26">COP26</a>) made at least two things clear: we need to move faster toward our goal to reduce greenhouse gas emissions and a fair transition won’t come cheap. Therefore, no enterprise can afford to waste time or money when it comes to aligning their sustainability ambitions with their actions.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Stakeholders are coming to the same conclusions that we have long been convinced of. Even before announcing our Climate 21 initiative two years ago, <a href="/2021/12/sap-leads-sustainability-rankings">we have been seen as front-runners</a> in providing environmental transparency. We have long understood the importance of measuring sustainability progress holistically and connecting financial and pre-financial data. We’ve been doing that since 2012. That’s when we merged our sustainability and annual reports into an integrated report.</p>
  <p>We know that the days of fragmented reporting must end. And now, many more businesses are seeing how fundamental the issues of transparency on environmental, social, and governance (ESG) impacts are. But many businesses still struggle with a multitude of reporting frameworks and lack of appropriate data. This is what stands in the way of consistent investor-focused disclosures. Our planet cannot afford this. Increasingly, consumers want to know the provenance of their products. They want to be assured that they are making choices based on data they can trust.</p>
  <p>The sustainability issues we face today are different from all other previous threats and opportunities — in scope, scale, and ultimately in the consequences. Measuring, reporting, and achieving the sustainable business goals we set is imperative to a <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/building-solutions-future-has-already-arrived-thomas-saueressig/?trackingId=sxlQXAPxQ2CzqFo6obbMjQ%3D%3D">net-zero, nature-positive and socially-inclusive future</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-sustainability-control-tower-a-commanding-business-view">SAP Sustainability Control Tower: A Commanding Business View</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="businesses-want-to-make-sustainable-decisions-they-need-the-right-intelligence-to-do-it">Businesses Want to Make Sustainable Decisions; They Need the Right Intelligence to Do It</h2>
  <p>The vast majority of business leaders I connect with want to lead their businesses sustainably. They care about planetary and societal impacts; in fact, their customers, investors, and employees demand it. At SAP, our aspiration goes far beyond enabling businesses to achieve efficiency. We work with customers to reinvent their business processes to achieve sustainable growth. That means enabling businesses to use data in agile ways, across all sustainability dimensions. We provide early alerts that allow companies to be responsive and we give customers the full picture they need to move proactively on their ESG issues.</p>
  <p>Sustainability data is “pre-financial,” not “non-financial.” That means the search for sustainability levers must go beyond the financials to bring together all sustainability data dimensions, including emissions, material flows, and social impacts. We know this and it is why we have made this possible today. For example, with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/product-footprint-management.html">SAP Product Footprint Management</a>, companies get visibility into their carbon footprint data throughout a product’s value chain, including for material sourcing and production. And that’s the insight businesses need to make proactive, sustainable supply chain decisions.</p>
  <h2 id="scale-data-across-business-networks-to-mitigate-planetary-impacts">Scale Data Across Business Networks to Mitigate Planetary Impacts</h2>
  <p>Individual businesses can only do so much. Emissions do not recognize company boundaries and therefore we must help companies reach beyond their own four walls. We know we must connect our customers into a network of intelligent, sustainable enterprises.</p>
  <p>Intelligent cross-enterprise scenarios that enable data sharing across value chains will create impact at scale. Business networks enable companies to continuously re-evaluate and re-engage with each other, creating additional value for their customers and our planet.</p>
  <h2 id="from-voluntary-to-mandatory-esg-standards-are-evolving">From Voluntary to Mandatory, ESG Standards Are Evolving</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="accelerating-a-new-era-of-sustainability-management">Accelerating a New Era of Sustainability Management</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/12/sap-sustainability-control-tower-new-era-sustainability-management">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>ESG reporting is maturing; there is no doubt about that. Climate-related disclosures are evolving from voluntary to mandatory. Around 100 countries have explicitly expressed support for starting negotiations for a global agreement on plastics in 2022. The European Union is already developing a social taxonomy based on global social and human rights norms. SAP also recently released an <a href="https://www3.weforum.org/docs/WEF_Joint_Open_Letter_to%20EU_institutions_Future_of_Sustainability_Reporting.pdf">open letter</a> asking the European Union to act on ESG disclosure standards. We want to encourage a global baseline set of standards. We fully support corporate transparency that meets the needs of all stakeholders and improves connectivity between sustainability and financial reporting.</p>
  <p>And, once again, we at SAP have stepped up to provide the solutions that companies need to execute on these evolving standards and connect their environmental, social, and financial values, holistically. Today, I’m proud to say that we just released <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability-control-tower.html">SAP Sustainability Control Tower</a>, a solution that enables customers to go further on their ESG integration and data transparency journey. Our solution enables non-financial — or, as I prefer to call them, “pre-financial” — disclosures focused on four aspects: people, planet, prosperity, and principles of governance. This includes measurements around greenhouse gas emissions, pay equality, and board diversity. It enables comparisons between companies, regardless of industry or region.</p>
  <p>Our two previously released sustainability products, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/product-footprint-management.html">SAP Product Footprint Management</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/responsible-design-and-production.html">SAP Responsible Design and Production</a>, feed precisely those new data dimensions, which businesses have so far been lacking, into SAP Sustainability Control Tower.</p>
  <p>Our new solution has the World Economic Forum’s Stakeholder Capitalism Metrics as its foundation. These metrics are based on existing standards to make ESG disclosures more comparable and consistent. They were developed within the International Business Council, a community of over 120 global CEOs who seek to improve the ways companies measure and demonstrate their contributions toward creating a more sustainable relationship with our planet.</p>
  <p>And of course, our partners are integral here. Deloitte, EY, and PwC are a few examples of the partners that bring immense knowledge, not only about the framework, but also about the ESG transformations of our customers. Strategic partners like BCG enable our customers to take a holistic perspective toward establishing ESG and climate compliance.</p>
  <h2 id="time-is-of-the-essence">Time Is of the Essence</h2>
  <p>Businesses that set out a 10-year agenda for dealing with their sustainability challenges are moving much too slowly. We all need to move quickly to enable the shift to new business models. Time is of the essence.</p>
  <p>At SAP, we know how important it is that corporate sustainability efforts be measured, reported, steered, and communicated effectively. And I am personally very proud of the <a href="/2021/12/sap-sustainability-control-tower-new-era-sustainability-management">leadership we continue to demonstrate here</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Thomas Saueressig is a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE leading SAP Product Engineering.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Takes Top Spots in Leading Sustainability Rankings]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/sap-leads-sustainability-rankings</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/sap-leads-sustainability-rankings</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP once again leads the sustainability rankings: CDP’s A List as well as the Dow Jones Sustainability Indices (DJSI). Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/djsi</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Achieves Top Scores in Dow Jones Sustainability Index and Carbon Disclosure Project]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/sap-achieves-top-scores-dow-jones-sustainability-index-and-cdp-carbon-disclosure-project</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/sap-achieves-top-scores-dow-jones-sustainability-index-and-cdp-carbon-disclosure-project</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP received a spot on the prestigious CDP A list, which announces the over 300 companies leading the way to a more sustainable future.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15d0fd22a994b277404768c0eda29f726d6465458.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15d0fd22a994b277404768c0eda29f726d6465458.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15d0fd22a994b277404768c0eda29f726d6465458.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Achieves Top Scores in Dow Jones Sustainability Index and Carbon Disclosure Project" src="./media_15d0fd22a994b277404768c0eda29f726d6465458.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-achieves-top-scores-in-dow-jones-sustainability-index-and-carbon-disclosure-project">SAP Achieves Top Scores in Dow Jones Sustainability Index and Carbon Disclosure Project</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Back in 2010, Christiana Figueres, the former executive secretary of the UN Framework Convention on Climate Change, said that the <a href="https://www.cdp.net/en/info/about-us">Carbon Disclosure Project (CDP)</a> is to the <a href="https://www.cdp.net/en/info/about-us/20th-anniversary">future of business what the X-ray was to the future of medicine</a> – without it, doctors could never see the inside of a patient’s health. Exactly this kind of laser-like transparency is needed to move the needle regarding the health of the planet, which incidentally contributes massively to the health of the economy.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>CDP was founded at <a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/organisations/prime-ministers-office-10-downing-street">10 Downing Street</a> 20 years ago in response to a warning by <a href="https://www.ipcc.ch/about/">IPCC scientists</a> that if climate change remained unchecked, the world would warm by six degrees Celsius within the century. As the number of climate-related catastrophes mounted over the years, CDP kept urging companies and governments to report on their emissions and take measurable action.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-2020-sap-integrated-report">Read the 2020 SAP Integrated Report</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/integrated-reports/2020/en.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="above-and-beyond">Above and Beyond</h2>
  <p>Today, the world’s economy looks to <a href="https://www.cdp.net/en/companies/companies-scores#1ea1731978553db35dcd1469b155011d">CDP as the gold standard</a> of environmental reporting with the richest and most comprehensive data set on corporate and city action. By scoring companies and other organizations from D to A on climate change, forests, and water security, CDP helps them evolve from disclosing sustainability metrics to taking measurable actions that lead to environmental leadership.</p>
  <p>In light of the recent <a href="/2021/11/cop26-reflections-enabling-business-action-and-planetary-ambition">climate conference COP26</a>, it is apparent more than ever that the private sector has a critical role in driving change and leading by example. SAP enforced its climate action commitment by moving its <a href="/2021/03/sap-carbon-neutrality-goal-2023">carbon neutral target up</a> by two years to 2023. This week, SAP received a spot on the prestigious <a href="https://www.cdp.net/en/scores">CDP A list</a>, which announces over 300 companies leading the way to a <a href="/">more sustainable future</a>.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.cdp.net/en/articles/media/cdp-reports-record-number-of-disclosures-and-unveils-new-strategy-to-help-further-tackle-climate-and-ecological-emergency">2021 was a record year</a>. More than 13,000 companies reported on their environmental impact through CDP, despite the continuing challenges of <a href="/covid-19">the pandemic</a>. This was 37% more than 2020 and 135% higher than when governments signed the Paris Agreement on climate change in 2015. Between them, disclosing companies in 2021 accounted for over 64% of global market capitalization, including 96% of the FTSE 100, over 80% of the S&#x26;P 500, and more than 1,500 companies in China.</p>
  <p>SAP’s CDP A rating comes only weeks after SAP was named the software industry leader in the Dow Jones Sustainability Indices (DJSI) for the 15th consecutive year, <a href="https://www.spglobal.com/esg/scores/?utm_source=email&#x26;utm_medium=email&#x26;utm_campaign=YB21_member">identifying</a> SAP as an environmental, social, and governance (ESG) front-runner.</p>
  <h2 id="setting-the-pace">Setting the Pace</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-solutions-for-sustainability-help-deliver-environmental-social-and-economic-impact">SAP solutions for sustainability help deliver environmental, social, and economic impact</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Achieving top scores in the CDP and DJSI rankings sets SAP apart as exemplar when it comes to disclosure. More importantly, SAP solutions for sustainability help companies measure and monitor their emissions, making it an enabler for companies that want to do due diligence on their own performance.</p>
  <p>“The DJSI and CDP awards recognize Fortune 500 companies that are taking concrete steps to tackle climate change challenges. It is good to receive ongoing independent recognition that SAP is on the right track,” said Daniel Schmid, chief sustainability officer at SAP, responsible for SAP’s sustainability efforts. “It’s equally important to embed sustainability in the business strategy, so that it impacts all aspects of the business. That’s how we can reduce the negative impact on our environment and create regenerative business.”</p>
  <p>SAP customers benefit from a range of products to help them to take climate action or to accelerate their participation in the circular, wasteless economy.</p>
  <p>The <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/product-footprint-management.html">SAP Product Footprint Management solution</a> enables organizations to combat climate change by capturing the environmental footprint of products across the value chain so they can build sustainability into the fabric of how they do business. Last month, SAP added <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/responsible-design-and-production.html">SAP Responsible Design and Production</a> to its portfolio. The solution helps companies gain better visibility of material flows through their processes including tracking and complying with rapidly changing regulations, especially those concerning product packaging and plastics.</p>
  <p>And finally, <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/06/10e155de-e87d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">SAP Sustainability Control Tower</a> helps customers meet their ESG performance targets. This solution enables integration of top-line and bottom-line management with an added dimension – a green line for integrated environmental and social sustainability insights and decision-making.</p>
  <p>The importance of disclosure cannot be underestimated. Business is still business, but in today’s challenging world, the purpose is not to just turn a profit; it’s to remain competitive, relevant, and sustainable while turning a profit. While the <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/10/21/seeing-beyond-the-sustainability-blind-spot-can-lead-to-long-term-growth/?sh=42b874502f2e">balance sheet may not always show it yet</a>, sustainability is already material to all companies because the fortunes of business are inevitably linked to those of the planet.</p>
  <p><a href="https://insights.sap.com/environmental-sustainability-affects-competitiveness/">A recent survey by SAP Insights</a> found that the more companies believe sustainability is material to their businesses, meaning it is likely to affect their financial condition and should be publicly disclosed, the more competitive and profitable they are likely to be.</p>
  <p>The good news is that after 20 years of running the world’s environmental disclosure system for companies, cities, and regions, CDP finally <a href="https://vimeo.com/239499952">sees a tipping point</a>. With companies disclosing and reporting more than ever before, it’s becoming easier to accelerate change, especially with the right tools and technology at hand.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/cop26</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shaping a New Sustainable World Through Responsible Design]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/new-sustainable-world-responsible-design</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/new-sustainable-world-responsible-design</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Together, SAP and Accenture support responsible design as they work to help companies to become intelligent, sustainable enterprises.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bc76d3473dc7a0276521c6bdb818788d09f75d41.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bc76d3473dc7a0276521c6bdb818788d09f75d41.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1bc76d3473dc7a0276521c6bdb818788d09f75d41.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Shaping a New Sustainable World Through Responsible Design" src="./media_1bc76d3473dc7a0276521c6bdb818788d09f75d41.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="shaping-a-new-sustainable-world-through-responsible-design">Shaping a New Sustainable World Through Responsible Design</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The typical understanding of what “design” means to many of us is the way something looks or feels — for example, the look of an iPhone, a movie poster, furniture, or everyday appliances. But what if design was a way of looking at the world with an eye toward changing it?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By adopting a fundamentally different approach in the way we create and design products, services, and solutions we can, for instance, take finite resources to design infinite, regenerative systems that can work sustainably in the long run. In doing so, we can apply circular design as a shorthand for the practice of applying <a href="https://www.sap.com/germany/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability/economy.html">circular economy</a> principles at the design stage of everything and enable the way design changes and redefines our relationship with the world.</p>
  <p>Today, we face a devastating pandemic, new levels of global warming, extreme ecological degradation, and continuous setbacks in our work toward global goals for more equitable, inclusive, and sustainable development. Simply put, the state of the planet is broken, where every tenth of a degree of warming matters and those who have done the least to cause the problem are suffering the most.</p>
  <p>Making peace with nature is the defining task of the 21st century. With recently concluded <a href="https://ukcop26.org/">COP26</a>, nations, along with businesses, negotiators, and citizens came together to address the burning issue of climate change.</p>
  <p>While the focus at COP26 was mostly on climate action, to ensure progress on our sustainability ambitions, we need a systemic approach that looks at the complete big picture. <a href="https://www.ellenmacarthurfoundation.org/publications/completing-the-picture-climate-change">Research from the Ellen MacArthur Foundation</a> finds that our transition to renewable energy “can only address 55% of emissions. The remaining 45% comes from producing the cars, clothes, food, and other products we use every day.”</p>
  <p>In acknowledging that ambitious goals require ambitious action, <a href="https://www.wemeanbusinesscoalition.org/g20-2021/">SAP has made its position on what governments need to do at COP26 clear</a>: to take decisive action and provide a mandate to business to drive solutions to achieve our shared global goals.</p>
  <p>As a part of our sustainability journey, we believe we can design and provide highly innovative and viable solutions that will not just repair the damage to the earth humans have caused so far, but actually prevent more harm. Eighty percent of a product’s environmental impact is baked in at the time of its design, proving that the only way we can create a successful circular economy is with a focus on how our products are designed, sourced, made, and delivered.</p>
  <p>I previously <a href="/2021/09/sap-s4hana-core-sustainable-intelligent-enterprise">discussed the sustainability portfolio in SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a> and how SAP is addressing four dimensions, including climate action, circular economy, holistic steering and reporting, and social responsibility. SAP has announced the availability of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/responsible-design-and-production.html">SAP Responsible Design and Production</a> — an embedded, cloud-native SAP S/4HANA solution — to help customers with the sustainable design and responsible management of materials and products so that they can accelerate their transition to a more circular economy.</p>
  <p>With SAP Responsible Design and Production, businesses can embed circularity principles into core business processes, helping to eliminate waste, circulate products and materials, and regenerate natural systems to unlock new value. The new solution gives companies better visibility into how materials flow through their processes, including tracking and complying with rapidly changing regulations for things like packaging and plastics.</p>
  <p>They can also keep pace with increasingly strict regulations like extended producer responsibility standards, which can put significant financial and physical responsibility on the company about how they manage the disposal of their products. These standards differ across regions and countries. For example, a shampoo brand manager has visibility into the full product life cycle, including extended producer responsibility obligations and the plastic taxes of different markets. These costs can be very expensive. This visibility helps the brand manager make design changes to eliminate waste and decisions on how to reduce the costs of re-use and recycling systems.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_190359534f70996b7d931842d76fcdd158f7c3b22.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_190359534f70996b7d931842d76fcdd158f7c3b22.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_190359534f70996b7d931842d76fcdd158f7c3b22.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_190359534f70996b7d931842d76fcdd158f7c3b22.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="485">
    </picture>Technology solutions like <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hCUoogKpbYk">SAP Responsible Design and Production</a> are a fundamental step in enabling businesses to become intelligent, sustainable enterprises and drive global impact at scale. But business should not commit only to doing less harm, but to doing more good. Business has the power to not only reduce and reuse, but also to regenerate. We need to go from seeking to reduce our ecological footprint and “chasing zero,” to becoming net- or nature-positive, building not just a circular economy, but a regenerative economy.
  </p>
  <p>The regenerative economy implies a circular approach beyond the narrow view of products to one that includes the social, natural, and built environment. It is an approach similar to natural ecosystems that find synergies and balance. The regenerative business is intelligent, using innovative technology to gather insight and apply it to scale change. It measures impact, holistically and in real time.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="optimize-material-choices-with-sap-reponsible-design-and-production">Optimize material choices with SAP Reponsible Design and Production</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/responsible-design-and-production.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="cementing-partnerships-to-drive-corporate-sustainability-and-circularity">Cementing Partnerships to Drive Corporate Sustainability and Circularity</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-news-and-coverage-from-cop26">Read more news and coverage from COP26</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/cop26">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/2021/11/sap-accenture-help-organizations-embed-sustainability">Accenture shares SAP’s vision</a> of zero emissions, zero waste, and zero inequality. To achieve a sustainable world, organizations must transform into intelligent enterprises, and intelligent enterprises must form a network of intelligent enterprises.</p>
  <p>In addition to the accepted top line and bottom line, a new “green line” covering the environmental, social, and governance aspects needs to be established as another dimension of success across business processes and along value chains. This way, organizations achieve transparency and influence that span beyond company borders.</p>
  <p>The recently published <a href="https://www.unglobalcompact.org/news/4795-10-31-2021">United Nations Global Compact–Accenture CEO Sustainability Study</a> shows that many global industry leaders are already demonstrating behaviors that are critical to achieving a competitive advantage from sustainability. Accenture and SAP are ready to help organizations accelerate in their journeys to become sustainable intelligent enterprises.</p>
  <p>According to Peter Lacy, chief responsibility officer and global sustainability services lead at Accenture, “With the circular economy we have an unprecedented opportunity to transform some of the challenges we face into opportunities, creating economic value and sustainability impact for business and society. In fact, our research shows the value at stake is massive: $4.5 trillion of upside, even at conservative estimates. We are proud to partner with SAP to seize the circular advantage, as we believe business can spur innovation, create new markets, and set our current global direction toward one that is more sustainable and resilient.”</p>
  <p>Just as the whole is greater than the sum of its parts, <a href="/2021/11/sap-io-foundries-north-america-accenture-sustainability-cohorts">SAP and Accenture recently welcomed two new cohorts</a> for the external startup accelerator SAP.iO Foundries North America. Thirteen startups were selected for the cohort among hundreds of applicants by a jury of SAP and Accenture experts, partners, and customers. They are building innovative solutions to drive sustainability for consumer and retail companies across the value chain in areas including reusable packaging, responsible and ethical supply chain, and emphasizing a circular economy.</p>
  <p>With the launch of SAP Responsible Design and Production, SAP aims to address two critical challenges: managing complex extended producer responsibility regulations and plastic taxes, which vary from country to country, and enabling every organization to reduce their use of plastic, thereby contributing to sustainable and profitable growth through less plastic and less exposure to regulatory costs.</p>
  <p>Because SAP Responsible Design and Production directly leverages data from core enterprise resource planning (ERP) processes, it enables determining material compositions and calculating extended producer responsibility fees across numerous product lines as well as adhering to a growing number of different extended producer responsibility declaration schemes.</p>
  <p>To date, we have four clients testing the beta version of the new solution, released at the end of August, and they will be closely involved in assessing new releases. We are co-innovating with many of the world’s largest consumer products organizations in the solution development to support long-term industry success and delivery of the zero waste ambition.</p>
  <p>To this end, our joint teams are ready to deliver. We are helping our clients to define their road maps, identify priorities, and accelerate their journeys through the selection and implementation of relevant SAP S/4HANA Cloud capabilities and new SAP solutions. Our sustainability management portfolio is enabled by a modular SAP S/4HANA Cloud, helping us to drive a positive planetary impact in a holistic manner while incrementally expanding it along further aspects, including water, energy, land use, and social dimensions.</p>
  <p>When sustainability is embedded in its DNA, building software that helps companies measure, account, and take the right action in dynamic and heterogeneous environments is the final step in managing environmental impact.</p>
  <p>As Sir David Attenborough rightly said, “If working apart we are a force powerful to destabilize our planet, surely working together we are powerful enough to save it,” before concluding, “In my lifetime I’ve witnessed a terrible decline. In yours, you could and should witness a wonderful recovery.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Jan Gilg is president of SAP S/4HANA.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[COP26 Reflections: Enabling Business Action and Planetary Ambition]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/cop26-reflections-enabling-business-action-and-planetary-ambition</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/cop26-reflections-enabling-business-action-and-planetary-ambition</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read to learn about the highlights from COP26 and how SAP played a key role in enabling customers and partners.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_197553fc5247d5c614cb901e50b004a4a6f988c2f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_197553fc5247d5c614cb901e50b004a4a6f988c2f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_197553fc5247d5c614cb901e50b004a4a6f988c2f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="COP26 Reflections: Enabling Business Action and Planetary Ambition" src="./media_197553fc5247d5c614cb901e50b004a4a6f988c2f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="cop26-reflections-enabling-business-action-and-planetary-ambition">COP26 Reflections: Enabling Business Action and Planetary Ambition</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-all-news-and-coverage-from-cop26">Read all news and coverage from COP26</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/cop26">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>COP26 was the first UN climate conference that truly recognized the critical role of business in driving change, and it was the first Conference of the Parties SAP attended. Now that COP26 is over, we can reflect on almost two weeks of SAP activity on the ground.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Building on the 2015 Paris Agreement and following the IPCC’s <a href="https://www.ipcc.ch/report/sixth-assessment-report-working-group-i/">2021 Sixth Assessment</a> report that human activity is the unequivocal cause of rapid changes to the climate, COP26 recognized this sense of urgency. Two weeks of negotiations among more than 120 world leaders resulted in the <a href="https://unfccc.int/sites/default/files/resource/cma2021_L16_adv.pdf">Glasgow Climate Pact</a>, which gives a strong signal to countries and businesses to be more ambitious and focus on the action needed to protect the planet from further irreversible damage.</p>
  <p>The Glasgow Climate Pact mandates countries to do more and strengthen their 2030 targets next year. The countries agreed on the rules governing international carbon markets, mobilizing financial flows to developing countries, phasing down coal and phasing out inefficient fossil fuel subsidies, and reducing methane emissions. It also recognizes the importance of international partnerships and includes language on development and deployment of technologies and technology transfer. There were pledges by groups of countries to end deforestation and move finance to clean energy.</p>
  <p>SAP’s Chief Sustainability Officer Daniel Schmid, along with a small team representing SAP’s leadership in the topics of climate action, circular economy, consumer industries, and government affairs, explored how the event worked, understanding the science and engaging with businesses, policy makers, and startups to emphasize SAP’s role and impact. Given the context of <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a>, planning was chaotic and most other businesses reported a rush to finalize plans in the final few days.</p>
  <p>At COP26, we engaged in as many forums as possible across business, media, and government and were inspired by the many CEOs, CSOs, policy makers, activists, NGOs, partners, and startups. In the middle of all this, our circular economy team also launched a game-changing software solution – <a href="/2021/11/sap-responsible-design-and-production-accelerate-circular-economy">SAP Responsible Design and Production</a>.</p>
  <p>We constantly heard the phrase ‘You can’t manage what you can’t measure.’ In almost every forum, from every stakeholder group, this simple idea was repeated and re-emphasized. It was explicitly linked to the strengthening role of data and digital solutions for climate action.</p>
  <p>The Glasgow summit also saw significant business presence, something lacking in previous climate meetings. It emphasized our view that SAP is a critical stakeholder in the operating system of business and that coming to grips with climate in industry is first and foremost a question of getting transparency and alignment with the business processes that drive the problem. In terms of how the business world configures itself to a regenerative and net-positive future – another part of the COP26 business leaders’ lexicon – SAP holds the key to the door. The question is how do we empower each and every stakeholder group to unlock the collaboration and transformation needed across business, finance, policy makers, and NGOs.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="become-a-sustainable-business-with-sap">Become a sustainable business with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Following nearly two weeks and countless interactions, it’s clear that SAP’s role is to help these key stakeholder groups with:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Fostering the transparency needed on material impact across the full system</li>
    <li>Connecting businesses across complex business networks and ecosystems</li>
    <li>Engaging the Global South equitably in solutions and supporting the social dimension of climate change</li>
    <li>Offering the insights needed to support the right allocation of capital to support initiatives that deliver regenerative business outcomes</li>
    <li>Navigating the complex policy environment and climate legislations that need to be delivered post-COP26</li>
  </ul>
  <p>On reflection, our role as SAP should above all support the goals of COP26 by positively advocating and inspiring action based on what business technology can do.</p>
  <p>Ultimately, climate conferences like COP26 have a simple purpose – to keep the world within the 1.5 degrees Celsius average temperature increase from pre-industrialized levels and to mitigate the impacts of climate change. COP26 has moved the world closer and kept the possibility within reach.</p>
  <p>The pact and the pledges mean nothing unless they’re delivered at the national level. Governments must build policies to give a clear direction to businesses across sectors to reach a net-zero economy, backed by substantial investments and engagement with businesses to drive multi-stakeholder initiatives. COP26 triggers consistent engagement over the next decade and beyond; it’s not a one-time effort.</p>
  <p>Our role is to help make this possibility a reality and help drive the action needed across all markets and industries.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/cop26</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Start Acting on a Circular Economy and Eliminate Waste]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/acting-circular-economy-eliminate-waste</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/acting-circular-economy-eliminate-waste</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A new solution from SAP helps companies take responsibility for sustainability and implement processes to eliminate waste.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15e522acc50ca66011b3077f8e0d8ceb72ce5d880.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15e522acc50ca66011b3077f8e0d8ceb72ce5d880.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15e522acc50ca66011b3077f8e0d8ceb72ce5d880.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Start Acting on a Circular Economy and Eliminate Waste" src="./media_15e522acc50ca66011b3077f8e0d8ceb72ce5d880.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="start-acting-on-a-circular-economy-and-eliminate-waste">Start Acting on a Circular Economy and Eliminate Waste</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Thanks to consumer concern about the environmental impact of their favorite brands, companies are focused on producing more sustainable products and implementing processes to prevent materials from going to waste.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Currently only a fraction of our plastic waste – <a href="https://ellenmacarthurfoundation.org/the-new-plastics-economy-rethinking-the-future-of-plastics-and-catalysing">14%, according to a report</a> by the World Economic Forum and the Ellen MacArthur Foundation – is collected and recycled after use. The rest ends up in landfills or in the oceans and waterways, contributing to global warming.</p>
  <p>At the same time, new regulations and policies are being established, such as extended producer responsibility (EPR) regulations. These regulations help ensure that producers are responsible for the recycling, reuse, or disposal of their products. Additionally, impending plastic taxes being proposed in Europe that apply to plastic packaging produced or imported that do not contain a specified amount of recyclable content.</p>
  <p>This is great news for the planet, but the new scenario creates a market-by-market challenge, especially for large producers, as it is very difficult to manage product regulations across different geographies. In fact, managing thousands of products and materials across hundreds of regulatory systems in multiple regions is one of the greatest complexity challenges facing global brands in the years ahead.</p>
  <p>According to new regulations, companies are required not just to design products and packaging to eliminate waste and pollution. They also must keep materials in use at its highest value for the longest possible period of time. The bottom line is that companies will need to base future decisions on sustainability and recyclability. This change is driven by consumer demand, the availability of technology, and the new regulatory environment.</p>
  <p>Manufacturers embarking on transformational journeys are often challenged by complex supply chains, heavy assets, and legacy technology. They must also transition to new business models that require a circular approach to product design from the outset and new approaches like reintroducing the product or its materials back into the manufacturing process at the end of the life cycle.</p>
  <p>The <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/responsible-design-and-production.html">SAP Responsible Design and Production</a> solution responds to the drivers behind the change and helps businesses tackle these challenges.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10d98ea5c6b30b9d92deedd53cd894449f723ece9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10d98ea5c6b30b9d92deedd53cd894449f723ece9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10d98ea5c6b30b9d92deedd53cd894449f723ece9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP launches SAP Responsible Design and Production" src="./media_10d98ea5c6b30b9d92deedd53cd894449f723ece9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/hCUoogKpbYk">SAP launches SAP Responsible Design and Production</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Stephen Jamieson, global lead for Circular Economy Solutions at SAP, says the new solution will help enterprises tackle this complexity as they move away from a take-make-waste linear economy to a circular one designed to eliminate waste, circulate materials, and regenerate natural systems.</p>
  <p>“The solution is designed to help enterprises comply with regulations,” he explains. “It’s currently focused on packaging and plastics, but it will be further developed as different material categories such as batteries or textiles come into scope for regulatory intervention.”</p>
  <p>The complexity begins with the roughly 400 different regulatory schemes that are currently in place or planned around the world.</p>
  <p><a href="/">SAP Responsible Design and Production</a> is, first and foremost, about tackling the complexity of packaging regulations and new taxation regimes. This helps brands to accurately assess and calculate those implications, use these insights to inform how products and materials are designed, and optimize these choices. This collaboration is crucial, together with non-governmental organizations (NGOs) and partners, in accelerating the transition to a circular economy.</p>
  <h2 id="investing-for-the-long-term">Investing for the Long Term</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-sap-responsible-design-and-production">Learn more about SAP Responsible Design and Production</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/responsible-design-and-production.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Extended producer responsibility won’t come cheap. Jamieson cites the example of the UK, where one study <a href="https://www.foodmanufacture.co.uk/Article/2021/04/08/Alarm-as-packaging-consultation-predicts-2.7bn-EPR-cost?utm_source=copyright&#x26;utm_medium=OnSite&#x26;utm_campaign=copyright">predicts a cost of £2.7 billion</a> per year for post-consumer packaging waste. The UK scheme incentivizes producers to design packaging that is easy to recycle and helps ensure that they pay the full net cost to manage this packaging once it becomes waste, in line with the polluter-pays principle behind the EPR concept.</p>
  <p>That is the cost in the UK alone, which represents three percent of the world. “Do the math, and you’ll see the global impact,” says Jamieson. “Some of the larger manufacturers produce thousands of tons of materials each year. In these markets, you’re talking about very meaningful numbers. And don’t forget the plastic taxes, which tally up to £250 per ton in the UK and €400 a ton in the European Union.”</p>
  <p>That may sound like a high price to pay, but the benefits outweigh the cost. Visionary enterprises like Unilever find that short-term sustainability costs can lead to long-term savings. According to the company, it has <a href="https://www.unilever.com/Images/unilever-q4--and-full-year-2020-results-presentation_tcm244-558978_1_en.pdf">cut costs by US$1.5 billion since 2008 by improving efficiencies in factories and using fewer materials</a>.</p>
  <p>In the long run, the EPR approach encourages innovation in product and packaging design. Reuse and recycling consume less energy than manufacturing from new materials. As the costs of collection, processing, and recycling are shifted from taxpayers to the producers of the materials, enterprises will find ways to cover the EPR costs through savings in other areas.</p>
  <h2 id="how-it-works">How It Works</h2>
  <p>SAP Responsible Design and Production helps businesses manage EPR regulations and prepare for upcoming plastic taxes, a benefit for companies that want to get a head start on meeting their responsibilities</p>
  <p>As an example, the solution is designed to enable EPR experts at large global consumer products companies to accurately calculate the packaging fees and meet packaging regulations for a particular market. These experts must understand what declarations are necessary then ensure that they are reporting accurately to those bodies. They must assess the data, understand any exceptions and challenges to the data quality, and ensure everything is codified properly according to regulations. The solution then enables EPR experts to draft an assessment of the policies and fees at play, and finally, to run a formal declaration that will be used as the basis of the company’s payment to the relevant authorities.</p>
  <p>An overarching analytics layer allows category managers to see the projection and the implications of different regimes on their product portfolios. This offers a more strategic view for people like chief sustainability officers to see progress toward commitments, such as the elimination of problematic or unnecessary single-use packaging.</p>
  <p>Jamieson concludes that SAP Responsible Design and Production is essentially an extension of enterprise resource planning (ERP) — something SAP has been leading for 50 years — with an additional element. “Now, we’re not only planning the optimization of resources; we’re optimizing them to be regenerative.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Natasha Pergl is lead for Global Circular Economy at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-news-and-coverage-from-cop26">Read more news and coverage from COP26</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/cop26">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/cop26</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Releases New Solution to Accelerate the Circular Economy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-responsible-design-and-production-accelerate-circular-economy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-responsible-design-and-production-accelerate-circular-economy</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The new SAP Responsible Design and Production solution is for designing products sustainably and transitioning to a circular economy.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19e0cfbb3e7943d0d84e10c6c55541dd98476dbf3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19e0cfbb3e7943d0d84e10c6c55541dd98476dbf3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19e0cfbb3e7943d0d84e10c6c55541dd98476dbf3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Releases New Solution to Accelerate the Circular Economy" src="./media_19e0cfbb3e7943d0d84e10c6c55541dd98476dbf3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-releases-new-solution-to-accelerate-the-circular-economy">SAP Releases New Solution to Accelerate the Circular Economy</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-sap-responsible-design-and-production">Learn more about SAP Responsible Design and Production</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/responsible-design-and-production.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announces the availability of SAP Responsible Design and Production, a solution for designing products sustainably and transitioning to a circular economy.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This is the latest offering in a growing portfolio of sustainability-specific software applications that help businesses increase their measurement and data management capabilities.</p>
  <p>As sustainable business regulations, such as plastic taxes, are put in place, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/responsible-design-and-production.html">SAP Responsible Design and Production solution</a> enables brands to accelerate their transition to circular-economy business practices. The new solution helps companies gain better visibility of material flows through their processes including tracking and complying with rapidly changing regulations, especially those concerning product packaging and plastics. As businesses increasingly develop sustainable products, managing materials and regulatory data is becoming one of the most complex challenges across the consumer industry today.</p>
  <p>“The circular economy is based on three principles, driven by design — eliminate waste and pollution, circulate products and materials, and regenerate nature,” said Andrew Morlet, CEO, <a href="https://ellenmacarthurfoundation.org/">Ellen MacArthur Foundation</a>. “Digital solutions play an important role in the transition to a circular economy. They enable businesses to embed circular practices across their operations, from designing products to reduce waste from the outset, to tracking the lifecycle of the materials they use.”</p>
  <p>With SAP’s new solution, businesses can embed circularity principles into core business processes, helping eliminate waste and unlock new value by designing products to be sustainable from inception. For example, a shampoo brand manager has visibility into the full product lifecycle, including their extended producer responsibility (EPR) obligations and the plastic taxes of different markets. This visibility helps the brand manager make design changes to reduce waste and decisions on how to lower the costs of the downstream reuse and recycling systems.</p>
  <p>“Every year, we use almost twice the amount of resources than the planet can regenerate,” said Scott Russell, member of the Executive Board of SAP SE and head of Customer Success, “Business can play a crucial role in keeping value in our systems for longer through smart, responsible product design that reuses resources rather than disposing of them. There is inherent complexity in designing products that eliminate waste and use responsible materials, but SAP Responsible Design and Production tackles that complexity and offers a ‘gold-standard’ solution to our customers, helping to deliver circular products and achieve a regenerative economy.”</p>
  <p>SAP Responsible Design and Production, a cloud-native solution co-developed with <a href="https://newsroom.accenture.com/news/accenture-and-sap-extend-partnership-to-help-companies-accelerate-sustainability-transformation-drive-new-sources-of-value-and-lead-in-the-circular-economy.htm">Accenture</a> on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a>, provides tailored intelligence that enables businesses to keep pace with EPR regulations and plastic taxes, embed circularity principles into core business processes and optimize design for sustainable business. Learn more by reading the blog “<a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/05/21/helping-business-thrive-in-a-circular-economy/">Helping Business Thrive in a Circular Economy</a>.”</p>
  <p>SAP has led by example as a sustainable business for more than a decade. In addition to being named the software industry leader in the <a href="/2020/11/dow-jones-sustainability-indices-sap-again-leads">Dow Jones Sustainability Indices</a> (DJSI) for 14 consecutive years, the <a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.sap.com%2Fintegrated-reports%2F2020%2Fen.html&#x26;data=04%7C01%7CCameron.Baker%40edelman.com%7C6fe81550b14a4592eea308d95dd601d6%7Cb824bfb3918e43c2bb1cdcc1ba40a82b%7C0%7C0%7C637643996927963163%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C1000&#x26;sdata=Fi22Vatgtc0gQD8YUjmw3BUZqTabx4hqwenHYSnJdgk%3D&#x26;reserved=0">SAP Integrated Report</a> and SAP’s membership in the <a href="/2019/08/value-balancing-alliance-sap-founding-member">Value Balancing Alliance</a> illustrate our commitment to integrating economic, environmental and social performance to drive business decisions.</p>
  <p>To learn more, check out <a href="/topics/cop26">SAP at COP26</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability/economy.html">SAP solutions for sustainability</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-news-and-coverage-from-cop26">Read more news and coverage from COP26</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/cop26">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a> and follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong></p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as a sustainable intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into sustainable intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Stacy Ries, +1 (484) 619-0411, <a href="mailto:stacy.ries@sap.com">stacy.ries@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/cop26</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrating Climate Action End to End]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/integrating-climate-action-end-to-end</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/integrating-climate-action-end-to-end</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how SAP is tackling climate action by embedding sustainability into its portfolio and across its purpose, strategy, and operations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10563aea73452ab4df96f0b3c9ac9b08a7bf73965.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10563aea73452ab4df96f0b3c9ac9b08a7bf73965.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10563aea73452ab4df96f0b3c9ac9b08a7bf73965.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Integrating Climate Action End to End" src="./media_10563aea73452ab4df96f0b3c9ac9b08a7bf73965.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="integrating-climate-action-end-to-end">Integrating Climate Action End to End</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The climate emergency has reached a new peak. To help accelerate the transformation toward a low-carbon, circular future, SAP is embedding sustainability end to end in its portfolio, as well as across its purpose, vision, strategy, and business operations.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Climate change is widespread, rapid, and intensifying, with some trends now irreversible, according to the recent <a href="https://www.ipcc.ch/report/ar6/wg1/">6th Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC) report</a>.</p>
  <p>The science is clear: unless immediate, fast, and large-scale action is taken to reduce emissions, the average global temperature is likely to reach, or cross, the 1.5° C warming threshold within 20 years. The alarming results are already with us, ranging from droughts and heat waves to wildfires and devastating flooding worldwide.</p>
  <p>While much hope is focused on a green recovery, the window of opportunity is closing fast. The latest report from the International Energy Agency (IEA) predicts that energy-related <a href="https://www.iea.org/reports/global-energy-review-2021/co2-emissions">carbon emissions are on course to surge again by 1.5 billion tons in 2021</a>, an increase of nearly 5% year-over-year and the second-largest in history, taking us back to pre-COVID-19 peak levels.</p>
  <p>The urgency to dramatically change course and accelerate decarbonization has never been higher. But only when businesses are moving beyond their siloed approaches, commitments, and climate pledges to fully embrace sustainability and embed these ambitions in an integrated way will we be able to drive the systemic change needed.</p>
  <p>It is a journey toward embedding sustainability across everything we do.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="register-today-for-the-upcoming-sap-sustainability-day">Register today for the upcoming SAP Sustainability Day</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="moving-away-from-add-on-to-core">Moving Away From Add-On to Core</h2>
  <p>Companies need to avoid thinking of sustainability as only an add-on to their strategies and operations. They need to integrate it across the business. Rather than defining a separate sustainability strategy, it is crucial to <a href="https://insights.sap.com/environmental-sustainability-affects-competitiveness/">set a corporate business strategy that is sustainable</a>.</p>
  <p>A first step toward SAP realizing this was linking sustainability to our purpose of helping the world run better and improving people’s lives. The objective: create positive economic, environmental, and social impact within <a href="https://stockholmresilience.org/research/planetary-boundaries.html">planetary boundaries</a> with special focus on climate action, circular economy, social responsibility, and holistic steering and reporting.</p>
  <p>This is reflected not only in the updated SAP vision to “reinvent how the world runs as a network of intelligent, sustainable enterprises,” but also in the executive compensation that rewards Executive Board members for customer loyalty, employee commitment, and SAP’s carbon impact, along with financial performance.</p>
  <h2 id="enabling-climate-action-through-technology">Enabling Climate Action Through Technology</h2>
  <p>The IPCC report has once again highlighted that harnessing the innovation power of enterprises has to be at the center of fighting climate change. For SAP, this means using digitalization to contribute to the United Nations Sustainable Development Goals (UN SDGs), <a href="https://www.sap.com/dmc/exp/2021-04-74301-unglobalgoals/Climate_Action">including #13, Climate Action</a>.</p>
  <p>In collaboration with customers and partners, SAP is working to optimize material, financial, and energy flows throughout end-to-end business processes in order to address planetary and social challenges. For example, <a href="/2020/06/climate-21-track-greenhouse-gas-emissions">the company’s multi-year Climate 21 program</a> helps build analytical and transactional capabilities into enterprise applications that can help SAP customers understand and minimize the greenhouse gas footprint of their products and operations along their value chains.</p>
  <p>During the <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">SAP Sustainability Summit</a> in April, <a href="/2021/06/sapphire-now-sustainability-management-by-sap">sustainability management by SAP</a> was introduced, providing an expanded portfolio of sustainability-specific solutions, including <a href="/2021/09/sap-product-footprint-management-launch">SAP Product Footprint Management</a>, which has been available since September 2021. There is more to come with the releases of the <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/05/21/helping-business-thrive-in-a-circular-economy/">SAP Responsible Design and Production</a> and SAP Sustainability Control Tower solutions in the next months, as will be shown during <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">SAP Sustainability Day October 28</a></p>
  <p><a href="https://sap.io/">SAP.iO</a> Foundries locations Berlin and Munich are fostering startup innovation by setting up the <a href="/2021/03/sapio-sustainable-future-cohort-accenture">Sustainable Future program</a> together with Accenture. The equity-free program is designed to propel digital transformation in four target areas: carbon tracking and trading, resource efficiency, climate risk tracking and mitigation, and circular economy.</p>
  <h2 id="setting-ambitious-targets">Setting Ambitious Targets</h2>
  <p>In addition to harnessing innovation, the climate emergency calls for bold targets for decarbonization. By mid-2021, countries representing around 65% of global carbon dioxide emissions and more than 70% of the world economy have made ambitious commitments to carbon neutrality. The U.S, the European Union, Japan, the Republic of Korea, and others — in total 126 countries — have pledged carbon neutrality by 2050; China says it will do so before 2060.</p>
  <p>The private sector also needs to step up. More than 1,900 companies, including SAP in 2017, have set emissions reduction targets grounded in climate science through the <a href="https://sciencebasedtargets.org/about-the-science-based-targets-initiative/">Science Based Targets initiative</a>.</p>
  <p>In 2019, SAP raised its commitment and adopted a <a href="/2019/07/sap-emissions-reduction-targets">1.5° C science-based emissions reduction targets</a> aligned with a net-zero future. However, the journey started much earlier; back in 2009, SAP set the first goal of reducing its global carbon emissions to the year-2000 level by 2020. <a href="/2018/03/sap-integrated-report-2020-targets-met-early">This target was met at the end of 2017</a>, even though SAP grew more than fourfold over the period.</p>
  <p>The next milestone is 2023, when SAP aims to be <a href="/2021/03/sap-carbon-neutrality-goal-2023">carbon neutral in its own operations</a> – two years earlier than previously envisaged. This includes all direct (Scope 1), indirect (Scope 2), and selected categories of value chain (Scope 3) carbon emissions, such as business flights, employee commuting, paper consumption, and external data centers (co-locations and hyperscalers).</p>
  <h2 id="monitoring-and-reporting">Monitoring and Reporting</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="chasing-zero-the-future-can-be-greener-cleaner-and-more-equal">Chasing Zero: The future can be greener, cleaner, and more equal</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html#chasing-zero">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It is essential to measure and monitor progress on the path toward achieving these targets. For example, SAP has increasingly embraced holistic steering and reporting because connecting financial and pre-financial performance leads to better management decisions and business success.</p>
  <p>SAP’s sustainability and annual reports were merged into the <a href="http://www.sapintegratedreport.com">SAP Integrated Report</a> in 2012. Since then, both material and immaterial value creation have been at the center of the company’s reporting and have been placed on an equal footing. Besides key financial information, environmental progress, workforce information, and social investments have been made transparent. In addition, an internal sustainability dashboard allows employees to explore the key sustainability key performance indicators (KPIs), such as women in management and carbon emissions by their country, location, and line of business, with updates every quarter.</p>
  <p>Our reporting shows that in 2020, SAP was able to overachieve by 43% on its target for net carbon emissions in 2020, generating 135 kilotons instead of the anticipated 238 kilotons. This trend continued in the first half of 2021, during which SAP’s carbon emissions totaled 45 kilotons compared to 90 kilotons in the first half of 2020 (-37%).</p>
  <p>The low emissions level is a consequence of the ongoing <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> pandemic, as well as the introduction of <a href="/2021/06/pledge-to-flex-future-of-work-at-sap">Pledge to Flex</a>, which enables a more flexible mix of remote and onsite work. SAP believes this trend will continue and has just announced in its <a href="https://www.sap.com/docs/download/investors/2021/sap-2021-half-year-report.pdf">2021 half-year report</a> that it has lowered its 2021 carbon emissions outlook from 145 kilotons to a range of 90-110 kilotons.</p>
  <h2 id="taking-action-measures-of-implementation">Taking Action: Measures of Implementation</h2>
  <p>To become <a href="/2017/05/sap-to-go-carbon-neutral-by-2025">carbon neutral in its own operations by 202</a>3, SAP is following a three-pillar approach: <strong>avoid</strong>, <strong>reduce</strong>, <strong>compensate</strong>.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Avoid:</strong> Whenever possible, SAP aims to avoid the creation of greenhouse gases. This is a top priority, supported by, for example, using virtual telecommunication instead of business flights.</li>
    <li><strong>Reduce:</strong> If greenhouse gas emissions cannot be avoided, SAP aims to drive efficiency and reduce all types of emissions; for example, building efficiency, data center operations, carpooling and car sharing, and e-mobility.</li>
    <li><strong>Compensate:</strong> SAP has extended its compensation models for travel. For business flights, it has introduced an internal carbon price to offset related carbon emissions. If greenhouse gas emissions cannot be eliminated altogether, SAP aims to reduce them through innovations in the areas of building efficiency, data center operations, carpooling, and car sharing, as well as e-mobility. For example, SAP has powered its own data centers and facilities with 100% renewable electricity since 2014, implemented an environmental management system with ISO 14001 certification in more than 30 countries and ISO 50001 at headquarters, adopting green IT initiatives in order to foster sustainable IT equipment usage and promoting tools such as <a href="https://www.ecosia.org/">Ecosia</a> as a default search engine.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>In 2020, SAP implemented additional energy and climate measures within its operations, ranging from opening a new office with energy-efficient design in Australia and implementing more efficient data center technology in Germany to introducing a bike fleet at SAP Hungary as well as a flexible mobility budget in Germany and installation of photovoltaic systems in Austria.</p>
  <p>For emissions that cannot yet be reduced or avoided, SAP thirdly invests in high-quality carbon credits. For example, <a href="/2020/08/sap-lcf-investment-livelihoods-carbon-funds">SAP has been a long-term investor of the Livelihoods Carbon Funds (LCF) since 2012</a>. SAP has also donated funds to restore ecosystems and improve people’s lives. In support of the UN Decade on Ecosystem Restoration 2021-2030, SAP recently joined the 1t.org corporate alliance, which aims to conserve, restore, and grow trees worldwide, with a <a href="/2021/07/enhancing-sustainability-people-technology-21-million-trees">pledge to plant 21 million trees by the end of 2025</a>.</p>
  <p>I am proud that SAP’s efforts to combat climate change and to strengthen its transparent reporting are <a href="/2021/01/corporate-knights-cdp-sap-top-esg-ratings">externally recognized</a>. The non-profit organization CDP included SAP on its <a href="https://www.cdp.net/en/companies/companies-scores?cid=9205306762&#x26;adgpid=95799580520&#x26;itemid=&#x26;targid=kwd-870315494871&#x26;mt=b&#x26;loc=9041983&#x26;ntwk=g&#x26;dev=c&#x26;dmod=&#x26;adp=&#x26;gclid=EAIaIQobChMIxpSS4e_Z7gIVjLh3Ch2xkAciEAAYASAAEgLpJPD_BwE">A List 2020</a>, thereby granting us the top rating for leading in environmental transparency and action.</p>
  <h2 id="partnering">Partnering</h2>
  <p>SAP recognizes that strong partnerships are an invaluable asset in tackling climate change. This is why we became a founding member of the European Green Digital Coalition and joined the World Economic Forum Stakeholder Capitalism Coalition and CEO Climate Leaders as well as the World Business Council for Sustainable Development (WBCSD), complementing our previous engagements with the UN Global Compact, the We Mean Business Coalition, the Value Balancing Alliance, the Ellen MacArthur Foundation, and many more.</p>
  <p>In addition, we signed the <a href="https://eur01.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.wemeanbusinesscoalition.org%2Fg20-2021%2F&#x26;data=04%7C01%7Cpreeti.srivastav%40eu.asahibeer.com%7C6b7d2eeaddaf447c6e2e08d97822af12%7C7ef011f8898a4d0182329087b2c2abaf%7C0%7C0%7C637672913526232765%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000&#x26;sdata=jX%2BiZ7Ipm3Wm9sXEgD6AbZ%2BWKk%2B4sePJIfTDXi7qNEI%3D&#x26;reserved=0">business letter to the G20</a> calling for greater climate ambition and we launched <a href="/topics/chasing-zero">Chasing Zero</a>, a new initiative that will feature executive thought leadership, best practices, and insights into a sustainability-related transformation of SAP and its global ecosystem to achieve zero emissions, zero waste, and zero inequality. The transition to a circular economy remains central to our vision for a world of zero waste and plastic free oceans by 2030. Consequently, we support stronger circular economy policies, such as the Worldwide Fund for Nature’s OneSource Coalition and the Ellen MacArthur Foundation’s Extended Producer Responsibility endorsement.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Daniel Schmid is chief sustainability officer of SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-21</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainability Management by SAP: Enabling Tomorrow Starts Today]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sapphire-now-sustainability-management-by-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sapphire-now-sustainability-management-by-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Sustainability management by SAP supports organizations on the journey to becoming sustainable enterprises. Read the news from SAPPHIRE NOW.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-21</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable Business Is Better Business for All]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-and-accenture-sustainability-better-business</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-and-accenture-sustainability-better-business</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Accenture are committed to working together and with customers to make sustainability ambitions a reality. Learn more about how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16958860638d1cb15960c1b14b8ecc6ccf1606de3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16958860638d1cb15960c1b14b8ecc6ccf1606de3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16958860638d1cb15960c1b14b8ecc6ccf1606de3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Sustainable Business Is Better Business for All" src="./media_16958860638d1cb15960c1b14b8ecc6ccf1606de3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sustainable-business-is-better-business-for-all">Sustainable Business Is Better Business for All</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Sustainability is the business challenge of our lifetimes.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Customers are increasingly educated and demand products and services that minimize negative environmental impact. Investors are integrating climate risk in their portfolio strategies. Government regulation is on the rise around the world, affecting carbon emissions, waste management, product design, and producer responsibility. Employees are increasingly vocal about their employer’s environmental policies and actions, making it challenging for businesses to recruit top talent without a genuine environmental vision and track record.</p>
  <p>Based on Accenture research*, enterprises with high ratings for environmental and social governance (ESG) performance attained operating margins nearly four-times higher than those with low ESG ratings and generated annual total returns to shareholders that were double their peers. According <a href="https://www.accenture.com/us-en/insights/strategy/ungcceostudy">Accenture and United Nations (UN) Global Compact research</a>, 54% of CEOs agree sustainability is critical to the future success of their organizations, and 71% of investors believe the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> will accentuate global policies to tackle risks related to climate change.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="catch-up-on-the-virtual-sap-sustainability-summit">Catch up on the virtual SAP Sustainability Summit</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="from-periphery-to-core">From Periphery to Core</h2>
  <p>Enterprises must show accountability through ESG performance and manage end-to-end operations responsibly. By reimagining its business model, any company can operate in an intelligent way, minimize negative environmental impact, and unleash a new dimension of enterprise resource planning (ERP). Decision-makers can use this intelligence to design better products, create engaging experiences, and equip employees to do their best work by eliminating busywork. They can create an efficient, ethical, and adaptable supply chain, reaching beyond organizations and first-tier suppliers to proactively manage performance and risks with trading partners around the world.</p>
  <p>Just like any other core business function, sustainability performance must also be managed in real time and integrated into wider business decision making. True, integrated reporting will go hand-in-hand with ESG management, and information transparency will provide a solid foundation to optimize financial results and sustainability performance together.</p>
  <p>Most companies have a long way to go before they move beyond the basics of simply reporting ESG performance to actively steering their business operations toward ambitious sustainability goals. While the UN Global Compact’s SDG Ambition program has challenged companies to enhance their commitment to the UN Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs), only <a href="https://www.accenture.com/us-en/insights/strategy/ungcceostudy">25% have set goals</a> aligned to societal or environmental needs. Although CEOs acknowledge the universal call-to-action to achieve a better and more sustainable future for all, <a href="https://www.accenture.com/us-en/insights/strategy/ungcceostudy">less than 50% have implemented sustainability</a> into their operations.</p>
  <h2 id="words-into-actions">Words into Actions</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-power-of-partnership-with-sap">Learn more about the power of partnership with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/partner.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1990c15effec3554d7ecb9b3e997d769082f31fb7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1990c15effec3554d7ecb9b3e997d769082f31fb7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1990c15effec3554d7ecb9b3e997d769082f31fb7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Graphic: SAP and Accenture Sustainability Goals" src="./media_1990c15effec3554d7ecb9b3e997d769082f31fb7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="800" height="950">
    </picture>If we plan to deliver on the UN SDGs by 2030, the performance of every process and product must be measured, managed, and delivered against sustainability goals. It is an imperative that spans across the value chain – from companies’ key design decisions to product lifecycle management.
  </p>
  <p>SAP and Accenture believe that steering a company holistically – by looking not only at financials, but also at the social and green bottom lines – leads to better management decisions and more resiliency in their value chain. SAP S/4HANA helps companies to drive bottom line profitability through operational efficiency, top line growth and adaptability. It offers flexible business model innovation and transparency into its green line environmental responsibility. SAP and Accenture’s goal is to make sustainability profitable and profitability sustainable.</p>
  <p>To achieve this, enterprises must integrate sustainability into the heart of their strategy and core business systems. This is the rationale behind the collaboration between SAP and Accenture, which focuses on innovation, development, and scaling sustainability across four go-to-market sustainability initiatives:</p>
  <p><strong>SDG Ambition: Scaling Business Impact for Decade of Action</strong></p>
  <p>The first of these initiatives is our partnership with the UN Global Compact on the SDG Ambition. Announced at the World Economic Forum 2020 in Davos with 3M as Patron Sponsor, SAP and Accenture are rolling out the SDG Ambition <a href="https://newsroom.accenture.com/news/un-global-compact-in-partnership-with-accenture-and-sap-and-with-3m-as-patron-sponsor-launch-sdg-ambition-guidance-to-accelerate-business-action-to-achieve-the-sdgs.htm">Benchmarks and Guidance</a> through the <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2021/02/08/2170997/0/en/New-programme-to-accelerate-business-action-on-the-Sustainable-Development-Goals-starts-with-600-companies-in-65-countries.html">UNGC Accelerator Program</a>. This includes how to implement these goals at a systemic level and how to develop new capabilities powered by SAP technologies. As of today, more than 600 companies have already signed up for the program.</p>
  <p>SAP and Accenture are working together to co-innovate and develop new SAP solutions that address sustainability and enhance existing core technologies. Both new and existing systems have a role to play in the other three joint sustainability initiatives.</p>
  <p><strong>Circular Economy: Taking Action Toward a Zero-Waste Economy</strong></p>
  <p>The power of SAP and Accenture’s partnership enables their customers to better manage material flows through their supply chains and innovate business processes to accelerate the circular economy. The initial focus is on packaging in the consumer goods and retail industries, specifically accelerating the development and delivery of the SAP Responsible Design and Production solution. Designing and promoting reusable products to address waste management is a fundamental principle of the circular economy.</p>
  <p><strong>Decarbonization: Enabling Our Customers to Contribute to a Zero-Carbon Economy</strong></p>
  <p>SAP and Accenture are working together to offer intelligent technologies that help companies – especially in natural resources, energy, and utilities – account, analyze, manage, and ultimately reduce carbon emissions. If companies cannot account for and manage total carbon emissions, they could lose their competitive edge. Solutions such as the <a href="/2020/06/decade-delivery-climate-21">Climate 21 initiative</a> and SAP Product Footprint Management help companies to embed sustainability as a new dimension of success into their analytical and transactional applications to enable ERP and intelligent enterprise to optimize their resources not only of an individual enterprise but across value chains for the entire product life cycle.</p>
  <p><strong>Startups: Collaborating with Innovators to Create a Positive Impact on Both Society and Business</strong></p>
  <p>Accenture and SAP are also tapping into their respective global innovation networks to nurture and engage startups through a <a href="https://sap.io/sustainablefuture/">sustainability focused startup program</a> to help address climate action, carbon reporting, and circular economy challenges across industries. Together, SAP and Accenture will leverage this rich source of creativity to help solve our customers’ biggest sustainability challenges.</p>
  <h2 id="helping-companies-become-twin-transformers">Helping Companies Become “Twin Transformers”</h2>
  <p>Untapped value exists at the intersection of digital technologies and sustainability, though only a few companies – referred to <a href="https://www.accenture.com/us-en/insights/strategy/european-double-up">as “Twin Transformers” by Accenture</a> – already link the two.</p>
  <p>From now on, twin transformation – directing innovation investment to initiatives that combine sustainability impact and the power of technology as opposed to splitting resources between advancing sustainability and technology deployment – will be critical to success. Companies that harness emerging technologies while finding new sources of value and pushing for green operations will gain a competitive advantage.</p>
  <p>Our customers provide daily proof of just how relevant our solutions are. Together, SAP and Accenture are committed to working with customers to make their sustainability ambitions a reality.</p>
  <p>We are showcasing our vision to jointly build a sustainable future at the <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">SAP Sustainability Summit</a> on April 28 and 29. Stay tuned for updates!</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><em>Jan Gilg is president of SAP S/4HANA at SAP.</em><br><em>Peter Lacy is chief responsibility officer and Global Sustainability Services lead at Accenture.</em></p>
        <p><em>*Source: Research analysis by Arabesque S Ray</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>