<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/partners/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Partners Recognized for Outstanding Achievements]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-successfactors-partners-recognized-for-achievements</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-successfactors-partners-recognized-for-achievements</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors partners received SAP Global Line of Business Partner Excellence Awards for 2024. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-global-lob-partner-excellence-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Defining the AI Opportunity for SAP and Our Partners]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-partners-ai-opportunity</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-partners-ai-opportunity</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and partners are seizing the AI opportunity, providing new solutions backed by expertise, business process knowledge, and SAP system data.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a591bef8055a8ff0903470a566a95b31994c8267.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a591bef8055a8ff0903470a566a95b31994c8267.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a591bef8055a8ff0903470a566a95b31994c8267.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Defining the AI Opportunity for SAP and Our Partners" src="./media_1a591bef8055a8ff0903470a566a95b31994c8267.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="defining-the-ai-opportunity-for-sap-and-our-partners">Defining the AI Opportunity for SAP and Our Partners</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Artificial intelligence is by far the disruptor of the decade. It can search, summarize, and analyze vast data stores, putting data-driven insights at employees’ fingertips in a matter of minutes. It can also generate content, anything from text to software code, streamlining workflows and saving precious time and money.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>And that’s just the surface. We are still learning just how far reaching the implications could be in the workplace.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-ai-revolutionary-technology-real-world-results">SAP Business AI: Revolutionary technology. Real-world results.</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As we explore this new realm and AI’s vast potential, SAP has adjusted its strategy with the goal of becoming not only the leading enterprise application provider but also the No. 1 business AI company. The foundation is now available with SAP Business AI that offers SAP customers a reliable, relevant, and responsible AI solution portfolio.</p>
  <p>A key element of that strategy is leveraging SAP partners’ expertise. The trusted relationships our partners have developed with our joint customers are essential to communicating the value of AI solutions from SAP and finding the best SAP products to meet their business objectives. It also poses a great opportunity for partners to expand their business.</p>
  <p>But first, let’s take a step back and explore why SAP is best positioned to deliver on the business AI opportunity.</p>
  <h2 id="saps-ai-advantage">SAP’s AI Advantage</h2>
  <p><strong>Deep Business Process Knowledge</strong><br>Before AI can make operations faster, data-driven, and more effective, organizations must optimize business processes. SAP brings a deep understanding of business processes to AI applications, enabling solutions that orchestrate workflows, data sharing, and automation for the greatest efficiency and productivity.</p>
  <p><strong>SAP Data</strong> AI solutions require data to train their algorithms to provide accurate, relevant, real-world outputs. SAP can draw on business data from thousands of customer systems across the value chain, helping to address our customers’ challenges and drive their digital transformation.</p>
  <p><strong>Focus on Application Creation</strong> SAP is partnering with technology providers to make the most of the AI opportunity by creating value with new applications. For example, large language models (LLMs) will become solution differentiators. LLMs perform a range of natural language processing tasks. Combining LLMs with AI solutions automates insight delivery, freeing users from the need to wait for help from their IT or data science departments. It allows companies to focus on data insights, rather than devoting focus to the technology that produces them.</p>
  <p><strong>Strong Partner Ecosystem</strong><br>SAP recognizes that it cannot reach the full addressable market alone. That is why our more than 25,500 partner ecosystem is a huge advantage when offering business AI solutions. Working together, we can drive innovation, accelerate AI road maps, and expand AI capabilities beyond its own limitations.</p>
  <p>I cannot underscore enough how important that fourth component is to our AI strategy. It is a linchpin to our success. That’s why we must ensure we are creating win-win scenarios for our partners that benefit us both for the long term.</p>
  <h2 id="partner-opportunities">Partner Opportunities</h2>
  <p>While AI offers a range of benefits to SAP customers, it also represents a significant business opportunity for SAP partners. As a part of the SAP ecosystem, partners can provide advanced functionality out of the box with embedded AI capabilities within SAP applications. They must also take advantage of the virtually endless opportunities that AI offers regardless of the chosen SAP partner business model:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Sell:</strong> Partners that resell SAP solutions can leverage the embedded AI portfolio from SAP to accelerate RISE with SAP and GROW with SAP deals. Sell partners can also enhance the appeal of the cloud with AI capabilities exclusive to SAP cloud solutions and enlarge deals with AI units from SAP required for premium AI capabilities.</li>
    <li><strong>Service:</strong> Service partners can drive adoption of SAP’s AI portfolio and custom AI capabilities built on SAP by bundling them with services and support. This approach enables customers to gain value through customized generative AI use cases built on the foundation of SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP), including the generative AI hub, and accelerate their cloud migrations and business transformation, backed by partners’ expertise.</li>
    <li><strong>Innovate:</strong> Partners also have the opportunity to develop innovative AI solutions and extensions to enhance the SAP portfolio. Partners can build customer-specific and repeatable use cases with AI services from SAP on SAP BTP and augment customer business processes.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="take-the-next-step">Take the Next Step</h2>
  <p>Ready to expand your partnership with SAP to build on the AI opportunity? <a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/products/aic/about.html">Explore our AI portfolio</a> and visit <a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/partnership/manage/expand.html">SAP Partner Portal site to learn more</a>. If you’re not currently an SAP partner, there’s never been a better time to explore the benefits of becoming a part of the SAP ecosystem.</p>
  <p>If you’re ready to start your SAP partnership journey and provide businesses in your market with reliable, effective AI solutions, <a href="https://www.sap.com/partners/partner-program.html">get started here today</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Karl Fahrbach is chief partner officer at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="win-more-customers-and-grow-revenue-with-the-help-of-saps-award-winning-partner-program-and-portfolio-of-industry-leading-solutions">Win more customers and grow revenue with the help of SAP’s award-winning partner program and portfolio of industry-leading solutions</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/partners/partner-program.html">Explore how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Global Line of Business Partner Excellence Awards: 2024 Winners and Finalists]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-global-lob-partner-excellence-awards-2024-winners-finalists</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-global-lob-partner-excellence-awards-2024-winners-finalists</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Global LoB Partner Excellence Awards celebrate partners' contributions to our cloud ambitions. Here are the 2024 finalists and winners.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-global-lob-partner-excellence-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Smart Manufacturing Creates Opportunity for Partner-Driven, AI-Infused Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-partner-ai-innovation-smart-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-partner-ai-innovation-smart-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In the age of business AI, SAP partners are developing and delivering industry innovations across discrete manufacturing.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_149e02fca5b080a1038dfae06eb31000b8cc98754.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_149e02fca5b080a1038dfae06eb31000b8cc98754.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_149e02fca5b080a1038dfae06eb31000b8cc98754.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Smart Manufacturing Creates Opportunity for Partner-Driven, AI-Infused Innovation" src="./media_149e02fca5b080a1038dfae06eb31000b8cc98754.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="smart-manufacturing-creates-opportunity-for-partner-driven-ai-infused-innovation">Smart Manufacturing Creates Opportunity for Partner-Driven, AI-Infused Innovation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>One of the perks of my job is that I get to spend a considerable amount of time with our industry partners. Whether I’m talking with a startup software company or an established global service partner, two words — two letters actually — are the hot topic of almost every engagement lately: artificial intelligence, specifically <strong>business AI</strong>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-at-hannover-messe-bring-out-new-manufacturing-excellence">SAP at Hannover Messe: Bring out new manufacturing excellence</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://events.sap.com/hannovermesse/en/home">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As we navigate this brave new world of business AI, SAP partners are playing an essential role as equal parts technology disrupters, trusted advisors, and innovation multipliers. They work and live at the edge, breaking technology rules with every new solution and innovation they bring to the table. These companies are passionate about their AI-driven solutions, which will provide what SAP manufacturing customers want most for their businesses nowadays: more efficiency, accuracy, and agility in their production operations and supply chains. Their energy and passion are positioning them to redefine the rules of engagement regarding how partner ecosystems work.</p>
  <p>It doesn’t matter what kind of partner you are — you could be on the build, implement/service, or sell sides of the SAP partner ecosystem, the opportunities to innovate, and co-innovate with SAP and other partners, solutions that bring value to customers in discrete manufacturing industries are as limitless as our imaginations. It’s an exciting time to be an SAP industry partner.</p>
  <h2 id="innovative-solutions-from-sap-and-partners-give-our-manufacturing-customers-a-competitive-edge">Innovative Solutions from SAP and Partners Give Our Manufacturing Customers a Competitive Edge</h2>
  <p>Giving our manufacturing customers the business AI solutions they need to thrive in highly competitive and often volatile markets is an absolute must. Whether those solutions are developed by an SAP partner, SAP itself, or collaboratively is secondary.</p>
  <p>This new drive to co-innovate on our customers’ behalf is creating opportunities for partners to develop and deliver industry innovations in three areas of discrete manufacturing:</p>
  <ol>
    <li><strong>Solutions that enable efficient, accurate, and agile manufacturing and supply chains</strong> by integrating processes, removing data silos, and seamlessly connecting manufacturing and supply chain applications with the whole of the business.</li>
    <li><strong>Solutions that improve decision-making</strong> by using AI to analyze data from internal and external sources in context and produce insights that increase manufacturing operations’ resilience and help customers strike the right balance among cost, sustainability, and customer satisfaction.</li>
    <li><strong>Solutions that promote collaboration within a business ecosystem</strong>. Many of the company executives I’ve spoken with recently wanted to talk about Manufacturing-X, the growing cross-industry initiative in which companies across various manufacturing value chains come together within a global business ecosystem to define a standard that enables them to share production and supply chain data across platforms and technology to further increase resilience, sustainability, and competitiveness.</li>
  </ol>
  <p>We are bringing this customer-focused, partner-driven approach to life this week at Hannover Messe, bringing center stage the latest, most compelling innovations to emerge from SAP and our partner ecosystem, across both discrete and process manufacturing — many embedded with business AI.</p>
  <p>Some of the showcases that have been developed collaboratively in action include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Modular manufacturing that orchestrates production cells with a hard independent fleet manager</li>
    <li>High-speed bottling that captures traceability data and in-line quality assurance</li>
    <li>A centralized operations control center that manages an offsite process production line</li>
    <li>AI-enhanced visual inspection and guided instructions during component assembly</li>
    <li>A quick guided journey through an Industrial Metaverse, showing how assets inside a power plant can be intelligently and remotely managed</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP partners are playing an integral part in our presence at Hannover Messe, just as they are in our overarching industry vision. Partners including Accenture, Camelot ITLab, Cideon Software &#x26; Services, FORCAM, Kinexon, Systema, and TeamViewer are all exhibiting their solutions alongside their SAP counterparts, demonstrating the true power of partnership and innovation at every turn.</p>
  <p>By leveraging resources like the new SAP AI Launchpad and generative AI hub, our partners will introduce industry innovations that will add immediate value for customers in the discrete and process manufacturing space. Hence, they have the intelligent digital tools they need to be future-ready.</p>
  <p>Kinexon’s OS extension to the SAP Digital Manufacturing solution is one example. Kinexon OS orchestrates the shop floor and automates previously manual processes, improving production speed, quality, and asset utilization. It is providing customers with an essential pathway to modular production and autonomous manufacturing.</p>
  <p>For those of you at the event, stop by the SAP space and experience innovation and partnership in perfect harmony firsthand. An electric injection molding machine developed by Fanuc with support from partner Syntax will be cranking out made-to-order drinking vessels.</p>
  <p>Come enjoy a cup of inspiration on us. It’s a small but meaningful taste of what’s possible for partners in our collaborative, customer-focused, and business AI-driven cloud ecosystem.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Sven Denecken is senior vice president and chief marketing and solutions officer for Industries &#x26; CX at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-power-of-partnership-drive-customer-success-with-solutions-from-sap-delivering-trusted-advice-and-deep-product-knowledge">The power of partnership: drive customer success with solutions from SAP, delivering trusted advice and deep product knowledge</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/partners.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/hannover-messe</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Solutions from SAP and Icertis Empower Enterprises with Contract Intelligence Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-icertis-contract-intelligence-innovation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-icertis-contract-intelligence-innovation</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Icertis are working to improve contract intelligence for enterprises, reducing revenue leakage and increasing efficiency. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/icertis</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Partnerships Help Customers Successfully Navigate a Data-Driven World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/partnerships-help-customers-navigate-data-driven-world</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/partnerships-help-customers-navigate-data-driven-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP partners can deploy SAP Datasphere and SAP Analytics Cloud to provide data access, effective planning, and trusted AI across operations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16fa40a8c4f0c1be7eb9eaf1afe27075d1230ec25.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16fa40a8c4f0c1be7eb9eaf1afe27075d1230ec25.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16fa40a8c4f0c1be7eb9eaf1afe27075d1230ec25.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Partnerships Help Customers Successfully Navigate a Data-Driven World" src="./media_16fa40a8c4f0c1be7eb9eaf1afe27075d1230ec25.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="partnerships-help-customers-successfully-navigate-a-data-driven-world">Partnerships Help Customers Successfully Navigate a Data-Driven World</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In the modern business environment, the critical need to effectively harness data is undeniable. Companies that fail to become data-driven risk falling behind in a world where agility and informed decision-making are paramount. In the recent <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/data-unleashed.html">SAP Data Unleashed</a> event we explored strategies to help organizations access data from any source, transform planning and analysis with a business data fabric, and foster trusted artificial intelligence (AI) across their businesses. Central to this transformation are <a href="/topics/ecosystem">SAP partners</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For decades, our partners have leveraged their industry expertise and technological know-how to bring immense value to companies of all sizes. They possess a rare fusion of deep industry insights and technological expertise, which they leverage to guide businesses through the delicate process of modernization while ensuring that the essence of their identity remains intact.</p>
  <p>We recently <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/partners.html#trending">asked several of our strategic SAP partners</a> how they’re helping customers take better advantage of their organization’s data. Our partners have observed a significant shift in the way data is perceived and utilized. It’s no longer just a byproduct of business operations but a core asset that, when effectively distributed and made accessible, can revolutionize customer experiences and enable a more strategic, company-wide approach to decision-making.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11f5934a69f41fbb435d136fc80e11b26ab8eb2f5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11f5934a69f41fbb435d136fc80e11b26ab8eb2f5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11f5934a69f41fbb435d136fc80e11b26ab8eb2f5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Partners Bring Out Your Best as a Data-Driven Organization" src="./media_11f5934a69f41fbb435d136fc80e11b26ab8eb2f5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/Cj3BF9-9I30">SAP Partners Bring Out Your Best as a Data-Driven Organization</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>However, the mere availability of data is not a panacea. The crux of the matter is transforming data into actionable insights. This is where our partners excel, mapping out advanced use cases and facilitating the transition to cutting-edge platforms like SAP Datasphere and SAP Analytics Cloud. These solutions can empower organizations to evolve into entities where data is not just present but central to every action and decision.</p>
  <p>The practical implications of data are vast and deeply rooted in the operational successes of our clients. AI, for instance, is a frontier rich with potential, but its success is inextricably linked to the quality and accessibility of data. Recognizing this, SAP partners are investing in building AI capabilities that can not only propel new business functions but also deliver substantial value.</p>
  <p>Another key area of focus for our partners is the concept of a business data fabric, which is critical in developing a flexible enterprise architecture. Such an architecture allows for co-innovation and customization of solutions, ensuring that data is not just an afterthought but a driving force in business operations.</p>
  <p>The journey toward a data- and AI-centric business model is an ongoing one, marked by evolving needs, emerging challenges, and a relentless pursuit of innovation. The ultimate aim is to convert potential into lasting business success.</p>
  <p>The essence of our relationship with our partners is rooted in a shared vision. We are united in our pursuit of discovery, innovation, and improvement as we navigate the future together. Be sure to <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/partners.html#trending">watch the videos</a> with our seven strategic partners and discover how the <a href="https://www.sap.com/partners.html">SAP partner ecosystem</a> can help your company become a data-driven organization.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Karl Fahrbach is chief partner officer at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-partners-are-helping-their-clients-solve-critical-business-challenges">SAP partners are helping their clients solve critical business challenges</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/partners.html#trending">Discover how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Pinnacle Awards: 2024 Finalists and Winners Announced]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-pinnacle-awards-2024-finalists-and-winners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-pinnacle-awards-2024-finalists-and-winners</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Pinnacle Awards recognize top-performing and innovative partners. Learn more about the SAP Pinnacle Awards 2024 finalists and winners.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11764e94c92ed4681b4c79ee2e132a07bdde6ab9c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11764e94c92ed4681b4c79ee2e132a07bdde6ab9c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11764e94c92ed4681b4c79ee2e132a07bdde6ab9c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Pinnacle Awards: 2024 Finalists and Winners Announced" src="./media_11764e94c92ed4681b4c79ee2e132a07bdde6ab9c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-pinnacle-awards-2024-finalists-and-winners-announced">SAP Pinnacle Awards: 2024 Finalists and Winners Announced</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The SAP Pinnacle Awards, our most prestigious global partner recognition program, shine a spotlight on our top-performing partners that demonstrate excellence in unlocking innovative new ways for customers to run their businesses.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP’s ecosystem plays a key role in our vision to enable every organization and every industry to become a network of intelligent, sustainable enterprises. Through their unique industry expertise, implementation methodologies, complementary solutions, and commitment throughout the Customer Value Journey, partners help customers thrive and succeed with SAP.</p>
  <p>Across 26 categories in the areas of Customer Success, Intelligent Enterprise Realization, Sustainability, and Social Impact, partners are recognized for their outstanding contributions, exponential growth, and simplification. Through delivering cloud innovations that help customers achieve their goals, these partners exemplify dedication to teamwork and embody our vision for partnering excellence.</p>
  <p>Twenty-five of the 2024 winners and finalists were selected from <a href="/topics/ecosystem">SAP’s wide-ranging partner base</a>, using system-generated data on core metrics and key performance indicators. A steering committee of global SAP representatives reviewed, vetted, and ranked the achievements according to our internal criteria, which aligned with SAP’s communicated business strategies.</p>
  <p>The only exception is the Social Impact category, which recognized a partner’s lasting societal impact by leveraging SAP innovation with concrete results. Partner nominations were evaluated and ranked by a panel of jurors consisting of SAP internal and third-party representatives.</p>
  <p>Winners and finalists for all categories will receive a communication package to help them promote their success to their customers, prospects, and the media, including logos for online and physical marketing vehicles. To increase their global exposure, SAP will list the winners and finalists on its Web site for an entire year, in addition to running a comprehensive campaign that promotes these winners and finalists to joint prospects and customers.</p>
  <p>Congratulations to the <a href="https://www.sap.com/partners/pinnacle-awards.html">winners and finalists</a>! We look forward to celebrating your success at SAP Partner Connect and SAP Sapphire.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Karl Fahrbach is chief partner officer at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-pinnacle-awards-showcase-partners-that-have-excelled-in-helping-customers-become-best-run-businesses">SAP Pinnacle Awards showcase partners that have excelled in helping customers become best-run businesses</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/partners/pinnacle-awards.html">Check out this year’s winners and finalists</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-pinnacle-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Convista Harmonizes Workplace Culture with SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/convista-harmonizes-workplace-culture-with-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/convista-harmonizes-workplace-culture-with-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Convista's people culture and respected brand built on trust and transparency is supported by SAP S/4HANA Cloud and SAP SuccessFactors.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a18052b07fa380b0a184821d2508dc2d57d515a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a18052b07fa380b0a184821d2508dc2d57d515a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11a18052b07fa380b0a184821d2508dc2d57d515a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Convista Harmonizes Workplace Culture with SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition" src="./media_11a18052b07fa380b0a184821d2508dc2d57d515a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="convista-harmonizes-workplace-culture-with-sap-successfactors-employee-central-and-sap-s4hana-cloud-public-edition">Convista Harmonizes Workplace Culture with SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In a merger between two well-matched organizations, cultural integration can be the key to successfully transforming into a single high-performing entity ready to take on new opportunities. Notably, more than a few high-profile mergers have failed due to cultural incompatibility. Add a third organization into the merger and the cultural complexities increase exponentially. But some multi-organization mergers do successfully navigate these challenges and reap the transformational benefits.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="https://www.convista.com/en/">Convista</a>, a consultancy and SAP partner based in Cologne, Germany, emerged stronger and better positioned to serve its clients following a <a href="https://www.convista.com/en/news/axxiome-health-and-enowa-become-part-of-the-new-convista/">recent merger</a> that brought together three former consultancies: Axxiome Health, ConVista Consulting, and enowa. With 25 years of experience delivering transformation projects to its clients, Convista used that expertise in its own rebranding to present its capabilities to clients and employees: a vibrant people culture as well as a respected and trusted brand supported by <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition</a> for ERP and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/employee-central-hris/features.html">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</a> for core HR.</p>
  <p>“Trust and transparency are common values that we share at Convista,” declares Convista CEO Martin Hinz. “Combined with a dynamic team spirit and passion, it’s what we bring to our clients every day.”</p>
  <p>With a workforce of around 1,200 employees, Convista has made a name for itself through its dedication and expertise providing end-to-end solutions to clients throughout the world with a presence in Germany, Austria, Switzerland, Poland, Spain, Brazil, Israel, and further locations across the globe. It supports client projects primarily in four sectors: insurance, industry, healthcare, and energy/utilities. In recent years, Convista has twice been awarded SAP <a href="https://www.convista.com/en/news/for-the-second-time-in-a-row-sap-partner-of-the-year-award-in-the-financial-services-sector/">Partner of the Year</a> in the Financial Services sector.</p>
  <p>“At Convista you meet everyone on the same level, independent of your skill level or where you are in your career,” says Stefanie Weber, project lead of People and Culture – HR Systems, Convista. “Also, when we’re working with customers, we try to approach them at eye level, which makes quite a good working environment. The implementation of SAP SuccessFactors came as a natural extension to our brand and our culture.”</p>
  <h2 id="the-challenges-of-data-siloed-in-three-systems">The Challenges of Data Siloed in Three Systems</h2>
  <p>Weber says one of the reasons she joined Convista in 2012 while studying business at university was the high priority its leaders place on trust and transparency, values that permeate the entire organization and empower employees in their work and career development. “Trust is one of our main values,” she underscores. “Also, the trust that people are willing to do their best to get motivated and move the company ahead.”</p>
  <p>Convista grew quickly both organically and as a result of mergers with other consultancies. In 2019, IT service provider Axxiome Health joined the ConVista Group to deepen the organization’s expertise in the health insurance sector. In 2021, enowa joined the group, infusing its knowledge of industries and insurance. With the mergers complete, the incipient organization became <a href="https://www.convista.com/en/news/axxiome-health-and-enowa-become-part-of-the-new-convista/">the new Convista</a> on January 1, 2023.</p>
  <p>Though team members were highly motivated to collaborate from the start, Convista’s vision for itself as a modern organization was held back in both its daily work for projects and internal services. Using disparate tools based on older technology and a patchwork of third-party solutions that lacked integration proved to be inefficient and unsuitable as a basis for decision-making.</p>
  <p>“Whenever we wanted to have a report, even something as simple as a headcount, we always had to go into three different systems, collect the data, and report on that,” Weber recalls. “It’s just one of the many examples of why we really urgently needed one IT platform.”</p>
  <h2 id="project-one-achieves-milestone-integration">Project ONE Achieves Milestone Integration</h2>
  <p>To build a strong foundation for future growth, Convista embarked on “Project ONE” with the goal to have one digital platform flexible and powerful enough for the entire organization. For this, it chose SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition and SAP SuccessFactors solutions with self-service capabilities for employees to log time-off.</p>
  <p>Overall, implementing SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition can result in streamlined HR processes; end-to-end integration with seamless connectivity between HR and finance functions for accurate and up-to-date employee data across the organization; greater transparency of data for analytics and reporting on workforce trends, costs, and profitability to enable better strategic planning and resource allocation; and compliance with regulatory requirements and data security.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-successfactors-solutions-can-fuel-the-success-of-every-individual-and-drive-org-agility-at-scale">SAP SuccessFactors solutions can fuel the success of every individual and drive org agility at scale</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Among the key advantages is the ability for employees to access their own HR-related information, such as personal details and time-off balances. This self-service capability helps empower employees, improve transparency, and enhance the overall employee experience.</p>
  <p>Convista’s project team decided for a phased approach to the implementation by first introducing the SAP solutions in Poland and later in Germany, Austria, and Switzerland – with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition planned to launch in the German-speaking countries during the course of 2024. To optimize success, the project team used the combined best practices of Convista and SAP and hosted regular meetings that provided clear communication to steer the project. “We were always aligned on the requirements of the other teams,” says Weber, who managed the HR workstream. “We all knew the main goal of the implementation. This was helpful for everyone on the project.”</p>
  <p>In-house experts from Convista certified on SAP SuccessFactors solutions contributed valuable knowledge for the implementation. Consultants from SAP Services and Support successfully integrated the cost center replication from SAP S/4HANA Cloud to SAP SuccessFactors and the workforce replication from SAP SuccessFactors to SAP S/4HANA Cloud, and delivered a detailed administration guide on the integration setup for Convista. Additionally, they provided an overview, the architecture guidance, and the navigation through major hurdles in performing the configuration to set up identity access governence (IAG), identity provisioning service (IPS), and identity authentication services (IAS). The SAP Early Adopter Care program supported Convista for the master data integration (MDI) during the implementation and helped to solve all roadblocks efficiently.</p>
  <p>On January 1, 2023, Convista’s 80-person team in Poland was the first to go live with the new SAP solutions. “It was really a great experience for them and quite an advancement,” says Weber, citing the benefits of the new solutions that provide optimizations and intuitive workflows. The project took a pivotal turn on January 1, 2024, with the launch of SAP SuccessFactors solutions for Convista’s 800 employees in the German-speaking countries.</p>
  <p>“The biggest milestone was to have [SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition and SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central] speaking with each other,” says Weber, who emphasizes how valuable it is for the team “to have an end-to-end process within one platform.” With an integrated IT platform in place, she says that it is no longer necessary to do workflows, authorizations, or any other processes in other systems.</p>
  <p>The seamless synchronization of data by using a common data model for SAP business applications helps reduce the need for manual data entry and redundant processes. This means, for example, employee data that is maintained in SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central is available in real-time in SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition; while master data, like cost center data, flows seamlessly from SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition to SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central. Eliminating data silos enables the HR and finance teams to work with consistent, accurate data for all-important employment decisions and legal reporting obligations.</p>
  <p>Now Convista’s team is unified in its brand, values, spirit – and employee data.</p>
  <h2 id="more-transparency-and-intuitive-workflows-are-just-the-beginning">More Transparency and Intuitive Workflows Are Just the Beginning</h2>
  <p>Feedback has been overwhelmingly positive, according to Weber, with employees speaking favorably about the improved transparency and workflows. “The first thing I heard from everyone was, well, this is simple and intuitive. They were so happy about it,” she says. “They are big fans of the mobile application. They find it very transparent and easy to use.”</p>
  <p>For some colleagues, the new solution lets them view their own data for the first time. “When we went live, everyone was viewing their profile,” says Weber. “This was also quite new that you are able to see what data is maintained for your person, your address, but also job information – to view it and have this transparency. People like this very much and also the ability to have the self-services in SAP SuccessFactors.”</p>
  <p>To strengthen communication between HR and employees, Convista will bring more people processes onto the new digital platform. In fact, the team very recently implemented the SAP SuccessFactors Performance &#x26; Goals solution for annual employee appraisals, goal setting, and project feedback. “It’s just the beginning,” Weber says. “There’s still a lot of work ahead of us.”</p>
  <p>Hinz says, “We have been careful to preserve our workplace culture during the transformation. Now that we are rebranded as one organization, we are seeing the benefits of that early effort. With SAP, we now have the digital platform to build people-centered processes that advance our vision as a unified, high-performing organization serving our clients.”</p>
  <p>Find out more about <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/solutions.html?url_id=ctabutton-us-hcm-convista">SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Jacqueline Prause is a journalist at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up today</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP AppHaus Network to Onboard New Partners in North America]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-apphaus-network-new-partners-in-north-america</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-apphaus-network-new-partners-in-north-america</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP AppHaus Network announced its plans to establish additional partner-driven locations in North America. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/human-centered-innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital Eco-Farming: How SAP Japan Helps Revitalize Rural Communities]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/minano-digital-eco-farm-sap-japan-revitalize-rural-communities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/minano-digital-eco-farm-sap-japan-revitalize-rural-communities</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Minano Digital Eco Farm, launched by PSI and SAP Co-Innovation Lab in Japan, is helping the town of Minano revitalize its community.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/agribusiness</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitization</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/internet-of-things</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-co-innovation-lab</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Announces Winners of Regional Partner Excellence Awards]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-regional-partner-excellence-awards-2024-winners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-regional-partner-excellence-awards-2024-winners</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Regional Awards for Partner Excellence recognize partner success in sales, innovation, tech, services, and solution areas in each region.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-global-lob-partner-excellence-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Invests in Partner Learning to Boost Availability of SAP Experts]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-invests-in-partner-learning</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-invests-in-partner-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Learning is reimagining partner enablement with SAP Learning Journeys, subject matter experts, and opportunities to earn credentials.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How SAP’s Retail Partners Became Innovation Multipliers in 2023 and Created the Ultimate Consumer Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-retail-partners-became-innovation-multipliers-in-2023</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-retail-partners-became-innovation-multipliers-in-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read to learn about the retail partners that served as innovation and growth multipliers for SAP customers in 2023.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/nrf</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coles Reimagines Volume Hiring with AI and Automation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/coles-reimagines-volume-hiring-with-ai-and-automation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/coles-reimagines-volume-hiring-with-ai-and-automation</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Coles uses an AI-powered solution integrated with SAP SuccessFactors to help revolutionize its hiring process and gain speed and efficiency.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_149ed3b06f07dcdc3485b441db14e19620bea42c6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_149ed3b06f07dcdc3485b441db14e19620bea42c6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_149ed3b06f07dcdc3485b441db14e19620bea42c6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Coles Reimagines Volume Hiring with AI and Automation" src="./media_149ed3b06f07dcdc3485b441db14e19620bea42c6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="coles-reimagines-volume-hiring-with-ai-and-automation">Coles Reimagines Volume Hiring with AI and Automation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.colesgroup.com.au/home/">Coles Group</a>, one of Australia’s most trusted and iconic brands, is steadfast in delivering on its purpose to help Australians eat and live better every day. Through its core business as a full-service supermarket retailer, Coles engages with millions of customers every week in its 860 supermarkets throughout Australia. The group’s other areas of business include its Click &#x26; Collect online platform, network of liquor stores, and financial services with nearly 1,000 additional retail outlets.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Guided by the organization’s clear <a href="https://colescareers.com.au/au/en/culture">vision, purpose, and strategy</a>, Coles’ team of 120,000 employees is dedicated to making a difference in the lives of customers and the local communities it serves.</p>
  <p>In fiscal year 2020/21, Coles Group hired nearly 30,000 people to deliver on its business needs. Mike Virgo, head of Talent Acquisition for Coles Group, said this hiring volume was necessary to make sure the company was “positioned well to support our customers.”</p>
  <p>The business environment, however, dramatically shifted as the public health crisis of the pandemic unfolded, resulting in repeated lockdowns and restrictions. As a neighborhood retailer dependent on in-person interaction to deliver most of its services, Coles found its workforce impacted by the pandemic. Faced with supply chain disruptions, panic buying behaviors by consumers, high employee absenteeism, and increased turnover, Coles urgently needed to step up its volume and pace of hiring to support its customers.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="create-ai-powered-experiences-that-drive-real-competitive-advantage-with-sap-successfactors">Create AI-powered experiences that drive real competitive advantage with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Around 2020-2021, we started to experience one of the most significant shifts in the employment market we’d ever seen,” Virgo said in a <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1693098679863001ykJ6">session</a> at <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/successconnect/virtual.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SuccessConnect Virtual</a>. “It started to create huge challenges for organizations around the world – around how we attract, retain, and hire talent.”</p>
  <h2 id="catalyst-for-change-and-a-new-way-of-working">Catalyst for Change and a New Way of Working</h2>
  <p>To meet pressing business demands, Coles doubled its hiring volume from 30,000 to 60,000 people and increased recruitment advertising spend by a factor of three. Its talent acquisition team grew proportionally to manage the increased workload – but then labored under manual transactional activities that slowed processing times. As a result of the huge strain, variability in the candidate and hiring manager experience became noticeable.</p>
  <p>Due to the volume of work, Coles looked for ways to evolve its system to create more speed, efficiency, and scalability. With a list of criteria, Coles began to review technology solutions on the market to find one that could support its vision for a new way of working. “We wanted to reimagine how we recruit for our stores,” Virgo said. “We needed automation and AI to remove a lot of the manual work in our systems. We wanted to create more consistency and uplift the experiences we were giving our candidates and our hiring managers. And ultimately, [the solution] needed to drive commercial benefit for us.”</p>
  <p>As a key requirement, the new solution needed to integrate with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/what-is-hxm-suite.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a>. In 2020, as part of an organization-wide <a href="/australia/2021/09/08/how-coles-group-is-transforming-hr-during-the-global-pandemic">digital transformation</a> that introduced SAP S/4HANA and SAP Ariba solutions, Coles modernized its HR and payroll processing, replacing a patchwork of outdated systems with SAP SuccessFactors solutions. It became the first organization in the southern hemisphere to launch all modules of the SAP SuccessFactors portfolio in one go. With all HR processes unified on a single platform, Coles benefits from having a single source of truth for people data that is accurate and available in real time for the entire organization.</p>
  <h2 id="two-way-integration-ensures-single-source-of-truth-in-data">Two-Way Integration Ensures Single Source of Truth in Data</h2>
  <p>To help with the project, Coles chose <a href="https://www.phenom.com/">Phenom</a>, an SAP partner whose AI-powered Intelligent Talent Experience platform provides two-way integration with SAP SuccessFactors solutions. Virgo said the two-way integration “allows us to have a holistic view of the candidates that progress through the process, no matter whether the team is operating in Phenom or SAP SuccessFactors, and it allows SAP SuccessFactors to be our single source of truth.”</p>
  <p>There are several key benefits of Phenom’s solution at Coles. One is candidate attraction and engagement, which is achieved primarily through the Coles career site and chatbot. Another is recruiter automation and interview management, which provides automation and process efficiencies from when a job requisition is created in SAP SuccessFactors solutions and replicated into Phenom until a hiring manager chooses a candidate for the job. Once a candidate is chosen, the two-way integration enables the HR team to access the data in SAP SuccessFactors solutions and complete all compliance aspects, such as working rights, contract generation, and onboarding.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-how-phenom-can-compliment-sap-successfactors-recruiting">Learn how Phenom can compliment SAP SuccessFactors Recruiting</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-2001007992_live_v1">Find out</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The Coles team gains additional efficiencies in its onboarding programs through the application of robotic process automation (RPA) powered by two bots that work in the background: <em>Ashbotty</em> processes the working rights and <em>Usain Bot</em> processes onboarding and manages pending recruits. “They take a lot of the transactional, manual work that we used to have team members doing. It can do that quickly, accurately, and it can do that 24/7 – which is particularly important for us as a seven-days-a-week business,” Virgo said.</p>
  <h2 id="ai-powered-experiences-for-candidates-and-recruiters">AI-Powered Experiences for Candidates and Recruiters</h2>
  <p>Coles reimagined the candidate experience to launch a modern, tech-enabled career site – which has been chosen as a two-time winner of Australia’s Best Careers Site. The site includes an AI-powered chatbot to guide candidates as they look for information, search relevant job postings, and submit their applications. It also includes Coles’ Expression of Interest, always-on advertising that drives the growth of its talent pool and advances its talent marketing by reducing the need to advertise every role. A Hosted Apply process, facilitated by integrations with Phenom, presents a consistent candidate experience and increases the conversion rate on applications.</p>
  <p>Phenom AI Scheduling, a key part of Coles’ hiring experience, enables candidates to book themselves an available interview slot and automates the coordination of hiring team calendars. The new solution provides a fully mobile-enabled experience to meet the demands of candidates for an omni-channel, real-time experience where they can learn, read, and apply for jobs where and when they want.</p>
  <p>Inundated by nearly 1 million applications each year to review, Coles also took steps to elevate the recruiter experience and increase the speed and accuracy of candidate screening and job matching. It implemented Phenom Fit Score, an AI-powered feature that assesses a candidate’s suitability for an open role, based on location and optimal travel distances, availability, and working rights; then, assigns a fit score and surfaces the most closely matched candidates to the recruiters. In addition, the new solution empowers in-store managers to collaborate with recruiters to review candidates and make quick hiring decisions with confidence.</p>
  <h2 id="talent-pools-grow-with-improvements-to-hiring-speed-and-efficiency">Talent Pools Grow with Improvements to Hiring Speed and Efficiency</h2>
  <p>With the new augmented solution, Coles is experiencing tangible benefits across multiple categories and key metrics for success: time-to-fill is down six days; time-to-hire is down two days, which is impressive considering candidates can book the in-store interview up to two weeks in advance; and advertising spend is down 50%.</p>
  <p>Most notably for Coles as a people-centric organization is the development of its talent pool, now numbering 2 million potential candidates. It achieves an 85% application conversion rate on up to 1 million applications per year. Through its <a href="https://www.colesgroup.com.au/media-releases/?page=coles-group-ranked-1-for-recruitment-of-aussies-with-disabilities">commitment</a> to be a safe, inclusive, and diverse workplace, Coles has applied the new solution to provide greater accessibility for more diverse candidates, resulting in an increase of 24% more hiring for people who identify as having a disability.</p>
  <p>Virgo said that the talent acquisition team will continue to evolve its solution and assess more opportunities for AI and automation to bring value to the recruitment process. Although these technologies are not cure-alls for every recruitment scenario, they can save recruiting teams precious time and resources to focus on more high-touch interactions further down the recruiting funnel. In sharing lessons learned, Virgo noted, “I think the important call out is the level of automation you can inject in your process will likely diminish as the seniority, complexity, and requirements of your roles increase because they are likely to be more high touch, perhaps need more interpretation or judgment calls from your recruiters to identify who the right talent is for your organization.”</p>
  <p>Watch <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/successconnect/virtual.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SuccessConnect Virtual</a> on demand.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-sap-news-on-linkedin-to-stay-up-to-date">Follow SAP News on LinkedIn to stay up-to-date</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/recruiting</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Supporting Midmarket Business with a Strong Partner Ecosystem]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/supporting-midmarket-business-strong-partner-ecosystem</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/supporting-midmarket-business-strong-partner-ecosystem</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP solutions help midmarket companies build relationships with partners that can enable continued growth and scale. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/sme</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Infosys Introduce New Sustainable and Innovative Industry Cloud Solution]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-and-infosys-introduce-sustainable-industry-cloud-solution</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-and-infosys-introduce-sustainable-industry-cloud-solution</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the SAP-validated partner use case program, Infosys and SAP created a solution to help companies monitor their carbon footprints.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_164f38f864e0733a6806af629b2d24613241a4b15.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_164f38f864e0733a6806af629b2d24613241a4b15.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_164f38f864e0733a6806af629b2d24613241a4b15.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP and Infosys Introduce New Sustainable and Innovative Industry Cloud Solution" src="./media_164f38f864e0733a6806af629b2d24613241a4b15.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-and-infosys-introduce-new-sustainable-and-innovative-industry-cloud-solution">SAP and Infosys Introduce New Sustainable and Innovative Industry Cloud Solution</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In today’s fast-paced and dynamic business environment, <a href="/topics/sustainability">sustainability</a> is no longer a buzzword; it’s a critical business priority. Investors and customers seek more sustainable business practices from their solution providers and enterprises are keenly focused on integrating sustainability into their operations. This is no easy lift, and it doesn’t happen overnight. Several challenges need to be addressed, including action planning, effective resource allocation, and prioritization.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For companies to act sustainably, responsibly, and efficiently, they must harness the power of data-driven decisions and advanced technology to reduce their carbon footprint and create sustainable product portfolios. Enter SAP and its broad ecosystem of industry cloud partners with a shared vision to help businesses become strategic, sustainable, intelligent enterprises.</p>
  <h2 id="hack2build-opens-door-for-innovation-and-sustainability">Hack2Build Opens Door for Innovation and Sustainability</h2>
  <p>The <a href="https://events.sap.com/hack2build/en/home">Hack2Build event from SAP</a>, organized by SAP Co-Innovation Lab, is an initiative designed to harness the creativity and speed of prototyping industry cloud solutions by SAP partners in days as opposed to weeks. At a September 2022 Hack2Build event, SAP partner Infosys presented a solution for organizations to identify, track, predict, and refine carbon emissions during sales and operations planning (S&#x26;OP) and make sustainable decisions. The solution, <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/08/7affe1f5-847e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Sustainable S&#x26;OP and Carbon Footprint Management</a>, was built using SAP Integrated Business Planning (SAP IBP) for Supply Chain, SAP S/4HANA, SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP), SAP Integration Suite, and SAP Sustainability Footprint Management.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="industry-cloud-solutions-from-sap-and-partners-can-help-you-find-a-competitive-edge">Industry cloud solutions from SAP and partners can help you find a competitive edge</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/industry-cloud.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="framework-for-tracking-emissions-leverages-the-power-of-saps-industry-cloud">Framework for Tracking Emissions Leverages the Power of SAP’s Industry Cloud</h2>
  <p>Infosys’ carbon footprint solution calculates carbon emissions based on greenhouse gas protocols and global warming potential factors across an organization’s procurement, production, and distribution processes. It helps calculate key information, such as estimates of CO2e emissions per order level, thereby helping to make decisions that can ensure a smaller carbon footprint. The solution also provides an innovative framework to help companies identify, track, predict, and refine their carbon emissions numbers throughout the entire supply chain process.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-validated-partner-use-case-program-offers-momentum-to-service-partner-solution">SAP-Validated Partner Use Case Program Offers Momentum to Service Partner Solution</h2>
  <p>Infosys’ solution is part of the SAP-validated partner use case program. The program was established to give SAP service partners the ability to showcase, position, and promote solutions and spotlight their expertise of SAP Business Technology Platform, leveraging the power of SAP’s vast customer base and industry networks.</p>
  <p>The SAP-validated partner use case program offers service partners the ability to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Get amplified market reach</strong>: Increased visibility enables service partners to target a broader audience, opening doors to new markets and untapped opportunities. Leveraging SAP’s robust platform, partners can position themselves strategically and expand their global reach.</li>
    <li><strong>Collaborate and co-innovate</strong>: Participating in the SAP-validated partner use case program can foster collaboration with SAP experts, industry leaders, and customers.</li>
    <li><strong>Access a dynamic ecosystem</strong>: Partners can benefit from SAP’s ecosystem, where they can collaborate, exchange knowledge, and share best practices with some of the industry’s best leaders.</li>
    <li><strong>Develop customer-centric solutions</strong>: The program helps put the customer at the core of solution development. Service partners can gain valuable customer insights though interactions facilitated by SAP, leading to better-tailored products and services that can precisely address users’ pain points.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The program presents opportunities for both customers and service partners to flourish. By achieving certification, service partners can earn credibility, expand market reach, and foster collaborative innovation with industry giants. Its streamlined processes help accelerate time-to-market, providing a significant advantage in today’s fast-paced business landscape.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-information-training-tools-and-resources-you-need">Get the information, training, tools, and resources you need</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/welcome.html?pexpRequestedURL=%2Fen%2Flibrary%2Feducation%2Fpsd%2F2023%2Fmar%2Fe_oe_te_w_rnbo_31837.html">Visit the SAP Partner Portal site</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The program unlocks a door to a dynamic ecosystem where partners can learn, grow, and develop customer-centric solutions that can meet industry demands head-on. For partners aiming to thrive in their respective industries, this program is a game changer. Service partners are encouraged to embrace the power of the SAP-validated partner use case program and transform their business.</p>
  <p>“Infosys is delighted to publish the Infosys Sustainable S&#x26;OP and Carbon Footprint Management Solution through the SAP-validated partner use case program,” said Atul Chorbele, AVP at Infosys. “We are confident that customers across industries will benefit from adopting this solution.”</p>
  <p>Holger Brammer, Global Partner Ecosystem vice president at SAP, praised this partner solution and the development process: “It was impressive to see how fast Infosys developed this solution on SAP BTP and integrated it with SAP S/4HANA, SAP IBP, and SAP Sustainability Footprint Management. I’m quite confident that this solution will resonate very well with customers.”</p>
  <p>To learn how to build industry innovation on SAP BTP and the SAP-validated partner use case program or get more information about <a href="mailto:lucca.sperl@sap.com">validated use cases on the SAP PartnerEdge site</a>, contact <a href="mailto:lucca.sperl@sap.com">Lucca Sperl</a>, industry cloud innovation program lead. To learn more about Infosys’ solution, <a href="https://www.infosys.com/campaigns/documents/sop-carbon-footprint-management.pdf">visit here</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Vidya Gugnani is senior director and industry cloud ecosystem lead for Strategic Partners, North America at SAP.<br>Nitin Majahan is COE lead for SAP Industrial Manufacturing at Infosys.</p>
        <p>Top image courtesy of SAP employee Karsten Hohage</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Industry Innovation Gives Partners a Runway for Sustained Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/industry-cloud-innovation-sap-partners-success</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/industry-cloud-innovation-sap-partners-success</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's industry cloud offers partners boundless opportunities to cultivate new markets, customers, and revenue sources. Read to learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11d9ba4b00dd11ddbd90c3e316d0c28742fc92154.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11d9ba4b00dd11ddbd90c3e316d0c28742fc92154.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11d9ba4b00dd11ddbd90c3e316d0c28742fc92154.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How Industry Innovation Gives Partners a Runway for Sustained Success" src="./media_11d9ba4b00dd11ddbd90c3e316d0c28742fc92154.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-industry-innovation-gives-partners-a-runway-for-sustained-success">How Industry Innovation Gives Partners a Runway for Sustained Success</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Have you ever wondered at the workings of the modern airport and the ecosystem around it, how so many complex and disparate moving parts come together to deliver a high-quality travel experience to flyers?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Granted, those experiences aren’t always positive. But when everything is working in sync – travel and transportation infrastructure, aerospace technology, energy, retail, hospitality, and more – to create a whole greater than the sum of its parts, my thoughts can’t help but shift skyward, to another more familiar ecosystem.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="grow-and-find-a-competitive-edge-with-industry-cloud-solutions-from-sap-and-partners">Grow and find a competitive edge with industry cloud solutions from SAP and partners</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/industry-cloud.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Among the many developments I’ve witnessed lately as a result of SAP’s growing focus on industry innovation, SAP’s industry cloud and the partner ecosystem that supports it stand out. They’re proving my long-held belief that a high level of collaboration with partners across companies and industries, similar to what occurs at airports, can open boundless opportunities to cultivate new markets, customers, and revenue sources. SAP’s industry cloud has yielded close to 400 solutions across 25 industry verticals, 80% of which were developed by partners either on their own or in collaboration with SAP. About 1,900 unique customers are using these solutions, and they’re renewing them at a rate above 90%.</p>
  <p>What’s driving the industry innovation momentum? And why should SAP partners consider engaging in the co-innovation effort if they’re not already, or get more involved if they are? Here are five competitive justifications:</p>
  <ol>
    <li><strong>Future readiness:</strong> A business landscape that is perpetually shifting and evolving, often in unexpected ways, demands a business mindset that embraces change and seeks out opportunities to innovate – a mindset of future readiness. A focus on industry innovation fosters future readiness on multiple levels. It gives partners a portfolio of solutions to help their customers prepare for a future where cloud solutions will be instrumental to their digital transformation efforts. One leading global consulting firm predicts that by 2027, enterprises will be using industry cloud platforms to accelerate more than half of their critical business initiatives. What’s more, working within an industry cloud environment like SAP’s can give partners themselves a future-ready model for growing their business.</li>
    <li><strong>Business ecosystems and networks:</strong> By bringing their industry knowledge and intellectual property to a business ecosystem like the one that supports SAP’s industry cloud, partners can become a multiplier for industry innovation, moving solutions through the development pipeline and to customers faster together than they otherwise could working individually. We’re witnessing this multiplier effect within specific industries like consumer products, life sciences, automotive, energy, and industrial manufacturing, where collaboration within industry-focused business ecosystems is fueling a fresh wave of co-innovation.</li>
    <li><strong>Modularity and integration:</strong> One of my team’s responsibilities is to maintain the industry cloud opportunity map, a comprehensive architecture of potential and already developed solutions that comprise the present and future of industry innovation in the cloud. A glance at the opportunity map tells a compelling story about all the white space available to partners to fill out the portfolio. Intellectual property and ideas are the building blocks in this case. The door is wide open for partners to bring use cases that enhance, extend, or add to an existing solution, or that fill gaps in the opportunity map. Using SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP) and SAP Store, they can rapidly develop their ideas and turn them into commercialized solutions that customers can readily integrate.</li>
    <li><strong>Industry convergence:</strong> Just like at the airport, we’re seeing the lines between industries blur and converge as traditional value chains merge. This creates massive opportunities for SAP partners to develop new revenue streams around solutions that they adapt from one industry for use in another, or that can be used by customers across multiple industries. Electric vehicle charging is sparking a convergence among automotive, energy, oil and gas, utility, and retail and consumer products, for example. And that, in turn, is providing fertile territory for SAP partners with use cases and intellectual property in these areas to collaborate and create new solutions that can add value for customers.</li>
    <li><strong>Customer experience:</strong> By focusing on industry innovation, our goal is to give customers exactly what they need to succeed from a digital solutions standpoint. The better SAP, our partners, and all of us collectively as an ecosystem are at delivering the solutions customers need, the more trust we create with them. And that opens even more possibilities for SAP, partners, and customers alike – possibilities that conjure the familiar feeling I get at the airport when I’m waiting to board my next flight.</li>
  </ol>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Sven Denecken is senior vice president and chief marketing and solutions officer for SAP Industries &#x26; CX.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent Partner-Driven Project Wins Highlight Huge Industry Cloud Opportunities]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/partner-gsps-wins-highlight-sap-industry-cloud-opportunities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/partner-gsps-wins-highlight-sap-industry-cloud-opportunities</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Global strategic partners (GSPs) are driving a surge of activity, collaboration, and investment in SAP's industry cloud. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Industry Cloud Builds on the Past to Invent a Future Where Industries Converge and Boundaries Disappear]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/industry-cloud-future-industries-converge-boundaries-disappear</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/industry-cloud-future-industries-converge-boundaries-disappear</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's industry cloud is driving business transformation and innovation, empowering enterprises through partner-focused digital solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's Industry Cloud Drives Innovation in Utilities Through Cloud-Based Apps and Partner Collaborations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-industry-cloud-drives-innovation-in-utilities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-industry-cloud-drives-innovation-in-utilities</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's industry cloud is driving innovation in the utilities sector through cloud-based apps and partner collaborations. Read to learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-co-innovation-lab</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Channel Partners Can Write a Profitable New Chapter in the Industry Cloud Story]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/channel-partners-profitable-industry-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/channel-partners-profitable-industry-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP channel partners are leveraging industry cloud to help diversify their businesses and monetize their intellectual property. Read how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How HCLTech Uses SAP BTP Innovations to Combat Water Scarcity]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/hcltech-uses-sap-btp-combat-water-scarcity</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/hcltech-uses-sap-btp-combat-water-scarcity</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP partner and global tech company HCLTech is tackling the problem of water scarcity with its AquaSphere solution. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/blockchain</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Leveraging SAP’s Industry Cloud, Going from Concept to Commercialization Can Be Fast and Fulfilling]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/cogniac-sap-syntax-industry-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/cogniac-sap-syntax-industry-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The industry cloud partnership between Cogniac, Syntax, and SAP illustrates how combining forces can deliver more value to customers.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-digital-manufacturing</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-io</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Helping SAP Partner Delaware Meet Its Recruiting Needs]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/partner-talent-initiative-delaware-recruiting-needs</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/partner-talent-initiative-delaware-recruiting-needs</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Partner Talent Initiative helped Delaware UK find, recruit, and retain knowledgeable, skilled individuals to bolster its success.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accelerating Value: SAP and Bain Partner to Help Leaders Drive Cloud-Enabled ERP Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-bain-partner-cloud-erp-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-bain-partner-cloud-erp-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Bain & Company are collaborating to help executives maximize the impact of cloud-enabled ERP transformation. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Using Weather Analytics to Reduce Food Waste]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/planalytics-weather-analytics-reduce-food-waste</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/planalytics-weather-analytics-reduce-food-waste</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Integrating weather as a demand signal, like with Planalytics, enables businesses to use analytics to drive measurable, repeatable benefits.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Partners Drive a Wave of Industry Cloud Innovation in Discrete Manufacturing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-partners-industry-cloud-innovation-discrete-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-partners-industry-cloud-innovation-discrete-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and its partners are capitalizing on industry cloud opportunities in the discrete manufacturing industries. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In Life Sciences and Healthcare, SAP’s Industry Cloud Is Key to Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/life-sciences-healthcare-sap-industry-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/life-sciences-healthcare-sap-industry-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP’s industry cloud is helping life sciences and healthcare customers preserve and improve human health one innovation at a time.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The “Show Me” Sales Approach: SAP Partner Demo Environment]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/show-me-sales-approach-sap-partner-demo-environment</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/show-me-sales-approach-sap-partner-demo-environment</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Partner Demo Environment delivers end-to-end, integrated, pre-scripted solutions to help partners showcase SAP solutions to customers.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partner-demo-environment</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Consumer Industries Witness Surge of Innovation, Thanks to SAP’s Industry Cloud Partners]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/consumer-industries-innovation-sap-industry-cloud-partners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/consumer-industries-innovation-sap-industry-cloud-partners</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Industry cloud solutions from SAP and our partners are changing the way consumer industries customers do business.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>