<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-sustainability-control-tower/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Putting Sustainability at the Heart of ERP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sustainability-erp-sap-business-ai-sap-sapphire</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sustainability-erp-sap-business-ai-sap-sapphire</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP’s ERP-centric, cloud-based, AI-enabled approach is redefining how companies manage sustainability. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19f549b1c60b71d253752564f5659b7cd5b69ae91.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19f549b1c60b71d253752564f5659b7cd5b69ae91.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19f549b1c60b71d253752564f5659b7cd5b69ae91.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Putting Sustainability at the Heart of ERP" src="./media_19f549b1c60b71d253752564f5659b7cd5b69ae91.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="putting-sustainability-at-the-heart-of-erp">Putting Sustainability at the Heart of ERP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Sustainability has evolved from a boardroom buzzword to a critical driver of business success and strategic differentiation. To thrive, companies are going to need to understand how to operate in a modern, low-carbon, circular economy. SAP solutions will support them by embedding sustainability into every aspect of their operations.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-sapphire-taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">SAP Sapphire: Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At our customer flagship event, <a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">SAP Sapphire</a>, we’re discussing how we support customers with their biggest challenges, looking at future trends, and unveiling the latest product innovations.</p>
  <p>This makes the event the perfect opportunity to highlight how we are redefining the way companies manage sustainability through our ERP-centric, cloud-based, AI-enabled approach.</p>
  <h2 id="erp-centric">ERP-Centric</h2>
  <p>For true business model transformation, sustainability needs to be at the core of how companies operate. At SAP, we integrate sustainability data into cloud ERP business processes, which helps companies connect financial and non-financial information and thus treat carbon like money. This makes all decisions financially <em>and</em> environmentally sound while enabling customers to record real impacts and report audit-ready environmental, social, and governance (ESG) metrics seamlessly.</p>
  <h2 id="cloud-based">Cloud-Based</h2>
  <p>Instant access to fast-evolving innovations is only possible through the cloud. Our modern cloud-based solutions ensure that businesses can quickly adopt new functionality and stay ahead in a rapidly changing environment.</p>
  <h2 id="ai-enabled">AI-Enabled</h2>
  <p>Business AI is revolutionizing the way we approach sustainability. At SAP, AI takes complex sustainability tasks reliant on sustainability data and ERP data and makes them automated and auditable. It enables companies to improve operational efficiency, foster greater transparency around supply chain emissions, design and plan more effectively, and automate time-consuming tasks. SAP Business AI is built on the data and processes that run the business world, including sustainability related information from both inside and outside the company’s walls, making our solutions smarter, faster, and more effective.</p>
  <p>With SAP Business AI, we support our customers’ efforts to optimize for sustainable impact. This year at SAP Sapphire, we are thrilled to announce two new AI-driven sustainability use cases:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Emission Factor Mapping with AI:</strong> Available in SAP Sustainability Footprint Management, this feature enhances the accuracy and speed of carbon footprint calculations through automated, intelligent suggestions. By reducing the manual effort involved in mapping emission factors, businesses can achieve more precise measurements and make informed decisions faster.</li>
    <li><strong>ESG Report Generation with AI:</strong> This capability allows for the automatic generation of ESG reports based on the data within SAP Sustainability Control Tower. This not only streamlines the reporting process but also helps ensure that the data is reliable and actionable, providing a clear picture of a company’s sustainability performance.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Our comprehensive approach to carbon management is becoming a reality as we introduce new sustainability tracking, monitoring, and reporting features within the SAP cloud ERP portfolio as well as a new solution that will help customers manage sustainability commitments and comply with global regulations.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Advanced Carbon Calculator Engine:</strong> This powerful tool featured in SAP Sustainability Control Tower and SAP Sustainability Footprint Management integrates ERP data from SAP S/4HANA Cloud and other sources and embeds results back into business processes for informed decision-making. As such, it allows customers to meet Greenhouse Gas Protocol reporting standards, offering advanced, granular calculations of both product and corporate carbon footprints.</li>
    <li><strong>SAP Green Ledger</strong> will be released at the end of 2024. The solution will help customers connect their emissions data and financial data, allowing customers to easily understand the correlation between emissions and finances, model sustainable business scenarios, and then act with decisions that are both financially and environmentally sound.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>At SAP, we believe that the future of business is inextricably linked to sustainability. This is why sustainability is a key pillar of our growth strategy. Businesses must recognize that sustainable practices are not just ethical choices, but strategic financial decisions that drive innovation, reduce costs, and mitigate risks.</p>
  <p>Moreover, sustainable transformation opens up significant economic opportunities. By transforming their operations around sustainability, businesses can create a modern, low-carbon, circular economy that benefits both the environment and their bottom line, enhancing overall resilience.</p>
  <p>This transformation aligns business success with global sustainability goals, paving the way for a more sustainable, valuable, and prosperous future.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Sophia Mendelsohn is chief sustainability and commercial officer at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-news-business-ai-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-cutting-edge-partnerships</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-news-business-ai-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-cutting-edge-partnerships</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New SAP Business AI innovations and collaborations with partners are igniting ingenuity. Read the news from SAP Sapphire Orlando in 2024.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best" src="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-infuses-business-ai-throughout-its-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-and-partners-with-cutting-edge-ai-leaders-to-bring-out-customers-best">SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP Business AI Innovations and Collaborations with Partners including Google Cloud, Meta, Microsoft, Mistral AI and NVIDIA Ignite Ingenuity</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td><strong><em>ORLANDO</em></strong> — At its annual SAP Sapphire conference, SAP unveiled generative AI innovations and partnerships that showcase how the company is taking business to the next level in the era of AI.</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By infusing Business AI across an enterprise cloud portfolio that powers the world’s most mission-critical processes and partnering with companies pushing the edge of what’s possible with AI, SAP is igniting a new wave of insight and ingenuity in global business.</p>
  <p>“The Business AI innovations we’re announcing at SAP Sapphire in 2024 will redefine the way businesses run,” says Christian Klein, CEO and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “Today’s AI announcements and partnerships build on our commitment to deliver revolutionary technology that drives real-world results, helping customers unleash the agility and ingenuity they need to succeed in today’s fast-moving business landscape.”</p>
  <h2 id="ai-that-means-business">AI That Means Business</h2>
  <p>As SAP embeds Business AI across its enterprise solutions, it puts rich insights at users’ fingertips, empowering them to deliver better outcomes and elevate the creative problem-solving humans do best. Examples include AI-generated reports in SAP SuccessFactors solutions that give people managers responsibly sourced insights for compensation-related discussions as well as forecasting capabilities in SAP Sales Cloud solutions that predict combinations of salespeople and products most likely to drive sales. Meanwhile, the SAP Business Technology Platform is adding large language models from Amazon Web Services, Meta and Mistral AI to its generative AI hub. This capability in the SAP AI Core infrastructure makes it easier to build generative AI use cases for SAP applications.</p>
  <p>SAP’s generative AI copilot Joule, which quickly sorts and contextualizes data from multiple systems to advance automation and improve decision-making, is expanding throughout the company’s solution portfolio. Joule launched in <a href="/2023/09/joule-new-generative-ai-assistant">SAP SuccessFactors solutions last fall</a> and is now embedded into SAP S/4HANA Cloud solutions and others including SAP Build and SAP Integration Suite. Further expansion by year-end will include SAP Ariba and SAP Analytics Cloud solutions. At Sapphire, SAP also announced <a href="/">plans to further broaden Joule’s scope</a> by integrating it with Microsoft Copilot to surface even richer insights. This deep, bi-directional integration gives users a unified experience built right into the flow of work, enabling seamless access to information from interactions with business applications in SAP and Microsoft 365.</p>
  <p>Reflecting Business AI’s increasing importance, SAP is redoubling its commitment to the principles of relevant, reliable, and responsible AI it pioneered. At Sapphire, SAP is adopting the 10 guiding principles of the UNESCO Recommendation on the Ethics of Artificial Intelligence, which aim to ensure that AI technologies are developed and used in ways that respect human rights, promote fairness and contribute to sustainable development.</p>
  <h2 id="partnerships-that-scale-innovation">Partnerships That Scale Innovation</h2>
  <p>SAP is partnering with best-in-class technology leaders to push the limits of what generative AI can do at an enterprise level. In addition to our expanded collaborations with <a href="/2024/05/aws-sap-generative-ai-new-innovation">AWS</a> and Microsoft, partnerships with Google Cloud, Meta, Mistral AI and NVIDIA ensure SAP can harness the power of AI-ready technology to innovate at speed and deliver richer real-world results.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Google Cloud</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP and Google Cloud are expanding their partnership, using Business AI to help enterprises better predict and mitigate supply-chain risks to minimize disruptions and maintain optimal inventory levels. The companies will integrate Joule and the SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain solution with Google Cloud’s Gemini models AI assistant and Google Cloud Cortex Framework’s data foundation.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Meta</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP will leverage Meta Llama 3 to generate scripts that render highly customized analytics applications in SAP Analytics Cloud. Meta’s next-generation AI model excels at language nuances and contextual understanding, making it an ideal candidate for translating enterprise business requirements into tangible outcomes.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Mistral AI</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP will also add <a href="/">new large language models from Mistral AI</a>, a global company headquartered in Paris specializing in generative AI, to the generative AI hub capability in SAP AI Core.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>NVIDIA</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP and NVIDIA Corporation advance a <a href="https://blogs.nvidia.com/blog/sap-sapphire-ai-omniverse/">cross-product partnership</a> to embed cutting-edge technologies into enterprise-ready business applications:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>As SAP trains Joule to serve as an AI assistant for the RISE with SAP solution implementations, NVIDIA’s state-of-the-art AI models sift through SAP consulting assets to provide relevant and precise answers to implementation-related questions;</li>
    <li>As SAP embeds Joule in the ABAP Cloud model to generate ABAP code for SAP developers, NVIDIA’s accelerated infrastructure will run, scale, and manage SAP’s generative AI model for ABAP code generation;</li>
    <li>As SAP infuses generative AI into the SAP Intelligent Product Recommendation solution, NVIDIA Omniverse Cloud APIs enable the simulation of complex manufacturing products and configurations as industrial digital twins.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="cloud-technology-that-drives-agility-and-sustainability">Cloud Technology That Drives Agility and Sustainability</h2>
  <p>Business success in the era of AI means being in the cloud. SAP is making the move easier than ever with initiatives that help customers find partners with the expertise needed for complex SAP S/4HANA Cloud transformations. Further cloud innovations at SAP Sapphire include features that help the world’s organizations measure, manage and execute their sustainability strategies. SAP Sustainability Control Tower and SAP Sustainability Footprint Management solutions now track carbon footprints at scale and help businesses meet regulatory standards.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Learn more in the 2024 SAP Sapphire News Guide</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE:SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 (650) 445-6780, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a> PT<br>Marcus Winkler, +49 6227-767497, <a href="mailto:marcus.winkler@sap.com">marcus.winkler@sap.com</a> CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you receive this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/abap-cloud</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CP Foods Selects SAP Solutions for Cloud Sustainability]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/cp-foods-selects-sap-solutions-for-cloud-sustainability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/cp-foods-selects-sap-solutions-for-cloud-sustainability</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[CP Foods has selected SAP software to future-proof its business and use data to make more sustainable decisions. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183175263685a353d3b61ffbc18dc57a24b395640.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183175263685a353d3b61ffbc18dc57a24b395640.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_183175263685a353d3b61ffbc18dc57a24b395640.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="CP Foods Selects SAP Solutions for Cloud Sustainability" src="./media_183175263685a353d3b61ffbc18dc57a24b395640.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="cp-foods-selects-sap-solutions-for-cloud-sustainability">CP Foods Selects SAP Solutions for Cloud Sustainability</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF and BANGKOK</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced Charoen Pokphand Foods Public Company Limited (“CP Foods”) has selected multiple SAP solutions to drive further growth and competitive advantage and to ensure the sustainability of its products for the future.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="record-report-and-act-on-your-sustainability-goals-with-sap-software">Record, report and act on your sustainability goals with SAP software</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability/solutions.html">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Catering to more than 4 billion people globally, CP Foods is embarking on its next stage of digital transformation with the RISE with SAP, SAP Sustainability Footprint Management, and SAP Sustainability Control Tower solutions. In addition, the SAP EHS Management, environment management application will be implemented to future-proof its business and to gain strategic insight into the sustainability impact of its products, processes and infrastructure globally. The company is a leading integrated agro-industrial and food business that is one of the world’s largest producers of feed, shrimp, poultry and pork. It has operations in 17 countries and exports to more than 50 countries.</p>
  <h2 id="global-net-zero-ambitions">Global Net-Zero Ambitions</h2>
  <p>In line with CP Foods’ goal of becoming the “Sustainable Kitchen of the World,” CP Foods is the first food processing company in the world with near- and long-term forests, lands and agriculture (FLAG) sustainability targets validated by the Science-Based Targets Initiative (SBTi). CP Foods is looking to realize the company’s <a href="https://www.cpfworldwide.com/en/media-center/oversea-operations-coal-free-to-net-zero">Net Zero goals</a> of reducing 42% of Scope 1 and 2 emissions and 30.3% of Scope 3 emissions by 2030 – and 90% of Scope 1 and 2 emissions and 72% of Scope 3 emissions by 2050. To achieve these goals, the company is implementing SAP Sustainability solutions to record, report and act on real-time sustainability data, driving carbon accounting at both corporate and product levels.</p>
  <p>“Net Zero is the only solution to climate change,” CP Foods CEO Prasit Boondoungpraser said. “It is important to us to understand and reduce our impact on the planet, so we create food that is not only safe and nutritious for people but also green and clean for the earth. Feeding our livestock, farming our food and transporting it to people’s plates incurs emissions we have to be able to record and report. With RISE with SAP and SAP Sustainability solutions, we will have insight into actual emissions automated in real time rather than relying on manual averages, allowing us to make quick, informed and sustainable business decisions for our operations and for the planet.”</p>
  <p>SAP plans to provide a technology foundation that will support CP Foods in complying with forthcoming carbon regulations in various markets, including the EU Carbon Border Adjustment Mechanism (EU C-BAM) and U.S. SEC climate risk disclosures.</p>
  <p>Key to reducing total emissions, CP Foods will focus on supply chain emissions, with its emissions mostly falling under Scope 3. CP Foods will work with the Customer Success organization at SAP, leverage YASH Technologies’ sustainability expertise and build on Amazon Web Services (AWS) to implement SAP Sustainability solutions. Doing so will allow it to record and report on its Scope 1 and 2 emissions in Thailand and select Scope 3 (3.1 and 3.4) for its feed business in Thailand covering both FLAG and non-FLAG emissions. The next phase of implementation will extend in scope to cover operations around the world.</p>
  <h2 id="cloud-sustainability">Cloud Sustainability</h2>
  <p>Paul Marriott, president of SAP Asia Pacific &#x26; Japan, said: “Sustainability is a huge opportunity for businesses across Asia. Using RISE with SAP and our sustainability solutions, CP Foods is getting ahead of forthcoming emissions regulation and future-proofing its business by using data to make more sustainable decisions. It can use those insights to drive more operational efficiencies, optimize supply chains, and differentiate its business against competitors.”</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-our-approach-to-sustainability-and-our-aspirations-for-a-world-with-zero-emissions-zero-waste-and-zero-inequality">Learn more about our approach to sustainability and our aspirations for a world with zero emissions, zero waste and zero inequality</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability/our-approach.html">Explore our journey</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE:SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Rizka Laksmi, <a href="mailto:rizka.laksmi@sap.com">rizka.laksmi@sap.com</a>, WIB<br>Lesa Plingen, +49 622 776 9000, <a href="mailto:lesa.plingen@sap.com">lesa.plingen@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-ehs-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From CSRD Reporting to Sustainable Business Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/from-csrd-reporting-to-sustainable-business-outcomes</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/from-csrd-reporting-to-sustainable-business-outcomes</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[By leveraging SAP Sustainability solutions, organizations can move beyond compliance, like CSRD reporting, and operationalize sustainability.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/compliance</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>news-tag/green-ledger</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sustainability-solutions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[North American Customers Continue Turning to SAP in Q3 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/north-american-customers-q3-2023</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/north-american-customers-q3-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In the Q3 2023, our North American customers spanned all shapes, sizes, and industries, proving the momentum behind the cloud revolution.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-north-america</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accelerating Sustainability Innovation in the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/accelerating-sustainability-innovation-in-the-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/accelerating-sustainability-innovation-in-the-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With our cloud-driven innovations, we help customers build the foundation for the evolution of their long-term sustainability strategies.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How High Tech Helps S.Oleum Deliver ESG Metrics You Can Trust]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/high-tech-helps-s-oleum-deliver-esg-metrics</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/high-tech-helps-s-oleum-deliver-esg-metrics</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[S.Oleum’s data-driven sustainability efforts will generate revenue and sequester carbon. Read how SAP helps lay the foundation for success.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_130d6fab1e2941e378a85881bd255a5fab73223e2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_130d6fab1e2941e378a85881bd255a5fab73223e2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_130d6fab1e2941e378a85881bd255a5fab73223e2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How High Tech Helps S.Oleum Deliver ESG Metrics You Can Trust" src="./media_130d6fab1e2941e378a85881bd255a5fab73223e2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-high-tech-helps-soleum-deliver-esg-metrics-you-can-trust">How High Tech Helps S.Oleum Deliver ESG Metrics You Can Trust</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>How can a three-year-old agroforestry company produce trustworthy, <a href="/topics/sustainability">sustainable</a> feedstock – raw materials for finished goods, energy, and more – while reducing the amount of carbon in the atmosphere?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“We do that by using the biodiversity of this region, the Cerrado in Brazil,” Francisco de Blanco, S.Oleum co-founder and CEO, told SAP at the company’s headquarters, an innovative farm just outside João Pinheiro.</p>
  <p>Why the Brazilian outback? This tropical savanna is home to the macaúba, a highly adaptable oil-producing tree with a penchant for scrubbing harmful CO2 from the air. Macaúba fruit yields advanced vegetable oils (AVOs) and high-protein food – and it can be 15 times more productive than soybeans.</p>
  <p>“We are restoring the landscape that was deforested…Macaúba was native here many, many years ago,” Felipe Morbi, S.Oleum co-founder and Agroforestry VP, said. “Now we are bringing back these trees, and also all the other species, to restore this biodiversity.”</p>
  <p>S.Oleum seeks to accomplish this scientifically, using macaúba and other crops in an integrated crop-livestock-forest approach, according to Morbi. The goal is to create working farms that rejuvenate degraded, low-yielding soil – and that sequester into the soil more carbon than they generate.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ba7dafe5dd92eabd85315450bbf0bdc404c57879.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ba7dafe5dd92eabd85315450bbf0bdc404c57879.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ba7dafe5dd92eabd85315450bbf0bdc404c57879.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How S.Oleum Will Use High Tech to Get Back to Brazil’s Roots" src="./media_1ba7dafe5dd92eabd85315450bbf0bdc404c57879.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/czukYJD_15c">How S.Oleum Will Use High Tech to Get Back to Brazil’s Roots</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="science-based-approach-to-reforesting-the-cerrado">Science-Based Approach to Reforesting the Cerrado</h2>
  <p>“We are looking for the balance of the system,” Morbi said in a new <a href="https://youtu.be/czukYJD_15c">SAP video</a>. “We will measure the amount of carbon in the soil, the moisture, the biodiversity in terms of the plants we have, and also native animals coming back to the area.”</p>
  <p>Toward that end, S.Oleum is starting small, but aiming big. Most of the current crop grows on a 700-hectare, or more than 1,700-acre, pilot farm. But S.Oleum intends to plant more than 65 million additional macaúba trees by 2029, which would reforest 180,00 hectares – about 444,800 acres – in Brazil’s southeastern state of Minas Gerais.</p>
  <p>Over time, macaúba trees also help improve the nutrient and moisture capacity of the soil, making it easier to grow other crops, according to de Blanco. And S.Oleum increases farm productivity by growing carefully chosen crops in between rows of macaúba trees, such as sunflowers, peanuts, and yucas.</p>
  <p>“If you do it right, agriculture as a system is positive for the environment,” de Blanco said. “Plants that were deforested a few decades ago, they are currently in a poor state because they were depleted by poor management…We believe there are better ways, and that’s what we are pursuing here.”</p>
  <p>An innovative case in point: macaúba trees increase a biome’s carbon sequestration levels. Removing this greenhouse gas helps more than the planet; S.Oleum also generates revenue by selling carbon credits and building trust via its data.</p>
  <h2 id="any-little-bit-of-data">Any Little Bit of Data</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="earth-overshoot-day-2023-reversing-the-clock-for-a-sustainable-future">Earth Overshoot Day 2023: Reversing the Clock for a Sustainable Future</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2023/08/earth-overshoot-day-2023-sustainable-future">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Any little thing, any generation of data that R&#x26;D is currently developing, is extremely important,” Mirelle Santos, S.Oleum Agroforestry R&#x26;D manager, said. “We want to deploy technologies as dictated by those urgent needs.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_117cccc01d32d21d19b8033c668004e09a27b9c1b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_117cccc01d32d21d19b8033c668004e09a27b9c1b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_117cccc01d32d21d19b8033c668004e09a27b9c1b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Macaúba thorns" src="./media_117cccc01d32d21d19b8033c668004e09a27b9c1b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="300" height="225">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Photo by Derek Klobucher</em></p>
  <p>This could include remote sensing via drones that run fruit-recognition software, according to Santos. This would help S.Oleum gather and compile data quickly, without human error – and without sending workers, who must dress in personal protective equipment (PPE) to defend against snakes, mosquitos, the brutal Cerrado sun (even in winter), and dangerous macaúba thorns, which grow even on seedlings.</p>
  <p>S.Oleum’s intricate business model combines agriculture, forestry, biodiversity, and carbon offsetting – and that leads to a lot of complexity. SAP technology will be an important differentiator for this small enterprise, as well as a foundation for its future growth.</p>
  <p>“We have a big project to run; so, a lot of people, a lot of machines, a lot of suppliers,” Morbi said. “And we need everything in the right moment, in the right way.”</p>
  <h2 id="how-to-best-manage-esg-metrics">How to Best Manage ESG Metrics</h2>
  <p>“SAP is different because it is recognized as one of the most reliable ERP systems on the market, not only based on the technology,” de Blanco said. “Also, because it has well-established and well-defined processes.”</p>
  <p>Standardizing processes was “extremely important” for S.Oleum both internally and to inspire customer, stakeholder, and regulatory confidence, according to de Blanco. SAP will also enable S.Oleum to run its circular enterprise as well as record, report, and act on its sustainability data.</p>
  <p>“We have a very integrated system, and a very circular way to produce things,” de Blanco said. “Finding out where waste is generated – and where it’s being used – is very important to ensure the carbon intensity and the circularity of our systems at our entire site…This is where SAP helps us.”</p>
  <p>SAP S/4HANA, SAP Ariba solutions, SAP Concur solutions, and SAP SuccessFactors solutions will help standardize all of S.Oleum’s processes, which will improve transparency and compliance, according to S.Oleum IT Director Marcio Propp. To help better manage and understand its myriad environmental, social, and governance (ESG) metrics, the company has also begun implementation of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability-control-tower.html">SAP Sustainability Control Tower</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/sustainability-footprint-management.html">SAP Sustainability Footprint Management</a>.</p>
  <p>“It is super important that we have a very robust core system in place because it will serve as the basis for all our other processes…and practically all niche applications focused on digital agriculture connect with this core with SAP,” Propp said. “SAP is an agribusiness market standard, and it makes perfect sense for S.Oleum to be part of this ecosystem.”</p>
  <p>That’s a big deal because compliant, transparent ESG metrics are crucial to S.Oleum’s success, according to de Blanco.</p>
  <h2 id="a-matter-of-trust">A Matter of Trust</h2>
  <p>“Somewhere around one-third of our revenues come from carbon credits,” de Blanco said. “This is our, let’s say, core business…to convert sustainability into revenues and financial results.”</p>
  <p>That will require trust. SAP core technologies, such as SAP S/4HANA Cloud and <a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">SAP Sustainability solutions</a>, will help S.Oleum keep that trust, thanks to a reliable foundation of sustainability data and robust, auditable ESG metrics for reporting.</p>
  <p>“My advice for companies that are starting their sustainability endeavor: do it as quick as you can,” de Blanco said. “And do it attached to science.”</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>For more information on how SAP helps companies record, report, and act on their sustainability goals, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">www.sap.com/sustainability</a>.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Top photo credit S.Oleum</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/agribusiness</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sustainability-solutions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[msg global: Future-Proofing Sustainability Ambitions with SAP Sustainability Control Tower]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/msg-global-sap-sustainability-control-tower</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/msg-global-sap-sustainability-control-tower</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[msg global implemented SAP Sustainability Control Tower to help enable the data transparency needed to achieve its sustainability goals.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Rated Top Three in IDC’s Sustainability Index]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-rated-top-three-idc-sustainability-index</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-rated-top-three-idc-sustainability-index</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP placed in the top three of 23 software vendors that were assessed for the IDC Sustainability Index for Software Providers. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sustainability-solutions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Introduces Transactional Carbon Accounting to Accelerate Climate Action]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-introduces-transactional-carbon-accounting</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-introduces-transactional-carbon-accounting</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is well-positioned deliver high-quality carbon accounting to rapidly scale business decarbonization. Learn about the new SAP solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-accounting</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>news-tag/decarbonization</category>
            <category>news-tag/net-zero</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sustainability-solutions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Steps to Profitable and Sustainable Energy Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/three-steps-profitable-sustainable-energy-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/three-steps-profitable-sustainable-energy-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Energy-intensive industries are exploring new trends for profitable, sustainable business and energy management. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/decarbonization</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-twin</category>
            <category>news-tag/greenhouse-gas-emissions</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-io</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainability Intelligence: The Vital Importance of a Business Technology Platform]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sustainability-intelligence-business-technology-platform</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sustainability-intelligence-business-technology-platform</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP partners are applying their attention, knowledge, and ingenuity to address key business sustainability challenges with SAP BTP.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PwC and SAP Launch New Innovation Strategy to Help Organizations Achieve Their ESG and Net-Zero Targets]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/pwc-sap-new-innovation-strategy-esg-net-zero</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/pwc-sap-new-innovation-strategy-esg-net-zero</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The PwC and SAP strategy is directed at creating trusted solutions to address key ESG business challenges. Read the news to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>news-tag/pwc</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Measuring the Carbon Footprint of Employees Can Help You Make More Informed and Strategic Business Decisions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/measuring-employee-carbon-footprint-business-decisions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/measuring-employee-carbon-footprint-business-decisions</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Executives can make informed decisions when considering the social and actual carbon footprint of employees in planning. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/experience-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plant-Based Food Company Upfield Maximizes Supply Chain Transparency]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/upfield-maximizes-supply-chain-transparency</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/upfield-maximizes-supply-chain-transparency</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Plant-based food company Upfield was on a mission to have end-to-end integrated planning in its supply chain. Read to find out how SAP helped.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-transportation-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Sustainability Control Tower: Creating the Right Data Foundation for ESG Reporting and Steering]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/data-foundation-for-esg-reporting-steering-sap-sustainability-control-tower</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/data-foundation-for-esg-reporting-steering-sap-sustainability-control-tower</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A new data foundation for ESG is needed to cope with several sustainability challenges. SAP Sustainability Control Tower can help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Partnerships Accelerate Sustainable Business]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sustainability-partnerships-accelerate-business</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sustainability-partnerships-accelerate-business</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has established a wide range of sustainability partnerships to help customers build trust and transparency in ESG reporting. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Sustainability Control Tower Update Opens Powerful New Opportunities for Holistic ESG Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-sustainability-control-tower-update-holistic-esg</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-sustainability-control-tower-update-holistic-esg</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how the new SAP Sustainability Control Tower update opens up powerful new opportunities for holistic ESG management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a2b46088d526871fed1f66aaea95c3509adb647c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a2b46088d526871fed1f66aaea95c3509adb647c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a2b46088d526871fed1f66aaea95c3509adb647c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Sustainability Control Tower Update Opens Powerful New Opportunities for Holistic ESG Management" src="./media_1a2b46088d526871fed1f66aaea95c3509adb647c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-sustainability-control-tower-update-opens-powerful-new-opportunities-for-holistic-esg-management">SAP Sustainability Control Tower Update Opens Powerful New Opportunities for Holistic ESG Management</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Corporate environmental, social, and governance (ESG) management has become a catalyst for companies to minimize their carbon footprints, reduce waste, and create fair, safe, and just working environments for employees.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Many companies are responding to rapidly increasing regulation in this area and have set ambitious ESG targets. Sustainable business is no longer a question of if or why, but how.</p>
  <h2 id="esg-management-relies-on-data-transparency">ESG Management Relies on Data Transparency</h2>
  <p>Current ESG management relies heavily on data averages and estimates. Most companies have not fully integrated their ESG data recording and control into their core financial, procurement, supply chain management, and human resources (HR) systems. This financial and non-financial data is disconnected, stored in spreadsheets, not updated from real-time systems, and not easily shared within the company or with partners such as upstream suppliers or downstream logistics providers.</p>
  <p>Considering that on average 90% of a business’s carbon footprint lies within its supply chain, the inability to track, manage, and gain insights from live data and embed it into core business processes can cripple even the best intentioned ESG efforts. Worse, it can mislead investors, create compliance issues, and misguide transformation efforts. Unifying ESG data provides significant gains in capabilities and competitive performance.</p>
  <p>Companies cannot make sustainable business decisions using data they do not have or cannot use.</p>
  <h2 id="esg-data-moves-from-averages-to-actuals">ESG Data Moves from Averages to Actuals</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="video-transform-into-a-sustainable-enterprise-with-sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises">Video: Transform into a Sustainable Enterprise with SAP Cloud for Sustainable Enterprises</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2022/10/2e55f8e5-477e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>That is why we developed <strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability-control-tower.html">SAP Sustainability Control Tower</a></strong>, which we introduced in January this year. In a market update available now, the solution offers what companies are looking for today to run more sustainably.</p>
  <p>First, companies want to record ESG factors based on actual data, not averages. SAP Sustainability Control Tower easily imports cross-enterprise data from SAP systems like SAP S/4HANA, SAP Product Footprint Management, and SAP Environment, Health, and Safety. It also integrates with non-SAP systems using a range of APIs to create audit-ready data. Businesses can integrate and analyze granular ESG data using the established structures from their finance, HR, and operations teams using templated data models and calculations.</p>
  <p>Second, companies want to report to existing and future standards. SAP Sustainability Control Tower effectively shares and organizes ESG data from across the company. With complete and integrated ESG data, companies can more accurately and readily report their performance to various reporting requirements and frameworks, such as GRI, WEF, TCFD, the EU Taxonomy, and upcoming U.S. SEC requirements. Through APIs, customers can further extend the functionality by bringing in their own metrics as well as industry and regulatory content, and use other applications.</p>
  <p>And third, companies want to act by planning with actionable insights, forecasts, and concrete targets to achieve measurable impacts. With SAP Sustainability Control Tower, companies can set targets, gain actionable insights into core processes, forecast outcomes, analyze scenarios and trade-offs, report progress, and create role-specific actions to improve sustainability performance.</p>
  <p>For example, our customer Grupo Energia de Bogota (GEB) aims to transform the way it manages and reports ESG performance.</p>
  <p>“Grupo Energía Bogota S.A. (GEB), an energy platform group of companies in Latin America with over 125 years of operations in the transmission, generation, and distribution of electric energy as well as the transportation and distribution of natural gas across Colombia, Peru, Brazil, and Guatemala, has chosen SAP Sustainability Control Tower powered by RISE with SAP, SAP Business Technology Platform, and SAP Signavio solutions to manage our sustainability strategy as part of our enterprise transformation goals,” said Jose Fernando Galvis Panqueva, CIO, Grupo de Energia de Bogota. “With this powerful combination of cloud solutions, our company will manage its overall holistic reporting requirements, including ESG KPIs; reduce time and effort in manual data collection and reporting variation with different regulatory requirements and timelines; standardize processes for subsidiaries; and manage and integrate existing SAP and non-SAP data.”</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_199b7b3684b51d81ce5e507cf81421b9bf01af3d1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_199b7b3684b51d81ce5e507cf81421b9bf01af3d1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_199b7b3684b51d81ce5e507cf81421b9bf01af3d1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Sustainability Control Tower – Holistic Steering and ESG Reporting" src="./media_199b7b3684b51d81ce5e507cf81421b9bf01af3d1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Nx5f8jQ2vDg">SAP Sustainability Control Tower – Holistic Steering and ESG Reporting</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="sustainable-business-means-working-together">Sustainable Business Means Working Together</h2>
  <p>Built on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP)</a>, SAP Sustainability Control Tower provides a flexible, extensible technology architecture that can help create complementary solutions or add custom content. Businesses operating in different regions or industries will have different needs, so this level of flexibility is essential. <a href="/2022/11/sustainability-partnerships-accelerate-business">SAP has the broadest range of global partners</a> to help companies develop specifications and implement customized sustainability solutions.</p>
  <p>Sustainable business is a goal we will achieve only by working together. It is a collaboration and innovation process for all of us, including SAP. We’re implementing SAP Sustainability Control Tower in our own business to enhance our holistic business management, create insights on the total economic, social, and environmental impact our organization has across a range of measures, and accelerate programs such as our net-zero emissions by 2030 implementation.</p>
  <p>Transforming a business to run sustainably is a long-term process, but one with urgency. We are seeing customers join us at different stages of their sustainable business transformations. They are pragmatic and recognize that the transition to sustainability is a “marathon with no finish line.” Some are looking to quickly regain compliance with rapidly changing regulations, while others want to optimize their ESG data management and performance. In nearly every case, these are multi-year digital transformations to become intelligent, sustainable enterprises.</p>
  <p>Since most of the world’s Fortune 2,000 companies run SAP software and almost 90% of the worlds finance and goods flows touch SAP systems, much of the data needed for holistic corporate sustainability management lives in SAP systems for enterprise resource planning (ERP) systems and related applications. Harnessing this data is essential to creating and managing a “green line” with the same rigor as their top and bottom lines.</p>
  <p>SAP Sustainability Control Tower is vital to creating this holistic capability. It offers a flexible open architecture, powerful integration and scalability, and support from a broad range of partners. The solution works in tandem with the sustainability solutions within <a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">SAP Cloud for Sustainable Enterprises</a>, which add additional functionalities including carbon emissions management, waste and materials management for circularity, and people sustainability.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>For more information on how SAP helps companies record, report, and act on their sustainability goals, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">www.sap.com/sustainability</a>.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Sebastian Steinhaeuser is chief strategy officer at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP BTP: The Technological Backbone of SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sap-btp-technological-backbone</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sap-btp-technological-backbone</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[What makes SAP BTP so unique? SAP's JG Chirapurath explains and gives examples where the platform is making a difference.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14acda8fa2476cd0aacdcb6efb7680c7c16ef4c45.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14acda8fa2476cd0aacdcb6efb7680c7c16ef4c45.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14acda8fa2476cd0aacdcb6efb7680c7c16ef4c45.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP BTP: The Technological Backbone of SAP" src="./media_14acda8fa2476cd0aacdcb6efb7680c7c16ef4c45.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-btp-the-technological-backbone-of-sap">SAP BTP: The Technological Backbone of SAP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>A stable house needs a strong foundation. This principle also applies to every organization. Under the pressure of current economic instabilities, enterprises need to remain strong, stable, flexible, and adaptable. To build resilient, intelligent, sustainable, and socially responsible business models, a strong technological foundation for digital transformation is required.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With the right platform, enterprises can transform data into business value and drive more intelligent decision-making. Combined with the ability to easily integrate and extend applications, enterprises can develop new products, processes, and business models more quickly than ever. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP)</a> can provide that strong, yet flexible, foundation for SAP customers.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d97d3eae014569fc7264eb13ddbe79547357c076.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d97d3eae014569fc7264eb13ddbe79547357c076.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d97d3eae014569fc7264eb13ddbe79547357c076.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="IN FOCUS: Spotlight on SAP Business Technology Platform" src="./media_1d97d3eae014569fc7264eb13ddbe79547357c076.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r72ExdS9CKA">IN FOCUS: Spotlight on SAP Business Technology Platform</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="sap-btp-in-a-nutshell">SAP BTP in a Nutshell</h2>
  <p>SAP BTP is a cloud platform that is available and scalable in every region worldwide. It includes on-premise and cloud-native technologies and services and integrates four technology portfolios into one unified environment hosted and managed by SAP. These include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Application development and integration (SAP Extension Suite and SAP Integration Suite)</li>
    <li>Data management (SAP HANA Cloud and SAP Data Intelligence)</li>
    <li>Analytics (SAP Analytics Cloud solution for business intelligence and SAP Data Warehouse Cloud)</li>
    <li>Solutions for intelligent technologies such as artificial intelligence (AI) or robotic process automation (RPA)</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP BTP offers what customers and partners need to develop new solutions and connect existing ones. “It’s basically what makes SAP applications work,” says JG Chirapurath, chief marketing and solutions officer for Platform and Technology at SAP.</p>
  <h2 id="what-makes-sap-btp-different-from-other-cloud-platforms">What Makes SAP BTP Different from Other Cloud Platforms?</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-technology-platform-shapes-a-platform-centric-future-in-the-cloud">SAP Business Technology Platform Shapes a Platform-Centric Future in the Cloud</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2022/10/sap-btp-shapes-platform-centric-paas-future">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP BTP is fully optimized for SAP applications. It helps customers, partners, and internal development teams store and manage their data and gain valuable insights. In addition, applications can be created, extended, or integrated, and entire business processes can be optimized and automated.</p>
  <p>The solutions provided take into account specific circumstances of different industries as well as local regulations. Unlike other cloud platforms, SAP BTP can add context to the data that is processed in business processes. This enables complete, real-time insights into the respective business contexts.</p>
  <p>However, it doesn’t stop at business processes alone. All functions are natively integrated into the SAP software stack. This enables customers and partners to optimize the interaction of services and technologies. The leaner and simplified processes allow an accelerated innovation capability. With the help of preconfigured, industry-specific content, new solutions can be implemented and developed in much less time, which can significantly reduce costs. Many customers are looking to extend their solutions and add new functionality. Chirapurath emphasizes that low-code and no-code development tools are often desired for this purpose.</p>
  <p>“You want to look at SAP BTP as the engine that enables those connections, enables you to understand how data flows, enables you to understand what is exactly happening inside your organization,” Chirapurath explains. SAP BTP can run in either a public or private cloud, providing the flexibility needed to extend the platform capabilities outside the “SAP world,” or on major hyperscalers such as AWS, Azure, or GCP.</p>
  <h2 id="royal-greenland-shows-how-sap-btp-supports-sustainability-goals">Royal Greenland Shows How SAP BTP Supports Sustainability Goals</h2>
  <p>Today’s customers have changed needs and expectations. They demand individualized offers, want personalized experiences, and pay attention to sustainable and ethical business practices. To meet this change, companies need to transform their businesses digitally.</p>
  <p>This is the case for Royal Greenland, a global leader in the market for seafood products that strives for a sustainable business model. Due to concerns about overfishing in the oceans, many consumers today want to know that seafood comes from responsible sources. The company’s goal is to ensure the health of the local ecosystem for fishery products while also prioritizing the prosperity of fishing communities.</p>
  <p>Based on SAP BTP, <a href="/2022/07/royal-greenland-local-fishing-communities-digital-journey">Royal Greenland has developed three applications</a> to streamline procurement processes for fishermen and support the company’s sustainability goals. The platform helps the company capture all data, including the location, quantity, and type of fish caught. This information is then fed into Royal Greenland’s enterprise resource planning (ERP) and supply chain system. With the help of analytics tools, managers now can get full visibility into fishing practices while ensuring that all fishermen are paid correctly.</p>
  <p>In the interview, Chirapurath talks about other examples where SAP BTP is in use and making a difference. Among them is the SAP-sponsored <a href="/2022/07/sap-hosts-its-first-ever-esports-tournament">esports</a> team Team Liquid, which uses SAP data and analytics solutions to make split-second decisions in the game. He also talks about the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability-control-tower.html">SAP Sustainability Control Tower</a> solution, which helps companies monitor and manage financial and sustainability and governance metrics.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Business Journeys from SAP Smooth the Path to Sustainable Business]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sap-business-journeys-sustainability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sap-business-journeys-sustainability</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Stay ahead of customer demand, stakeholder expectations, and regulatory changes with SAP Business Journeys for two sustainability solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-journeys</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Capgemini and SAP Accelerate Automotive Sustainability]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/capgemini-and-sap-accelerate-automotive-sustainability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/capgemini-and-sap-accelerate-automotive-sustainability</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In the automotive industry, sustainability must be at the foundation of every decision. Learn more about SAP and Capgemini's initiative.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/capgemini</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-green-token</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-supply-chain-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Extending the Reach of SAP Cloud for Sustainable Enterprises]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/extending-sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/extending-sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Cloud for Sustainable Enterprises combines a comprehensive portfolio of solutions to holistically manage sustainability performance.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Business Journeys Provide Prescriptive Services Packages to Deliver Targeted Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/sap-business-journeys-prescriptive-services-targeted-outcomes</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/sap-business-journeys-prescriptive-services-targeted-outcomes</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New SAP Business Journeys combine expertise and insight to address customers’ events as they move to the cloud and the latest SAP technology.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-journeys</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Business Journeys: Delivering Targeted Outcomes with Prescriptive Services Packages]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/sap-business-journeys-prescriptive-services-packages</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/sap-business-journeys-prescriptive-services-packages</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Business Journeys provide a quick, clear path to help solve specific cross-company challenges with services and support offerings.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/cloud-success-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-journeys</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and the Ellen MacArthur Foundation Announce Circular Economy Partnership to Deliver Regenerative Business]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/circular-economy-partnership-regenerative-business-ellen-macarthur-foundation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/circular-economy-partnership-regenerative-business-ellen-macarthur-foundation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has become a partner in the Ellen MacArthur Foundation’s network to deliver circular economy solutions led by regenerative business.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BCG and SAP Join Forces to Transform Companies into Sustainable Enterprises]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/bcg-and-sap-transform-sustainable-enterprises</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/bcg-and-sap-transform-sustainable-enterprises</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Together, BCG and SAP will help companies tackle the generational challenge of climate change. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/bcg</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Disrupting Business Models to Protect Our Most Valuable Asset: The Planet]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/sap-and-bcg-partnership-protect-planet</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/sap-and-bcg-partnership-protect-planet</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The SAP and BCG partnership supports companies in the digital transformation to become intelligent sustainable enterprises.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/bcg</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Changing Our Reality for the Better by Moving Toward a Sustainable World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2022/01/moving-toward-sustainable-world</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2022/01/moving-toward-sustainable-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP wants to make 2022 the year an interconnected world transitions toward a more sustainable world. Learn more about how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12de401c221ecaa5cca1ef1e16db0e23766e63072.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12de401c221ecaa5cca1ef1e16db0e23766e63072.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12de401c221ecaa5cca1ef1e16db0e23766e63072.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Changing Our Reality for the Better by Moving Toward a Sustainable World" src="./media_12de401c221ecaa5cca1ef1e16db0e23766e63072.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="changing-our-reality-for-the-better-by-moving-toward-a-sustainable-world">Changing Our Reality for the Better by Moving Toward a Sustainable World</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Gone are the days when companies discussed the <strong>why</strong> of sustainable business practices. Today, it is all about the <strong>how</strong>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>How can businesses take climate action? How can they turn linear processes into circular resources and product flows? How can they ensure socially responsible value chains? And ultimately, how can they integrate economic, environmental, and social performance into strategic decision-making?</p>
  <p>These questions are top of mind for executives. In 2021, sustainability <a href="https://go.alpha-sense.com/wp-sap-sustainability/">became the top trending topic for the C-suite</a>.</p>
  <p>At SAP, we deliver answers to these questions through our products. Our customers can benefit from solutions that help them achieve <strong>zero emissions</strong>, <strong>zero waste</strong>, <strong>zero inequality</strong>, as well as <strong>holistic steering and reporting</strong> of their sustainability efforts.</p>
  <p>Last year, we launched three new solutions: <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/product-footprint-management.html">SAP Product Footprint Management</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/responsible-design-and-production.html">SAP Responsible Design and Production</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability-control-tower.html">SAP Sustainability Control Tower</a>. All are embedded SAP S/4HANA cloud-native applications that are delivered in a modular way and built on top of SAP Business Technology Platform.</p>
  <p>What is more, we are embedding sustainability across SAP’s entire solution portfolio. A recent example is the inclusion of product footprints in SAP Integrated Business Planning, so customers can monitor the greenhouse gas emissions from their production plants. Another example is the integration of SAP Sustainability Control Tower with SAP SuccessFactors solutions, enabling customers to obtain insights into how their organization is faring on crucial aspects such as diversity and inclusion.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="choose-both-profitability-and-sustainability-with-sap">Choose both profitability and sustainability with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="sustainable-business-strategies-sustainable-enterprises">Sustainable Business Strategies, Sustainable Enterprises</h2>
  <p>For the last 50 years, our innovative solutions have helped our customers transform their business processes and stay ahead in rapidly changing business environments. And we will continue to take and enable organizations of any size and in any industry to take a transformative approach to sustainability as well.</p>
  <p>Quick fixes that do not get to the root cause of problems won’t make businesses more sustainable in the long run. Fragmented sustainability strategies won’t help. Sustainable business strategies will. That is why we support companies in integrating sustainability into the heart of their business processes.</p>
  <p>Our approach pays off. Today, the most sustainable companies run our software. According to our analysis of S&#x26;P Trucost Limited data and <a href="https://www.spglobal.com/esg/solutions/data-intelligence-esg-scores">S&#x26;P Global ESG Scores for 2021</a>, SAP customers with high digital maturity — those adopting SAP’s latest technologies — on average have 75% better environmental, social, and governance (ESG) scores compared to their industry peers. They also produce 24% less CO2 emissions than the market average.</p>
  <p>To further facilitate the sustainability transformation for our customers, we recently launched a new offering. <a href="/2022/01/sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises-take-action-together">SAP Cloud for Sustainable Enterprises</a> is a flexible bundle of sustainability-specific applications. It allows businesses to adopt our solutions based on the current stage of their sustainability transformation. Depending on where they stand, they can implement holistic management or start with specific areas of sustainability performance.</p>
  <h2 id="chasing-zero-together">Chasing Zero, Together</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises-taking-action-together">SAP Cloud for Sustainable Enterprises: Taking Action Together</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2022/01/sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises-take-action-together">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The past year has been all about delivering the tools that help businesses transition into sustainable enterprises. So, what’s next? 2022 will be the year to implement these tools <a href="/2022/01/global-sustainability-ecosystem-power-scale">globally in close collaboration with our customers and partners</a>.</p>
  <p>Ultimately, the transition to a more sustainable global economy is not something one company can achieve on its own. In today’s interconnected world, we must rely on our ecosystem to ensure sustainability across the entire value chain. Let’s make 2022 the year we transition toward a more sustainable world, together.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Thomas Saueressig is a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE leading SAP Product Engineering.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Our Planet Cannot Afford Fragmented Reporting – Can You?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/12/planet-cannot-afford-fragmented-reporting-sap-sustainability-control-tower</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/12/planet-cannot-afford-fragmented-reporting-sap-sustainability-control-tower</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The days of fragmented reporting must end. Go further with ESG integration and data transparency using SAP Sustainability Control Tower.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fa4922faa7ff4ba0376ab0f75cc3ace85cd4e944.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fa4922faa7ff4ba0376ab0f75cc3ace85cd4e944.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1fa4922faa7ff4ba0376ab0f75cc3ace85cd4e944.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Our Planet Cannot Afford Fragmented Reporting – Can You?" src="./media_1fa4922faa7ff4ba0376ab0f75cc3ace85cd4e944.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="our-planet-cannot-afford-fragmented-reporting--can-you">Our Planet Cannot Afford Fragmented Reporting – Can You?</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>There is consensus. The recent <a href="https://ukcop26.org/">United Nations Climate Change Conference of the Parties</a> (<a href="/topics/cop26">COP26</a>) made at least two things clear: we need to move faster toward our goal to reduce greenhouse gas emissions and a fair transition won’t come cheap. Therefore, no enterprise can afford to waste time or money when it comes to aligning their sustainability ambitions with their actions.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Stakeholders are coming to the same conclusions that we have long been convinced of. Even before announcing our Climate 21 initiative two years ago, <a href="/2021/12/sap-leads-sustainability-rankings">we have been seen as front-runners</a> in providing environmental transparency. We have long understood the importance of measuring sustainability progress holistically and connecting financial and pre-financial data. We’ve been doing that since 2012. That’s when we merged our sustainability and annual reports into an integrated report.</p>
  <p>We know that the days of fragmented reporting must end. And now, many more businesses are seeing how fundamental the issues of transparency on environmental, social, and governance (ESG) impacts are. But many businesses still struggle with a multitude of reporting frameworks and lack of appropriate data. This is what stands in the way of consistent investor-focused disclosures. Our planet cannot afford this. Increasingly, consumers want to know the provenance of their products. They want to be assured that they are making choices based on data they can trust.</p>
  <p>The sustainability issues we face today are different from all other previous threats and opportunities — in scope, scale, and ultimately in the consequences. Measuring, reporting, and achieving the sustainable business goals we set is imperative to a <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/building-solutions-future-has-already-arrived-thomas-saueressig/?trackingId=sxlQXAPxQ2CzqFo6obbMjQ%3D%3D">net-zero, nature-positive and socially-inclusive future</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-sustainability-control-tower-a-commanding-business-view">SAP Sustainability Control Tower: A Commanding Business View</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="businesses-want-to-make-sustainable-decisions-they-need-the-right-intelligence-to-do-it">Businesses Want to Make Sustainable Decisions; They Need the Right Intelligence to Do It</h2>
  <p>The vast majority of business leaders I connect with want to lead their businesses sustainably. They care about planetary and societal impacts; in fact, their customers, investors, and employees demand it. At SAP, our aspiration goes far beyond enabling businesses to achieve efficiency. We work with customers to reinvent their business processes to achieve sustainable growth. That means enabling businesses to use data in agile ways, across all sustainability dimensions. We provide early alerts that allow companies to be responsive and we give customers the full picture they need to move proactively on their ESG issues.</p>
  <p>Sustainability data is “pre-financial,” not “non-financial.” That means the search for sustainability levers must go beyond the financials to bring together all sustainability data dimensions, including emissions, material flows, and social impacts. We know this and it is why we have made this possible today. For example, with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/product-footprint-management.html">SAP Product Footprint Management</a>, companies get visibility into their carbon footprint data throughout a product’s value chain, including for material sourcing and production. And that’s the insight businesses need to make proactive, sustainable supply chain decisions.</p>
  <h2 id="scale-data-across-business-networks-to-mitigate-planetary-impacts">Scale Data Across Business Networks to Mitigate Planetary Impacts</h2>
  <p>Individual businesses can only do so much. Emissions do not recognize company boundaries and therefore we must help companies reach beyond their own four walls. We know we must connect our customers into a network of intelligent, sustainable enterprises.</p>
  <p>Intelligent cross-enterprise scenarios that enable data sharing across value chains will create impact at scale. Business networks enable companies to continuously re-evaluate and re-engage with each other, creating additional value for their customers and our planet.</p>
  <h2 id="from-voluntary-to-mandatory-esg-standards-are-evolving">From Voluntary to Mandatory, ESG Standards Are Evolving</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="accelerating-a-new-era-of-sustainability-management">Accelerating a New Era of Sustainability Management</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/12/sap-sustainability-control-tower-new-era-sustainability-management">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>ESG reporting is maturing; there is no doubt about that. Climate-related disclosures are evolving from voluntary to mandatory. Around 100 countries have explicitly expressed support for starting negotiations for a global agreement on plastics in 2022. The European Union is already developing a social taxonomy based on global social and human rights norms. SAP also recently released an <a href="https://www3.weforum.org/docs/WEF_Joint_Open_Letter_to%20EU_institutions_Future_of_Sustainability_Reporting.pdf">open letter</a> asking the European Union to act on ESG disclosure standards. We want to encourage a global baseline set of standards. We fully support corporate transparency that meets the needs of all stakeholders and improves connectivity between sustainability and financial reporting.</p>
  <p>And, once again, we at SAP have stepped up to provide the solutions that companies need to execute on these evolving standards and connect their environmental, social, and financial values, holistically. Today, I’m proud to say that we just released <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability-control-tower.html">SAP Sustainability Control Tower</a>, a solution that enables customers to go further on their ESG integration and data transparency journey. Our solution enables non-financial — or, as I prefer to call them, “pre-financial” — disclosures focused on four aspects: people, planet, prosperity, and principles of governance. This includes measurements around greenhouse gas emissions, pay equality, and board diversity. It enables comparisons between companies, regardless of industry or region.</p>
  <p>Our two previously released sustainability products, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/product-footprint-management.html">SAP Product Footprint Management</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/responsible-design-and-production.html">SAP Responsible Design and Production</a>, feed precisely those new data dimensions, which businesses have so far been lacking, into SAP Sustainability Control Tower.</p>
  <p>Our new solution has the World Economic Forum’s Stakeholder Capitalism Metrics as its foundation. These metrics are based on existing standards to make ESG disclosures more comparable and consistent. They were developed within the International Business Council, a community of over 120 global CEOs who seek to improve the ways companies measure and demonstrate their contributions toward creating a more sustainable relationship with our planet.</p>
  <p>And of course, our partners are integral here. Deloitte, EY, and PwC are a few examples of the partners that bring immense knowledge, not only about the framework, but also about the ESG transformations of our customers. Strategic partners like BCG enable our customers to take a holistic perspective toward establishing ESG and climate compliance.</p>
  <h2 id="time-is-of-the-essence">Time Is of the Essence</h2>
  <p>Businesses that set out a 10-year agenda for dealing with their sustainability challenges are moving much too slowly. We all need to move quickly to enable the shift to new business models. Time is of the essence.</p>
  <p>At SAP, we know how important it is that corporate sustainability efforts be measured, reported, steered, and communicated effectively. And I am personally very proud of the <a href="/2021/12/sap-sustainability-control-tower-new-era-sustainability-management">leadership we continue to demonstrate here</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Thomas Saueressig is a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE leading SAP Product Engineering.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Sustainability Control Tower: A Commanding Business View]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/sap-sustainability-control-tower-business-view</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/sap-sustainability-control-tower-business-view</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The new SAP Sustainability Control Tower solution helps companies monitor and control financial, sustainability, and governance indicators.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_178ac8cffe9c3f119cbea667aae6c42edcad8f7aa.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_178ac8cffe9c3f119cbea667aae6c42edcad8f7aa.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_178ac8cffe9c3f119cbea667aae6c42edcad8f7aa.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Sustainability Control Tower: A Commanding Business View" src="./media_178ac8cffe9c3f119cbea667aae6c42edcad8f7aa.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-sustainability-control-tower-a-commanding-business-view">SAP Sustainability Control Tower: A Commanding Business View</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP unveiled the new SAP Sustainability Control Tower solution today, designed to help enterprises monitor operational performance and steer their business according to a combination of traditional- and sustainability-related performance indicators.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The cloud-based solution’s dashboard provides executives a commanding view of business operations and enables faster decision-making in response to events that, if unrecognized, would imperil company objectives.</p>
  <p>“The release of SAP Sustainability Control Tower represents another key milestone on our mission to establish the ‘green line’ alongside the top and bottom lines as key dimensions of performance,” says Gunther Rothermel, head of SAP S/4HANA Sustainability Management. “Based on the power of SAP Business Technology Platform, the solution provides the necessary agility and flexibility to quickly adapt to evolving and changing requirements without having to write code.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability-control-tower.html">SAP Sustainability Control Tower</a> enables companies to transform into intelligent and sustainable enterprises based on financial as well as environmental, social, and governance (ESG) indicators, allowing them to fully assess global impact both within their operations and across their business networks.</p>
  <p>“The very first thing companies need to do on their path of becoming sustainable enterprises is to understand their environmental footprint based on facts and figures,” says Jan Gilg, president of SAP S/4HANA, SAP. “Using these insights, SAP Sustainability Control Tower combines a company’s critical ESG metrics into one aggregated view, helping leaders take informed decisions to shape a better, sustainable future.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="our-planet-cannot-afford-fragmented-reporting">Our Planet Cannot Afford Fragmented Reporting</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="the-push-to-become-more-sustainable-and-socially-responsible">The Push to Become More Sustainable and Socially Responsible</h2>
  <p>A number of drivers – ecological, economic, and societal – are currently motivating businesses and entire industries to make their operations more sustainable. Companies have taken notice, for example, that investors, shareholders, regulators, and consumers increasingly demand responsibly derived products and services with a smaller environmental footprint.​</p>
  <p>In a <a href="https://www.stern.nyu.edu/experience-stern/about/departments-centers-initiatives/centers-of-research/center-sustainable-business/research/research-initiatives/csb-sustainable-market-share-index#:~:text=Our%20findings%20include%3A,products%20not%20marketed%20as%20sustainable.">study of consumer purchasing from 2015 to 2019</a>, the share of sustainability-marketed products grew more than seven times faster than other products, delivering 54.7% of CPG market growth. According to The World Bank, <a href="https://carbonpricingdashboard.worldbank.org/">65 carbon pricing initiatives</a> have already been implemented worldwide. A <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/global/en/pages/about-deloitte/articles/millennialsurvey.html">Deloitte survey from 2021</a> confirmed that younger generations want to work for companies with a purpose beyond profit.</p>
  <p>Most recently, the ambitious goals discussed at the <a href="https://ukcop26.org/">UN Climate Change Conference</a> (COP26) in Glasgow made it clear that businesses are under growing pressure to accelerate their sustainability efforts in conformance with regulations and that ESG-related KPIs have become part of the “license to operate.”</p>
  <p>In a <a href="https://insights.sap.com/environmental-sustainability-affects-competitiveness/">2021 SAP Insights global survey</a> of business professionals who are knowledgeable about their organization’s sustainability goals, actions, and reporting methods, 17% of respondents believe environmental issues are already materially affecting their companies’ finances and operations.</p>
  <p>But, as with every new venture, there are challenges. Early adopters seeking a complete picture of their ESG impact struggle with many reporting frameworks and standards. This hinders their ability to produce consistent and comparable investor-focused disclosures, creating a negative impact on global business. The International Federation of Accountants <a href="https://internationalbanker.com/finance/global-regulatory-fragmentation-an-impediment-to-economic-growth/">reported in 2018</a> that fragmented financial reporting systems cost the global economy US$780 billion per year.</p>
  <h2 id="embedding-sustainability-into-business-processes">Embedding Sustainability into Business Processes</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="accelerating-a-new-era-of-sustainability-management">Accelerating a New Era of Sustainability Management</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/12/sap-sustainability-control-tower-new-era-sustainability-management">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP Sustainability Control Tower addresses fragmented financial reporting head-on by giving companies tools to extend their top- and bottom-line optimizations to the “green line,” based on sustainability KPIs. Using a data-driven approach, businesses can now embed sustainability throughout their business and gain actionable insights across the value chain to enable the transition to low-carbon business processes.</p>
  <p>“The insights from combined data provide a continuous view on a company’s performance that manual processes based on spreadsheets cannot match,” says Rothermel. “Simplified steering, reporting, and performance management meet the requirements of a growing number of legal obligations as well as the emerging sustainability standards.”</p>
  <p>Users can drill down into strategic areas within the company and across a business network to make informed decision-making based on financial and pre-financial (ESG) indicators. An optimization can then be made between costs and greenhouse gas emissions. For example, a company’s chief financial officer could quantify the total impact of a business activity on the environment and society and manage trade-offs based on a comparable monetary currency.</p>
  <p>SAP Sustainability Control Tower uses the World Economic Forum’s <a href="https://www.weforum.org/stakeholdercapitalism">Stakeholder Capitalism Metrics</a> as a foundation. These can be applied by companies to align reporting on performance against ESG indicators and include non-financial disclosures centered around four pillars: people, planet, prosperity, and principles of governance. The Stakeholder Capitalism Metrics promote alignment among ESG frameworks and create data points that are comparable between companies, regardless of industry or region.</p>
  <h2 id="co-innovating-with-customers-and-partners">Co-Innovating with Customers and Partners</h2>
  <p>As part of its co-innovation model, SAP has worked closely with numerous customers and partners to test SAP Sustainability Control Tower during development to ensure it meets market requirements and is focused on users’ needs. Customer feedback is continually used to improve the product and adapt the road map to customer priorities. Partnerships with BCG, Deloitte, EY, and PwC will help reinforce SAP’s strong value proposition to its customers on ESG reporting and climate compliance.</p>
  <p>SAP has long been committed to fully integrating sustainability into its strategy and business model, and <a href="/2021/12/sap-achieves-top-scores-dow-jones-sustainability-index-and-cdp-carbon-disclosure-project">recently achieved top scores</a> as an ESG leader by the Carbon Disclosure Project (CDP) and Dow Jones Sustainability Indices (DJSI). It is only natural, therefore, for the company to apply SAP Sustainability Control Tower in its own operations.</p>
  <p>“At SAP, we believe in managing business success holistically and have been reporting on our financial, social, and environmental performance in one <a href="http://www.sapintegratedreport.com/">integrated report</a> since 2012,” says Daniel Schmid, SAP’s chief sustainability officer. “We are excited about being an early adopter of SAP Sustainability Control Tower, which will help us further simplify and automate our reporting processes by enabling us to integrate financial and pre-financial data on an ongoing basis. Based on the insights derived from the combined data we can manage and steer the company performance while minimizing manual processes.”</p>
  <p>SAP Sustainability Control Tower is one of numerous sustainability solutions SAP released in 2021. In November, the company introduced <a href="/2021/11/sap-responsible-design-and-production-accelerate-circular-economy">SAP Responsible Design and Production</a>, a solution for designing products sustainably and transitioning to a circular economy. With <a href="/2021/09/sap-product-footprint-management-redesign-sustainability">SAP Product Footprint Management</a>, introduced in September, companies can gain visibility into carbon footprint data throughout a product’s supply chain, enabling intelligent supply chain decisions that improve sustainability KPIs. This product-related carbon footprint data – collected during production, material sourcing, and transport – can be used by other solutions, such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/integrated-business-planning.html">SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain</a>.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-21</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>