<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/contingent-workforce-management/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Total Workforce Management Evolution: How OG&E and Brightspeed Manage Employees and Contingent Workers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/oge-and-brightspeed-manage-employees-contingent-workers</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/oge-and-brightspeed-manage-employees-contingent-workers</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[OG&E and Brightspeed highlight the importance of strategic planning and the effective use of technological tools in managing the workforce.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/contingent-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[To Improve Business Results, Insurers Must Modernize External Workforce Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/insurers-modernize-external-workforce-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/insurers-modernize-external-workforce-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The external workforce is a key lever in enabling business performance. Learn why insurers must prioritize external workforce management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/contingent-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>industry/insurance</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-insurance</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[If The Pandemic Was Their Wake-Up Call, This Is How Employers Are Reacting]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/pandemic-wake-up-call-workforce-resiliency</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/pandemic-wake-up-call-workforce-resiliency</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Organizations are devising new strategies to increase workforce resiliency in the wake of the pandemic and the Great Resignation. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/contingent-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Once-in-a-Generation Opportunity for Workforce Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/once-in-a-generation-opportunity-workforce-innovation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/once-in-a-generation-opportunity-workforce-innovation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A new report by Harvard Business Review Analytic Services sponsored by SAP explores workforce planning in a time of labor shortages.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/contingent-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Take: Seismic Shifts in the Labor Market]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/the-take-labor-market-shifts</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/the-take-labor-market-shifts</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Unprecedented global disruption has created seismic shifts in the labor market, including how, where and with whom we work. Get SAP's take.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/perspective</category>
            <category>news-tag/contingent-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/the-take</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Sanlam Developed a Diverse, Engaged, and Future-Ready Workforce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sanlam-diverse-engaged-future-ready-workforce</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sanlam-diverse-engaged-future-ready-workforce</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Sanlam launched a HR shared services model using SAP solutions to embrace a total workforce management strategy. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/contingent-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Companies Choose SAP to Help with Supply and Demand Volatility]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/companies-choose-sap-to-help-with-supply-and-demand-volatility</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/companies-choose-sap-to-help-with-supply-and-demand-volatility</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To help with supply and demand volatility, hundreds of companies worldwide have chosen SAP Ariba and SAP Fieldglass in Q3 2021.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d415aacc3ac94c9eeb05f9f24e47bd885f1ef09a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d415aacc3ac94c9eeb05f9f24e47bd885f1ef09a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d415aacc3ac94c9eeb05f9f24e47bd885f1ef09a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Companies Choose SAP to Help with Supply and Demand Volatility" src="./media_1d415aacc3ac94c9eeb05f9f24e47bd885f1ef09a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="companies-choose-sap-to-help-with-supply-and-demand-volatility">Companies Choose SAP to Help with Supply and Demand Volatility</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-ariba-digitalize-and-simplify-all-your-processes-end-to-end">SAP Ariba: Digitalize and simplify all your processes end-to-end</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://www.ariba.com/?campaigncode=CRM-IS20-PRL-OOCWA01">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that Palace Resorts and Siemens Energy are among the hundreds of companies worldwide to have chosen <a href="http://www.ariba.com/?campaigncode=CRM-IS20-PRL-OOCWA01">SAP Ariba</a> and <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/?campaigncode=CRM-IS20-PRL-OOCWF02">SAP Fieldglass</a> solutions in the third quarter to help digitalize procurement and external workforce management.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Hundreds more companies also renewed licenses and went live with solutions from SAP to optimize spend management.</p>
  <p>SAP maintains the largest share of the procurement applications software market, according to the recently published “<a href="https://www.ariba.com/resources/library/library-pages/worldwide-procurement-applications-software-market-shares-2020">IDC Worldwide Procurement Applications Software Market Shares, 2020: Digital Became the New Normal</a>” report.* IDC estimates that <strong>SAP’s market share has grown to 32.8%,</strong> maintaining its position of having the largest share of the market — more than the next 11 vendors combined.</p>
  <p>IDC Vice President of Enterprise Applications and Digital Commerce Mickey North Rizza said, “SAP clients have told us collectively that they have chosen SAP Ariba solutions for the extensive benchmarking across industries and spend categories and integration with SAP S/4HANA. They also love the guided buying experience in the SAP Ariba solutions. Many others have told us SAP Fieldglass solutions have helped improve their services procurement processes for engagement with consulting firms, marketing agencies, field services, maintenance and business process outsourcing.” According to the report, IDC estimates that the <a href="https://www.ariba.com/solutions/solutions-overview/procurement">procurement software</a> market has grown 5.4% to $6.2 billion in 2020 alone.</p>
  <p>Ongoing shifts and imbalances in supply and demand have led companies across geographies and industries to recognize how critical digitalizing operations is to procuring goods and services and keeping the global economy running.</p>
  <p>“Right now, business leaders are recognizing the power of procurement and flexible workforces to help them achieve more than just cost savings,” said Etosha Thurman, Chief Marketing and Solutions Officer, Intelligent Spend and Business Network, SAP. “We believe our market leadership is one of the reasons why they are turning to SAP to help increase agility and reduce risk in a world where supply and demand is volatile, disruption is expected and risk in various forms is more pervasive than ever before.”</p>
  <p>Highlights from the third quarter include:</p>
  <p><strong>Grupo KUO</strong>, a Mexican industrial conglomerate, selected SAP Fieldglass solutions for contingent workforce management. By digitalizing and automating its processes for sourcing, hiring and managing external talent, the company aims to comply with Mexico’s recent labor outsourcing regulation while also improving the experience for its workers and talent suppliers.</p>
  <p><strong>Mubadala Investment Company</strong>, a global investment group based in the United Arab Emirates and owner of the <strong>Acelen</strong> oil refinery in Brazil, has chosen SAP to support its growth strategy. Acelen will adopt the RISE with SAP offering, combining SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition, and the SAP Analytics solution to unify operations under one robust platform. In addition, cloud-based SAP Ariba, SAP Concur, SAP Fieldglass and SAP SuccessFactors solutions will help transform spend management and total workforce management so Acelen can maximize savings and deliver a better human experience for all workers.</p>
  <p>The <strong>Palace Resorts</strong> hotel chain in Mexico has selected RISE with SAP to support its IT strategy of digitalizing business processes in the cloud. The hospitality group also chose SAP Ariba solutions to help transform its procurement function and improve the buying experience and collaboration with its suppliers.</p>
  <p><strong>Petrobras</strong>, the Brazilian energy company, is accelerating its digital transformation with SAP. Taking a phased approach following the adoption of SAP S/4HANA, this quarter the company went live with SAP Ariba solutions for guided buying and catalogs to help improve its procurement and supply chain processes and provide a better user experience for employees and suppliers.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-fieldglass-solutions-for-the-modern-external-workforce">SAP Fieldglass: Solutions for the Modern External Workforce</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/?campaigncode=CRM-IS20-PRL-OOCWF02">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Siemens Energy AG</strong>, based in Munich, Germany, is focused on shaping the energy transition worldwide to help protect the climate while meeting growing energy demand with its strong and resilient portfolio. It selected SAP Ariba solutions to help improve, harmonize and automate procurement operations across the organization.</p>
  <p><strong>Waters Corporation</strong>, the Massachusetts-based analytical laboratory instrument and software company, selected SAP Ariba solutions — after a highly competitive evaluation and selection process — to help digitally transform its supply chain and improve its procurement operations with standardized and automated processes. Connecting to a digital network and aligning stakeholders and trading partners to a common plan will help Waters gain real-time visibility to anticipate and respond to changes in demand more quickly and orchestrate its multitier supply chain more effectively, with the goal of improving inventory management, customer service and on-time shipments.</p>
  <p><strong>Zijin Mining</strong> is one of China‘s largest gold mining companies. To support its rapid global expansion, the company selected SAP Ariba solutions to help improve the transparency, intelligence and compliance of its procurement system, strengthen group governance, and meet different procurement requirements around the world.</p>
  <p>For more information, visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong></p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as a sustainable intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into sustainable intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want — without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong> Kelly Sheldon Murray, +1 (978) 708-6821, <a href="mailto:kelly.murray@sap.com">kelly.murray@sap.com</a><u>,</u> ET<br>Geraldine Lim, +1 (415) 418-0945, <a href="mailto:geraldine.lim@sap.com">geraldine.lim@sap.com</a>, PT<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p><em>*“IDC Worldwide Procurement Applications Software Market Shares, 2020: Digital Became the New Normal” report (Doc # US47984421, August 2021).</em><br>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="http://www.sap.com/corporate-en/legal/copyright/index.epx#trademark">http://www.sap.com/corporate-en/legal/copyright/index.epx#trademark</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/contingent-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Helps Red Hat Advance Contingent Workforce Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/sap-red-hat-contingent-workforce-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/sap-red-hat-contingent-workforce-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Red Hat has streamlined and consolidated its external workforce program with the help of SAP Fieldglass Contingent Workforce Management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/contingent-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-news</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Helps Customers Align Spend Decisions to Business Strategy in a Networked Economy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/networked-economy-align-spend-decisions-business-strategy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/networked-economy-align-spend-decisions-business-strategy</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In today’s disrupted global business environment, All companies have unique challenges. SAP helps companies thrive in a networked economy.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_123749872455d177f83412d1799939080d0e9f9ad.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_123749872455d177f83412d1799939080d0e9f9ad.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_123749872455d177f83412d1799939080d0e9f9ad.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Helps Customers Align Spend Decisions to Business Strategy in a Networked Economy" src="./media_123749872455d177f83412d1799939080d0e9f9ad.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-helps-customers-align-spend-decisions-to-business-strategy-in-a-networked-economy">SAP Helps Customers Align Spend Decisions to Business Strategy in a Networked Economy</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>April marks my first six months back with SAP, now leading the Product Engineering organization focused on our intelligent spend and business network solutions. I came back because of our strong foundation.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We continue to invest and innovate to help customers move to the cloud, with no better example than the tremendous value companies continue to gain from both our acquired and organically developed solutions across SAP Ariba, SAP Fieldglass, SAP Concur, and SAP S/4HANA Procurement. Each solution set in our business unit is market-leading in its own right.</p>
  <p>I’m also excited because we are in a unique position to deliver a next-generation network-driven spend management solution suite that addresses all spend — everything a company spends money on except for payroll — connected to a vast and growing digital business network.</p>
  <p>The past six months have been tumultuous for everyone, to say the least. There have been a variety of supply risks and business disruptions: the ongoing pandemic, geopolitical unrest, and severe weather that slowed supply in different parts of the world. Most recently is the reminder <a href="https://apnews.com/article/cargo-ship-stuck-suez-canal-egypt-d8b6696716ab45794cba583ecf0e4001">that even one single ship</a> can impact tens of billions of dollars of supply every day.</p>
  <p>While highlighting the importance of having resilient procurement and supply chain operations, these events have also emphasized the obligations of technology companies — we need to ensure that our customers have the tools to assess such risks and rapidly execute alternatives. The opportunities for digital transformation and leveraging business networks are at the heart of facilitating such data-driven decision-making, and it is why I believe SAP is best suited to deliver on this promise for our customers.</p>
  <p>These lessons learned during recent disruptions combined with new processes and ways for doing business will pay huge dividends in the long term. In many ways, they already have.</p>
  <h2 id="what-intelligent-spend-and-business-network-really-means">What Intelligent Spend and Business Network Really Means</h2>
  <p>My job is to make sure that SAP continues to pioneer and lead the market with intelligent spend management and business network solutions that solve our customers’ greatest pain points, while tapping into the broader SAP portfolio so customers benefit from a completely integrated suite. Our mission is to deliver the solutions our customers use to align every spend decision to their business strategy in the networked economy.</p>
  <p>Ultimately, that means we focus every day on developing the best possible solutions to help our customers spend smarter and drive impact for their organizations and communities. Along with delivering business outcomes, we also want to help our customers take a stakeholder view into how their overall spend management function works.</p>
  <p>This commitment is reflected directly in our capabilities, in which we continue to invest to meet customer needs. They are historically strong and market-leading individually and will be even stronger far into the future as we continue to integrate and evolve best of breed into a truly unmatched best of suite.</p>
  <p>Like our customers, we don’t only think for the short term. We have a long-term commitment to seamless capabilities developed over time.</p>
  <h2 id="our-commitment-to-capabilities">Our Commitment to Capabilities</h2>
  <p>At SAP, our vision for procurement is focused on three core areas: One Procurement, Travel and Expense, and Business Network.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="manage-all-categories-of-spend-with-the-markets-leading-cloud-solutions-and-worlds-largest-business-network">Manage all categories of spend with the market's leading cloud solutions and world's largest business network</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/e-procurement.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="procurement">Procurement</h3>
  <p>We introduced the concept of One Procurement last year and, quite frankly, it generated a lot of questions. It’s on us to set the record straight: One Procurement is our vision for the future of procurement, how we bring innovations like artificial intelligence (AI) and insights to our customers. The idea of One Procurement may have been misconstrued as a single product destination, when in reality it’s truly a journey, centered around our market-leading SAP S/4HANA, SAP Ariba, and SAP Fieldglass solutions. We cover all categories of spend — direct, indirect, and services, including contingent and external workforce — with one strategy for the continual innovation our customers want to solve their business pain points. Our recently released <a href="https://www.ariba.com/solutions/solutions-overview/strategic-sourcing/sourcing-solutions?campaigncode=CRM-IS20-PRL-OOCWA06">guided sourcing capabilities in the SAP Ariba Sourcing solution</a> is an example of innovation that falls into the One Procurement vision.</p>
  <p>We are committed to maximizing each asset in our portfolio to enable procurement to drive business productivity, an end state that we call autonomous procurement. Autonomous procurement is an essential part of our intelligent enterprise strategy, with end-to-end integration and embedded intelligence that allow customers to streamline and automate procurement processes and thereby focus on more high-value tasks.</p>
  <p>Furthermore, as part of One Procurement, we are committed to continued superiority in services procurement and <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/solutions/contingent-workforce-management">contingent workforce</a> management with our SAP Fieldglass solutions. As we start recovering from the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, it is expected that many of our customers will turn to leveraging flexible external workers. To support this, we recently launched <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/solutions/assignment-management?campaigncode=CRM-PR21-FIP-FGAMLAUPRM">SAP Fieldglass Assignment Management</a>, a brand new solution that helps organizations manage contractors performing ad hoc work under existing supplier agreements. The most <a href="https://www.gartner.com/smarterwithgartner/9-future-of-work-trends-post-covid-19/">recent findings from Gartner</a> show that the external workforce is fast-growing and versatile, supporting organizational needs of all shapes and sizes. We continue to invest in SAP Fieldglass solutions and their ability to help companies streamline and scale external workforce management to help maximize their investments and meet business needs.</p>
  <h3 id="travel-and-expense">Travel and Expense</h3>
  <p>We are committed to continue leading the travel and expense management market, which has been significantly disrupted in the past 12 months. Similar to how we supported B2B spend via SAP Ariba solutions, we’ve developed capabilities in SAP Concur solutions to better manage organizational spend as well. Our <a href="https://www.concur.com/newsroom/article/leverage-expense-category-summaries-to-keep-spend-budget-on-track">spend management assessment</a> tool helps streamline and guide employee discretionary spend, helping keep budgets on track and align spending with business goals.</p>
  <h3 id="business-network">Business Network</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="related-new-guided-sourcing-capabilities-in-sap-ariba-sourcing-harmonize-experience-and-drive-adoption">Related: New Guided Sourcing Capabilities in SAP Ariba Sourcing Harmonize Experience and Drive Adoption</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2020/11/new-guided-sourcing-sap-ariba">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We are committed to driving value through a digital business network, helping our customers connect with buyers and suppliers via <a href="https://www.ariba.com/ariba-network">Ariba Network</a>, connect asset operators with original equipment manufacturers and services providers with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/asset-intelligence-network.html">SAP Asset Intelligence Network</a>, and collaborate on logistics, including tracking and tracing goods and materials, on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/logistics-business-network.html">SAP Logistics Business Network</a>. These networks are all strong on their own, and their combined power enables customers to manage their global supply chains from start to finish. The integration among networks is a key area of focus for us going forward, offering customers the advantages of a common data model, set of services, intelligence, and analytics engine. In this environment, processes and data flow freely and securely across functions and workflows.</p>
  <p>No one can predict the future, but I am certainly optimistic. We are dedicated to helping customers on their journeys to achieve real-time intelligent spend management aligned to the business so they can best prepare to be agile in the face of disruption, because let’s face it: disruption is <em>expected</em>. We just never know when or from where it will come.</p>
  <p>All companies have unique challenges within the common context of today’s disrupted global business environment. Our technology has evolved alongside our customers and will continue to do so – whether that’s SAP Ariba, SAP Fieldglass, SAP Concur, or SAP S/4HANA solutions, elements of each, or all of the above. We are a long-standing leader in spend management because of the breadth and variety of our solutions and our deep expertise in business process transformation across industries. Our investments in providing outcome-oriented solutions to complex problems will continue to be guided by our customers’ needs.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>John Wookey is president of Intelligent Spend and Business Network at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/contingent-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>