<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-erp/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Offers Maximum Attention for Customers’ High Standards]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-offers-maximum-attention-for-customers-high-standards</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-offers-maximum-attention-for-customers-high-standards</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Every customer has its own cloud strategies. That's why SAP MaxAttention prioritizes individualization within the customer's success plan.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/premium-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-activeattention</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-integrated-delivery-framework</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-maxattention</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-maxattention-summit</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Customer Checkout Ready to Hit the U.S. Market]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/sap-customer-checkout-hits-u-s-market</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/sap-customer-checkout-hits-u-s-market</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Customer Checkout is expanding its globalization strategy, moving into the U.S. market with camera manufacturer Leica Camera AG.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/nrf</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-erp</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Disrupted ERP Systems Rise to Reckoning in the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/composable-business-for-disrupted-erp-systems</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/composable-business-for-disrupted-erp-systems</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Composable business is the future for cloud ERP software, promising faster innovation for stronger resilience against market disruptions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/new-ventures-and-technologies</category>
            <category>product/sap-erp</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microsoft Selects RISE with SAP to Drive Business Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/microsoft-selects-rise-with-sap-business-innovation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/microsoft-selects-rise-with-sap-business-innovation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Microsoft selects RISE with SAP to deploy new capabilities and technologies faster and run on a flexible cloud-first solution. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/microsoft</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-erp</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nordic Electronics Leader Spearheads Retail’s Next Generation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/nordic-electronics-leader-spearheads-retails-next-generation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/nordic-electronics-leader-spearheads-retails-next-generation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Elkjøp Nordic’s new integrated architecture delivers a seamless customer journey with increased mobility and unified channels. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b3b9bdb6a22c4a5332b437dab7e4b4d3f060227b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b3b9bdb6a22c4a5332b437dab7e4b4d3f060227b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b3b9bdb6a22c4a5332b437dab7e4b4d3f060227b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Nordic Electronics Leader Spearheads Retail’s Next Generation" src="./media_1b3b9bdb6a22c4a5332b437dab7e4b4d3f060227b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="nordic-electronics-leader-spearheads-retails-next-generation">Nordic Electronics Leader Spearheads Retail’s Next Generation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Since its founding in 1962, Elkjøp had been known for the continuous improvement of its business processes. As the last decade ended though, the company faced a quandary – maintaining its reputation while being saddled with 12 different legacy software systems.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In order to support its vision for a next-generation retail experience, Elkjøp decided to replace all 12 systems with a new integrated architecture. The dramatic, cloud-based overhaul resulted in a next-gen retail platform that has both improved workflow and delivered 100% uptime.</p>
  <p>The strategy has yielded an array of other benefits for Elkjøp, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>100% in-store mobility for employees</li>
    <li>500 legacy interfaces evaluated and either replaced, updated, and/or re-connected</li>
    <li>4,500 employees trained on new systems using an e-learning platform</li>
  </ul>
  <p>But these achievements only came about because Elkjøp was willing to take a critical look at what employees and customers needed and honestly assess the changes that had to be made.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-elkjøps-sap-innovation-award-proposal">Read Elkjøp's SAP Innovation Award proposal</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2281">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="whats-in-a-name">What’s in a Name?</h2>
  <p>In Norwegian, the brand “Elkjøp” literally means “el buy” – with the “el” being a shortened version of elektrisk (electric) or elektronisk (electronic).</p>
  <p>It’s no surprise, really, since the Oslo-based company is the largest consumer electronics retailer in the Nordic region.</p>
  <p>A subsidiary of Dixons Carphone, a multinational consumer electrical and mobile retailer and services company, Elkjøp sells a variety of goods, including mobile phones, computers, and kitchen and other domestic appliances to both consumers and businesses.</p>
  <p>With a brisk online trade, as well as more than 400 stores, the company employs over 11,000 workers while operating under a number of names in its home country, as well as Sweden, Denmark, and Finland.</p>
  <h2 id="stepping-into-the-future">Stepping into the Future</h2>
  <p>The decision to create the next-generation retail platform did not come easily – Elkjøp had little choice but to take this dramatic step. Systems serving critical processes did not support the latest innovations, and the legacy retail systems could not provide mobility to the sales staff.</p>
  <p>In order to deliver certain services or close a sale, a store representative might be forced to leave a customer, seek out a desktop computer, then return. Other times, employees had to log in and out of multiple systems to complete a sale. In addition, legacy systems were incapable of adapting to new business models, like wireless subscriptions.</p>
  <p>Change was critical, yet daunting. Upgrades to systems capabilities meant adjusting all 12 different interconnected legacy systems, touching 500 different interfaces.</p>
  <p>As Elkjøp re-evaluated its strategy, it turned to a solution that had been serving the company well for several years.</p>
  <h2 id="cloud-first-advancement">Cloud-First Advancement</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="give-shoppers-and-consumers-the-products-and-personalized-shopping-experiences-they-want">Give shoppers and consumers the products and personalized shopping experiences they want</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/retail.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Elkjøp first deployed SAP ERP Central Component in 2015. The application is a core component in managing transactional and financial processes. Modules communicate with each other, working to create a fully integrated solution specific to customers in a variety of industries.</p>
  <p>Because of this successful experience, the company opted to base its next-gen retail platform on SAP ECC and other SAP solutions. A number of requirements were met with micro-services based architecture – software applications designed as suites of independently deployable services.</p>
  <p>Custom add-ons came from ASAPIO/Kafka, enabling information to flow between SAP and non-SAP applications, on premise and in the cloud, in real time.</p>
  <p>The monitoring challenges of Elkjøp’s high volume retail business were supported with an approach centered on SAP Fiori – a set of applications for business functions, like work approvals, and apps specializing in finance, calculation, and various self-service tasks.</p>
  <p>Failover architecture was created to protect computer systems from mishaps, allowing standby equipment to automatically take over if something went wrong.</p>
  <h2 id="unified-execution">Unified Execution</h2>
  <p>The next-gen retail platform went live in Denmark on May 8th, 2020 and was quickly deployed in 110 of the 460 stores. Changes were immediately evident. Using one unified customer master record, the new architecture <strong>delivered a seamless customer journey</strong> across in-store and online channels, with employees better prepared to anticipate clients’ wants and needs.</p>
  <p>Today, employees say the next-gen retail platform has enabled them to be more productive, while customers report quicker service times both online and in person.</p>
  <p>For “delivering the retail experience of the future,” Elkjøp Nordic earned the distinction as a finalist in the <strong>2021 SAP Innovation Awards</strong>, meeting the key requirements of improving customer experiences, solving complex challenges, and serving the greater good. Learn more in Elkjøp’s SAP Innovation Awards <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2281">proposal</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Keith Greenberg is an SAP Global Marketing contributor.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fiori</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Australia’s Asset-Intensive Industries Save Millions Managing the External Workforce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/australia-asset-intensive-industries-external-workforce</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/australia-asset-intensive-industries-external-workforce</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Organizations in asset-intensive industries can integrate data to holistically manage contingent workers for safety and savings. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
            <category>product/sap-erp</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Indian Startup Innovates Supply Chains for Dynamic IoT-Based Intelligence]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/tagbox-innovates-supply-chains-iot</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/tagbox-innovates-supply-chains-iot</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Indian startup Tagbox utilizes Internet of Things (IoT) technology to support greater supply chain reliability and resiliency. Learn more!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fb3b6af7f49a7db83bed3c8de9941011ffbb2eed.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fb3b6af7f49a7db83bed3c8de9941011ffbb2eed.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1fb3b6af7f49a7db83bed3c8de9941011ffbb2eed.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Indian Startup Innovates Supply Chains for Dynamic IoT-Based Intelligence" src="./media_1fb3b6af7f49a7db83bed3c8de9941011ffbb2eed.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="indian-startup-innovates-supply-chains-for-dynamic-iot-based-intelligence">Indian Startup Innovates Supply Chains for Dynamic IoT-Based Intelligence</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In a world struggling to recover from <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/intelligent-technologies.html">intelligent technologies</a> like the Internet of Things (IoT), machine learning, and artificial intelligence (AI) are transforming supply chain logistics and quality assurance for groundbreaking innovations. Indian-based startup <a href="https://www.tagbox.co/">Tagbox</a> has developed a cloud solution that dynamically tracks shipments on the move.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>IoT-based sensors capture the temperature and other critical parameters of products in real time, using machine learning and AI algorithms to automatically send alerts about risk anomalies so people can take corrective action and head off damages.</p>
  <p>“Our vision is to make supply chains more holistically intelligent for greater reliability and resiliency,” said Adarsh Kumar, co-founder and CEO of Tagbox. “Organizations have full visibility into shipment risks like shocks, temperature changes, tampering, or pilferage at any point along the supply chain. Our technology shares that data to the cloud, sends shipment risk alerts to relevant stakeholders, and logs data into the ERP system. People can immediately see when something’s gone wrong and take fast action.”</p>
  <p>Most Tagbox customers are located in India, but the startup is gaining traction with organizations in other parts of Asia-Pacific, including Singapore.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="ignite-innovation-in-your-business-with-intelligent-technology">Ignite innovation in your business with intelligent technology</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/intelligent-technologies.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="automated-triggers-for-quality-control">Automated Triggers for Quality Control</h2>
  <p>Traditional supply chain quality management was typically one dimensional and tracked shipment risk post-delivery. In contrast, Tagbox’s technology monitors products at every step of the journey with small battery-powered sensors attached to product packaging by individual SKU, box, or pallet. Hosted on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a>, the tool uses SAP Internet of Things (SAP IoT) and is integrated with <a href="https://www.sap.com/india/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP ERP</a>. Data sharing includes product or order information with designated employees in order management, transportation and logistics, quality parameters, warehouse and inventory metrics, and first to last mile delivery.</p>
  <p>For example, after downloading a mobile app, a delivery person driving a refrigerated truck transporting medication would be alerted to temperature changes in the vehicle and receive recommended actions to prevent spoilage.</p>
  <p>“People can immediately intervene when they’re notified of a temperature change or other risk, while managers can spot systemic issues and address those,” said Kumar. “Reports reveal patterns, such as where temperature excursions happen regularly. The company may decide to improve product packaging or select different transportation routes.”</p>
  <p>One pharmaceutical customer saved thousands of dollars by reducing post-delivery assessment times by up to 72 hours. Having collected real-time data throughout the shipping process, the company eliminated time-consuming reports after delivery.</p>
  <h2 id="business-growth-from-sap-partnership">Business Growth from SAP Partnership</h2>
  <p>Kumar credited his company’s recent growth partly to his team’s experience at SAP Startup Studio, an accelerator program at <a href="https://www.sap.com/india/about/labs-india.html">SAP Labs India</a> for early- and growth-stage tech startups.</p>
  <p>“Our IoT sensors collect and send data to supply chain, SAP IoT, and other SAP ERP systems that provide the business context for product shipments and locations, making this an ideal partnership,” he said. “We’ve accelerated our time-to-market because SAP experts have provided us with industry-specific opportunity guidance and introductions to a wide range of SAP customers.”</p>
  <h2 id="data-fuels-insights-to-action">Data Fuels Insights to Action</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="with-stylumia-real-time-data-intelligence-powers-competitive-retail-advantage">With Stylumia, Real-Time Data Intelligence Powers Competitive Retail Advantage</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/04/stylumia-data-intelligence-retail-advantage">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While pharmaceutical companies are obvious candidates for fully traceable quality control of vaccine and other medicine cold chains, numerous industries can also benefit from real-time insights. These include food and beverage companies and consumer electronics. One e-commerce grocery company using Tagbox improved its cold chain temperature compliance while reducing missing inventory rates by 20%.</p>
  <p>“They have end-to-end traceability of real-time temperatures for products like meats and dairy products from warehouse to consumer,” said Kumar. “They can track what percentage of orders were delivered at the right temperatures, cascading to employee performance metrics and training, as well as infrastructure and other supply chain decisions.”</p>
  <p>Appliance, home electronic, and glass manufacturers have also found benefits from Tagbox when it comes to product damage prevention during transport.</p>
  <p>“Any combination of factors can damage fragile goods on the road, whether it’s bad driving and accidents or because products weren’t packaged or loaded properly,” said Kumar. “With our sensors, companies can see precisely what kind of shock happened and when it occurred. Our algorithms translate the data into meaningful metrics such as if the product was in freefall, turned upside down, tilted, or unsecured. In the moment, they can repack the item, adjust the temperature, and keep going without damage.”</p>
  <h2 id="turning-data-into-business-value">Turning Data into Business Value</h2>
  <p>Kumar, Saumitra Singh, and Sameer Singh co-founded Tagbox, drawing from 25 years of collective experience in IoT, data analytics, AI, and integrated circuit and chip design.</p>
  <p>“We realized that despite all the talk about IoT as a data generator, there wasn’t enough focus on using that data for concrete business decisions,” he said. “We wanted to tackle supply chain inefficiencies and product quality control for high-value, fragile goods traveling across cold chains. There are so many diversification opportunities in B2B operations using IoT and machine learning.”</p>
  <p>Kumar said future international expansion plans for Tagbox included the United States, providing dynamic intelligence for supply chains worldwide, long after the pandemic recedes.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me: @smgaler</em>.<br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/06/08/indian-startup-innovates-supply-chains-for-dynamic-iot-based-intelligence/?sh=53116be4bcb6">This story originally appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-technologies</category>
            <category>news-tag/internet-of-things</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-labs-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/startups</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[INTURN Turns Sales Calls into Meals for New Yorkers Hit by Pandemic]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/inturn-sales-calls-meals-nyc-pandemic</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/inturn-sales-calls-meals-nyc-pandemic</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With nearly three-quarters of food pantries and soup kitchens reporting an increase in visitors, providing support for those experiencing hunger was a clear, effective way ...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>product/sap-erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-innovations4good</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Iren Innovates Invoice Processing with SAP Business Technology Platform]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/iren-innovates-invoice-processing-sap-btp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/iren-innovates-invoice-processing-sap-btp</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Iren leverages SAP Business Technology Platform for a supplier portal with a frictionless, chatbot-supported invoice processing experience.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-hana</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ERP Strategies for High-Impact, Behind-the-Scenes Business Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/erp-business-transformation-strategies</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/erp-business-transformation-strategies</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn why when it comes to ERP business transformation, the most significant changes are still relevant to legacy business functions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1999d0b7355fc77701365e4b4079ba1b0c6ac1c32.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1999d0b7355fc77701365e4b4079ba1b0c6ac1c32.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1999d0b7355fc77701365e4b4079ba1b0c6ac1c32.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="ERP Strategies for High-Impact, Behind-the-Scenes Business Transformation" src="./media_1999d0b7355fc77701365e4b4079ba1b0c6ac1c32.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="erp-strategies-for-high-impact-behind-the-scenes-business-transformation">ERP Strategies for High-Impact, Behind-the-Scenes Business Transformation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>New go-to-market models, digitalized products and services, and process automation – all these changes bring tremendous value. But don’t forget long-simmering evolutions in legacy business functions, as they also require the attention of a well-supported transformation plan to keep IT costs low and help ensure business continuity.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Many executives guide their transformation efforts by following the signs of emerging market trends and ticking off the boxes of their corporate strategy. This mindset unquestionably generates exciting new business models, products, services, and experiences. But it still misses the ultimate goal: to reimagine everything from the innermost depth of their infrastructure to the furthest reach of their operational edge, including soon-to-be decommissioned legacy business functions.</p>
  <p>This reality is also true when modernizing enterprise resource planning (ERP) systems. When moving from SAP ERP to SAP S/4HANA, IT teams must also support the change process for legacy business areas with a three-fold approach:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Reduce overall IT complexity and total cost of ownership</li>
    <li>Maintain a stable IT environment for current operations</li>
    <li>Prepare for and provide a future-ready IT landscape and operation</li>
  </ul>
  <p>By paying attention to these less strategic functions, ERP modernization can further minimize IT cost and effort. More importantly, unplanned shutdowns and intelligence displacement can be avoided while operations and data security remain stable.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-sap-advisory-services">Explore SAP Advisory Services</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services/advisory-development/business-transformation.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="strategy-1-keep-legacy-erp-as-is">Strategy #1: Keep Legacy ERP As Is</h2>
  <p>When considering the future of legacy ERP, some organizations choose to preserve their existing system as long as possible and carry out housekeeping activities to simplify the system operations, especially when supporting less strategic business areas. This approach helps ensure stable, continuous operation of the SAP production environment while avoiding new investments.</p>
  <p>Sounds good, right? Unfortunately, extending an ERP system beyond its useful life can require incremental expenses that do not fully deliver any real impact – for example, cost savings – for the business. On the IT side, the historically grown complexity of the ERP system keeps IT operational costs high.</p>
  <h2 id="strategy-2-convert-legacy-erp-to-sap-s4hana">Strategy #2: Convert Legacy ERP to SAP S/4HANA</h2>
  <p>Converting the legacy ERP to SAP S/4HANA is the best choice when organizations must retain proven business processes and value chains, use in-house applications, support numerous subsidiaries, or rely on historical data. In addition, the overall business benefits from a long-term maintenance and support relationship with SAP.</p>
  <p>Our team of advisory experts supports the conversion model in two phases: first, housekeeping and preparation and second, execution. During the initial stage, organizations simplify their existing ERP system by reducing its data footprint and removing unused custom developments, data, and software inconsistencies and redundancies. The latter phase delivers the measures necessary for the transition to SAP S/4HANA, including delta solution design and a multi-cycle execution plan covering every aspect up to full production.</p>
  <p>This tactic gives our customers the ability to adopt SAP S/4HANA with few training and change management needs and no additional data migration. The conversion also allows organizations to maintain operations for their familiar legacy processes in a new technical environment, helping to ensure that SAP S/4HANA and the data it leverages is maintenance proof.</p>
  <h2 id="strategy-3-implement-sap-s4hana-with-a-steady-move-to-the-cloud">Strategy #3: Implement SAP S/4HANA with a Steady Move to the Cloud</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-about-services-and-support-from-sap">Read more about services and support from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/support.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP S/4HANA can be built alongside an active legacy ERP system, which can be retired later. While it encourages organizations to redefine processes and consider new ways to balance traditional operations with new capabilities, this approach may not make sense for legacy business, considering the cost and effort involved.</p>
  <p>This is where deploying SAP S/4HANA in a public cloud environment can help. By following the SAP Activate methodology and standardizing business processes, our customers can quickly start moving to a modern ERP, build it up intelligently, operate it with simplicity, and innovate continuously.</p>
  <p>While implementation costs can be reasonably controlled by adopting the SAP software standard, the public cloud allows customers to significantly reduce operating costs by scaling their digital capabilities and processes to meet today’s business needs. Plus, they can simplify system operations to prepare for tomorrow’s changes with a future-proof, maintainable, and scalable ERP.</p>
  <p>However, this doesn’t mean that these customers must start with a new implementation and move to the cloud immediately. With a mixed mindset of “keep legacy as is,” and “implement the modern ERP as new,” organizations can first maintain the status quo and improve the legacy system operations. This perspective gives executives additional time to react to market trends, business changes, and innovations. Then, they can define a comprehensive transition strategy to SAP S/4HANA. Meanwhile, SAP S/4HANA continues to evolve with broader functional innovations.</p>
  <p>When ready, our customers can transition SAP S/4HANA fully to the cloud to help ensure a future-proof, lean ERP that further optimizes operating costs and reduces IT complexity – even across legacy business functions.</p>
  <h2 id="bringing-the-true-spirit-of-transformation">Bringing the True Spirit of Transformation</h2>
  <p>C.S. Lewis once wrote, “Mere change is not growth. Growth is the synthesis of change and continuity, and where there is no continuity there is no growth.”</p>
  <p>The same is true for ERP transformation: Projects that bring the most significant changes are still relevant to legacy business functions that may no longer appear as strategic as newer approaches to go-to-market models, products and services, and organizational processes.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Explore how <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/advisory-development/business-transformation.html">SAP Advisory Services</a> can help energize your business’s digital transformation with flexible and scalable options for deploying a modern ERP software, such as SAP S/4HANA.</p>
        <p>Stay in the conversation by following SAP Services and Support<br>on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/sapsupportinfo">YouTube</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/SAPDigitalSvcs">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/138840">LinkedIn</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SAPDigitalBusinessServices">Facebook</a>.</p>
        <p><em>Di Li is a principal business consultant and enterprise architect at SAP.</em><br><em>Georg Heberle is a senior business consultant and enterprise architect at SAP.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="subscribe-to-the-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter">Subscribe to the Innovation and Transformation Newsletter</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advisory-services</category>
            <category>product/sap-erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>